[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, May 3rd, 2009, will we see multiple motion controllers at this year's E3?
[SPEAKER_01]: Are the Ninja Turtles being remade for a new downloadable game?
[SPEAKER_01]: And a new video game will let you show off your ironing skills.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are that show dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm with you here every week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob Roberts also joining you tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Say hello to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: Always here with us as usual.
[SPEAKER_10]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm recovering.
[SPEAKER_10]: Recovering?
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you an alcoholic?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_10]: From the week from hell.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry to hear about the week from hell.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or is there a lot of gaming to be done in the week from hell?
[SPEAKER_06]: Some, actually, a little.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, we'll get to that in just a moment, but we can't start the show without introducing the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_10]: Good.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I see your normal Sunday ration of fast food.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have some Burger King tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sticking with the traditionals.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to get McDonald's, but I somehow was in a daze and drove past it.
[SPEAKER_09]: How exactly do you select what your fast grub is going to be before the show, before you get here?
[SPEAKER_10]: Just what I feel like.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just what you feel like?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: What are you going to stop at on the way?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was driving home from Oakland right before the show, so I wouldn't have been able to stop somewhere healthy because it takes a lot longer.
[SPEAKER_09]: and unfortunately fast food didn't take quite as, it wasn't as fast as I had hoped because an idiot in front of me decided to use a coupon for their fast food order and the coupon didn't apply to what they had ordered so he sat there arguing with them for a good 10 minutes and that sucked.
[SPEAKER_10]: Misty in our chat room at chat.orangelandradio.com starts us off tonight wanting to know but the question is what kind of BK noms?
[SPEAKER_10]: Double Bacon Cheeseburger Very healthy Exactly, it's very delicious
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, and Black Wolf, the gentleman before us here Sunday nights when we tape live on All Games Radio at about 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Black Wolf is in chat and says, hey, I heard this was a show about video games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Once in a while, once in a while we do talk about video games.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, let's get to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We always like to start off a little bit of how is your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_10]: There's no guests tonight, just you guys in the chat room, chat.orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll start off tonight with Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_07]: I played Cooking Mama on iPhone while waiting for Wolverine to start.
[SPEAKER_07]: The rest of it was spent on homework.
[SPEAKER_07]: All week, homework.
[SPEAKER_07]: The end.
[SPEAKER_10]: It cuts into your cooking moment time.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's annoying, but it is smart marketing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I try not to think of it one way or another.
[SPEAKER_07]: The bottom line is all that matters to the companies.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, of course, they're going to try to get the word out there in every front possible that's just marketing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm really, I guess, indifferent towards the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I may not care about what does that show with What's-Her-Face, Kira Sedgwick, but the only good thing I saw her in was singles anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: I liked the first 15 minutes of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That part was great.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was all about Wade not shutting up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Without spoiling anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now the listeners should know you're a total Deadpool fan girl.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am a total Deadpool fan.
[SPEAKER_10]: So this was very important, the treatment that he received in the movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I'm sure you love the end.
[SPEAKER_07]: Depending on which ending.
[SPEAKER_09]: The actual end and not the end after the end.
[SPEAKER_07]: The bonus end, okay, if you watch after the credits, there's one of two endings.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I got the more lame one.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I got to see the other one on YouTube before it got pulled off.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I wish I'd had that one because it made me a lot happier and had some fourth wall breakage.
[SPEAKER_09]: We don't want to give spoilers, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not saying anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're just doing that so they can whore that character out for another whore movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's more warning Loki than you.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, because I've been reading several interviews and articles where they're leaving it open for a Deadpool movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which would make me happy if they do it freaking right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Question from chat, and a comment from chat, I like old people in chat, which by the way, I still love that name, says, X-Men applies to games because there is a game of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, there's been several games about the X-Men.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember an old school one on the PC, like back in the early 90s, where you were trying to rescue Storm.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't even remember what the game, I think it was just X-Men, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, X-Men and games have always been kind of tied together a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's always those tie-ins.
[SPEAKER_10]: But DJRamaS asks, how well did Ryan Reynolds play Deadpool?
[SPEAKER_07]: Deadpool, Wade,
[SPEAKER_07]: X-Men X-Men X-Men X-Men
[SPEAKER_07]: It was pure and utter ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had nothing to do with each other, you know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: They tipped the hat, is what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then Gambit, I mean, hello, I was a little worried about how they were going to portray Gambit, but he showed up and was like, hi, I'm Gambit, I'm going to be awesome now.
[SPEAKER_07]: What I was actually most pleased with about him is that his accent is legitimate.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not one of those overdone fake Cajun accents.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sounds pretty right for the area, so I was pretty pleased with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft is in our chatroom and says I couldn't see the movie since theaters are closed in Mexico because he lives in Mexico and you know how swine flu is all the rage down there as it is starting to be up here too they're closing all the movie theaters Rei Ayanami said sine flu and I'm certainly thinking cosine flu next alright, let's get into more video games Loki, did you play anything this week?
[SPEAKER_09]: yes I did, I played some DS stuff
[SPEAKER_09]: Zero plus zero equals zero Exactly
[SPEAKER_09]: Rick!
[SPEAKER_09]: Actual games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I played more of the Great Giana Sisters DS game.
[SPEAKER_09]: How is that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I need to check that out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a basic DS game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just, you know, very much a ripoff of Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's what made the old school one on the Commodore 64 so awesome, was that it was such a ripoff of Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_10]: How's the music?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I love the soundtrack to the Giana Sisters.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not, I mean, I didn't notice any old remakes or whatever, but maybe there were, I mean...
[SPEAKER_09]: I never really played the original.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it was funny though, I like how she gets the red orb or whatever and becomes Emojiana or whatever and just starts throwing fire that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, oh look, I went to Hot Topic, now I'm gonna kick ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that was okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Played a little bit more Rhythm Heaven, but I still can't stand that game because it's not forgiving at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, just, I'm trying to get gold on stuff and it's just not...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: It feels like a copy of a copy, and it's also confusing.
[SPEAKER_09]: They don't really tell you what you're supposed to be doing a lot of times.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, it's not like, you know, where it's like chop, and you kind of get what you're supposed to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: This I couldn't figure it out, so it was annoying.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they played a lot more Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm trying to make a flamethrower, and I kind of got one sort of made out of a sniper rifle and some fire effect thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it works pretty good, except sometimes you can catch yourself on fire, which is kind of annoying.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, now that's no fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: When another one, like a hurricane bomb or something, where you throw it down and it just throws everything around, but it can kill yourself also pretty violently sometimes.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, just kind of messing with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then...
[SPEAKER_09]: What else?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I tried playing Bionic Commando, but the problem is, at our work, our internet's like, even though we're on a T1, it's like split 200 ways, and it's slow as hell, and I couldn't connect to any games.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that was very disappointing, and fortunately this weekend, being so busy, I didn't get a chance to actually play that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I do want to play that, because that game looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, that's pretty much it for this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think I may have played a little bit more Excitebots somewhere in there, because I finally unlocked Super Excite, so I'm actually even playing through that tonight, which apparently is very unforgiving, even more so than the first game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and Excitebots is here in studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, on Justin.tv.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the wife finally let it go for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: She gave up on it, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my gosh, really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, she said it was too hard.
[SPEAKER_10]: And by the way, if you've never listened to the show before, something you should know about Loki's wife, she really doesn't play a lot of games.
[SPEAKER_10]: But there'll be that occasional game she gets obsessed with, and Excitebots is one of them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, Excitebot, or Excite Truck was really the one that, yeah, and then, you know, Excitebot she was really looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_09]: And she still, you know, had fun with it, but it's just, she's gotten to, you know, kind of a wall right now where she can't, you know, S-rank these super Excitebots.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I got, I mean, it's really hard.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, you have to get even more points than you did in the first time.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the first time, you know, in just normal Excite race,
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, getting S sometimes requires you to play a track like 20 times, if not more than that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And now you have to get even more than what you got before.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just like, you want to pull your hair out.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then you get mirror mode, which is even harder.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's always fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you unlock more bots.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw the hand.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, there's a hand that tries to smack you for some reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the Smash Brothers hand.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess it's Master Hand, but it's a hand that tries to smash you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: for no apparent reason whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do kind of want to check this game out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope... No, we don't have any guests to play it on JustinTV tonight, but hopefully we'll have an in-between stories, kind of be able to play some.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I also played a 101-in-1 retro game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I forget what it was called.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's that Atlus collection of little mini-games.
[SPEAKER_09]: That sucked too, because apparently you start off with like 10 games, and you have to play through all of them, and they don't control very well, and...
[SPEAKER_09]: You have to score so many points before you can unlock another game, and I can't, because it doesn't control very well, and it's annoying.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dope.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, well, let's see, Mikey.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, oh, but I did want to mention something else we played, which I don't remember exactly the title of the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought it was something like, um, was it, uh, Eat Poop Cat or something like that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah, the one, uh, Eat... Yeah, I remember, yeah, it had a very weird name.
[SPEAKER_10]: Eat Something Cat Poop or something like that was the name of the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: And then you pass it again, the next person writes the caption they think goes with the picture, then they fold over the picture, and the next person draws a picture to go with the caption, and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know it sounds stupid as I'm describing it, but it's actually a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because there's always someone in the group who will turn everything into penis.
[SPEAKER_10]: No matter, you know, what you do.
[SPEAKER_10]: That person was Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Truth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: Other games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: My gaming week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I didn't play a lot of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still had the old standby old stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Especially a lot of classic gaming on the Nintendo Wii this week going into my archive of like Zelda and Kid Icarus and all the old school stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not a lot of new stuff for me this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think there's been a lot of new stuff that's been out recently that's kind of caught my attention.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I am excited though about some of the Xbox Live arcade releases coming up at least this coming week that I'm hoping to try out before
[SPEAKER_10]: Animae Central
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get into some housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wanted to talk about and give a little reminder.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am going to be at Anime Central this weekend in Chicago.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a panel on Friday.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's called So You Think You Can Podcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you ever want to hear more about how OLR got started or kind of the story behind it, or you want to start your own podcast and kind of curious where do I begin, what kind of mics do I need, how do I get a listener base or what have you, I'm going to be doing that panel 4.30 on Friday.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I believe it's panel room 7, but I'm doing that off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_10]: Please check the program for the specific location.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know it's one of the smaller rooms because they're not anticipating there's going to be a big crowd for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So let's prove them wrong and make it standing room only.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, I want to give another thank you to the listeners for the wonderful show computer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sadly, we're not broadcasting off that tonight, but I think when we come back in two weeks, we're going to be on that show computer, the new one, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, we're having a chance to actually put it together.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it just hasn't worked out.
[SPEAKER_10]: And by the way, since of ASEN next week, I do not believe there's going to be a show next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: So next week we will be off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately, I don't get back from Chicago until... Actually, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: I get back at like 7 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm just going to miss.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's hoping there's no delays or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sadly, we will not be here next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Bobby, of course, will be here as always.
[SPEAKER_10]: So give his show a listen.
[SPEAKER_10]: He'll probably run a little long next week to compensate.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, Bobby was saying that he played Paul's Big Adventure on WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which I've been meaning to actually...
[SPEAKER_09]: Play or install.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I haven't gotten a chance to do that yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's a pretty awesome game.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the one that kind of rips off of all these different old school games.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have like the Castle from Mario Brothers and stuff in it and like weird stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: for a personal thing I do I've been using YouTube a lot more recently for like a non-gaming thing so I've learned how to like edit video a lot better and do that stuff so I'm excited to go to ASEN and actually shoot some video so I hope our listeners aren't camera shy because I will be in your face with a camera and if so too bad yes too bad alright
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, that's really it for housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get into some video game news.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have a lot of rumors tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rumors, rumors, rumors.
[SPEAKER_10]: But aren't rumors fun to talk about?
[SPEAKER_10]: And we're going to see if they seem real or not to us.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think Loki's going to start us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, one rumor that we have came from Engadget.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, they have somebody that has captured what they...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: They were saying that you can use it in a trivia game over the internet with live images of each person playing and the buzzing you would clap.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some other stuff, including sensor detects when the person is playing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Only the person that's playing the game and not the people that are just watching it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I do believe they showed this off the company behind it during CES this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it looked interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's basically...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: They were using actually just a normal webcam and they had a boxing game.
[SPEAKER_09]: They were showing some guy doing that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It almost looked like an eye toy boxing game because you could see the guy in the background and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have like a flight sim game and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: So basically the same kind of applications you would use like an eye toy for this would be used for.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the eye toy sucked.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, but technology is getting better.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just like the PlayStation Eye is a lot better than the original eye toy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, first off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Real or bullshit?
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: There's an image of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say it's real and this is something that they've already... Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: We live in a day and age of Photoshop.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, but they've already teased that, oh, we're going to show something off at E3 that's going to revolutionize the way you play games or the way you enjoy entertainment.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, hello?
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, real or bullshit?
[SPEAKER_10]: You're not good for real.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even though it's real, it's not that new.
[SPEAKER_10]: We already have a camera on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: And when I hear about this, I shudder because I think of Totem Ball, which was that horrible, horrible video camera game they had that they tried to do the full-body motion controls with.
[SPEAKER_10]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, granted, technology's gotten a little better, but come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: That game was shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_09]: I agree with you.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this technology, they actually bought a company.
[SPEAKER_09]: Microsoft bought a company.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I hear that guy, I forget his name, I want to say Bobby Lee, but I don't think it's Bobby Lee.
[SPEAKER_09]: Something Lee.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember the guy that did all those wonderful Wiimote things with the stereoscopic or the...
[SPEAKER_09]: Head Tracking, and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: The one who did all those experiments.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah, the demos and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, he works for Microsoft now.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is such a Microsoft thing to happen to.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's so funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I would not be surprised if this is at E3.
[SPEAKER_09]: This makes sense.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we're going to get into a little bit more later on with other things.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if you think about it, these companies now are starting to take away what...
[SPEAKER_09]: is unique about the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: And when you take away the motion sensing from the Wii, what's left?
[SPEAKER_09]: A GameCube.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo franchises.
[SPEAKER_10]: SSJ100 Matt in chat says, if at first you don't succeed, buy a company that does it better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chat.OrangeLinger.com if you want to join us in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's the other thing about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Video conferencing, not new.
[SPEAKER_10]: We already have that on the Xbox 360 with a camera.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just that nobody bought the camera.
[SPEAKER_10]: Except people who wanted to play Strip Uno.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the only reason people bought the camera.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember that game, You're in the Movies?
[SPEAKER_09]: Drop down to $20.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, I forgot about that game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's $20 with the camera bundled in.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's actually cheaper than buying the camera by itself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you think it's because they're unloading the cameras because they're not going to need them anymore?
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm assuming it's going to be more than just a single camera, because obviously that didn't work before.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they have new technology now.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've even seen it before, like in past E3s.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can remember way back to E3 2005, they were showing off camera technology that was actually putting bounding boxes around people's heads and was able to track individual people and was able to differentiate who's playing the game and who's not.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I wouldn't be surprised if we see this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Deathwishing says, I bought the camera for Rainbow Six Vegas.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you know, there were a lot of little games that would use the camera.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, like Uno had it in some of the other online Xbox Live games.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then some of the other games, like Burnout Paradise, you could take your driver's license picture with the camera.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, ah.
[SPEAKER_09]: A little dumb shit like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, every time you, you know...
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, I also want to say some other comments from chat here.
[SPEAKER_10]: BlackWolf, of all people, actually says, You're in the movies doesn't work too well, sadly.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't get the right lighting.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's always a pain in the ass with these camera setups, too, is the lighting.
[SPEAKER_10]: If it's not just right, the game works terribly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, I had a couple of those iToy games on PlayStation 2, and they work like crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, you have to have the exact right lighting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I'm hoping that this stuff that comes out for wherever this camera peripheral is going to be...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's hopefully going to be a little bit better than the current camera out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been a sucker.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've bought all three cameras, both the PlayStation Eye toy and the Vision camera and the PlayStation Eye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Granted, I haven't really used the PlayStation Eye.
[SPEAKER_09]: I meant to use it when I was going to make all these little big planet levels, which I never did.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Vision camera was... I don't even remember what the hell I bought the Vision camera for.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just to have it, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, man, I can tell you at least with... I haven't tried the PlayStation 9 too much, but the other two, disappointment.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except we did get a good webcam out of the iToy Play.
[SPEAKER_09]: Back in the day.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that kind of worked out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember when iToy Chat was going to be the next big thing on the PlayStation 2?
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever happened to that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, the PlayStation Eye though, they're definitely doing a lot of things with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, like they have that, you know, Eye, was it a pet thing that's coming out?
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know, the other concept games that they've made, you know, where they can capture images and stuff that people draw.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wish they would actually... I have crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wish they would actually implement, you know, that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, this wasn't the Eye of Judgment stuff because scanning cards is retarded.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's been around forever.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, hell, there's the e-reader on the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm talking about actually...
[SPEAKER_09]: Something unique where you can actually draw the tanks and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they never released it because it was just a little demo that they made.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well guess what?
[SPEAKER_10]: This rumor about motion controllers does not stop with Microsoft and the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sony apparently is working on something as well, which shouldn't come as too much of a surprise, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo has been leading in sales and the big thing that separates their system from their competitors right now is the motion controls.
[SPEAKER_10]: So of course...
[SPEAKER_10]: Microsoft and Sony want to find ways to get a piece of the pie.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we hear this out of Microsoft's camp and out of Sony's camp.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a rumor, according to this blog called The Cutscene, which is related to Variety.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's not just some Joe Schmoe's blog.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is related to Variety, which is a huge magazine in the entertainment industry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some sources leaked to The Cutscene blog that Sony is going to be unveiling a new device at E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not quite the same thing, though, that Loki's been describing for Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not a camera.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's something that's going to have pointing in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's basically... They don't know yet if it's going to be the regular controller infused with a pointer, which is a possibility.
[SPEAKER_10]: But this thing that I'm looking at, according to these patents, almost look like... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks like somebody's playing Samba de Amigo with these maraca-type things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, they're not actually maracas, but the little pointers look like little devices.
[SPEAKER_09]: But here's the thing, though, is really they're targets that are being used with the PlayStation Eye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's not...
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's basically like the reverse of the Wii setup.
[SPEAKER_09]: Instead of actually having the
[SPEAKER_09]: Sensor bar just being a couple lights and then having the receiver being in the actual remote.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is actually using the camera as the receiver and then the points or whatever of reference are actually on the controller.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, continuing on the patent here, they actually say, yeah, this small camera will track the movement of multiple LED lights on the controller.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you use your PlayStation Eye and maybe they're going to put lights in these controllers or something so that you can actually move them around, they call it a Wiimote in reverse.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, because it wouldn't be that hard for them.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've already got 6-axis, which does all the tilting and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now they really need depth of field and kind of the IR pointing stuff that the Wii has.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've said it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, let me read you this one final quote about this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quote, Because the camera can read different color lights and the shape and angle of each light, it's much more accurate than the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_10]: It can track precise movements, including along the Z-axis, pushing towards and away from the TV, something the Wii is really bad at, as well as velocity.
[SPEAKER_09]: Truth or bullshit?
[SPEAKER_09]: Truth, but I'm not sure if they're announcing ID.3.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to say distorted truth.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think it's necessarily – I'm along the lines of what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think that they're going to launch this whole new controller, this motion controller that you're going to have all this extra crap for your TV.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think they're going to find ways to use the devices they already have, maybe releasing a new six-axis controller with the lights in it that's going to involve this.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I would say distorted truth.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's one of those where there's smoke, there's fire type of things.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Every Sony rumor has been true.
[SPEAKER_09]: So let's just go with true on this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because seriously, every time they're like, no, that's not really happening.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have no plans for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_09]: And then it's like, oh, hey, look.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, look.
[SPEAKER_09]: Price drop on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: That totally surprised you.
[SPEAKER_10]: But wait, how many times have there been rumors that the PlayStation 3 price is going to drop or be redesigned?
[SPEAKER_10]: That never happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think that's rumors.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's wishful thinking.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of those rumors are coming from people thinking, okay, Microsoft's dropping their price or this is coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've got to drop it in order to be competitive.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they don't care.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's no price drop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just consider the source.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: So knowing that Microsoft and Sony, one way or another, we all pretty much agree, except DarkSakura's not sure, but we all pretty much agree they are making movements to go towards motion control.
[SPEAKER_10]: We at least all agree that Microsoft's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_09]: If one of them does it, it's either Sony or Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_09]: The other one's pretty much going to have to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course Microsoft's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Microsoft has made their machine out of ripping off good ideas and doing it well.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not a slam on Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_10]: They do a great job of ripping off good ideas.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_10]: And making them better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, here's what I want to ask.
[SPEAKER_10]: Should Nintendo be worried?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because really, everyone's looking at innovative motion controls.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what they pride themselves on, these games.
[SPEAKER_09]: And granted, they have franchises and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't get me wrong, Mario Kart's awesome, Mario Galaxy's cool, Zelda's really nice, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of people just pick up Tiger Woods' game on the Wii, even if they own both, because they want that extra immersion for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But now you can take those awesome, like Red Steel or something like that, or Matterworld, that looks awesome, but is kind of limited by the hardware.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now you've got more power for the hardware and the motion controls.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's going to be some really awesome games.
[SPEAKER_09]: And unfortunately, Nintendo...
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't see them doing anything very innovative at E3, and I bet you anything all their announcements are not going to be innovative and they're just going to be sequels to their franchises.
[SPEAKER_09]: Much like a Pikmin 3, or, you know, like a sequel to Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hell, I mean, they have a sequel to basically the Wii Moat coming out, you know, with Wii Motion Plus, the fix, something they should have had in the first place.
[SPEAKER_09]: And a sequel to Wii Sports, because that's what sells on their system.
[SPEAKER_10]: And funny enough, that's why I disagree with you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think Nintendo has nothing to worry about.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, when I first heard this earlier in the week, I had the same reaction you did.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like, oh, Nintendo's fucked.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now they're going to have this new thing with the motion control.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're taking what makes the Nintendo Wii so great.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're putting it on this new hardware.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo's screwed because everybody's going to want to go to the better looking games.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I thought about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not really going to happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: at the end of the day Nintendo is still going to have kids and soccer moms and that's who they've built their audience on that's how they built their system that's who's still going to be loyal to them remember people are not buying the Wii for the Wii they're buying the Wii for Wii Sports and at the end of the day Nintendo still has Wii Sports will this put a crack in it?
[SPEAKER_10]: yes some of the fanboys and the hardcore a little crack might be put in Nintendo because of this but is it enough to shatter Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_10]: absolutely not
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, they're already too far ahead, but I think it will slow them down.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because now they can't say that they have all this innovative control stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now they actually have to think on their feet and come up with something new.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, that's really, I think, what they should be doing is coming up with something new.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because now they've caught up to, you know, you can only be really innovative so long.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now people have caught up to what you had.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just like, you know, with Rumble and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: People started implementing Rumble, now everybody has it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, you've got to come up with the next big thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: And here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, keep in mind, the motion is built into the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is a part of every Wii game because it is what makes the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, besides maybe a couple games here and there that decide to ignore it, but you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is integrated into the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: The motion control is the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: With the Xbox 360, this is something extra.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is not something that was not already in the system by default.
[SPEAKER_10]: Power Glove, U-Force, Power Pad, and...
[SPEAKER_10]: Video cameras, which we were just talking about, the vision cameras.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but I think they would have done a lot better if they were bundled in with games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look at what Nintendo's doing now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_09]: They want to sell a lot of balance boards, so what they did, they included the software free.
[SPEAKER_09]: They wanted to sell a lot of remotes and stuff like that, so they included a game for $10 more.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do want to say before somebody in chat screams their head off, some peripherals do break the mold and do well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Guitar...
[SPEAKER_10]: and Drum and DDR have all shattered.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Wii Wheel.
[SPEAKER_09]: You'd be surprised how freaking popular it is for a piece of plastic.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I don't... But for the Wii Wheel, we had a Lynx crossbow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's the problem, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, and I understand, you know, Lynx crossbow training, well, with the Wii Zapper, that sucked, and yeah, the Wii Zapper is a horrible peripheral.
[SPEAKER_09]: The thing is...
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's the problem Microsoft has.
[SPEAKER_09]: All the people that wanted the Wii for Wii Sports and that kind of stuff, they're going to buy the Wii because it's cheap or cheaper.
[SPEAKER_09]: But now, with Microsoft and stuff, actually, if they can come out with some sort of way to bundle in a sports game in this motion sensor, they might be able to pull it off.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they're going to have to have a must-have game with this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because if they try to pack in Totem Ball, don't fucking bother.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously, don't fucking bother Microsoft if you're going to put in a game of that quality.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to have to put in a must-have game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they've got to be careful if they're going to try to be competitive with the Wii Sports thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to need to have the must-have game with this in order to sell this thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, that's how Guitar Hero and all those peripherals did well, is because they came with must-have games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Link's Crossbow Training, not so much a must-have game.
[SPEAKER_10]: DDR, pop culture icon of the late 90s, early 2000s, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_10]: The DDR pads did fairly well because of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: and also it depends Microsoft's going after Core Gamer they're trying to get into more of the casual game market Nintendo not so much anymore with the Core Gamer they just want to bring on new people that haven't played games
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think they're going to overshadow Halo ODST right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, that's more of an announcement for next year.
[SPEAKER_09]: And
[SPEAKER_09]: They need something more than Halo because Halo is not going to bring in the casual gamer.
[SPEAKER_10]: And to be fair, GameGuru said the same thing and said that's the game you need to put the X-Mode in.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just, you know, I just think it would be if Halo 4 supports it, it'll help drive it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I just don't think, you know, I think they're going to turn off a lot of their Halo because there's some people that don't want this.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I like to run and fill about and kill people.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think the fitness bandwagon is where it's at.
[SPEAKER_07]: EA Playground did it first.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the people that leaked the Forza 3 rumor have also sent in an image showing that there's going to be Perfect Dark on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so it could possibly be it has the same thumbnail image that Rare leaked in April.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I was just watching what Loki was doing with the controller.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki's playing on Excitebots right now, so it's a little bit distracting.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks a little perverse.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks like you're driving the Batmobile or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is an interesting car.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, it is an actual bat he's driving.
[SPEAKER_10]: This game looks kind of fun, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: As I was saying, the thought overall is that there could be more rare Nintendo 64 titles coming out on Xbox Live Arcade, but there's not really enough to support it yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have to wait and see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know there's a lot of Perfect Dark fanboys, and certainly I did not like that new one they had on Xbox 360, like their launch title at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, you know, going back to the classics, I think it'll be a lot better.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's also funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: They also had Bean listed on there, which I don't remember if that's a... It was a codename for either the original Perfect Dark Zero or if it's the sequel to Perfect Dark Zero.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was also listed on there, which is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, of course, Ash...
[SPEAKER_09]: 4 is the 3
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Forza, not a racing series I particularly get into.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a little heavy for me, but I guess there's a lot of fans of Forza, certainly.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I know there will be a lot of folks that are all about this at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we have other big, big rumors, and this one has to do with portable gaming.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yes, it involves the PSP, and apparently the rumor has leaked out about the new PSP that's going to be shown at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's called the PSP Gauntlet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go!
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently the rumors are starting to snowball with this due to some one-up reporting from earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: According to some inside sources, apparently it's going to be getting a complete hardware redesign.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks to me like a cell phone with one of those screens that pops out like a sidekick.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think it's supposed to be like that, but the way this thing looks is it looks like a sidekick to me where the screen kind of pops out and then you have the controller underneath it.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the silliest thing I've ever seen in my life.
[SPEAKER_10]: it's going to be meaning no discs so meaning that the game will be entirely fueled and this is where the rumor has been going for a while now that there's going to be this PSP 2 that's fueled this way that this PSP Go is going to be fueled entirely off downloadable titles in fact over 100 classic and new PSP titles they are saying available at the systems launch one of the biggies Gran Turismo Mobile
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope for their sake they're not doing this move in hopes that it's going to cut down on their piracy because I'll have them know all the PlayStation Network titles that they have available there are only for download only.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those have already leaked out, and they leak out just as fast.
[SPEAKER_09]: So they better hopefully fix whatever ways people have of exploiting their system and putting custom firmwares on because if they don't, this is going to be completely useless.
[SPEAKER_09]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: What's interesting about this, you're not talking about a hardware upgrade with this, which is what I find really interesting about this.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not a PSP2.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's where I'm kind of like, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: At what Sony's doing here, because they're not taking this opportunity to upgrade the hardware at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I don't really see the point of needing to hide the controls in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, really, is there any reason why you need a sliding screen unless the screen is going to be touchscreen or something like that?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a look thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I put a little protector on the screen, I can carry it around in my pocket and not have to worry about breaking the buttons.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just like a cell phone.
[SPEAKER_10]: You concealed the keyboard underneath the screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, we'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure if they're going to announce it, they're going to announce it at E3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although, I kind of find it funny that they've already revised their system like three times already.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're just trying to find the perfect fit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's read some comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is stirring a huge response in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com if you want to comment.
[SPEAKER_10]: GoldAnthro in chat says, No UMD is fucking retarded and the downloadable titles will probably be DRM to hell.
[SPEAKER_10]: DeathWishing says, I like owning cases.
[SPEAKER_10]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: HungryMister says, Oh shit, this is amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: TheRobD says, Yeah, that's interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: It might be a good idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if storage can support it though.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's kind of true too is that when you're talking about how many games are going to fit on 8GB.
[SPEAKER_09]: The largest
[SPEAKER_09]: This UMD game is 2 gigs.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that you're talking like maybe... But most of them are not 2 gigs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, so maybe 7 games.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there better be an easy-ass way for me to move games on and off this thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like an iTunes-ish thing to manage my system.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the problem, though, is if you don't have high-speed internet, even still if you have high-speed internet, downloading a 2-gig game is going to take a long time.
[SPEAKER_10]: And all these caps now, too, with Comcast and all this says 250 gigabytes and so on.
[SPEAKER_10]: That could be dangerous, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: If it's all digital, it's just going to make it a little bit cheaper for them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me get some other comments from chat real quick.
[SPEAKER_10]: TigerClaw says, I prefer owning a physical copy of the game rather than a digital version.
[SPEAKER_10]: Brad from PodCulture says, Not a fan of the no UMD deal though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it looks kind of neat too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Make the Switch and do something like Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Put the game on a chip.
[SPEAKER_10]: A slot wouldn't take up near the space that UMD would.
[SPEAKER_09]: And at the same time, this is not going to really sell to people that, say, for example, own a bunch of PSP games already, because now they've got to replace them all or buy them again.
[SPEAKER_09]: And really, do you think people are going to buy their games again?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, that's wishful thinking, Sony, if that's what you think is going to actually happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's another thing, is that if I already own this game on UMD, there better damn well better be a way that I can transfer this onto my PSP without having to rebuy the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's going to be...
[SPEAKER_10]: Shitty, if not.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I have a bad feeling that's where we're going.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because how else is it going to know?
[SPEAKER_09]: And there's no other way unless, I mean...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: Download Game System Download Game System Download Game System
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: and I'm sure if they had a way to do standalone games they'd probably be selling games for it as well but that's the only means to get stuff on there and the fact that they're going to try to compete with that
[SPEAKER_10]: It's kind of dumb with taking the UMD out of the picture.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hitstun in chat says, Sky, apparently you can go to a store and they'll have a kiosk that will transfer your UMD game to a memory stick.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope to hell that's true.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because if it's not, and I'm going to be forced to rebuy the game I already own on the PSP1, I will turn to piracy.
[SPEAKER_09]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate to openly admit that on the show, but that's...
[SPEAKER_10]: That's dumb.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's even more retarded if they're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's going to stop Joe Blow from loaning his game to somebody?
[SPEAKER_09]: I could buy one copy of Grand Theft Auto Vice City Stories and loan it to 50 people and they can all get it dumped to their... Unless they use a key.
[SPEAKER_09]: But not for old games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Old games don't have that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And each game isn't marked.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can't tell one from another.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what though?
[SPEAKER_10]: What about Joe Blow taking this latest CD that he bought at the store and his friend ripping it to his iTunes?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know that happens rampantly as it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, but they're trying to figure out ways not to do stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, yeah, granted, we can assume that someone's doing that, but they're making it super easy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just like, you know...
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob, I can have you buy a game and then now we all have the game because you bought the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's my question to you.
[SPEAKER_10]: If it was that easy and it was that open, would you steal the game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because there's nothing easier than not driving to the store and not, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't understand you sometimes because you pay extravagant amounts of money for some games and other games you're just like, yeah, I'll just download it.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know, I blame Nintendo for not having demos for their... Well, they do have demos for their games, and I guess I could have tried it out online.
[SPEAKER_09]: Big deal.
[SPEAKER_09]: That still takes too long on the Wii, and really, I don't want to do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, I just wanted to present both sides of it for the people that get, you know, little angry clouds over their heads when you talk about piracy and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to be fair and present both sides.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, to be honest, the last game I played on my PSP, I don't even remember when.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was so long ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: The last thing I played on my PSP?
[SPEAKER_09]: Rift Tracks for Twilight, and that was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, that's going to do it for our PSP discussion.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to call in about this later, I'm sure we'll get some calls about this a little later on the show, but we want to move on to some release dates and some non-rumors, things we know that are coming out very soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll start off in the UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, UK, nothing until the 12th.
[SPEAKER_10]: What a bummer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Must be a slow release week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or a non-release week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that everyone's recovering from May 1st being a fertility holiday.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't there a bank holiday?
[SPEAKER_09]: That could be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it was on the 7th or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well then so much for UK releases.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about the US?
[SPEAKER_09]: In the US, there's actually some stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: This week, actually, it's very ironic that we were just talking about all these digital downloads.
[SPEAKER_09]: Patapon 2, the digital download only, or you can get the little card to redeem it, is actually going to be available on PSP this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also this week, we're going to be getting...
[SPEAKER_09]: Donkey Kong Jungle Beat, part of the new Play Control re-release series on the Wii Fantasy Aquarium World, looks like shit, so don't buy it, it's on the Wii, really cheap though Puzzle Kingdoms, game from Zoo Games, actually created by the creators of Puzzle Quest and it's basically a rip-off of Puzzle Quest, but you can get that on the DS this week
[SPEAKER_09]: Night at the Museum, Battle for the Smithsonian, that's going to be on Xbox 360, Wii, and DS this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, Jagged Alliance coming to the DS, which, man, that's an old game that they're porting over there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Crysis, the Maximum Edition, I believe that's with Crysis Wars, the original Crysis, and the online multiplayer one.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's going to be available for PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: Destiny of Zorro coming out this week on the Wii Leisure Suit Larry boxed off his bus finally coming out on the PS3 if I need to remind you guys that got horrible reviews and apparently really sucked so keep that in mind and then probably the best one this week Klonoa coming out on the Wii which is pretty awesome price now $30 $30 you can't beat that um
[SPEAKER_09]: and then of course, you know, to go along with that, you have to have a really crappy game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Imagine Music Fest.
[SPEAKER_09]: Imagine if I cared.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dance Dance Revolution Universe 3
[SPEAKER_10]: If you're into the Chinese rock and stuff, you might want to check this out because I do not believe there's ever been a DDR with Chinese music.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know they've had Korean, they've had Japanese, of course, and American, naturally.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if there's been one before with Chinese.
[SPEAKER_10]: That could be the first one, to my knowledge.
[SPEAKER_10]: On the PlayStation 3, nothing this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a very slow week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's looking very similar to Europe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even on the Nintendo Wii, not a thing as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's not a release coming up until May 14th when you have a winning XI game coming out
[SPEAKER_10]: on the PlayStation 2 nothing this week either same thing on the DS it is a very slow week in Japan right now so not a darn thing being released except that DDR in other Asian regions so there you have it we'll have more to talk about next week hopefully so let's get back into some gaming news
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there is a little news regarding a particular bit of rock and roll royalty.
[SPEAKER_07]: As in Prince, who is now, again, Prince and not that weird symbol.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was actually incredibly brilliant on his part.
[SPEAKER_07]: I won't go into it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look it up on Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_10]: But still, he does some serious drugs or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Prince Turn Down a Deal to Have His Songs in Guitar Hero
[SPEAKER_07]: He has said that he doesn't have a problem with them, but he thinks it's more important that kids learn to actually play the guitar.
[SPEAKER_07]: To put the effort into it and not have it just basically handed to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was quoted as saying, to play music is one of the greatest things.
[SPEAKER_09]: I agree with that, but at the same time, I think Guitar Hero and Rock Band gets people playing the fake guitars and gets them interested.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, stop being arrogant.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I understand.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know plenty of people who play those games who have zero interest in learning the guitar for real.
[SPEAKER_07]: They want the instant gratification.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, but it's better than no appreciation for music whatsoever, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the same thing with Wii Music.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember we had the same discussion when Wii Music came out about how, hey, as dumb as this game looks, if it gets kids interested in music, it's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's different for younger kids, which I think Wii Music would more appeal to, than usually the people who are buying Guitar Hero and Rock Band already have an interest in the music they'll be playing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, one benefit with all the download content is being introduced to new bands and hearing new things, but at the same time...
[SPEAKER_07]: I really don't think that it's a great introductory medium now for people learning about music.
[SPEAKER_07]: We Music, I think, is a completely different animal.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just think it's a darn shame that he feels this way because When Doves Cry would be the most epic rock band song, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would be fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would buy that in a heartbeat.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what would be better than that?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's Get Crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or 1999.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's more synth.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be fun too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but you know, since we're never going to get the keyboards, you know, they do synthy songs in rock band once in a while.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just think it's a darn shame.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's some pretty kick-ass Prince songs.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wish they would just go above his head and go to Warner Brothers, which owns the old music, and just get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, honestly, honestly, I would rather them get it from, get the permission of the artist, because that's more respect to the artist himself.
[SPEAKER_07]: If he doesn't want his music in the game, he has every right to turn it down.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if that's his reason... And I have every right to call him a cockknocker because of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: If that's his reason and it's his music, like, I would be the same way with my art if it was something that I didn't agree with.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I had done something... Now, if it was something that I was doing just, you know, like, corporate something or the other, and that's the purpose I was being paid for, yeah, but if someone saw something that I did and say, wow, I think this would work good in my ad for anti-puppies.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I like puppies, so I say, no, you can't, you do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or for, you know...
[SPEAKER_10]: You made an ad against puppies?
[SPEAKER_10]: What exactly is an anti-puppy?
[SPEAKER_07]: A cat?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well played.
[SPEAKER_10]: Cats rule and dogs drool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Love, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: If it was for something that I didn't really support on my own, then I would say no, and it would be my right because it's my work.
[SPEAKER_07]: I agree with him.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's his work.
[SPEAKER_07]: He has the right not to support it with his work.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I have the right to think he's kind of a douche because of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's just fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: We just want to have fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can think that all you want to, but it doesn't change the fact that it's still... You're right, it's not going to change the end result, but... It's still his right to say no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Luckily, though, for you guys, that Guitar Hero was put together so lazily that there are a lot of programs out there allowing you to create your own custom mixes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't want to go to that kind of trouble.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just saying that if you want to put the effort in, you could
[SPEAKER_09]: Get your own Prince Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but I'm too lazy and that's what it really boils down to.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what can you do?
[SPEAKER_09]: Who would really want to own a Prince Guitar Hero?
[SPEAKER_09]: I would not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unless it's like weird shaped guitar.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would if you get purple velvet suits with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you get guitars shaped like that symbol, I actually might have to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be kind of cool See, even Loki can't resist It's just because it's so ridiculous I would like to see one that would actually have clips of Purple Rain in it
[SPEAKER_09]: Now the thing is, though, I want to see if they have, you know, available the, was it the Guitar Wolf microphones?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, the ones that shot fire out of them when you sang into them?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that's cool shit right there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, is that like Dance Dance Immolation?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have a Burning Man, the version of DDR that when you screw up it shoots fire at you.
[SPEAKER_09]: But all I know is Guitar Wolf is awesome and the movie Wild Zero is retarded and, you know,
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully it comes with a vacuum too then.
[SPEAKER_10]: Glitter is one of those things, like if you throw glitter in your house ever, or you let somebody that has too much glitter on their body sit on your furniture, you will be finding that glitter like a year and a half afterwards.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, why is there glitter on my sofa?
[SPEAKER_09]: Glitter sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: This week, Rock Band's actually getting quite a bit of content.
[SPEAKER_09]: including a Franz Ferdinand 3 pack, which will include Do You Want To?, Lucid Dreams, and Take Me Out.
[SPEAKER_09]: All those available for $2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Separately are 160 Microsoft Points, or if you want to save 50 cents, you can buy the pack for 440 Microsoft Points, or...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: or Luscious Jackson.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's one of the ones I'm going to buy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Idealistic Types by Prong and The Banishment by Prong.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not to play fanboy or anything here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm
[SPEAKER_09]: Really pro-rock band, but it's sad when you see, and we're going to probably get into Guitar Hero's lineup for next month or for this month, it's sad to see that what's coming out one week for rock band is about the same as coming out the entire month for Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still don't own Guitar Hero World Tour.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't see the point.
[SPEAKER_10]: To be honest, all the songs I want to play are in Rock Band, and I don't mean to sound fanboy either, but too bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: When I look at the list of songs in Guitar Hero and put it next to the list of the songs, including download content in Rock Band, Rock Band wins for me, and I don't see the need to own both.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't...
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, the ironic thing, though, the guitar I own is a Guitar Hero guitar.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you're a Guitar Hero fanboy, just STFU, sit down.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still own the Guitar Hero guitars.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, yeah, I don't really care for the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the best part about Rock Band, though, is there's a lot of songs available on their Rock Band store.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, they have finally hit the milestone of 666 songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: 666.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was there a 666 song like Skinnered or Marilyn Manson, or what did they do?
[SPEAKER_10]: Was there a celebration for the 666 song?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, there wasn't, but I didn't see what exactly was the 666 song.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I guess it was...
[SPEAKER_09]: It didn't really say, but as part of whatever Jane's Addiction's Nothing Shocking, one of those hit 666.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess Jane's Addiction works.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess I can see that.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least it wasn't... But it would have been funnier if it was one of those... You know how they've done the SpongeBob SquarePants stuff and they had some of the Nickelodeon show or whatever?
[SPEAKER_10]: It would have been funny if they had had Hannah Montana or something as the 666 song that came out.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would have been pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: We Rock, Drum King, Rolling Stone
[SPEAKER_10]: and Drum King.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's not because it has a deal with the actual band, the Rolling Stones.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's based off the Music Magazine.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know Rolling Stone?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a huge magazine.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like an oversized magazine.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've been around for many, many, many years talking about music.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yeah, kind of interesting that it's going to tie in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're just going to have to have two Wii remotes for air drumming.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's all you use in the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's being developed by ARC System Works.
[SPEAKER_10]: And some of the songs that you can see in the game, We Will Rock You by Queen, Final Countdown by Europe, Song 2 by Blur.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know you're a Blur fan.
[SPEAKER_10]: Feel Good Inc.
[SPEAKER_10]: by The Gorillas.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, there's lots of... That makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's lots of Damon love in this particular game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And such 90s classics as All Star by Smash Mouth.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just some of the songs you can play in the Rolling Stone Drum King.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's a name change from We Rock Drum King.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I guess it means lots of free ads in the magazine.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_10]: A little more news for you guys before we take a break here on Orange Line Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there is a particular game that lots of people play just to make stuff in.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am one of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually The Sims.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's stuff on Sims 3 out now.
[SPEAKER_07]: There actually is going to be...
[SPEAKER_07]: You get six pounds worth of sim points to spend at a Sims 3 store.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can buy clothes and furniture and all kinds of other stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can get extra points in bundles of 500, 1,000, and 2,000.
[SPEAKER_07]: You also get a game launcher, which is meant to be a hub for the Sims community.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can get information and downloads and uploads and stuff online.
[SPEAKER_07]: 5th of June, 5th of May
[SPEAKER_10]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: you gotta come sometime sorry, 5th June which will have a full community and product site and a new town which you can download and some stuff but it's coming out for PC, Mac, iPhone and iPod Touch and I actually might have to play it on my phone so it can go you people suck I just will be happy as long as there's textures and stuff
[SPEAKER_09]: I just want different ways to kill my Sims.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's really all I want.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want more haunted houses.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to make Silent Hill in Simverse.
[SPEAKER_10]: I always liked making the elaborate death traps in The Sims.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that'll be fun to do in Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I always like to build a pool with no ladder to get out and so they drown because they're not smart enough to just climb out the side.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like going in debug mode and putting them up on the third floor of my house on a balcony that has no way out and a toilet.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that they at least could go to the bathroom but they'd starve to death.
[SPEAKER_10]: Didn't you try to build the diving board really high up into the pool?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, on the third floor.
[SPEAKER_10]: And what you were going to do is you were going to pause it while they were in midair and then take out the pool?
[SPEAKER_09]: I wanted to do that, or I wanted to put the diving board out so that they, you know...
[SPEAKER_07]: My favorite thing to do is just to make the human terrarium where you get all clear doors, glass walls, and then you get them to go into the room by leaving some chicken or something in there, and then you pause the game and add the other walls so that people can just watch them.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know what I'm going to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know this new one, they've got a lot of video editing features and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Saw.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder if we're going to get any more Strangerhood with The Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that was pretty funny by the guys that do Red vs. Blue.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I had more time, I'd say let's do like an OLR in The Sims.
[SPEAKER_10]: That'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: We could totally.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will never forget, however, the house that my old roommate built in The Sims where he put like... What was the most people he could have in a house?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like six?
[SPEAKER_10]: So he put five men that would all like make out with each other and kiss each other and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: He put five men in the house and one woman...
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_09]: and basically a quote from John F. Kennedy saying the world is very different now for man holds in his hands the power to abolish all forms of human poverty and all forms of human life.
[SPEAKER_09]: And people are thinking, huh, that's probably Front Mission now coming out on 360 or maybe the PS3.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Front Mission is a mech military strategy game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's more of a tactical game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it would be very cool if they brought it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I have played this after all.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I did play this on another system a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: And also, apparently, I guess the same image was used at teaser, also in the official Xbox magazine, according to 1UP.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it made very clear, or the teaser text made it very clear that it was going to be front mission for the 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, without saying that it is, they, you know, pointed their finger at it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Soul Calibur Broken Destiny
[SPEAKER_10]: Dampierre Wristblades
[SPEAKER_07]: Tekken 6
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be on the PSP, though, along with the console version, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except it'll have some exclusive content.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll have certain items, certain stages, and a ghost mode, which means that you can download and share character data to play versus matches with.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I guess sort of like how the conquest mode was in...
[SPEAKER_07]: The old Soul Calibur in the arcade where we used to beat up each other's characters.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: S&K The King of Fighters Online
[SPEAKER_09]: No word on whether that's coming out over here as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know right now it's supposed to be available in the Asian regions, and it's coming out on the first half of 2010.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't tell if this is actually a fighting game or a brawler game, but it looks good though, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's up with this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Didn't we just have a King of Fighters shoot-em-up last week, and now we have an RPG?
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're branching out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why suddenly all the King of Fighters love?
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, don't get me wrong, it's a fun series, but it's a little weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, really?
[SPEAKER_10]: A shoot-em-up?
[SPEAKER_10]: With fighting game characters?
[SPEAKER_10]: A role-playing game?
[SPEAKER_10]: What the heck?
[SPEAKER_10]: This reminds me of the Mortal Kombat story modes and some of those, um, like, you know, the Mortal Kombat games they had on the Xbox and stuff?
[SPEAKER_10]: You had those story modes that were really cheesy?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's kind of what this reminds me of for some reason.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if it has anything to do with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, one more story for you guys before we get to the classic game of the week and the end of this half of the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: You might have heard us talk about a game previously called Six Days in Fallujah.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a game that was going to be published by Konami, and the game had to do with one of the big battles that happened in, of course, the recent Iraq War that is actually still going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Konami has pulled the plug on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: with this quote.
[SPEAKER_10]: After seeing the reaction of the video game in the United States and hearing opinions sent through phone calls and email, we decided several days ago not to sell it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that came from a Konami spokesperson talking to Asahi, which is a Japanese news site.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't know, though, if the game has been pulled entirely because, you know, the developers, Atomic Games, they could still put it out with another publisher, but this is certainly going to be a dent in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some people are saying, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was just too soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you think it was?
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you think it was too soon for a game like this?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's relevant.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you wait any longer, it loses its relevance.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't have the same impact it would otherwise.
[SPEAKER_10]: I kind of agree.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you don't like it, don't buy it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I went about this game because I don't like war games anyway, whether it's World War II or history wars.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's very few of those types of war games I'm into at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I just kind of looped this in with that category.
[SPEAKER_10]: But these memories, there have been people that died in this war that has happened very recently.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had a friend from high school who passed away in Iraq.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's tragic.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so wouldn't it actually be respectful to pay what they went through justice?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I don't have a problem with the game, but I'm just... This actually goes to me with a tendency of people to want to bury their head in the sand and ignore that bad shit happens in the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, people who just want to go, oh, well, that sucks, boo-hoo, Perez Hilton, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it's that whole, we want to look past it and not think it was really there by claiming that it's too soon or disrespectful or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think that people really need to have the reality of the situation driven home.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what better way to do it than a video game that's based off of accounts of people who were there.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: See?
[SPEAKER_10]: See?
[SPEAKER_10]: And you're laughing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, that's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: See?
[SPEAKER_10]: But like, you know, that was the day she died.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this wouldn't be meant to be humorous.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a different story.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I know, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I'm a fan of shock humor.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_10]: I say that because we all have different ways of remembering things.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, and for me personally, I laughed my ass off at that joke.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I loved Bea Arthur because I grew up on the Golden Girls.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I remember watching that with my mother, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I was saying that people probably take offense to the fact that the game, not only they spoke to, obviously, the soldiers that were fighting over there, but also the insurgents as well, including, you know, some terror cells or that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: It
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: I wanna talk about Bea Arthur.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: No, the one I picked is, you know, eight years old.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so it's still... But I want to see if our people in the chatroom can figure out what it is based on the intro to the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: James, honey, did something happen to you?
[SPEAKER_05]: After we got separated in that long hallway?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you confusing me with someone else?
[SPEAKER_05]: You were always so forgetful.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember that time in the hotel?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maria?
[SPEAKER_05]: You said you took everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you forgot that videotape we made.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder if it's still there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep, we've got guesses already.
[SPEAKER_07]: How do you know about that?
[SPEAKER_07]: We're pretty close.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Silent Hill 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Rod's the first one to get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: You win something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: TheRobD, you win my TurboGrafx Wow, that was easy Yep I can even take it to him too
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Get it to me next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll go take him to TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll have to autograph it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, Rob, you win my no-controller TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't even know you were doing a giveaway.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was the surprise.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, look at you.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I have to just remember where we put it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, we've been cleaning.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, Silent Hill 2 is the game du jour, or I should say of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the reason why I picked Silent Hill 2, even though this is not my favorite of the Silent Hill series, it's a lot of people's favorites.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I wanted to throw the bone out to the big fans of Silent Hill 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: So with this particular...
[SPEAKER_07]: With this particular game, it's, you know, basically this guy goes back to the town of Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's, you know, third person's perspective.
[SPEAKER_07]: He plays this dude named James who is mourning the loss of his wife, Mary.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he gets a letter from her saying to meet at their spot.
[SPEAKER_07]: And instead, he finds Maria.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, as the game goes on, it's pretty disturbing Silent Hill stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blood.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pyramid Head.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yes, this game is the introduction of...
[SPEAKER_07]: By proper name, Red Pyramid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Two of them, in fact.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the game that gave us the Red Pyramid.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or as you all know him as, Happy Funtime Rapey Pyramid Head.
[SPEAKER_07]: P. Hitty.
[SPEAKER_10]: P. Hitty.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I call him, P. Hitty.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, we're tight like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, um, so, you know, you solve your little puzzles, and you pick up things, and you find things, and you get a chainsaw at some point, chainsaw is awesome, um, and, um, which I've seen Shane beat the game with a chainsaw, didn't he?
[SPEAKER_10]: I wasn't there for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, you also have multiple endings on this game, so you've got up to, um, you have three endings, um, actually is it, yeah, three endings, I think, involving the actual story of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, some of them are really fucked up and sad, um, some of them are, oh, there's one that's kind of happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then you get joke endings, you get the UFO ending, which every Silent Hill game has, and
[SPEAKER_07]: and then my favorite, the dog ending.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, with the dog ending, it shows that a Shiba Inu is actually controlling the entire events of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, the UFO ending, James gets abducted.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's also, though...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the music from the dog ending.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love the dog ending.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love the dog ending, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just like, he goes, what?
[SPEAKER_07]: You did all this?
[SPEAKER_07]: And the dog comes up and licks him.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like that the dog, though, is wearing headphones listening to a karaoke music.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, I had my audio jammed.
[SPEAKER_07]: At any rate, there's also some of the newer special versions.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, in the special edition releases, there is a game, a little side story called Born from a Wish.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is actually in the Restless Dreams edition, or for Europe, the Inner Fears edition.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's wrong?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just pricked myself.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: I just want to point out, this is a scary, scary game.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you've never played a game like this before, you've got to try these types of survival horror games, especially the Silent Hill series.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I'm telling you, these games are so scary, they'll make your asshole slam shut.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of those games where you're so tense, you're like, oh my gosh, I'm so scared, I don't know what's going to happen next.
[SPEAKER_10]: So this is a scary game.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you think games can't scare you, play a game like this.
[SPEAKER_10]: with all the lights off during a rainy night.
[SPEAKER_07]: The biggest thing, and this is why I like the Silent Hill series so much, is that it's a big look into the disturbing parts of the human psyche.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why I like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's actually an enemy in this game who...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, for the main character, you go into a room and he finds the dress that his dead wife wore.
[SPEAKER_07]: And different things that relate to his psychosis, including the Red Pyramid being part of his psychosis.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only character who does not see any of the monsters in the game is a little girl, because she is innocent.
[SPEAKER_07]: She doesn't have those type of deep-rooted...
[SPEAKER_10]: Even though I seem to recall her being kind of a bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was a character based off of Eddie Murphy when he was supposed to be more pleasant.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a character named Angela who was based off of the protagonist in The Net.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I never realized that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: They've all been... And also, and this is something I didn't know, this layout of Silent Hill in the game was based off of San Bruno, California.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it is, to me, one of the best games ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually used to wake up every morning to the theme of Lara, which was on that soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every morning.
[SPEAKER_07]: Until I got sick of it and had to change it to The Birthday Massacre.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, if anyone wants to know about the movie, yeah, the second movie's coming, but Gonzo's not involved.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, has nothing to do with the game, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, as far as this game and that story being involved together.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, Silent Hill 2 is freaking rad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And by the way, my favorite is Silent Hill 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: SILENT HILL 3
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Stay tuned, because guess what?
[SPEAKER_10]: The contest, you know, I didn't even know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was such a surprise contest we just had on the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't even know it was happening.
[SPEAKER_10]: But DarkSakura just gave away TurboGrafx-16.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not the only thing we're giving away tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are giving away a signed autographed copy of DDR on the PlayStation 2, signed by SmileDK.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's thanks to Bress Lowell, who got that at the SakuraCon.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we're going to be...
[SPEAKER_10]: Telling you more about that contest very soon on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is not something you have to be listening to live.
[SPEAKER_10]: Our podcast listeners will get a chance to win this as well, as well as our live listeners.
[SPEAKER_10]: So stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: and we are back here on Orange Lounge Radio and guess what guys it's time to do the giveaway or at least I'm going to tell you guys a little more about the giveaway but first we are going to turn the moderation on in the chat room there so that there's no talking amongst chat so that you guys don't try to give away the answers to each other here's how it's going to work is that what we're going to do we're going to play five clips
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you know the answers to those, we'll draw one from the total, whoever has the most correct answers, we'll draw from that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So even if you don't know all five, send it in anyway, because if people can only get four of the five, you might still win.
[SPEAKER_10]: And again, what you're going to win, a copy of DDR Supernova II for the PlayStation 2, autographed by SmileDK, who is infamous for Butterfly.
[SPEAKER_10]: And various other DDR songs as well, you should know them if you're a fan.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yo, don't block me, don't beat, just watch me
[SPEAKER_10]: Here is song number three.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here is song number four.
[SPEAKER_10]: And lastly, here is song number five.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Make sure the subject says contest somewhere in it or it will not count.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't stress that enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: You need to put contest in the subject or something with the word contest in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can put I love Rob, contest.
[SPEAKER_10]: As long as the word contest is in there, it'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: The five songs for the contest this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Giving away an autographed copy of DDR Supernova 2 by SmileDK.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, I'm going to let you guys be able to talk and chat again.
[SPEAKER_10]: So no giving away answers.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, no giving away answers.
[SPEAKER_10]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess we're ready to get back into tonight's Orange Lounge Radio, so let's do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio on this lovely Sunday evening, May the 3rd of 2009, where we tape live every Sunday night, of course, here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: On All Games Radio, www.allgames.com is where we tape our show and allow you guys to interact with us through ways such as chat and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: is a game being shown off on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's an alpha version of what looks like a remake of Turtles in Time.
[SPEAKER_09]: And by the looks of it, you would probably guess that it's for Xbox Live Arcade, but of course, possibly could make its way to the PlayStation Network and WiiWare as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it looks kind of cool, but definitely looks like Xbox Live Arcade material.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know this is a game a lot of people are very excited about.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and it's alpha right now, so it could be a while.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like that they've kind of re-skinned it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not just a re-release of the game, but they've totally re-skinned the whole thing, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it looks nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: XBOX LIVE ARCADE
[SPEAKER_10]: XBOXLIVE ARCADE
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, the Edinburgh Zoo renames their Wolverine in honor of Wolverine.
[SPEAKER_07]: They named him Logan.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I guess the tie-in that this has is that the picture that they put up is a picture of the Wolverine and behind him was one for the game Standy.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they are using the, I guess, the fame of the movie right now to promote the fact that these are endangered animals, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: I had lots to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: It happens.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: More gaming news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we've got some other, well, kind of unfortunate news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also kind of tied in with the movies, you know, the whole Batman stuff, very successful movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there's of course a new game coming out for Batman, Batman Arkham Asylum.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's supposed to be out in June.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, it's been delayed now to the end of summer.
[SPEAKER_09]: D'oh!
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just because they can?
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically, to give the devs an extra amount of time to make sure the game is the highest quality for gamers.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, in other words, the game's broken right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's got too many bugs.
[SPEAKER_10]: They don't want to release it the way it is right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what it sounds like to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't it worth the wait, though?
[SPEAKER_10]: If they're going to fix the problems with the game, it's worth the wait, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: That they had.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was the last one I really remember liking.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess I heard Lego Batman's pretty good, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't checked it out, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't played it, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't played it, so maybe I'm not being fair.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Lost Planet 2 is the game we knew was coming apparently some new footage has been revealed for Lost Planet 2 and apparently Capcom is trying to get a demo available for E3 and guess what not only is it going to be playable on the show floor at E3 but they are going to try to do one of those you know
[SPEAKER_10]: Bring It Home type things on Xbox Live again.
[SPEAKER_10]: They did with the first one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep, and they'll release a demo during E3 for everybody to play at home via Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this is all from the Capcom Unity blog.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's some new trailers, some new screenshots that you can look at, and they are hoping that there will be a demo
[SPEAKER_10]: Available by E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, there will be four-player co-op in the game, if you haven't heard yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there's going to be a ranking system as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you can compete for the biggest E-peen in Lost Planet 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which looks to have ditched the snow for more of a... Looks like more of an Amazonian... Well, they didn't really ditch the snow.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just the planet's starting to thaw.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which I guess there was a little bit of it in the first game.
[SPEAKER_06]: They put it in a defrost setting in the microwave.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently, because it does look a little thawed out this time, so it looks a little more jungly.
[SPEAKER_10]: You do still see the snow in some parts, but it has more of a lush green look to it than last time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you know, there's other things that have, you know, a green look to them, and that would be zombies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Zombies.
[SPEAKER_10]: To be green or gray.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, usually they're red after dining on blood.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, enough blood on them, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I mean the flesh tone, you know, it's kind of that green-gray sickly looking thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there is news about Dead Rising 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: When they said that there were going to be multiplayer sessions, well...
[SPEAKER_07]: They were actually correct on that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Capcom said that there will be online multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_07]: No details on it, but it said that there will be.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, the one thing that Dead Rising 1 was missing is going to be in Dead Rising 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: That sounds pretty amazing to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: As long as you can still run over Amina with a L'Amour.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I'm hoping for.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they were showing off some pretty cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently the main character now, since he's not, you know...
[SPEAKER_09]: A photographer.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's more of like a carpenter guy.
[SPEAKER_09]: He can kind of fashion his own weapons.
[SPEAKER_09]: So he had like two chainsaws strapped to this giant stick.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then he strapped two chainsaws to his motorcycle and drove through a crowd of zombies.
[SPEAKER_07]: So he gets the MacGyverism skill.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and apparently they had up to 7,000 zombies on screen at a time.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that sounds sweet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Another thing that sounds kind of sweet, actually, even though the first game...
[SPEAKER_09]: Very disappointing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Red Steel 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Red Steel 2 has been announced, and it's apparently going to the Wild West.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to feature MotionPlus support.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not really sure if it's actually a Wild West game, but the main character kind of looks like he could be on the Wild West.
[SPEAKER_09]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: GS68 in chat disagrees, says no, Red Steel 2 will suck.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft says they'll probably bundle Red Steel 2 with Motion Plus.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they're doing a lot of those bundles.
[SPEAKER_09]: They gotta try to sell that Motion Plus.
[SPEAKER_10]: So does this mean that Motion Plus is gonna be required for the game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, that's what they're saying right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if they don't have a bundle with Motion Plus, aren't they severely limiting their audience?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would think the people that would buy this would not necessarily be the same audience that's going to pick up a game like Wii Sports Resort.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, MotionPlus is going to be sold separately, though, a month prior to that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they've also got a bundle with Tiger Woods.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're also doing a bundle with EA Sports Tennis Grand Slam that's going to be...
[SPEAKER_09]: or Grand Slam Tennis that's coming out before Tiger Woods even in Europe.
[SPEAKER_09]: And who knows how many more bundles with this thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've got to sell those Motion Plus things.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've got to get people to realize, hey, you guys should spend another $20 on sensors that should have been in there in the first place.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then we can come out with the controller with the sensors built in.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ha, bitches!
[SPEAKER_10]: Then they can think of something else they forgot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then it'll be, oh, but now you want to get the Wii HD so that our graphics can be on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: You need to get the Wii Balance Board Plus because now it has more sensors and it's even more sensitive than before.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bet you anything you'll see something stupid like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, haven't there already been rumors of a Wii Fit Plus?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, there has been a Wii Fit Plus with the Balance Board, but I don't know if that's just the same Balance Board.
[SPEAKER_09]: It might be the same Balance Board, I mean.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, have you ever tried controlling balance board games?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not very fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just Wii Fit, and it works okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like the marble rolling game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's very, very sensitive.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's very, very, very sensitive.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I think because those games are supposed to challenge your balance, it's why it's that way.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't played any of the standalone balance games.
[SPEAKER_10]: There hasn't been anything that really, you know, caught my eye that I really want to get.
[SPEAKER_10]: Adventure 2600 Reboot
[SPEAKER_10]: and we're looking at a little YouTube here in studio what this game looks like and it's pretty cool because they actually have the dragon flying around and
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: and he had a whole little interview with GameSetWatch talking about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a whole team of people.
[SPEAKER_10]: It wasn't just this guy but he was kind of the spokesperson talking about the project.
[SPEAKER_10]: So pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I might have to check this out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think you will?
[SPEAKER_07]: For real?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I will.
[SPEAKER_10]: For real.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to find this it's at slashx.googlepages.com There's a whole little page about the Adventure 2600 reboot.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I get the sense why?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because we can.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura is going to dive in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pye Pye Pye always wins
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, we actually have one from Dan Shadow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey guys, what's more dangerous, chimps or raptors?
[SPEAKER_07]: Help me out here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are these for real tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: I am serious, and I'm reading them because you fucking made me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_10]: Raptors, look at Jurassic Park.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although, chimps can carry Ebola virus, like you saw in Outbreak.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're thinking of velociraptors.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_07]: A raptor is like a hawk.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aren't velociraptors a kind of raptor?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think chimps are dangerous if you give them a gun.
[SPEAKER_09]: RAPTORS RAPTORS
[SPEAKER_10]: I would bet anything the emailer meant to say Velociraptors because raptors by themselves are not that scary.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Velociraptors?
[SPEAKER_10]: Terrifying.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're carnivores.
[SPEAKER_09]: And raptors the jets.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those are pretty dangerous too, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Skipping on!
[SPEAKER_09]: Flying Velociraptors.
[SPEAKER_07]: This comes from Gil.
[SPEAKER_09]: and the monkeys the band.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know how dangerous they'd be.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's my first time writing in and I'll make it a short one.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you think about the new PSP Go?
[SPEAKER_07]: How long until it will be hacked because the 3000s are not hackable to the public yet?
[SPEAKER_07]: Should they release the hack or wait for the new PSP?
[SPEAKER_09]: If they were smart they would wait for the new PSP to come out but they won't.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've already got a sort of
[SPEAKER_09]: Proof of Concept done already for the new PSP 3000.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hacker groups are pretty competitive.
[SPEAKER_10]: They don't want to sit on it and wait to have someone else beat them or else all their work is for naught.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you will better believe that when that new system comes out, all they have to say is, it's unhackable, and then they'll be like, oh, we're going to get down on that shit, and it'll be hacked before you know it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It may take a little bit of time.
[SPEAKER_10]: The problem is it may have to use an exploit in the game to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it'll be interesting because if everything is downloadable, they'll start to sneak the patches in the games and all that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you'll have to patch.
[SPEAKER_10]: It'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're always going to find a way.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're always going to find a way to hack it.
[SPEAKER_07]: This one, ready for the next email?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, OLR, I was wondering if you guys buy the PSP 3000.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been thinking, okay, bad grammar.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I currently own four PSP2 Slims, and if that, I'm interested in your thoughts because tonight you're going to talk about the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Guy, it's Y-O-U apostrophe R-E, not Y-O-U-R, that's possessive, duh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe I should ust wait instead of just wait for the rumored PSP2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry for the late notice.
[SPEAKER_07]: L-O-L-C-U in chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sincerely, HungryMurcrunk.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hungry Mr. Crunk.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was that typed on a PSP?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it says Hungry Mr. Crunk.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or your OLR member, Columbia99.
[SPEAKER_10]: What was the question?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's only two periods in this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Should he get a PSP 3000?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not when you know that this PSP goes on the horizon.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wouldn't get either.
[SPEAKER_09]: The PSP 3000 really only had the microphone built in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_10]: If you really love your PSP, then wait for the PSP Go.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if you already have a couple PSPs, which it sounds like you do, I don't see the point.
[SPEAKER_10]: Again, this PSP Go is not going to have any additional hardware to it that we know of so far.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, granted, they might come out and say something at E3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure, buy one, help the economy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I love how they're like, oh, well, we don't want to add another analog stick to it because then that'll make certain games incompatible.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're making them all download anyways, so they're going to be incompatible with whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just have...
[SPEAKER_09]: Buy one and help the economy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ain't my money, so I don't care.
[SPEAKER_09]: Send your money to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll stimulate the economy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I bet you will.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, hey OLR peep shizzles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: With all the rumors about the PSP 2 or whatever Sony will call it, I was wondering what are your top three features that you want for it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, this could be a list list.
[SPEAKER_07]: I personally would like a larger screen and separate mini USB device that allows you to load your UMD games onto it for playing games that you already own without switching disks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, I would love dual analog sticks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Much love, someone who dearly loves old people.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait a minute, didn't we already hear from somebody like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, we did.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry, I got kicked from IRC in the middle of that question.
[SPEAKER_10]: Top three features for the PSP Go?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that you would want to see.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want a Tic Tac dispenser.
[SPEAKER_10]: Made of bacon?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, I want orange Tic Tacs.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, because they're not going to do much that they're not already doing with the PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's so hard to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, they may as well add like a phone unit on that thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like one anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: The number one thing I want to see is I want to make sure it's easy to download the games and get them on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to see integration with my PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to see something that when I plug this thing into my PC, it has a cool little front-end system like iTunes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I got criticized for that earlier by somebody in chat saying iTunes isn't that great.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're actually right.
[SPEAKER_10]: iTunes is not that great, but it still makes managing the device a lot easier than if you didn't have something like that at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm talking about something pretty...
[SPEAKER_10]: for stupid people that will allow me to manage the content on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I would like more than anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, soccer ball!
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you watching Loki playing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I was watching Loki play because he's a soccer ball.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's my idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, do you have anything?
[SPEAKER_09]: Touchscreen would be nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: A better web browser.
[SPEAKER_09]: And...
[SPEAKER_09]: Paygle.
[SPEAKER_09]: More RAM, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they should add more RAM to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, who cares?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, just add a more beefy web browser, more RAM, and... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Touchscreen would be nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Xlink in chat says porn.
[SPEAKER_10]: PSP needs more porn.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's plenty of porn out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Plus, you can convert it all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, plus the thing gets on the internet, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's all the porn you need right there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why you need a better web browser.
[SPEAKER_07]: It should have a GPS.
[SPEAKER_10]: That might be neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it should have, instead of a Tic Tac dispenser, an Altoid dispenser.
[SPEAKER_10]: And apps like the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_10]: Open-end development.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the Tamagotchi.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's on my list, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Open-end development.
[SPEAKER_07]: It should have the little tiger games on there, like football and all those games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, we've given more than three.
[SPEAKER_10]: This listener should be satisfied.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dear God, whoever wrote a novel... Oh, that's Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is your friendly and swine flu-free neighborhood Mexican, Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I just say, swine flu, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_10]: People need to stop it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stop it with the swine flu garbage.
[SPEAKER_10]: More people die from lots of other things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like...
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'll admit, at first, if you go back and read my Twitter, at first I was kind of like, eh, because I was worried that it was actually going to be an outbreak, but like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_10]: More people die from the regular flu.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not as big of a deal as people were making it out to be in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_10]: Knock it off.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you can eat pork and not get swine flu, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: It made me want to cry when there was an actual caption on CNN saying you do not get swine flu from eating pig.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just think it's an excuse for people to use swine in everyday conversation
[SPEAKER_10]: Since this swine flu thing came out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to go get pork chops.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: He actually said on the news, if people will just eat a pork chop a week and some bacon, we'll all be fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm thinking in the back of my head, boy, Loki's probably sitting there watching this going, no problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not sitting there watching.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm eating pork.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think all our listeners, unless you are Muslim or Jewish or any other religion that doesn't allow you to eat pork.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or vegetarian or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or vegetarian, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go to your local IHOP and order a bacon platter.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Please help keep my uncle in business.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go get some bacon right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unless, you know, Jewish, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everyone get together and just do the bacon march and hold up banners that say, Bacon does not give you swine flu.
[SPEAKER_07]: Eat up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bacon is meat candy.
[SPEAKER_10]: H1N1 be damned.
[SPEAKER_10]: I heart bacon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bacon is meat candy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need a shirt for ASEN that says I heart bacon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I get that quickly?
[SPEAKER_07]: I bet you could.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a shirt that says I heart bacon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I borrow it for ASIN?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, damn you.
[SPEAKER_07]: That, of course, was only half one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll figure it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is your... Okay, I already read that part.
[SPEAKER_07]: As we may already know, Harmonix is going to release some Rock Band games to expand the franchise.
[SPEAKER_07]: Though what I don't get is why people are bitching and whining about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: First of all, all those that are saying that Harmonix is trying to milk the franchise and are going the way of Activision, look at all the Guitar Hero games that have been released and all those to come in the near future.
[SPEAKER_07]: Guitar Hero Metallica, Smash Hits, Van Halen, On Tour Decades, and the arcade game, just to name a few.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, the movie theater had a Guitar Hero arcade, just thought I'd let you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now look at what Harmonix has released or will release at the same time span.
[SPEAKER_07]: ACDC tracks, Unplugged, The Beatles, Lego Rock Band, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Guitar Hero has overloaded the market while Rock Band is expanding its current market.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not to mention that you can export tracks and play DLC in whatever Rock Band game with no problem except for The Beatles and Unplugged.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we don't know about Lego yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: while with Guitar Hero you have to own every disc to be able to play every song you have on them not to mention changing discs every time you want to play a song that's on another disc yes I know this isn't a problem for some but it's still something that would be more quick and useful
[SPEAKER_07]: To top it off, people are also asking, why Rock Band Unplugged on the PSP?
[SPEAKER_07]: Where's the reason on that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the reason is that if they had more info on it, they would know it is a spiritual sequel to Frequency and Amplitude made by Harmonix nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_07]: No instruments, just press the buttons, and according to what the track is, and of course, according to the rhythm.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the new songs featured on it will be on the Rock Band Music Store for consoles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, Unplugged will have its own music score, not like Guitar Hero on Tour, in which you need the peripheral to play and you can't play on Tour on your DSi.
[SPEAKER_07]: And not to mention the awkwardness when you're playing it with EndNote, DLC, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_07]: To sum it all up, Rock Band is not turning into guitar heroes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop bitching about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Harmonix knows what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was all in caps, but I feel like screaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry if this email is a long FU rant, but I need to get it off my chest.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for reading and for listening to your listeners.
[SPEAKER_07]: Smile face.
[SPEAKER_07]: Happy face.
[SPEAKER_07]: You just, you did the smiley, my favorite smiley.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
I agree that Rock Band isn't milking it as bad as Guitar Hero, but I worry that it might be going that direction.
If this Lego thing will not let you import songs
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not going to.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a different publisher.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's the only reason.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, my mic wasn't on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was going to say, if this rock band will not let you import songs, I'm going to be very disappointed.
[SPEAKER_10]: This Lego one.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think rock bands jumped the shark as bad as Guitar Hero, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd be surprised if they let you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think there's going to be too many problems because it's a different publisher, but if it were the same publisher, I'm sure they would let you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Same with the Beatles thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Beatles thing, they have a special deal there.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's, you know, Beatles only.
[SPEAKER_09]: If they come out with a Rock Band 3, you better believe all that stuff from the other games are going to be, you know...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: and in place, you're getting these standalone games that you have to spend $60 for.
[SPEAKER_09]: No thanks.
[SPEAKER_09]: But again, those are optional too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, I want to make a comment about emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: Henceforth, unless I feel otherwise at the moment, if I get any more emails during the show, I'm probably not going to read them until next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you may as well just understand that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep, good idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, last email comes from Cheeseburger.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey guys, sometimes you talk about how you need to stop getting on random tangents.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I would just like to say that I would not listen to OLR if not for the personality from each host.
[SPEAKER_07]: Random food news and political talk are just random tangents about randomness.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've never seen random you so much in a sentence before.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, that's what makes OLR different from other video game shows.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sometimes I'm not in the mood for just straight video game news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sometimes I want a good laugh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep on podcasting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Keep in mind that the bitching about tangents is also part of what makes the show the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it all goes hand in hand.
[SPEAKER_07]: Brought to you by Halo 3, home of the never-ending four-year-old rocket noobs.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's over!
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the deal there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, the developer doesn't really matter if it's going to be in the same series.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just like Guitar Hero has been developed by a bunch of different people.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's been Harmonix for a lot of it, but then now they have... I don't remember the last developers doing a new one.
[SPEAKER_09]: For Guitar Hero?
[SPEAKER_09]: Neversoft.
[SPEAKER_09]: Neversoft, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's not developer, it's publisher.
[SPEAKER_09]: And because it's a different publisher, it's not EA.
[SPEAKER_09]: If EA was putting it out, then yeah, I'm sure they could do some sort of way to port that stuff over.
[SPEAKER_09]: But because it's Warner, it's a little different.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But also because it's Warner, it may have some good music in it because they do have the Warner Music license.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, kind of completely off the topic of Guitar Hero and Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_09]: 1 vs. 100.
[SPEAKER_09]: You may remember that they kind of teased this actually last E3 when they were showing the brand new Xbox interface.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, of course, the
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: So, um, they have a little teaser trailer for it, and of course, you know, you're going to be able to play with your avatars, um, play as part of the, you know, the mob, or the person actually playing the show, or as the audience.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that looks kind of cool, and they're going to be doing, you know, we can win real prizes.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I mean, sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: How do they pick the person that's going to be the one?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, it'll be interesting to see how it works.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm sure we'll see more about it at E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I'm kind of curious to see more about it too.
[SPEAKER_09]: You think it's not going to release to the network before E3?
[SPEAKER_09]: It might actually, because it's supposed to be coming this month, I thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I thought too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or last month, April, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it was May.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: So maybe we'll see it just before E3 and we'll hear about the next game show at E3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or maybe they're going to hold it off until June and then announce some more stuff at E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm afraid of embarrassing myself with my lack of knowledge.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's my question.
[SPEAKER_10]: How are they going to prevent people from having a laptop right next to them Googling all the answers?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because one of the questions they show off in the trailer, they're all, you know, the director of 300 also directed what other movie?
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's like...
[SPEAKER_09]: Watchmen, they gave two other ones.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't know who?
[SPEAKER_09]: Some people wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of people wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nerds do, but other people don't.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously, you could totally Google that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unless you're going to be given a certain time limit or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's not going to be like the TV show where you can just sit there going, um, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, Tiger Claw says, didn't 1 vs. 100 get cancelled on TV?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, it did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, SSJ100Matt in our chatroom, chat.orange.com, says, uh, you were also scored on time, so they can Google it, but they will get a crappy score.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: How is that going to play into it on 1 vs. 100?
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess I'm going to have to see how it kind of looks.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Furniture racing, card boxing, log cutting, mud sliding, tuna tossing...
[SPEAKER_10]: Cheese rolling and extreme ironing.
[SPEAKER_09]: These are all real sports, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: These are all real sports from around the world.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cheese rolling, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I've heard of cheese rolling, but tuna tossing?
[SPEAKER_10]: That sounds dirty.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's like toss your cookies.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's from New Zealand, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: New Zealand or Australia.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's one of those.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are they going to have an event for tossing your salad?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that's not a sport.
[SPEAKER_09]: For some it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm afraid to say it's not a sport.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just like DDR will never be a sport.
[SPEAKER_09]: For some it's a sport.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tossing your salad would be a hobby.
[SPEAKER_09]: They don't have any leagues for that, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, maybe someone should start one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that'd be a big step backwards there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just looking forward to Extreme Ironing.
[SPEAKER_10]: How is that a sport?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: How is it not a sport, Rob, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: I could say, so I could say, you know, instead of get back to work, get back to training.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm looking at the trailer here, by the way, if you want to know what the noise is you hear in the background.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: That guy looks like Naruto.
[SPEAKER_10]: He does.
[SPEAKER_10]: That car just fell apart.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like Naruto and Wario had a baby.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it was towards the end here.
[SPEAKER_10]: They had, yeah, here's that.
[SPEAKER_10]: The guy's doing the tuna tossing and there's the cheese.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've seen that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've seen the cheese rolling.
[SPEAKER_10]: That I've seen before.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then they have the extreme ironing here towards the end, which I just did not recognize at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like, what the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a whole little article here on extreme ironing.
[SPEAKER_10]: A performance art in which people take an ironing board to a remote location and iron items of clothing.
[SPEAKER_10]: The latest danger sport that combines the thrills of an extreme outdoor activity with the satisfaction of a well-pressed shirt.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_10]: There's this person ironing on top of a big rock in the middle of fucking nowhere.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is amazing!
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't know shit like this existed in the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to do this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everything exists.
[SPEAKER_10]: I could be an extreme ironer.
[SPEAKER_10]: All I have to do is climb the fucking rock and then iron a shirt at the top of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's easy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do my ironing in a rotating cylindrical container with heat.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what that's called?
[SPEAKER_07]: My dryer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about something else that has to do with rolling, Rob?
[SPEAKER_10]: They call them ironists.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about more rolling?
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rolling and rolling.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is our favorite thing to roll ever?
[SPEAKER_10]: Cheese?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sushi?
[SPEAKER_07]: Money.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about Katamari?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yes, we here at Orange Lounge Radio, we love Katamari.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're scaring me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Read your damn story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Katamari is going to be on PS3 with Katamari Forever, which I believe we might have mentioned before.
[SPEAKER_09]: We mentioned the Japanese one, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there's a trailer out with different wild animals making commentary on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: The cool thing is that it's going to have different features available for it as far as visual filters.
[SPEAKER_07]: You get a wood grain, a cell shaded...
[SPEAKER_07]: A Color Pencil, and then the normal version.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, this, of course, has no involvement from Keita Takahashi.
[SPEAKER_07]: But what I got from watching the trailer is that you're actually going to be able to, well, roll up entire planets.
[SPEAKER_07]: And roll up the universe.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw it rolling up, you know, the Earth.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm successful at life, thank you very much
[SPEAKER_09]: so yeah lots of interesting stuff going on including PixelJunk Monsters Deluxe is actually coming to the PSP you know we've been talking about a lot of different games coming to the PSP this might be the year of the PSP although last year was supposedly as well the year of the PSP as well
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: Everyone loves their tower defense games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess, although they've kind of been jumping the shark as of late.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it seems like they all have one, especially the Final Fantasy tower defense game, although it's kind of fun, I've got to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, you know, that's on every system and, you know, pixel junk and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, obviously, swine flu has been all the rage this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't believe I'm reading this story.
[SPEAKER_10]: But swine flu has been all the rage this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: But did you know that swine flu has actually existed in the World of Warcraft for quite some time?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: World of Warcraft has seen the swine flu for a little while now, ever since they released Wrath of the Lich King.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's these pigs in Borean Chandra, which is in the new area of Northrend.
[SPEAKER_10]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's really Blizzard that has caused the swine flu.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, it was Blizzard's fault all along.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the fact that I'm even talking about this story makes me cry inside a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: And when I get hurt by the stories that we read, that makes us very angsty.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's when the FUs of the Week happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, your FUs of the week, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: My FU goes to Citrus Heights Cops, just in general, because they really like to find reasons to give you a ticket.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had one tailgating me, well, practically tailgating me on the way here, I guess waiting for me to speed or something, and thankfully someone decided to jaywalk right in front of us, so the cop turned on the sirens and got the jaywalker.
[SPEAKER_07]: Still, a bit, uh, I feel like they don't have enough to do or something, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, FU goes to, I guess, police as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of funny, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: You see them turn on their sirens or whatever and see who pulls over to the side and they give them a ticket.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not sure why.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not necessarily people speeding, but people think that they want them to pull over and then they get a ticket for some reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't get tickets, though, because I can see them sitting there.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Am I the only one that doesn't have police issues this week?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I didn't really have anything other than sitting in, you know, driving the Oakland sucks, so.
[SPEAKER_10]: F you to the fact that everything seems to close at like 10 o'clock in this city.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was out in Roseville last night trying to find some late night eats and everything was freaking closed.
[SPEAKER_10]: So F you to stores that close early.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's annoying.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I'm sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to the finale of Heroes.
[SPEAKER_09]: It sucked.
[SPEAKER_09]: And what they did with the villain in the series is retarded.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm eight episodes behind on Heroes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I kind of gave up.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're going to...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there is a teaser that was put out on the Pokemon Sunday TV show that's on TV, of course, in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they were saying that there would be a remake of Pokemon Gold and Silver.
[SPEAKER_07]: They said that they would have a world-exclusive first announcement on the 10th of May.
[SPEAKER_07]: So maybe that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It could be a rumor.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, but they were showing, um, gold and silver confetti balls, so that could possibly be it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't want to see their gold balls.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wherever they can milk for money, they will.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, Scorpion.
[SPEAKER_10]: www.justin.tv slash orange lounge radio
[SPEAKER_09]: Atsuku Atsuku Atsuku
[SPEAKER_09]: Akatsuki Rising Akatsuki Rising Akatsuki Rising Akatsuki Rising
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, yet another, is this related to all the other Naruto games in the world?
[SPEAKER_10]: God, there's so many of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I think this is going to be like the... Shippuden is basically what people are referring to as the time jump.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah, so he's a little bit older in this.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they've been doing the Shippuden games, like they did Ultimate Ninja 4, which is Shippuden, and then they have a new Shippuden game for the DS that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Next month, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then this one's going to be another fighting game because they've been doing PSP Naruto Ultimate Ninja games like the Ultimate Ninja Heroes series.
[SPEAKER_09]: But now, you know, kind of going along with the whole shipping and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, why not?
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, well, a couple more new games that are coming out in the future.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is going to be coming out on the DS this winter.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you're a fan of the Phoenix Wright series, which I guess you could really call the Ace Attorney series, there's a new game coming out called Ace Attorney Investigations, Miles Edgeworth.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not going to be like the other games.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is more about investigating the crime scene, not so much in the courtroom.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're actually going to become Miles Edgeworth, and you're going to investigate crime scenes, trying to find the truth.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's a weird CSI type thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're actually going to be on the crime scene as Edgeworth looking for contradictions.
[SPEAKER_10]: You identify clues and question material using logic and gathered evidence.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, there are several episodes in this game as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: The first one is a murder that happens in Edgeworth's office.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, this game is teen rated and it's supposed to have 15 hours worth of gameplay.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm sure those of you that are fans of the Ace Attorney series will be happy about that, although the game is going in a little bit of a different direction this time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully not for the bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, speaking of bad as in badass, Raven Software is actually wanting to make a particular game since they've been, and of course they were the ones that made the X-Men Origins Wolverine game.
[SPEAKER_07]: They want to do a Deadpool game.
[SPEAKER_07]: They really want to do a Deadpool game, it says.
[SPEAKER_07]: And actually, their project lead for the Wolverine game, Dan Vondrak, said that they really want to do it because of Deadpool's smartass attitude.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if they made one, I will buy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: On every platform.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just watch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just on principle alone, even though it might suck?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if the X-Men Origins game was pretty good, then I would expect them to give the Deadpool game a good treatment.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, hey, I'm feeling good about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, do we have any word yet on whether you will be able to break the fourth wall in this game?
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to.
[SPEAKER_07]: It won't be a Deadpool game if you don't break the fourth wall.
[SPEAKER_10]: There should be a button to smash the fourth wall.
[SPEAKER_07]: He should know he's in a video game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's going to be like Eat Lead?
[SPEAKER_10]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the big thing about Deadpool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did not know this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually read up on Deadpool after seeing the Wolverine movie to figure out why Jamie was so obsessed with Deadpool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I get it now.
[SPEAKER_10]: It sounds like a very Jamie thing from what I read.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to have to just send you some images that you'll know.
[SPEAKER_07]: You saw the little yellow boxes?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's like ultimate right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But by the way, the article that I'm reading actually did compare what they imagine as being like Eat Lead.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well guess what?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's that time of the show where we're going to take your phone calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: The phones are already ringing.
[SPEAKER_10]: A 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: So let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, it's been a while since I've been on here.
[SPEAKER_10]: It has been a little while.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, it's DJ Ranma S from New York.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now see, I knew that, but I always make people introduce themselves for the sake of new listeners.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, what's on your mind, DJ Ranma S from New York?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a couple questions, but first, Loki, congratulations.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_10]: You weren't able to get through last week when, of course, it was announced that Loki's looking at twins in the future.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fun, fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what's up?
[SPEAKER_08]: My only qualm was about
[SPEAKER_08]: Konami cancelling Six Days in Fallujah.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's my only beef.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's your problem with it?
[SPEAKER_08]: This is the way I look at it.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it's okay to have various World War II simulating fighting games, I don't see how that's any different from Six Days in Fallujah or that's any different from the America's Army game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, they're all more or less based on real-time events.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's too soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: People we know died there.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's too soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's too soon for this.
[SPEAKER_10]: The wounds are too fresh.
[SPEAKER_07]: I applied the Dennis Leary quote to this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut the fuck up!
[SPEAKER_07]: By Dr. Dennis Leary.
[SPEAKER_10]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just being devil's advocate here.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't say I necessarily believe this, but what do you say to those people?
[SPEAKER_10]: Besides shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can't say that to somebody who's, I guess maybe you can, but it's not a very nice thing to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, is there anything else to say besides?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me ask this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why should they shut the fuck up?
[SPEAKER_08]: Me personally, I'm just tired of hearing about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you've got people who are over there fighting who are actually all for the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: They want their experiences in it, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: They're over there doing what they have to do for us to do what we have to do here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I feel that this is their game.
[SPEAKER_08]: They earned this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let them have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: If people don't want to see it, then they just don't have to buy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't it interesting that Konami might take more flack over not releasing this game than they would have if they had released it?
[SPEAKER_08]: One way or another, it'll be released, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: If not, someone's going to release a beta for everyone to go play, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it'll leak.
[SPEAKER_10]: It'll get pirated.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't that the inevitable?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's always the case.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, anything else on your mind tonight, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just glad that you guys got all the parts for the new studio PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're all here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sadly, we haven't put it together yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just the timing hasn't worked out.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Loki's going to do it during our break next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that when we come back, we'll be on an all-new computer.
[SPEAKER_10]: So maybe we'll try to find some other new things to show off next week after a little break.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which we've been taking a lot of breaks this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: I feel bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: It happens.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: um it's a possibility for later this year I really want to get back there but it's just because I promised ASEN I would do that sometime I'm doing that this year and that's going to be a chunk of money um and then you know I still really want to do PAX and E3 that's just going to set me back financially um I still really want to try and do New York in the fourth quarter and if things continue to go well for me in my day job and everything and I don't have any worries about the economy or anything like that um I'm hoping to do New York in the fourth quarter of the year like maybe October again
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: And on behalf of the New York Oil Army, we have one request if you make it out this way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pack Jamie in the suitcase with you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll do what I can.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I had the money for it, I would be happy to, but as it is, I've had to already call off one trip that I was going to make at the end of this month, and having to put in extra massage time just to save up for a trip in two months, so I'm broke.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm flat broke.
[SPEAKER_07]: School is wiping me out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know what I feel.
[SPEAKER_10]: I should say this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sadly, DarkSakura is not going to be doing E3 with us, which is unfortunate, but real life, greater than radio show, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, just trust me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really wanted to come back out there this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I really wanted to.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we'll make it work somehow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then we'll have, you know, the economy set us back a little bit, but, you know, hopefully things will start to pick up and then 2010 we'll have lots of visits.
[SPEAKER_10]: You come here, I'll go there, we'll have a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sort of like an exchange program.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'll give in and I might even go to Atlanta for Bobby and go to a Friday Night Gaming show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I will be down in Atlanta this year, so.
[SPEAKER_10]: Will you really?
[SPEAKER_10]: For what, a convention or something?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, my company, we may be doing DragonCon this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, if you're going to be there for DragonCon, I doubt Bobby's going to be there with his Friday Night Gaming shindig.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if you happen to be there on a weekend and he's doing that, you should go say hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know he likes to see the visitors out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry, the name of the town escapes me that they tape in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I'm bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: The name of the town that Bobby tapes Friday Night Gaming in is not Atlanta.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's one of the suburbs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alberta?
[SPEAKER_10]: Marietta?
[SPEAKER_10]: and actually our internet went down in studio that's why we lost DJ Ranma is anybody online doing nobody's doing anything okay well right now it is trying to reconnect right now we went down um oh there we go woo Roswell is the town that they tape in I'm still on there we go fine I'm sorry I got it back but the the stream is down right now unfortunately so can we post that in chat that the stream is down but Skype is still open hold on all right
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, we unfortunately have that outage right now, but that's what happens sometimes with live radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Things go down.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Streams back up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1877 GameOLR, username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Give us a call.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll take some calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you can't get through, keep trying.
[SPEAKER_10]: That little spurt of downtime we might have just had could have affected the calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we're getting calls again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're breaking up there a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, I did this earlier, but apparently I sent the email a little bit too late.
[SPEAKER_02]: More or less, I'm going to repeat a couple of questions.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're more or less directed towards you because you got your
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to point out, the connection's still really bad, but go ahead and ask your questions and we'll try to answer them.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I don't know if we can stay on, but keep going with your questions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, basically, what's your overall impression of PlayStation 3 this season?
[SPEAKER_10]: Overall impression of the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's very similar to how I feel about the PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: The PSP
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: you know the internet browsing on it is better than it is on the Wii it has some cool little built in things for the CD music so it's kind of like it's not my favorite of the gaming systems I think my Xbox 360 is my favorite gaming system but I love the fact that it's quiet and I think that it's kind of I don't think it's a bad system at all I just wish they'd get some better exclusives but they do have some games I love like Little Big Planet and
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, in terms of the multi-platform games out there, do you ever have a difficult time trying to pick and choose which system you're going to get the game for, especially if there's no real difference between, let's say, the 360 version and the PlayStation 3 version?
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have been in that situation before.
[SPEAKER_10]: Street Fighter 4 was the last time I had to make that decision because I pretty much swore up and down to myself I was going to get Street Fighter 4 on PlayStation 3 because PlayStation 3 had the better controller and I knew I'd be able to pull off the moves easier on the controller.
[SPEAKER_10]: Damn, I wish Microsoft would fix that.
[SPEAKER_10]: As opposed to doing all this motion controller BS that they're starting, I really wish they would just fix the controller they've got and make that D-pad easier.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyhow, I ended up getting it on the 360 because I thought Microsoft can fix their controller later on
[SPEAKER_10]: and just more people are on the 360 playing it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can go on Xbox Live and there's way more people playing it whereas on my PlayStation 3 friends list there's not nearly as many people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, completely unrelated topic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I finally found something that's far, far worse than being rickrolled.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh-oh, what's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of similar to be Rick Roll where someone sends you a link just saying it's one thing and it turns out to be something else.
[SPEAKER_10]: As long as it's not that two girls one cup crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, actually there is a girl involved.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe you're kind of familiar with the story because it apparently occurred out your way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently some girl in California died like
[SPEAKER_02]: on Halloween Day two years ago, and some cop released the accident photos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone sent me a...
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, Spazinator, we gotta let you go, but thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, and if you want to call, give us a call.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or your username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's 1-877-GAME-OLR or your username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll take a couple more calls here tonight and then we're going to wrap things up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: DSMaster26.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, hello, DSMaster26.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not much other than...
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the whole Guitar Hero vs. Rock Band debate, it's kind of rambling for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, I mean, what the heck?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I've heard my friends at the Hanna Club kind of rumor again and again at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're probably, knowing what, you know, how Konami teamed up with Disney a bunch of times to get, you know, the Disney DDRs and whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you saying that you're afraid this is going to go the route of the DDRs or that it's not such a bad thing because there's been so many DDRs with the Disney and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, probably to expand our audience.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I guess it could work, but I mean, the Wii was a family system to begin with.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, and I'm thinking of just springing and getting a 360 anyways if I'm doing Guitar Hero stuff and using it for then and using the Wii for everything else.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I mean, I could see that being a little bit of a competition fence.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, but at the own... I think you're breaking up there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: What can we say?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, my internet's been crap all day at home, and I am with Comcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have been having issues here in the area, like when the rain started and all that stuff, so I don't know what the hell's going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I apologize to folks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, let's try to get one more call.
[SPEAKER_10]: If it doesn't work, it doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, or username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go ahead and give us a call.
[SPEAKER_10]: See, the chat room stopped again, and I'm wondering if that means do we crap out on... No?
[SPEAKER_10]: We're still broadcasting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just to be on the safe side, since we're toward the end, I closed all my browsers.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I pinged out a chat, so I don't think... Yeah, I'm not... So we can't see it.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, and the stream went down on top of all that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Boy, what a fun time we're having tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everybody sure they're not downloading anything?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is my roommate...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, I like pie
[SPEAKER_09]: Ultima Online is actually bringing out a new expansion, the Styganian Abyss, I guess, and apparently it will allow you to play as a new class, the Gargoyle class, and you'll also be able to explore the new Gargoyle home of Termur and the Styganian Abyss, I guess, dungeon, which is the largest dungeon area ever introduced into Ultima Online.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't believe that Ultima Online is still alive and kicking after all these years.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's pretty impressive in itself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, hello, caller.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're on the air.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're supposed to wait for me to acknowledge you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind, buddy, while we're having crappy internet problems tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: Nothing much.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just praying that the street doesn't go down again and just enjoying the fact that me and my bro have the house to ourselves because mom's on vacation in Peru.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_10]: What possessed you to call in tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: You're just bragging that you have the house all to yourself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_10]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, are you there?
[SPEAKER_10]: Caller, are you there?
[SPEAKER_10]: We lost another one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, we're going to turn off Justin TV and hope that that'll help things.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, boy oh boy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: What a dumpy end to the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, well, that happens sometimes, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: If Zaku can get his question out in chat, we'll try to answer it, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to get your questions out in chat, we'll try to answer them while Loki gets some last-minute stories out of the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mr. T and Will Wright are teaming up against Nazis in a new Zootfly game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Zootfly, if you remember, is the company originally they were pitching the Ghostbusters game.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've also done some other stuff beyond that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But now they're making a Mr. T game.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, he will take on Nazis.
[SPEAKER_06]: Will you tell people to get nuts?
[SPEAKER_09]: It says apparently the first game will see Mr. T take on Nazis and their gigantic machines in a varied universe of South American rainforests, lost ancient cities, industrial complexes, and contemporary military installations.
[SPEAKER_09]: Along with Mr. T and other characters from the graphic novel, the game will feature none other than Will Wright.
[SPEAKER_09]: In this universe, Will Wright is a top-notch game designer, but also, but a top-notch, I guess he's not a top-notch game designer, but a top-notch American geneticist who was kidnapped and coerced to work on a diabolic plan, and Mr. T and Will Wright will join forces to annihilate the Nazis and their hardware.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who was smoking crack when they thought of this?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bet you anything they saw the Snickers commercials with Mr. T.
[SPEAKER_10]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_10]: And yeah, we're just trying to finish up the show at this point.
[SPEAKER_10]: We just turned off Skype because the calls just aren't cooperating tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know what's going on, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: All of our configurations are fine on our end.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's no cable problems.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nothing's falling apart.
[SPEAKER_10]: No video card issues.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's something on the Comcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then there was an update to Noby Noby Boy, which apparently added the 4-boy offline multiplayer mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: In addition, there's a new boy that you get to play as, Fart Boy.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, Fartboy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that his given name?
[SPEAKER_09]: That is his given name, Fartboy.
[SPEAKER_09]: As well as, I guess, the lower key updates.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have variations to the boys' house hairstyles and new poses to the game's bird.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then we were talking a little bit about the rumors of the PSP Go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there's a new game coming from Capcom, Fate Unlimited.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to put that actually on...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be download-only in Europe.
[SPEAKER_09]: But apparently Capcom is releasing on the UMD elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: So they're kind of testing that whole thing to see if people actually buy the download-content-only games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe it is a sign of things to come.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you think is going to happen if the answer is no, they don't?
[SPEAKER_10]: and they've invested all this in this PSP Go thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I heard the rumor about the PSP Go is that the design is not finalized yet and so they could add the UMD drive if necessary.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it would be a good idea if they were...
[SPEAKER_09]: Marvel vs. Capcom 2
[SPEAKER_09]: and then also they had a PS3 demo that came out this week actually so if you want to check that out you can and of course that was that countdown that they had going they're going to have apparently all 56 characters will be unlocked from the beginning and they're going to also feature I guess some HD upscaling as well as widescreen options and custom soundtracks on both the PS3 and Xbox 360 and
[SPEAKER_09]: and they also have three different screen modes that you can do.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can do just the classic, you know, kind of pixelated look and then they have a smooth and a crisp look that you can do.
[SPEAKER_10]: And finally, I just want to say for the live listeners, while the stream is up, I have double-checked everything in the house, including what's going on with my roommate and everything, and we don't know what's going on with the stream right now, so we're just going to try and limp our way through the end of the show at this point.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're almost there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's been a picture of the homebrew enabler on the PSP-3000 working, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's only a matter of time before the custom firmware is on the PSP 3000.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Finally, we were talking a little bit about Wolverine Origins, the video game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, since Activision is fun like that and Blizzard likes doing all sorts of crazy stuff, they've hidden a lot of little Easter eggs in the game, including references to Portal.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have a surprise cake that you can get that unlocks an achievement.
[SPEAKER_09]: and also they even have the Frostmour from World of Warcraft as well in there that you can get an achievement that's entitled Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: So lots of little hidden goodies.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well we're going to go around and wrap up the show and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want animal style fries and a milkshake.
[SPEAKER_10]: My final thought is I hate internet problems that you can't explain.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, thank you guys so much for tuning into our show and downloading and especially the live listeners who stuck with us through the ups and downs of the connections tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: The internet's crazy like that sometimes.
[SPEAKER_10]: But thank you guys for staying with us, especially those of you on the podcast for downloading and supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We will be back in two weeks here on Orange Lounge Radio with more and so we'll see you back here on May 17th with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you guys so much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio