Orange Lounge Radio
With your hosts, DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
It's the most wonderful time of the year
When we learn of the games in the near future
We'll discuss mentor hope and so on this show
Orange Lounge Radio
Thanks for that, Jason. Hi, welcome back everybody to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
It's Orange Lounge Radio, live tonight with episode number 734 of our show for this June 10th, 2018
And yes, it is that time of the year, the most wonderful time of the year to be a gamer
Because we get to find out all the games that we'll be playing about a year and a half from now
It used to be the games that we would play this holiday, but now it's eh, the games we'll play about a year and a half from now
Just kidding, we're not that cynical about it, but it is kind of funny
It's E3 week everybody, and we're here in studio to talk about all the latest and greatest that is unfolding literally before our eyes tonight
My name, Rob Roberts, you might know me on Twitter at Skie, S-K-I-E
Her name, DarkSakura, or Jamie Summers
Oh, hi
How are you, Ms. Summers?
Tired
I know, you had a prideful day, right?
I did
Today was Sacramento Pride
I worked a booth at Pride and wandered around all over the place
But I was there with the Sisters of Perpetual Indulgence
And some of the San Francisco Sisters came out and it was great to see them again
And I just had a really good time, but by the time I was ready to go, I was fucking ready
And I went home and cleaned off all the makeup and exfoliated and sheet masked
And nearly fell asleep with the sheet mask on my face
It's like the equivalent of a waffle iron she puts on her face to remove all the...
No
Well, the makeup may be as thick as a waffle iron
You were all nervous about coming here with no makeup on tonight
Lights, camera, and me without a stitch of makeup on
That's a very obscure movie reference if you get it
I came with the pink powder zit spot stuff on my face
I was gonna say you look marvelous, darling
Thank you
You don't need makeup, but I understand it is part of the sister ritual
Well, yeah, but the thing is that I like, you know, going out with a little bit on
Just because it's artistry for me
And today I was just like...
Lazy Sunday
I do appreciate your rainbow watch, though
You've got a very prideful watch
Oh, yeah, I switched to my pride band
Your LGBTQIA+, et cetera, et cetera
No, I ordered the new pride band
And it didn't arrive yet because I have the new face on my watch, too
Yeah, that has little dancy lines
It is really cool, but I actually like the older pride band better
The new one I wish was on, like, a black background
With the stripes, it would have been better to me
I do want to also introduce the chat room over at live.vognetwork.com
Because we do tape live every Sunday night at the Voice Geeks Network
vognetwork.com
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show at about 6 o'clock Pacific and 9 o'clock Eastern
And tonight, obviously, our show is being interrupted by one of the E3 press conferences
But I'll get to that in a minute
But if you are listening live, you can go to live.vognetwork.com
Where JD is saying you don't need makeup, especially for radio
That's true, you know, I've been told plenty of times that I have a face that's perfect for radio
Anyway, also a man fit for radio
Say hello to Techmaster Loki
I don't know how to take that, but sure
It's a compliment, question mark, no I'm just kidding
How are you doing, Loki?
I'm fine
Good, good
Enjoying all these announcements so far?
Most of them, yeah
Yeah
Not so much EAA, but you know
Alright, well, let's jump right in
We only have about 20 minutes before we get to Bethesda's press conference
So here's how it's going to work
So tonight, it's about 6.07 Pacific time
As we're broadcasting live here at the Voice Geeks Network
We are going to kind of pause our show at 6.30
So that we can all watch Bethesda's E3 press conference together
Because there will likely be some big news that comes out of that
We know we're going to get a better look at Fallout 76
Even more so than we saw at Microsoft's event today
So we're going to watch that together
For those of you that are listening live
We have decided this year to do it a little differently than we have in the years past
And as long as the bandwidth cooperates
That's a big footnote because here in the studio the bandwidth is sometimes crappy
We will provide you live commentary tonight
So if you want to keep OLR on while Bethesda's thing is going
We will do live commentary as Bethesda's event is going
Because you guys have asked for it, the live folks in previous years
And if you don't want to listen to that, that's fine
I will not be offended if you turn it off
And come back to us when it's all over
And we'll continue on with news and our regular segments
As we come back into the show
I don't know how long Bethesda is tonight
I don't know if they're 60 minutes or 90 minutes
So I would think they're only 60
Because I wouldn't think they have 90 minutes worth of stuff to announce
But if they were to surprise the hell out of us with Elder Scrolls 6
Which I don't think they will at this point
What continents do they have left?
The undiscovered one that we never knew about until now
That's the clever video game trope
But anyway, I'm not expecting that though
I assume that Fallout 76 is their big title
Maybe they would tease a little bit Elder Scrolls for next year
But I just don't see that happening
But anyway, let's talk about until then
Let's talk about what we've seen so far
So yesterday EA did their bit
And Loki, you watched the whole thing, right?
Yeah, I watched everything
What were your thoughts on EA?
I think it was kind of let down
But I mean, it's typical EA
They didn't really announce too much
Even with Battlefield 5, they did this whole preview thing like a week before
But they didn't really show too much
They kind of talked a little bit about multiplayer
There's going to be, of course, some changes
They reiterated that there's no loot boxes or season passes
However, I overheard someone talking about
The pre-order stuff that they had for Battlefield 5
And then it mentioned airdrops
Which were possibly something alluding to
They're going to have a couple of Macs hooked up to airdrop
Yeah, so a couple
Basically alluding to that there might be some sort of content or something that comes in
But I don't know
So we'll see when it comes out if they actually stick to the no loot box thing
But that's what they said
They announced that they're going to be doing Battle Royale as well for it
Because everybody's got to jump on that bandwagon
And then talking about customization
Their destruction systems getting even better
And they had some other stuff like Grand Operations and whatnot
Then along with that
Of course, they talked about FIFA 19
So they have this new
They have a trial for 18 available now
And then some new Champions League mode
They talked about their EA Cloud streaming service
Which they didn't really say what that was yet
But something that's going to be coming
And that includes this Origin Access Premier
Where you'll be able to access games as they come out
Through Origin
It's $15 a month or $100 a year
How's this different from the EA thing they already have on Xbox?
Or is it kind of like the same thing?
No, EA is
The EA Pass
EA Play
I don't even know what the fuck they call it
I think this is on PC
So there's like a new one for PC
And the one on PC will be new stuff
Whereas the EA catalog on Xbox One
I think it's both new
New and old stuff
Okay
I'm confused
There's a lot of stuff they're trying to sell me
Of course, it's EA
Well that's business, whatever
And then Respawn has a new game coming out
A new Star Wars game
That's going to take place between episodes 3 and 4
This was a holiday 2019
Called Jedi Fallen Order
And then of course they showed off
Some more updates for Battlefield 2
It's going to have a new season
Which is going to be
So that took place in the prequel stuff
So they have new heroes and villains
So General Grievous, Obi-Wan
Count Dooku and Anakin Skywalker
And a new Starfighter mode
There's also going to be stuff coming out for the solo movie
So content from that
They announced Unravel 2 which is out today
And so a sequel to their other indie game Unravel
That was kind of part of that EA original thing
Yeah, that was a pleasant little surprise
Especially the fact that it's out today
NBA Live 19 and Madden 19
They showed some trailers for that
Then they had this thing for Command & Conquer Rivals
Which is a new mobile strategy game
Which looked terrible and they spent way too much time on it
You were a big Command & Conquer fan though
I was
This looks like Clash of Clans or something
So no thanks
Ouch, okay
So then they got to Anthem
So Anthem, they had a new trailer
They talked about it once again
No loot boxes or anything like that
They will have cosmetic items but it'll be like
You know what you're getting when you're purchasing them
You can play the game solo
They're going to have a demo for it
Also different clips
They are showing some of the gameplay and stuff
There's four different classes you can play as
Different, what they call
I don't remember what they're calling their
Javelins, their suits, yeah
I still am an extremely bitter Betty
And probably unrationally so, I will own that
When it comes to Anthem, due to
How much of a middle finger
I feel like EA has been giving us
When it comes to Mass Effect
But there's two things
That gave me a little bit of positivity
One, Casey Hudson
Went on record and said Mass Effect's
Not done, I don't even know if you saw that
But Casey Hudson did
I did and then I rolled my eyes really hard
At least they're not done
They're not going to abandon Mass Effect
We're going to have more books
I got the sense they meant games
What I want is that Quarian DLC
Yeah, I don't blame you
But if they decide, you know what, we're going to go
Somewhere completely different next
Or we're going to do, I don't know what's left to do
Maybe they would have to do a prequel to The Shepherd's
Story or something, I don't know where they would go next
But maybe they'll
Do a really fucking ballsy thing
And do Mass Effect 4
They had N7 skins by the way
For the Javelins, I did notice that when they were doing
Their little thing
Keep it, but anyway
I will say this though, at least with as much
Very angry gamer face when it comes to
Anthem right now, because of the hurt I feel
In my heart
I was very encouraged by the fact
That they went out of their way to say
You can do this completely solo
So that tells me there is something to Anthem
Besides just wanting to copy
Destiny completely
If you can play this completely solo
I'm a little more like
Alright
So show me some more video, let's see
I don't know yet though
I'll go back and watch that whole thing later
But just right now, right now I'm still
Feeling hurt
Some folks in our chat over at live.vognetwork.com
SHJ100Matt says Anthem looks really neat
Dungeon Buster says they're trying to
In quotes, figure out Mass Effect
You know, aren't we all
And then there was also
Another indie game that they were showing off
Which I can't remember the name of it
Right now, but it was basically this big
Flooded world type thing
That looked kind of cool
So, that was
That, but yeah
With the Command and Conquer rivals though
I can't trust them at all, because I mean look at Dungeon Keeper
That they released, it was just terrible
They like ruined that franchise
By just destroying it with all the crap that you would get
With
Just, you know, your typical mobile game
I don't know, not a fan
Of that
So that was pretty much EA right there
Alright, so let's talk about Microsoft
Which I did watch, I did watch Microsoft
Yeah, Microsoft, they had tons of games
To announce, so lots of stuff they showed off
So a brief tease for a game called
Halo Infinite, not sure what that's
Gonna be, but it is in the Halo universe
Looked like an MMO maybe
It looked really pretty, like when they were showing all the
Really diverse landscapes and stuff
Especially because I was doing the whole
Watching on Mixer in 4K
And I was really impressed with how
Good it looked, so there is that
They had a new
Sequel for Ori
And the Will of the Wisps, that looked pretty nice
That was pretty gorgeous
A new game from software
Or from
From software
Sekiro Shadows Die Twice
Which is almost like a samurai
Ninja Dark Souls
Which is what people are kind of assuming from what we saw
But that looked pretty sweet
But here's the thing, I just have to
Get this out, like although Microsoft
Showed a lot of great games
Like how many of them are Microsoft
Xbox exclusive
Or even Microsoft Xbox
Windows exclusive
A lot of the stuff they showed
Is coming to multiple things
You know what I mean, and that's the one area
Where I do think Microsoft
Still, don't get me wrong
I'm not trying to derail what was
A fun, especially
As the opening act, I think a
Fun tone of games, games, games
To show us at E3
Even if a lot of them were for 2019
We found out
Last night I think the Kingdom Hearts
Was going to get bumped a little bit
We just found out that Crackdown 3
Now it's going to get bumped a little bit
So don't get me wrong, they had this great games, games, games tone
But how much of that was really like
But you need to go get an Xbox One today
Because you are missing the fuck out
If you don't do it
That was the impression I was getting
But don't get me wrong
I enjoyed it just as a
Games keynote
Sorry, I don't mean to jump ahead
But there were some things where I was like
Okay, this is why I own an Xbox One
Because I want to be able to play this
This is why I have a beefy PC
So I can play this
I just had to get that off my chest
They showed off Fallout 76
Which is kind of surprising
Being that we are about to see Bethesda
Which looked interesting
It is a typical Fallout game
Four times the size of the map from Fallout 4
And it looked pretty
So there doesn't seem to be any
Oh, it's an MMO
Or all these things people were anticipating
It could be co-op
They had a new game
That's in
A new game called
The Awesome Adventures of Captain's Spirit
Which is in, I forget, the universe of
Life is Strange
Square Enix's
That's coming out free on the 26th
Well, I imagine it's like Life is Strange
Where the first episode is free
That's cool
They showed Crackdown 3
February is when that's coming out
How did you like that though?
It looks nice
I'm excited for it
I just wish it was coming out this year
Yeah, but they gotta take the time to get it right
How much time do they fucking need?
It's been like four years now
4K is probably a bigger pain in the ass
than people think
I love the Tron look of it
For the record
As God's Edition
February 26th
It's kind of remastered and everything
Metro Exodus
Everybody in chat is trying to correct me
On the whole free thing where they say
100% free
But doesn't that still leave the door open?
Sure, the first episode that they just showed us
That is this
Is 100% free
But then they're gonna sell more episodes
Don't you make video games to make money?
There's gotta be a catch here
If it is 100% free
If it's a one-off side story thing
That's maybe trying to push back copies of Life is Strange
Then great
I still took 100% free
To mean
It's like a little teaser for something else
JD says
It's a promo for Life is Strange 2
Okay
Then fine
It's 100% free
Sorry Loki
I gotta pay attention to chat
They showed off a new trailer for Metro Exodus
Which looked pretty cool
Kingdom Hearts 3 had a new trailer
Metro is coming out February 22
Kingdom Hearts January 29th
They showed off
I don't know if they mentioned it before
The Frozen world
They have Frozen and stuff
As much as I'm over Frozen
Again
Getting to watch that in 4K
You can just see how fucking good it looks
With all the particle effects
And the additional neon
They throw in it
The summons and the way that Wreck-It Ralph
Looks like a digitized arcade
It looks
Really good
The graphics have come so far
From Kingdom Hearts 2
They showed off
There's two expansions coming for Sea of Thieves
Cursed
Cursed Sails
I don't remember the other one
They have those coming out
They showed off another trailer for Battlefield 5
Which is the one that EA was telling you
Tune in for this peek at the
Blah blah blah
It was so brief
I thought they were going to do a deeper dive into it
But they didn't
What they did do a pretty deep dive into
Was Forza Horizon 4
Which is going to be coming out in October
What's awesome about that is
In Britain this time
They have the different seasons
I don't know if that's going to sync with the actual seasons
What part of the world is it going to sync to
I don't know but it looked cool
I'm down for that
We Happy Few is going to be finished
August 10th
They of course announced that they had bought a bunch of companies
This was the biggest news
The whole night in my opinion
They acquired four and built one
Right?
That's huge
The fact that they have Ninja Theory
I kind of think this is something they should have done
Two or three years ago
They identified that their exclusives
Were not really holding up
Next to Sony's as well
But I guess better late than never
The problem is you're not really going to see the effects of this
For another couple years I don't think
And these new games that these companies are making
But no disrespect
I still think Xbox is in a much better place
Under Phil Spencer than it was previously
So again, no hate
It would have been really exciting
To see this a couple years ago
And then of course
We showed off another trailer for PUBG
Then there was a bunch of different announcements
Tales of Vesperia
Definitive Edition coming out this winter
Also on the Switch
Tom Clancy's The Division 2
Why Ubisoft?
Why did you have to do the fake
Co-op chatter?
That fake Co-op chatter is like
The one time a year
Where I feel like I can actually hear
People playing a game together online
And treating each other with respect
It's like a nice change of pace
Where I'm like, wait a minute
Two women are playing this demo with two guys
And they're not being asked about their boobs
They're being treated respectfully
The guys aren't calling each other
Fancy ass guys
You know what I mean?
Everybody is being very respectful
And I'm like, I almost prefer
Fake dialogue planet
How do I get an account on Xbox fake?
Alright, well whatever
They had a new trailer for Shadow of the Tomb Raider
They have a session
Which is basically
Standing in for Skate 4
Because there is no Skate 4
And the new Tomb Raider
Lara Croft's No Good
Very Bad Day in Latin America
And then we have
A new MMORPG called
Black Desert
Which is supposed to be out this fall
Black Desert Online is already on PC
Is that not the same thing?
And they showed it last year too by the way
Don't be wrong
It looked really good
I remember last year going, wow this game looks really good
And somebody tweeted me
Black Desert Online is already on PC and it's not good
And I was like, oh well alright
Womp womp
Then they had of course Devil May Cry 5
Which they showed off
Cuphead in the delicious last course
Which is DLC for Cuphead
That sounds like fun
And they have a new playable character
And crying
Cuphead of course
But work Miss Chalice
There's a new character
Miss Chalice
It's like Mugman with a bow in her hair
No I'm just kidding
Totally fleshed out character
They had a game called Tunic
Which looks like Zelda
That was my favorite thing
Second favorite thing
The Legend of Little Cute Fox
Jump Force
Which is Shonen Jump
It looked like a fighting game
Anime is real
Dying Light 2
Battletoads
Actually new Battletoads
But they didn't show anything
They didn't show anything but say it's happening
And it had a sense of humor
Don't get me wrong
It's nice to have that confirmation of the thing we've been saying should be happening for years
Just Cause 4
Which is awesome
That's coming out this year as well
And then this is where they started teasing all the Gears of War stuff
So they first said
Oh yeah we got new Gears of War
Gears of War Pop figure
Mobile game
There was like awww
And they're like just kidding
We actually have a real Gears game coming out
Gears Tactics
And then they're like oh just kidding
Gears 5
So there's a new Gears game coming
The three of them
And they're going in a completely different direction with Gears with this
They switch the protagonist to
My Gears characters as well
But the way it's set up you're not playing as Phoenix
You're playing as the female
In their group
Who I don't know her name so I apologize
But then it looks like her and one of the other guys
That was kind of like the side character
In the earlier games
This is their game
So they go off together
I'm all for strong female leads
So let's make those
People that don't get it cry
And that was supposed to be
The end of the show and then the one more thing
They showed off a trailer for Cyberpunk
2077 it looked fucking awesome
That looked hot
Yeah that looked really hot
If you don't know that's being done by CD Projekt Red
Who did The Witcher 3
And obviously The Witcher before that
Witcher 3 is an extremely cinematic game
So now it's like okay instead of like the medieval
Setting that The Witcher games were in
Now it's going to be like a cyberpunk setting
It has a really great look to it
And then of course they were talking about Games Pass as well
You still get all these
First party games out day in
Date with Crackdown 3
And Forza
Horizon 4 are going to be coming out
Their Netflix type of thing
Which by the way since you went through it so fast
I did not get a chance to fanboy about Forza Horizon 4
But it looks so good
It looks so good
Oh my god it was like one of those things
I had my tweet deck up on one screen
While I'm watching the press event
On the other screen and as I'm watching the tweet
That go by there's all these people that are like
Yawn car game
Yawn potty break I gotta go poop
It's a Forza game and I'm like
If I knew where you lived
I would be banging pots and pans over your head
While you sleep until you play Forza
Forza Horizon
Specifically because look look I get it I get it
I'm not super into the Gran Turismo games
Or even the mainline Forza series
The car sim games don't do it for me
But Horizon is like
Mario Kart
Without the items
And it's like in a real setting
With awesome like
Euro rave
Techno stuff
And it's fucking great
They have seasons now so like they're showing off this one lake
And they're all well in the winter it'll be frozen
You can drive over the lake and yes
Yes so I'm down and down
Locopogo says I don't even like Forza games
Forza Horizons look great
That is the correct attitude to have on my Twitter
Thank you very much
Everybody's backing up a little bit there
And well we're almost at conference time
But I just want to mention one last thing
Because they did talk about a bunch of games
PlayStation T is a bunch of stuff
But of course we have to talk about Tetris Effect
Oh my god like
E3 is done
Tetris Effect I am so here for it
Yay
It's like Tetris getting the luminous effect
Mizuguchi Tetris
And again the people replying to that on Twitter
They're like it's just Tetris
I'm like I will cyberbully you
Like I am all for
I am all for treating people with respect
And dignity online
But if you come after Tetris Effect
I will cyberbully you
I will alright
Alright let's do this
Alright so we're gonna have to switch over to Bethesda
So for the podcast listeners we're gonna get a little break
For those of you that are listening live
We're gonna do a quick
Save break you're gonna hear some silence
While we save we will be right back
To register participation
For this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
At vognetwork.com
Use the passphrase
Coke
Welcome back everybody
To Orange Lounge Radio
Live here during this
Special E3 edition
We just got done watching
The Bethesda press conference
So for the live folks
You guys
Actually yeah sorry we have a
The joy of live radio is that we have our
Live thing playing okay I just need to
Like turn off the system over here
So we get no more input from
YouTube on auto forwarding us to other streams
Anyway so
Some of you were listening along some of you weren't
I saw mostly encouraging words there in
Chat on the commentary but not everybody
Is in the commentary so some of you didn't listen
To it and that's fine so let's talk a little
About especially for the sake of the podcast folks
What we just saw although
Before we get into that let me quickly
What you may not have heard if
You're listening on the podcast feed
During that time that Bethesda's thing was going on
Jamie had to bow out
So she is no longer here
In the studio but who is
Joining us in the studio is an old friend
Of the show an old friend
Of mine goes way back we used to do some
Other shows together welcome back
To OLR everybody Extover
Hey hi nice to have you here
I'm doing uh oh
You didn't ask how I was doing
When Sky's on a show happening
Oh
That little thing
How are you doing? I'm doing fine
How are you? Good good
I'm great you know watching some video
Games yeah nice
So alright fun time of the year
It is it's like the gamers
Gamers Christmas in some ways right
It's when we get to see what's coming out not for holiday
Anymore but for next year
I know yeah mostly next year
Yeah alright
Let's run down kind of some of the things we just saw
So overall what did you guys think of the Bethesda
It was really padded out
Yeah I don't know
If it needed to be 90 minutes
But you know there was still some
Good stuff it was interesting and this is
What I wanted to ask on the commentary feed
That I said I'll wait and ask this on the main show
So we were kind of talking at the end there
So obviously Fallout 76 was one of the last things
They showed and so we got the confirmation
That it's going to be like an online
Type of game that's the direction it's going
So it's going to be a little more multiplayer
Which looks really cool you know
I never have gotten super into the Fallout games
But I imagine like if you are a fan of
Fallout like this is probably like the type of thing you've been waiting
A very long time for so I know there's probably
Going to be a lot of happy people about that
And then I was kind of thinking okay well that's
Where they're going to end it right
Well they didn't end it with that they had this Elder Scrolls
Blades that they showed off which you
Were saying was originally a PSP thing
I thought it was a PSP thing I remember they were doing
A PSP game or they were trying
To do a PSP game but you know
You just can't run the Elder Scrolls
On a PSP right so
It just didn't turn out
That it would be anything but so then
They kind of had that going and said okay this is going
To be on mobile
It's going to be on Switch
Consoles it's going to be on virtual reality
Like if it fucking has a screen
We're putting it on there almost
An illusion to that little funny bit they did
Where they did Skyrim on the Alexa
That was hilarious yeah that was really funny
Does it have a mode to clean that shit up?
That was my favorite line of holding
So but then after that they said
You know we want to tease you
About stuff out in the future too
Because I think they probably have a sense
That we're all sitting here going
Elder Scrolls 6 Elder Scrolls 6
Elder Scrolls 6 so sure enough
They give us first a game called
Starfield which is
It was nothing except
It's a space game it's a new IP that's all we know
And then there it was
The Elder Scrolls 6 but
All we really saw was like
A landscape
Elder Scrolls 6 is coming after Starfield
Some music
Well not necessarily because Starfield
Could be mid next year
Maybe not you're right
Or 2021
So anyway what did you guys think
Of that concept of
Leaving us at the very
End with a really big
Tease and you know honestly
Microsoft kind of did this too
When they said we're working on
The next Xbox I mean
Xboxes
Oh yeah okay they said they're working on the next
Xboxes plural
Little bit of a tease in itself too I mean
We all know these hardware
Things are planned years out
So of course Sony is working on
PlayStation 5 I see where you're going with that
So what do you think though about these
Extended teases
I mean we're making all these jokes about how we're
Seeing games in 2019 but now
These like final notes that we're getting left on
On these press conferences are
Here's the long play
Oh I think it's designed for people
For the consumers
To keep that in mind
It's like designed for us to be like
Oh I have a lot more to look forward to
So I just I need to keep
Subscribing to their newsletter
Or just like hey you know we've heard you
Working on it you know you can stop asking us
Now it is in development it's just true
It's a long ways out you know type of thing
But I mean did they have
To confirm that they're working on an Elder Scrolls
Game we all of course they're fucking doing
Elder Scrolls 6 I think they did
No I think they still needed to
They needed to like try to meet expectations
Okay for what it's worth
I'll give them this It's just like Metroid Prime
4 last year all we saw was
Like yeah we're working on it I'll give them this
At least it was like Elder Scrolls 6
And not Elder Scrolls
Forever
You know or something
But I think it's different
Than the Metroid Prime 4
I feel like Metroid Prime 4
Is happening this year I feel like it's not
Quite the extended tease
But I think the way it's different
Is that I mean I don't know I can't speak
For the Elder Scrolls fandom
But with the Metroid fandom
We were all like
Anxious because we thought Nintendo
Had given up on Metroid
Honestly we didn't think we didn't
Know for sure if it was in the cards right
So that was like a big surprise
But did you did the Elder Scrolls
Community like did they ever
Doubt that another Elder Scrolls
Game was ever gonna come out I thought for sure
That they would do something like an
Elder Scrolls 4 remastered
Or something like that you know just like
Yeah I thought there'd be like an Oblivion remaster
Like a remaster just you know bring it into the new engine
There still could be
It's not something they need to announce months and months out
You know
Anything else you guys want to highlight from that conference
That we saw for those of you listening on the podcast feed
We will offer that comment some people
Cause we kind of got a little bit off topic
In some places so if you have an hour
There was much much
Objectification of the developers
By the males
Not including myself
Why would you do that? Rob
Anyway you robbed me
If you want to hear that
That will be posted on our social media channels
This is an exclusive over at Twitter
Twitter.com slash O-L-R
It'll also be on our Facebook
Facebook.com slash orange launch radio
And it'll be posted first
In our Discord over at vognetwork.com
Slash Discord so check it out
I think that the very first part
Of the whole conference
Should have just like they should have not
Done it I mean I get it for entertainment
Value yay we have a big rock band
But you know what nobody in the audience
Was excited
They showed the audience and they're all like
Really old white nerds
I just realized you are way louder than
Jamie is
Sorry for the volume issues
Old white nerds sitting in
There going like looking
Like they don't belong
Well no they're probably just like dude I came here to see video games
Not watching Andrew WK not that
We hate Andrew WK but it's like dude
Come on
Let's get the show on the road here
To watch a concert or watch a
You know a band play
I thought it wasn't like
I thought the Rage 2
Thing went on a little long
Yes
It looks okay
It's by Avalanche they did you know
They've done the Just Cause games
Avalanche actually
I'm sorry my studio is confused here
I think they did
I think Avalanche was Just Cause
And Mad Max
That or it might have been
What was the other one that was EA
I don't remember no that was Pandemic
Never mind
So yeah they did Mad Max and stuff
So it looks very much like Mad Max or like a
Borderlands type game just you know not with the
Stylized graphics
Just a couple other quick things I want to hit and then I'll open it up
If you guys have anything you want to add but
Doom Infinite so we have
Eternal
It's a stupid name
Insert forever
Synonym here
It's the new Rage in gaming
Doom Eternal
They said that's a thing
But they didn't really show us
Stay tuned for QuakeCon for more
Which was lame
A little bit of a disappointment
I guess it wasn't much more than they showed at the end
They had to make room for
Andrew WK
We knew that Doom would get a sequel
So that's not too surprising
And it's probably still a ways out
Yeah that's kind of like a little spin off
And then that Elder Scrolls
card game is coming to Switch
Except they didn't really say that
You just see it in the trailer
They were very clearly playing it on a Nintendo Switch
So it does seem like
Bethesda is showing the Switch a lot of love
If you're a Nintendo fan you probably love them
Bethesda right now because they also just put Fallout
Shelter out right now on the
Switch so I bet there's some people probably
downloading it
Fallout Shelter they said was now right?
Am I crazy? Didn't they say they were putting that out right now?
I don't remember. I'm glad they did
So anyway
Alright
And they're saying in chat over at live.vognetwork.com
S2100Matt says
Apparently Andrew WK did another concert
after the show
Kaijuto in chat says E3 should be fun
Not just trailers and predictable crowd reactions
I know but like with other like
They've done that before with I don't know if it was
Microsoft or Sony they'll do like a musical number
Like either at the end I think
Do it for the crowd
Warm them up and everything
But like you know if you tell me to tune in at 6.30
to see game trailers I want to see game trailers
Or like if you're doing that concert
where he's playing live you know playing the song live
Do it to like gameplay
video or something like that
Mix it in
Things like that assume
that all of us that like games
like Rage also like that kind of music
And I don't like that kind of music
But yet I do like
games like Rage
So for me it's not entertaining
I don't care what people say
That's not entertaining
That's just padding the show and saying
Hey we got this famous person
Love us because we're cool
and hip but we got this stupid
heavy metal band
Hey we got this famous person
It's fine whatever
I would say overall though
I do feel very positive on Bethesda
I do like that they were
willing to tease past the next year
You know and I kinda
You know and I've talked about this on a previous
OLR like the movie industry
Fuck we know Marvel's plan for like the next four
years right so why doesn't the
gaming industry like are they afraid
that somebody's gonna steal the idea or something like
I don't know yes I would actually see yes
because look at like look at all these
battle royale games coming up I guess that's true
But okay for all we know Elder Scrolls 6
is battle royale
We don't need to necessarily know that tonight
Elder Scrolls 6 should be multiplayer that'd be pretty awesome
I don't wanna even tease
the potential but it could be
but it could be alright anyway
Moving on
So anything else you guys wanna say on
Bethesda?
No I don't have anything
It was alright it just seemed like a bit slower paced this year
and they really dragged it out I don't think it needed to be 90 minutes
long and I just felt last year
they announced it was like more kind of exciting announcements
They had some that were pretty cool
but most of it was just kinda like
I'm bored
Honestly last year because they did the whole
Bethesda land thing and that was all
really it was you know
I felt like it was more concise
you know what I mean it felt like everything was just like
in this neat little package
so we didn't have time
to like pan or have those awkward
moments cause it was all like you know pre-done
Yeah
Okay so I am gonna do our gaming weeks
real quick here I will ask Loki
can you be prepared to run through some headlines here in a moment
just as soon as we are done
so we can touch on some other things that have been happening
during E3 we'll talk about our gaming weeks
a quick housekeeping thing though since Jamie
did have to leave earlier than expected cause we
thought that thing would only be an hour
and it ended up being 90 minutes there's actually
not gonna be a classic game this week so it's
kind of a rarity in OLR history
so we're gonna roll she actually I guess
I gotta say this she was going to do a peripheral
tonight so we will roll that over
till next week which is our big
and it's a good knowing
what it already is it is a good one
for the 16th anniversary of the show that's all
I'll say it's a good choice for
our anniversary which is coming up next week
so we will
though talk about our gaming weeks so
Exeter I'll actually start with you if you want to talk about any
video games you've been playing what are games
you're enjoying lately
like Greece I know you've been very busy
preparing for your move but surely you've snuck
a game in here and there
so you know I'm addicted
to Binding of Isaac so really that's my
that's my go to game to like
just pick up and play you know
and not worry about anything like
you know worrying about paying attention to
story or anything like that just to pick up
and play a game so I can spend
hours in it
and so that's that's
that's pretty much what I've been playing
oh
I did play a little bit of
Overwatch on my Xbox
you know I was
I was actually testing
I was doing it to test out the
Wi-Fi on the Xbox because we were
we were putting as
everybody heard on the live
on the Bethesda stream or whatever
I am moving to North Carolina
so we've had to unhook
everything and so because I unhooked
the ethernet cable I was like I wonder
what the Wi-Fi is like so I tested Overwatch
and I ended up playing like three hours
of Overwatch and I'm like oh my
god like you just can easily get sucked
back into that game right yeah
but but yeah
I have a lot of games that
I'm meaning to go back to
but I just
haven't for whatever reason
like I started a way out
I've been playing it with Flaco Jones
and we
we had a really good time playing that so
but that's dependent on his schedule
you know being available right so
so we're not gonna play I'm not gonna
finish it until I know that he's
available to finish it so anyway
alright
I'll talk about Mike
are we allowed to talk about where your man
works or do we want to keep that off here?
oh I think we've already said he works for Ubisoft
but he wouldn't
talk obviously
I don't know
even you don't know what he's working on?
well it was announced today
Division 2
so you knew
so I know what he's going to be working on
I don't know the details or anything
but yeah he got transferred
he was so
he
worked for San Francisco
Studio, Ubisoft
you can see him in Rocksmith
promo videos if I remember right wasn't he
in the Rocksmith promo?
he worked a lot
on Rocksmith and then he worked
very heavily on South Park
the Fractured But Whole
and he I giggle every time
I know I know I giggle
and then he
decided that
Bay Area expensive
hard to raise a family
we eventually want to have kids
so he thought
it might be a better idea to
just try and get a transfer to the
Ubisoft studio in
North Carolina and
basically their name is Red Storm
Entertainment and they work on a lot of the
Tom Clancy
so Division is
the game that they work on
in tandem with
Massive Entertainment
Massive is the main studio
and they're the ones in Sweden
Malmo, Sweden
alright awesome awesome
so cool
if he ever wants to come
via Skype and promote whenever the game's out
cool cool there's some fans of
Division in chat so we'll see
alright anyway
so let's talk about other gaming weeks
yeah I didn't play a whole ton of stuff
I played more Mario Odyssey
just still trying to get the rest of the Power Moons
so I've been going through all that stuff
I played more Pokemon
Quest
I've evolved a few things on there now
you play that more than anyone I know
but it's such a grind though
it's alright
it's getting kind of boring so I'll play it while I'm doing
other things because
basically it's on autoplay so I just
set it up, hit a button
and come back in two minutes
and it's done
yeah you can autoplay it
I don't know if you've played a game like
Non-Stop Night or something like that
where basically the character auto
they autorun and you have the option
to where you can control their special moves
to when they do them or you can just say
just autoplay and I find
that when I do the autoplay stuff it ends up
passing more levels than I do if I'm trying to control it
so I'm like ah fuck it who cares
I just let it play itself
and then what else
I downloaded a game called
Totally Accurate Battlegrounds
it looks fucking hilarious
which by the same people
they did Totally Accurate
Battle Simulator and also
Cluster Trucks and some other stuff
definitely a game I want to check out
it was free for like 100 hours
and now
you can get it for 5 bucks
but it's a battle royale game
much like PUBG or something like that
it's its own
unique spin on it
where it's just really bad
as far as the physics and everything are just shit
the characters look like shit
because they look like the
Totally Accurate Battle Simulator
characters they have these big bug eyes
and everything is just really weird
you can do gangster style
where they'll beatbox and turn the guns sideways
they have guns that are
enormous that will launch you across the map
when you fire them
what's this game that's out right now
I'm wondering if it's the same game
where you turn into a chicken
when you get shot enough
I saw it being streamed on Twitch
and they make this like
horrible
that could be the same game
I don't know
that sounds like something they would do though
it was the number one game streaming on
Twitch because that Ninja guy
was playing it
it could be that
I don't know but
it's a silly game they've done
other stuff they did a game called Stick Fight
that's pretty awesome
they have some pretty fun games that have come out
I think that
it sounds like it could be
I'm going to check real quick to see what was more popular
games no they don't even have it on there
but yeah it could be
something that he played
I probably will check it out
I watched some streamers play it
it looked hilarious
you know how in
Fortnite if you drop out of this
flying bus thing
this one you're on the cluster trucks
and you get launched out
into whatever you aim at
it is a little creepy
because they've got these giant blocks
as the arena is closing in on you
they kind of ominously come down
and crash into the ground
so it's pretty cool
but it's really funny
and then Pokemon Go
because they started that whole water thing
so I've been getting my water Pokemon on
and yeah
it was a little bit angerous
that freaking water event is going on
and I still can't find more Lotads
that's like the one thing
that you can
I don't want to say easily get but I feel like the one
non-regional, non-legendary
the one thing I have left
to get is
well wait I take that back because I still don't have Luna Stone
I have Soul Rock but I don't have Luna Stone so I need one of those
and then I need that Lotad's final form
I have the second form
but I don't have the final form
Lone Bray is the second form I think
I've been getting a lot of Mudkips
yeah no there's tons of that and then Sirskit was one of the other ones I needed
that I was missing but I got
that because there's Sirskits everywhere right now
so that was something I was able to do
okay
let's see talking about my gaming week
it's a bit simple I've also been playing Pokemon Go
obviously
got sucked back into Heroes of the Storm
that's one of those games that comes in waves
it's like my love of Blizzard stuff
it's like I play Overwatch for a couple weeks
and I play Diablo 3 for a couple weeks
now it's Heroes of the Storm I'm back on that bus
so I've been having fun with that
and yeah just checking out some of the character changes
and leveling up my own characters
there's an event going on right now that's kind of fun
it's like a luchador themed thing going on
so I was able to get the little pictures
like my new
little picture looks like a corgi in a luchador's
outfit it's amazing
so that was worth the event right there
otherwise
yes Bobby after last week's
show I played Just Shapes and Beats
with Bobby on stream and that game
was fun I had a good time playing
Just Shapes and Beats great music
great soundtrack in that game
is the Mortal Kombat theme in there? not that we
found unless it's like an unlock later down
the line but I have a feeling that was
probably a license that cost him more money
so it's not in there now unless one of you
guys has unlocked it oh
apparently it is it is the last
unlock says the chat oh that's
awesome that they made it in there okay cool
so hopefully I'll
hopefully I'll get that far at some point
nice
so besides that
I've been playing more Hyrule Warriors
on Switch cause I missed the
boat when it was on Wii U and 3DS so now I'm
finally playing it and that game is also a lot of fun
and then still some more Final Fantasy 14
finally I have not played
my buddy Shane online
in months and so we actually have been doing
for those of you that play Final Fantasy 14
we decided to do some of the Eureka
leveling which is like this separate
kind of zone that has like a separate leveling
for your character and there's a lot
of stuff in there that kind of reminds us of Final Fantasy
11 which if you know
Shane and I's friendship we played Final Fantasy
11 online for
years Loki was a part of that too
so Eureka kind of has a lot of throwbacks to how
11 works so it's just like losing
XP when you die and all that stuff
so but it's
separate from the other like
that's the interesting thing that 14 does cause it did
this in Deep Dungeon too is that your XP
in there is separate from the regular game XP
so it's kind of neat that they have all these other side things
but that's all I'll say about my gaming
week so again follow us on
social media twitter.com slash OLR we're also
on Facebook facebook.com slash Orange Lounge
Radio we will be here next
week for our 16th
anniversary show but we will not
be here in two weeks I will be off
that weekend I am going to be in Chicago
seeing some
of my friends out there celebrating
my 40th birthday if you can believe it
is at the end of the month so gonna be celebrating that
so anyhow let's get into some
headlines some of the other things we have yet to talk
about tonight so you're gonna
we don't have a show roll tonight we're
doing this a little more free form so Loki
do you have some stuff we can talk about some talking points?
we're talking about the big thing so
valve
here we go
so valve
you may remember
we talked a few weeks back how valve was
planning on banning
these visual novel games
because they were too risque for steam
so now basically
they've decided that they're
gonna take a hands off approach on it
saying that hey
we've decided the right approach is to
allow everything onto the steam store
except for things that we decide are illegal or
straight up trolling so
the pendulum swung the other direction
yes so swung the other direction
and so
what did we get from that? well we got
school shooter simulator
whatever that was active shooter simulator
which ended up getting pulled off
and then the newest game
of the week that people
you know want to talk about that was totally a trolling
game AIDS
simulator
and that also got taken off of steam
well I mean at least they took it off
eventually okay they took it off
but how many
how many sold
because some people will buy that shit
because they like to troll
and so they want to bump that shit up in the rankings
and like people I knew were seeing
that game as a recommended game
because you like this other stuff because other people were buying
it and steam was happy to take a
30% cut of that stuff like
they need to have less of a reactionary
thing and be proactive
steam valve should fucking
know better at this point seriously
what the fuck is happening at valve
it is 20 steam is
coming from your no 20
it no but here's my point yeah it is
2018 what the fuck is
valve doing right now yes I know the actual
answer is they're working on HTC Vive
and VR but like that
is kind of like in my opinion that's kind of like
its own little thing that's kind of like
separate from the company that bought us
portal 2 okay here's the thing
guys the valve that we all
know and love the cake is a lie
all that shit 2011
portal 2 came out in 2011
that was 7 fucking years ago
and look I get they're working
on this Vive stuff they're doing this other stuff or whatever
but like valve has been slipping
y'all valve has been slipping
hardcore and especially when it comes to steam
because you know what the last interesting
steam sale was probably also in
2011 so like
valve because they
have the strong dominant end of the market
right now feels like they can do
this shit and like look I get
that the bad games got pulled
that's fine my point is
this whole cockamamie attitude of
and it wasn't just the fact that they were like
oh we're gonna allow everything on steam it was the way
they delivered that message of well
there should be some offensive
things that should offend
you and if we're not if we don't have that
then we're not doing it right and I'm like
um
I would not walk into a store
that sold that shit
so why am I gonna walk into yours
you cocky fuck
yeah they're trying to the thing is valve
needs an attitude adjustment right
the fuck now and it is up
to the people that sorry extra I'll
let you have a quick it is up to the people that have been
lifting them up for no
reason over the past
five years and I say no
reason because again okay sure maybe
you like dota 2 maybe you're into the
vibe stuff whatever you can lift them up on those
platforms as far as steam goes
steam has been fucking slipping
for several years now
the storefront is not as
good as it used to be the
sales are not like steam sales
are just kind of a meh now you know what I mean
like steve's been slipping over the few years
and after this fuckery
I'm sorry but like gog
itch.io humble bundle
are all starting to look more attractive right now
so don't think you're fucking invincible
valve that's my
point sorry extra go ahead no I didn't mean
to talk over um I just wanted to say
that like when you when you
get as big as as
steam or you get as big
as valve
you can't just give up on responsibility
I think that they're
they're trying to justify irresponsibility
that's all it is to me
you know and I don't see
people I saw
their announcement and I looked at the comments
and they were horrible they were like yay valve
free speech I you know
come on guys with the free speech stuff
this has nothing to do with free speech
it has everything to do with
being a good curator
of content for your customers
and this is not good curation
no one is preventing free speech by not putting
your game on the steam storefront it's the fucking
internet you can put it anywhere you want
thank you thank you thank you thank you
if you want to release aid simulator
in your stifling stinky little
black hole of the internet then that's
what the internet is for have
have fun actually I don't even want to tell you to have fun
just go fuck yourself honestly
but you have a little space to go do it in but like I don't understand
like the whole point like they made this big deal
like they're like okay we need to get rid of
Greenlight cause it's not working
but I think it was doing more
like so this filter
that we had wasn't working let's just get
rid of the filter like how the fuck
is that any better like that doesn't make any
sense the filter is that oh
we're charging $100 to submit a game
but you get it back you know if it sells
they don't want to be responsible
they don't and they don't want to hire a bigger team
to be responsible either they're a small team
that is a big problem too
their customer service sucks
yeah stop letting so many games
on your platform then cause it's drowning
out all of us it is finally time for the
rest of us to hold them fucking accountable so that
is why I'm here on this show today to say
because I've been accused of this in the past
and it will no longer happen
Valve does not get a free pass
anymore I don't fucking
care if they have these gigantic sales
or what have you you know what everybody's got a fucking
sale this is the internet GOGS has
sales Humble Bundle has sales
Valve does not get a free pass
anymore because they are Valve
that is
that is why I'm setting forth today and that ties
to this comment in our chat over at
live.vognetwork.com
e3inator in chat says Rob Roberts really
if you get right down to it Valve doesn't
have to do jack shit why because
they're making money hand over fist and
laughing all the way to the bank they can wipe their
asses with one thousand dollar bills if they
so choose you know what
not on my watch Satan
we're done with that and you're right
it has to start with the rest of us saying
you know what there are
other places to buy some fucking games
nobody knows that better than you
raginator there are
other places to buy games and find deals
make Valve
fight for first place
the attitude that they could print money and
they don't have to care is
is pointless to me so
so that's the same thing as saying
Martin Shkreli you know that guy
who raised the pharmacy
you know pharmaceutical drugs
is practically too rich to
care you know whatever but we all
like rose up and said no
you know what I mean and look where
he is now he's in prison
I'm not saying
Gabe should go to prison I'm just saying
no I am I'm saying they should go to prison
no I'm not I'm saying that
like somebody at his level
needs to come out and say
we fucked up exactly
I need I need that to happen
they need to take
we fucked up PS
as an apology Half Life 3
I'll take the first part at least
anyway
Rama says in chat when Valve brings us
Half Life 3 then I'll give a fuck
Bob Coffee says it's time for GOG to shine
Bobby Blackwolf wants to point
out he isn't in prison for the drug stuff he's in prison
for tax evasion yeah I know but you know
what Karma is a bitch
exactly yeah I don't care
what the actual circumstances
we got mad at him and he
got like in trouble and we're
all happy about it alright so anyway
I guess I don't
need to keep going off but my point
is from now on
Valve needs to earn that number one
spot as far as I'm concerned
because I will be looking for where the deals
on other games are I'm not gonna sit here and go
I'm gonna delete my fucking Steam account because you and I
both know that's not true I got too many games to do
exactly I got too many games locked in there
and like if I want to play Civ 6
I'm going to have to do it on Steam but I
can sit here and go I'm gonna think
twice before I just drop money
on a PC game on Steam because it's
on Steam and because you know
of the fucking trading cards or whatever is keeping
me on Steam I'm gonna start saying
you know GOG
that's a thing Humble Bundle that's
a thing itch.io that's a pretty cool thing
and Battle.net
uh fuck it
do you know how serious
I am everybody I'm about to show you how
fucking serious I am
I'll update my Origin account
oh yeah
oh no oh no bitch
nope I want
you all to pay fucking attention that's
how serious I am I'm gonna
update my Origin account
oh but you were gonna do that anyway when they brought
out their next Mass Effect
game right? in 2025
I love thank you guys for
playing along and chat oh shit now let's
not go overboard no I'm fucking serious
next thing you'll be telling me that you want to reinstall Uplay
or something like that I forgot
about you know what and if Uplay
has got a deal I play
I'm a proud member
of Uplay and I'm
biased you're biased alright
to be fair to give them props
I do like the fact that you can earn like points
or achievement points or whatever to like
get free shit in other games
yeah I like that too I like that but that's the
only thing I like I fucking hate everything else about it
I was about to be like oh I love that too
which ones do you play?
my whole like thing
give us another headline cause I hate that I'm the angry
bitch tonight
this is your role Loki I'm sorry
he's hand picking the stories that'll piss me off
uh Pokemon Let's Go
Pikachu and Eevee require an
online subscription of course
because it's Nintendo and they want to sell that subscription
oh it's Nintendo's new thing
that kind of actually does surprise me
isn't it like a single player game?
yeah I was under the impression it was gonna be a single player thing
does it only require the online
thing for like trading
with maybe it needs it to access
Pokemon Bank well wait a minute no it's not a mainline
game so you wouldn't it says it will have online
play functionality battling trading
with other players over the internet
but will the entire game require
is this gonna be another
Nintendo thing?
I think that's I think he just said it
like I think that's what you get there are
some things in Pokemon games you go online
for trading battling etc you want any
of that I'm thinking about I'm over
like paying for the subscription it's $20
a year I don't fucking care I spend
I spend more than that show of hands is anyone
not buying the Nintendo thing I know
I'm totally buying the Nintendo thing
Loki is buying the Nintendo
thing it's 20 fucking dollars
I mean that's like a couple
of meals and we have
when Tuesday happens and they announce
everything that's coming with it I think we'll be all like
okay let me put it this way the only
reason why I'm still
um giving them shit about it is
because I don't wanna just like them go
oh well it's only $20 well
but that doesn't give me an excuse to not do anything
for that $20 other than
oh well now we're letting you play online
even though we just didn't let you to do that
earlier for free but
I'm gonna give him a chance on this whole new
virtual console thing we'll see let's
let's I'm crossing my fingers it's
not gonna suck we'll see I have mod
chips if that's not the case
alright Tuesday's coming
there'll be a lot more coming on Tuesday
Tyco Drum Master
sorry I'm just gonna say
the one thing I
hear consistently
from more casual
but I bet a lot of you fit in this category too
the one thing I hear consistently about Tuesday
is this
I hope Nintendo announces a new
anyone wanna fill in the blank?
the number one thing I hear from casuals
no from casuals
no
Mario game?
I hope Nintendo announces a new
and it would be something that would completely
people would throw that $20 down
in a heartbeat
Animal Crossing
I want a new Animal Crossing
god dammit
I hate Animal Crossing
do you or do you hate the love it?
I hate it
I hate that every version of Animal Crossing that comes out
has less features than the one before it
and by less features I mean
none of them have virtual console games in them
I do wanna give JD a cookie in our chat
room because he answered, I love that the chat
jumped in, JD said new
IP
I will give you a cookie for that
the good news is I'm gonna give you a cookie
the bad news is it's oatmeal raisin
I want excite bike to come back
that's what I would shell down money
excite truck
yes!
excite bots bullshit
no! you should never have to play mini
games in the middle of a fucking race
that is dumb, that is dumb shit
excite truck though
act deft is getting angry
over here because you started to say taiko drum master
and I cut you off, sorry, taiko drum master
the Nintendo switch version
is coming to Asia in English
on August 9th
so yes, you may not necessarily get it
in North America, although I thought they were gonna
release it over here as well
but they're gonna be doing an English patch for free
on August 9th
so remember, the switch is region free
so if you want it, you can import it
you know what games I like better
than taiko drum master?
are the persona dancing games
there's a lot of those coming out
oh I know, well I mean persona dancing
all night, persona 4
I platinumed that
why can't we have both extrovert?
well I'm just saying I like it better
I can have both
there's
a new unannounced Diablo game
coming thanks to a
development job listing
that's all we know
but there's hope
it's gonna be so erect at Blizzcon
if they announce Diablo 4
that's another one
where I assume that they have been
working on something
since the necromancer didn't
end up being an expansion
then I'm assuming Diablo 3 is done
I mean, it could be
another Diablo expansion
it could be this switch thing
that maybe would be the
way to do this new Diablo 3
but there's a part of me that says
you know what, they're just gonna
whip out the number 4, why not?
Diablo 3 kinda had that cloud
over it ever since the beginning with the auction house
and all that other stuff, even though it's a great
game now, like
because Diablo is a console and PC
thing for them, it doesn't
necessarily have that exact same sort of
foreverness that Overwatch does
although, I don't know, the rifts and stuff
are still interesting, I still play them
why not? Let's do Diablo 4
the only thing that's weird about Diablo 4
is that Blizzard
hasn't done a
sequel game in a very long time
like the last sequel game I can think of
when was Starcraft 2?
because I think it was Diablo 3
so that's the only weird
thing about it, is that Blizzard
isn't exactly known for cranking out the sequels
and when they do announce it
it takes a very long time for them to get
that's true, they'll announce it now and then it's really
out in 3 years, so we'll see
oh shit, you know, I just realized
something, which makes
the Square Enix thing very exciting
tomorrow
they have that Marvel project, fuck yeah
fuck yeah
that's a good chance that we're gonna see that Marvel
project tomorrow, I can't wait
speaking of which, the rumor with that
Marvel project is
a reboot of Marvel Ultimate Alliance
which I am totally down for
oh, interesting
Ultimate Alliance is fucking awesome
those games weren't like bad
or needing a reboot, but I guess then again
they do this all the time with games, they just kind of start over
maybe it could be just similar
like a similar type of gameplay or something
I'm down, that's cool
Hitman 2 is something that's
also gonna be probably shown off
Sony confirmed that
Sony confirmed Hitman 2 I think
yeah, so they've got that coming out and they've got
this collector's edition with a rubber duck
that's kinda cool
what else
we have the lineup for
Sega and Atlas
so they're gonna be showing off
Shining Resonance
Refrain, that's coming out on
PlayStation 4, Xbox One, Switch and PC
Team Sonic Racing
which is also on PlayStation 4, Xbox One
Switch and PC
Valkyria Chronicles 4
on PlayStation 4, Xbox One and the Switch
and Yakuza Kiwami
on PlayStation 4
and then one
thing that they'll be showing but that won't be playable there
is Total War Three Kingdoms on PC
and then
I wanna say that there was another
like Catherine, Catherine Full
Body was something else that was being announced
and then
I feel like that Catherine thing they'd already announced though
and then, and then
that was a PSX reveal or something wasn't it?
and then Atlas, they've got some more
stuff that they said they found including
you know there's, they found websites
for Persona 3 Dancing Moon Knight
and Persona 5 Dancing Star Knight
and of course those
have been confirmed
and both
look amazing
so, neat
let's see what else we got
here, while you're looking I'm gonna go ahead and open
up the Skype line if anyone does wanna give us a call
Orange Launch Radio, all one word on Skype
if you wanna talk to us about an E3
that's already happened or that's
going to happen, maybe you
have some things you wanna talk about with
Sony or Nintendo tomorrow, let me ask
Xtifer, cause we don't get to hear from you
a lot here at OLR
but I know you're a big gamer, what
what do you hope for from Sony and
Nintendo?
I'm looking forward most out of all
of E3
for the Death Stranding
stuff
gameplay finally?
I'd be satisfied with another
trailer, honestly
I need to see the game
I'd love to see the game
it'd be great, it'd be great
if there's another trailer that is also
very cryptic, I'll watch it for days
but be angry that we didn't get gameplay
at the same time
but when it comes to Nintendo
obviously I think it would be
Metroid Prime 4
you're a big fan of Metroid Prime
I love Metroid anything
I'm hoping for Mario Maker
I would like to see a Mario Maker port
too, I feel like I'm in the minority
I just wonder how, I mean I
get how it would work
on the docked, but it'd be kinda more clunky
compared to
using it portable, right?
Yeah, but there's no reason you can't create portable
and then play docked
part of the fun of Mario Maker is playing
all the crazy fucking stages
Mario Maker, like that, but here's the twist
it's two player because
the Switch has two
like maybe co-op or something
like that, what a twist
split screen, yeah because you know they're gonna
wanna use their two player gimmick
thing that they have going on, co-op
I don't think there's
any, maybe
I'm pretty sure they won't show anything else
with Bayonetta 3, but
maybe, maybe
a new trailer, maybe a little teaser
yeah, maybe another morsel or something
Let's get to the phones, we got a call coming in, let's do it
Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
Hi, this is Ray G. Nader
Hey Ray G. Nader, what's up buddy?
I know a whole lot, well
since the topic is pretty much
solely E3
I'll chime in on that
Go ahead
Sorry if I'm a little measly looking there
sick as a dog, but
well
take what I'm about to see
with a little bit of
a grain of salt
I always do, ba-da-bum
I missed
some of
some portions
of the conferences because I was
supposed to be out and about
but based on what I did see
overall
I was pleased with what
I saw
Now if I were to be
nitpicky about one
thing
is that
while I kind of saw this coming
in the back of my mind
I was kind of sort of hoping
that
I would hear about a new Magic
Together game
that was in the works
That's something up your alley
Oh yeah, well you know me, I talk about
those Magic Together games
all the time, in fact
the newest one
Magic Duels came out
I believe in
2014 or 2015
and that was like
three, four years ago
so I think we're kind of
overdue for a new one
and you know
Grand is not as popular
as say Gears of War, Halo
or Mass Effect, but it does have
a pretty strong following
Sure, of course
with the trading card game and everything, of course
Yeah, and plus
knowing that, but
Grand is not as
extensive as actual
card game, but at the same time
it's a whole lot cheaper than
going out and getting the booster packs
and trying to find
the rare cards individually
you know, you'll save a lot of money
that way, so
that's why I love
the game myself, so
but
there was
I loved everything else
you know, the
talk about Doom
the Fallout
talk, you know
Let me ask you this question, RageNator
because there's a comment in our chat
where Kaijuto says, take it from a guy that plays a lot of
card games, there are so many better games than Magic
well, I mean, opinion
is a big thing, but I'm curious
RageNator, especially because
we're talking about Bethesda, Bethesda does have their
Elder Scrolls based card game
do you ever try some of the others?
Uh, no
honestly, yeah
really, I mean, the main reason why
I got into the
Magic the Gathering
video games is because
I've been involved with
the card game way back when
I was in high school, back in the Stone Age
so, I'm already familiar
with concepts and
the mechanics and this and
other, and plus now there's the
Paul and the Stabs thing for me
so, I'm not saying
that these other games are any
way, shape or form
bad games, I'm not saying that
if other people love these
I totally get it, it's like me and
Elder Scrolls Online when we were talking during the
thing, it's like, I just
tend to gravitate towards Final Fantasy 14
It's your comfort zone
Yeah, it's my comfort zone, it's not that Elder Scrolls Online
is bad, it's just, it's
the game that other people like, you know
some people like action movies, some people
like comedies, some people like
There's a lot of people that don't understand
my love for Binding of Isaac
but, it's my comfort zone, it's my game
with choice, you know
Yeah, I kinda like what you like, it's cool
I'm curious if you do the
experimenting with the other games, that's all
Uh, no, I
well, I did manage to get
a free copy of GWENT
through DLG
but honestly, let's be
honest here, I haven't even
installed it yet, I haven't
fired it up yet
and honestly, I probably
never will
I'm not saying that these other
games are anyway bad
other people love them
There's just only so much time in a day, I understand
Yeah, well
I'll probably get a free off the lines that way
if someone else wants a call
but have a nice night
Thanks, thanks for the call, take care buddy, bye
Such a nice guy, that regenator
Orange Lounge Radio, all one word
if you wanna give us a call
For such a, for such a
testosterone-y filled name
Like Rage?
Maybe it's just one of those ironic
It's one of those ironic names, maybe
I don't know, I don't know, or maybe like
he's like Terminator, he terminates the Rage
The Rage stops here
I think that's what he was going with
Perhaps, perhaps
Loki, any other headlines you wanna run down with us?
Uh, yeah, Final Fantasy XV is getting mod support on PC
or I should say it has mod support on PC now
Oh, like official mod support
So like, now we can have
Nudie mods officially
There's pictures of Keyblades
and Thomas the Tank Engine
I feel like we knew this was coming because I remember this guy
the guy behind Final Fantasy XV
Don't make nudie mods
Please, we're just gonna ask the community
nicely to not make the nudie mods
and like, within
30 seconds the nudie mods were here
If not, look
If you're not into dudes
I'm sure they've got a Sydney
like, and the
Dragoon, Ariana, what was her name
the Dragoon lady, I'm sure they get naked too
so whatever you're into
And Valve, Valve is just like
whatever the fuck you wanna do
you know, just don't troll people
Okay
Valve and I are fighting right now so
I don't care what they're doing
Valve can go do whatever they want
in their corner right now where I'm just side-eyeing them
Speaking of mods
of course, you know, with the emulated version
of Breath of the Wild
people have modded Mario
and Valve's are in there
Because why not?
Because you can do all that kind of shit
You sure can
I don't know
if we talked about this or not
but there's a new game streaming service
I guess they're saying with Facebook
facebook.gg
Oh yeah, this is like their answer to Twitch
and Mixer
and all that stuff
They're doing this facebook.gg
Are we still mad at Facebook right now?
Are we on a cooling off period?
Facebook is like
that person you hang out with that you know
is nothing but drama and trouble
but like once in a while
like they're cool
So it's like you're guarded
when you hang out with Facebook
Facebook's kind of like the friend
that I
never really
It's more of an acquaintance
not a friend
I feel like Facebook doesn't need to be in this space
There's a lot of spaces Facebook is getting into
where I'm like Facebook, I think you should just stay out
Exactly, it's trying to be a jack of all trades
but it's really horrible
Game streaming is one of them
It's just like, it's not going to happen
I don't know, I just read an article recently
I say that, but I think actually
because so many people are glued to Facebook
it's going to pop up in people's
feeds so easily
I read an article recently about how
they question Mark Zuckerberg
when he was
questioned by Congress
about the shadow
profiles, about how they make
profiles for people that don't even have
Facebook accounts
and I was like, that really rubbed
me the wrong way
and his answers were not very
reassuring
and so I'm like, wow
So I don't feel like I can trust
them, you know what I mean? In fact
I went into their privacy settings
just recently, which basically
their UI is so
convoluted, and we all know
this, right? But I was trying to go
into every single Facebook privacy
setting, which is like a headache in itself
and turn everything off
because I don't want to allow anything
but even that, I don't trust
because they don't
have that there, so why would I trust
them with a streaming thing?
Honestly, my
biggest comment with this is
I will still be streaming on my Twitch
channel over twitch.tv slash Rob Roberts
Go give me a follow, please
That's really all I have to say
Not that Amazon is
really that much better, but
At least
I feel like Twitch, for the most
part, when they have
issues, they're really good at resolving
them quickly and doing better, you
know, and maybe it wasn't always that
way, but like lately, you know
so I can't
I enjoy being a Twitch streamer
you know, when I have the time for it
which isn't all the time, but when I have the time for it, I enjoy it
so, and honestly
if Twitch wasn't around, Mixer's not bad
there's a lot to like about Mixer
I wish I had the time where I could
do a stream here and there, you know
but I just, I don't have that kind of time, sadly
but I watched the Xbox
thing on Mixer today and it looked great in 4K
so, because my monitor
on my computer is 4K
so it looked great. I watched it on YouTube because
I was out and about
when it was going on. I forgot it was
early on. It was a weird hour
They always do their
concerts. I'm not talking about
Bethesda. They always do their
conferences early
in the day, right? Well, it's early
for us, but
it was 4 o'clock on the East Coast
so a little more reasonable. So maybe they're just trying to be
friendly to the East Coast
but Sony always tells them like 6 o'clock
in the afternoon. Also
not just us, but Europe, that would've been
9 in the evening in Europe, so let's not
forget Microsoft's a global thing
so it makes a lot more sense
for them to go so early so that way it's
you know, because when Sony does
their thing, it's always later. That's gonna
be like 2 in the morning for Europe
so that's not as nice for them. So that's
part of the reason why, you know, there are
morning press conferences with ether. But I think that
maybe Sony has it in their mind, you know, well
this, you know, E3 is
primarily like North American
announcements, whereas Gamescom
is like more Europe, you know?
Yeah, at least Sony kind of
gives a little bit to Gamescom too, you know?
Yeah, because they have those like
E3 style press conferences. Plus they have
PSX too. And you know what?
I think for Sony more, the thing
they have to consider is
Japan. And so for Japan,
it is the morning when
Sony goes. So I think they all just kind of
have to consider like, you know, because you can't
do anything that's gonna be a
great time for Japan, the US, and
Europe. So you just kind of have to pick two.
I just assume E3 has
already happened because Japan is in the
future. Yes.
Alright. Oh, back to Loki.
See if there's any other stories you want to cover.
I was trying to find out what
happened with the Devolver Digital
thing. All I know is it
involved the physical loot coin that you
can buy for a very large amount of money
that keeps changing price.
I'm not really sure what else.
I am so
wanting to see this. Everybody in chat was
screaming about Metal Wolf Chaos, I guess was the
thing. Yeah, I thought that was rumored
to be something they were going to be bringing out.
Devolver Digital was my highlight
last year. They were like the best.
It made no sense.
Tim and Eric.
They're kind of like the
frat kid game company in some
ways. You have to admit it was
funny last year. I didn't watch it. We were
doing this show. You didn't watch the
stream of it? No.
There's a new
serious Sam game
coming out. I don't know.
But the actual
you have to watch that, Rob, if you've
never watched it. It's really funny.
Sorry, that was my
Google chat that just went off. Again?
I know. It's like, God, I think it's safe
to keep it open so I can have a show roll up.
Well, to be fair, we didn't have a show roll tonight.
We just had an email, so that's why I had it up.
It was irony. Anyway.
And you know what the funniest thing about it?
There was a message from Alan going, what are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
He also knows that the show lately has been
wrapping around 8.30, so he's probably curious
if we're done yet or not. But I think we are
about winding up. Yeah, I think we've run out of
some stuff to talk about right now.
We've run out of steam. Well, we haven't
run out of steam, but there's like a
Dead or Alive 6 reveal trailer.
There's a lot more we'll be talking about, I'm sure,
after everything's done. Yeah, next week's gonna be crazy
because we're gonna have Sony and Nintendo to talk about.
Happy E3 week, everybody.
Try not to be too cynical.
Not everything sucks.
There should be something you enjoy this week,
so I hope, hey, I got Tetris
Effect. If nothing else,
I have Tetris Effect. I'm telling you that
that is, and do you have,
by the way, just for shits,
do you have the Tetris Effect
when you play a prolonged
amount of time? Oh, do I suffer from it?
It's not, you don't suffer from it,
but it's something that a lot of people haven't. I do.
Um, I get it with other video
games. Really? Yeah. I'll dream
about other video games like that.
Well, no, no, I mean when,
well, that's one thing. Isn't that
kind of the same thing?
I think it goes, it also goes
into the fact that when you play something like that
with like basic shapes for a long period of time,
then you actually, when you close your eyes,
you almost see it in your head.
And that's what happens to me.
It's called the Tetris Effect. With all the music
games I've played over the years? Like, I've totally seen
Falling Notes. Exactly. That's what it,
that's the Tetris Effect. Yeah. And that's the actual
official name of that
phenomenon. Yeah. So that
trailer was so cool the way they did that, yeah.
Like, it pisses, again,
if you're one of those people out there on Twitter
that's like, a fucking Tetris
game, that should be, like, do not
Oh, fuck you. Tetris is the best game in the world.
Seriously, I will cyber-bully you.
Like, you think Steam got
it bad tonight? Just wait until I find out where you are.
There's a reason why they keep
re-releasing that game. It's because
it's a tried and true formula and it works.
Exactly. And, like,
seriously, seriously, the first time
I played Luminous, my reaction was,
man, can you imagine if they made, like, a Tetris game like this?
And, like, we're fucking getting it. So,
sit down, shut up,
and eat pie. And eat your rice.
I don't know.
It's not coming to the Switch, though, which is unfortunate.
Well, no,
yeah, it's exclusive. Not out the gate.
Right now, it's exclusive for Sony.
That Luminous reboot, though, is out at the end of June.
This is true.
And that is on the Switch.
I just like the soundtrack for Tetris Effect.
I just want everything to be on Switch, because
I just, I wish it was more powerful
that they could put more of the other things.
Did you notice, though, that Microsoft kind of snuck that
in there, where they were like, you can play on your phone,
and even though I know we're all laughing at that, like, ha ha,
I feel like that was kind of
like their way to say, like, well, you know,
you can play anywhere on Microsoft, too.
It's just a little different.
Yeah.
I get it. A little bit. Yeah, I get it.
But I appreciated that Microsoft
is kind of trying to slyly go, you know.
Anyway,
go ahead and chat.
SG100Matt, I like this little piece of positivity here.
We get tied up in
winners and losers of E3, when
in reality, the winners are all of us gamers,
and the losers are the hate-filled
people who want to put down others
and make gaming an unhealthy place
for everyone. Be a winner, folks.
Aw, we could bake a cake.
Winners don't use cynicism.
FBI warning.
2018. Follow your dreams.
NBC star.
Let's see. E3inator
in chat says, Tetris is overrated,
Rob Roberts.
Okay. You want to talk about reading?
Let's talk about reading.
Aren't you the guy that just
called into the show to talk about Magic
the Gathering? I can see
where he got his name.
He's enraging us.
That's all I'm gonna say.
You're not the nice little guy that called in earlier.
I gave you all those compliments,
and now I think you're shit.
You're not shit.
You just have an opinion.
Yeah, you just have some really bad opinions.
I mean,
we all sometimes have incorrect
opinions, and it's just about, you know.
And I kind of like Magic
the Gathering, but like the old school card game
the most. Nothing beats the card game.
You know, Matt, my boyfriend,
he likes Magic the Gathering.
He used to like it a lot. He doesn't play it now.
I used to play
the shit out of it. He has a ton of old cards
in his... I used to play
in high school, and then I found out one day we were
completely playing it wrong.
The rules of that game are kind of complicated.
Now you've got YouTube's tutorials and shit
and computer games to help you understand the rules
of Magic the Gathering, but trying to read it out of a book
we were playing it wrong.
What I want to know is, where does the title
like, why is it called The Gathering?
Like, what do you gather
in it? Do you gather magic?
Yes, you tap your lands.
You tap your lands!
Tap the land, bitch!
Is it Magic comma The Gathering?
No.
Like, is Magic the title of The Gathering?
Magic colon The Gathering.
Oh, Magic colon...
I want to know
what caused the
original people to come up with this title.
Magic colon
The Gathering.
Wait, wait, is Magic the IP
and The Gathering is the name
of the game?
Listen, you gather the magic
to summon the monsters while you tap the lands.
Why is it so complicated?
That's the game's core mechanic.
Yeah, but when you think about it,
though...
I don't know.
I just wish...
I agree with Dungeon Buster. Dungeon Buster says,
Magic colon The Gathering sounds dangerous.
We're gonna leave it at that.
That was a joke I knew Extro would like.
I like that joke.
Anything else to share with us, Lowkey, or are we shutting it down?
Ah, we can shut it down. I was just checking the Wikipedia page
for Magic the Gathering to see if they had an explanation.
Explain yourself!
You know, I'm glad I can
provoke these moments of
education. It's what I
live for.
You're welcome.
Alright,
so here we go.
Let's explain what it was.
The game,
while the game is simply called Magic
through most of playtesting,
when the game had to be officially named,
a lawyer informed them that the name Magic
was too generic to be named.
Mana Clash was instead
chosen to be the name used
in the first solicitation of the game.
However, everybody involved in the game
continued to refer to it as Magic.
After further consultation with
the lawyer, it was decided
to name the game Magic the Gathering,
thus enabling the name to be
trademarked. So that's why they don't
just call it Magic. Interesting.
But you know what? Mana Clash sounds...
You can't trademark Magic.
Mana Clash sounds
like an 80s synth-pop band.
But it also, in the context of today's
media and everything,
it sounds like a generic mobile game.
It probably is a game
called Mana Clash on the store right now.
And it's probably a match three game.
Mana Clash!
Alright, anyway.
We're going to wrap things up. Extrovert, the chatters
are loving you tonight. S2100 Matt says
don't be a stranger. Call in when you get settled in.
You're missed here. And Judge Boeser said thank you for
suggesting... S2100 Matt is suggesting
that you should have... Oh, I don't know about this.
I don't know about this. But he's suggesting
you should have a segment called
Hot Game Developer of the Week.
You know my
habits when it comes to podcasts.
I'll always miss that.
He'll do it for 12
weeks.
And they'll be like, oh, like
five weeks later. It's like, you're like,
do you want to do it again?
Guys, there's something about
the guys on the show, I think the revival went
for like 12 episodes, right?
Pokestop podcast went for 12 episodes.
Shaking and crying, we have 13
episodes and we've been off for five weeks.
Okay, so it's you. It's your fault.
I think it might be. You're the constant
in this. Alright, no.
No, no. I'm going to own up to the guys on the show.
But, but, but
um, most... And I am
trying to get Victoria in gear for us to move again.
And it is partially my fault why we put it
on a stop for a while. Most revivals
only last 13 episodes.
Roseanne.
Yes, but that's
because the last time I checked
I don't post stupid shit
on my Twitter.
I have to say, I have something
to say.
No, shaking and crying is coming back.
It's just, you notice, it's been a little
bit. So some of you might think it's been
ending, but as long
as Victoria isn't stopping, we
shouldn't be stopping. Anyway, sorry.
I was just going to say, you know, I, by the way
I've, people that
have listened to the show know I take
Ambien. I'm a friend to the
Ambien. I speak Ambienese.
Right. And so I have
taken it for 13 years on and off.
Do you play with Amiibo on Ambien?
No, I don't. I don't.
I play with my Amiibo on Ambien.
Right.
I'd like to play
with some of those guys on the show.
On Bethesda.
Okay, so I'm going to
summarize beside the point,
but what I want to say is
never have I
ever wanted to post
a racist tweet on Ambien.
Just going to go, just going to make
that clear, right?
Okay, just so that's clear. You've never been
compelled to just get on there. No, no, because
the thing about Ambien is you still
know right from wrong when you're on
it, so you're not going to do things that
aren't you. It's like you're not allowed to murder
it. Like guns don't kill people.
Ambien kills people. Exactly.
So let's say that I did
make a racist tweet on Ambien.
That would mean I'm a racist.
Uh huh.
Connect the dots there, Rob.
I kind of already did.
Like Roseanne, she's
canceled. Like literally and
figuratively. I didn't like the show anyway.
It came on as like, this is
just too much propaganda
bullshit nonsense.
It got so bad. It got
so bad in my opinion. Like I'm like,
this isn't funny anymore.
Anyway, wow. So this is
not the Roseanne podcast. No, it's
not. It's not. So I think, I think
we're ready to wrap up.
Bobby Blackwolf in chat says, you have
said stupid shit, Rob. Like Super Metroid
is better than Chrono Trigger on
your Twitter, so that's hate speech.
Well, I mean
when you're going to spell the truth. Facts are facts, America.
Honestly,
I can't judge Chrono Trigger. I
never played it. Here's the thing.
I always get shit
over that line, which I, I'm going to
stand by. I'm going to stand by. You can
put it on my fucking tombstone. Super Metroid
is the greatest video game ever made. Here's
the thing though. When have I ever said
Chrono Trigger is a bad game?
Like, and that's the whole thing. This is like gaming
in a nutshell. Can't we
just enjoy both?
Can't we enjoy both?
Isn't there room
in your collection for
both? And also, if we're going to go further,
what if you did think
Chrono Trigger was a bad game?
What does that matter? You're not actually
destroying world peace. That's just your opinion.
It's true. Lavos
destroyed world peace. I didn't do shit.
I don't care if you don't like my favorite
things, but like, I mean
I might get a little irked and be like,
well, they're stupid.
That's like when you talk shit about Forza Horizon
4. I'd be like, that's your wrong opinion.
But go ahead.
Well, it's kind of a derivative game.
You know, with those cars. I think you meant to say
a deriving game. It is a deriving
game. A deriving, yeah. And you drive
in the winter and the summer
and the autumn and we're gonna leave it at
that before I'm gonna put
you in Valve's corner.
Nobody belongs in that corner
except for Valve, Rob. Nobody puts
Valve in a corner. Yeah.
Nobody wants to put Valve in a corner.
This hurts me more than it hurts you, Valve.
Are we done?
Can we sign off now? Alright. Yes.
That's it. We're gonna be back in another
seven days to do this all again.
Without Extfer. No, but they can't.
Sorry, guys.
I appreciated you being here. You're a lot of fun as always.
Do you have anything you want to plug?
Like, things that people should follow you on
if they miss you? You know, you can follow
me on Twitter. I'm
GamerExtfer. It's
G-A-Y... Why do I always have to
spell this stuff? Well, cause there's...
Well, Extfer is E-X-T-O-F-E-R.
It's not X-T-O-F-E-R.
It's E-X-T-O-F-E-R.
But Gamer is G-A-Y-M-E-R.
Like Gay,
Gamer, GamerX. Right.
Happy Pride. Yes.
You should spell that name. That is
what I would think. There you go.
Cool. I don't have
anything else, though. I don't have anything else I do
lately. I don't stream
anymore. Support Ubisoft cause
then... Yeah, yeah. Buy the
Fractured But Whole.
Because, you know, it's nice to show
people support. A lot of hard
working people worked on that game.
That's right.
Still haven't played through all the DLC.
I know. He keeps telling me to
play through the latest one.
The second DLC. He says
it's really good. I bought the Season Pass
and I was like, that's what I typically do
with games. Like, I'm gonna buy the Season Pass.
And then I stopped playing the game. I did Fallout 4.
I did that with Call of Duty.
And I did it with that one.
I'm sure there's other games.
Skyrim. It happens.
It happens. Alright.
So as I always say at the end of the show, thank you
so much for listening to Orange Launch Radio. If you enjoyed
what you heard here at the show, leave us
a nice five star review on iTunes or
tell a friend or wherever you hear the show.
iTunes, Google Play, whatever. And tell a friend or
two about the show. Help us spread the word because
we are the show where every gamer has a voice.
And we can't get the
voices out here to air unless
y'all know about the show. If you didn't
enjoy tonight's OLR, try
to download one of the other episodes
that didn't get interrupted with E3
and Extoverne.
I'm just kidding. I'm kidding.
No, I consider that a compliment.
Anyway, if you didn't enjoy
tonight's episode, you're just wrong. Sorry.
Hate to say it. Anyway.
Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
Dexter, do you have a final thought?
I want to
sleep with that guy and his dad on
the Bethesda conference.
Maybe you should keep that thought
internal. I don't know if my boyfriend
would really appreciate
the final thought. Probably not.
Loki, can you give us a real final thought, please?
I'm looking forward to seeing all of the
game announcements this week.
Hopefully there's nothing
disappointing. Death Stranding.
My final thought is I'm gonna hold out
hope for Super Metroid 2.
Have a good night, everybody.
We'll see you in seven days. What about F-Zero? What are the odds
of F-Zero this year?
I hope so. None to none. Can I play the credit
music now? We'll see you in seven days. Bye.
The views and opinions
expressed in this program do not
necessarily reflect those of the staff
of Orange Lounge Radio or
VOG Network, but you know
they were all still true.
See you next week.
Thanks for watching!