[SPEAKER_07]: I miss forensic files really badly.
[SPEAKER_07]: I go through withdrawal.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I miss, and like everyone's now telling me that at least five, six people have told me that Stargate show's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I downloaded the first episode of the Atlantis one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got that downloading.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I love Iron Chef, so I've been trying to download as much Iron Chef as possible.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have the liver battle and the caviar battle and the broccoli battle.
[SPEAKER_07]: They made broccoli ice cream.
[SPEAKER_07]: You both have like...
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, I need more Iron Chef.
[SPEAKER_07]: I even have one of the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: ones, The Egg Battle, which I actually need to watch just to see how bad it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm actually, the other thing I'm downloading right now is like a PaintShop Pro 8 beta, I think.
[SPEAKER_23]: Speaking of TV, I've been watching a TV show I've been keeping up on.
[SPEAKER_23]: TV Nihon has been so gracious to be fansubbing these for us, but the Sailor Moon live action show has got to be one of the greatest things ever.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh my god, it's freaking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_23]: Even with the plushies!
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh my god, yeah, it's in the, like, it's everything.
[SPEAKER_23]: My girlfriend, who doesn't even like, you know, Rice Princess, she doesn't even, she hates Sailor Moon with a passion.
[SPEAKER_23]: But she loves this show because it's just so cheesy.
[SPEAKER_23]: Like, they never, when they're fighting, instead of them fighting, they just do cartwheels around each other, and that supposedly, we will defeat you with our cartwheels.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's almost how it is on the show itself, you know, they do the, I find it so funny that Usagi is supposed to be so...
[SPEAKER_23]: Clumsy yet she can do all these elaborate poses All these crazy cartwheels and backflips and stuff It's just crazy It's so funny too And for people who do like Sailor Moon If there's anybody who likes Sailor Moon I've watched all of it They rewrote the script so it's still kind of fresh and new I mean they have some elements from the cartoon, the original But it kind of adds a little more And a little more adult Not really adult but I guess more mature humor I mean there's no sex or anything Darn
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, we need the Haruka Michiru action.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sailor Uranus and Sailor Neptune.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to go to a break because we haven't been to a break for a little while now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, actually, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should ask Lanky Saldo, since he's here, how was your week and how was your day since we were just finishing that segment up?
[SPEAKER_23]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_23]: Same as always, except I just got some new crack from Irene.
[SPEAKER_23]: I downloaded the Harry Potter game, The Prisoner of Azkaban, and she's, you know, it's so childish, but, you know, for a fan, like, as big of a fan she is of Harry Potter, you know, she has to play it, so, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_23]: And it's, like, really skipping and stuff during the dialogue, so it's so funny, it'll be talking, and it'll be like, what's up, Harry?
[SPEAKER_23]: And it's, like, it's great, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_23]: And I just bought a new graphic card on the way here, I bought a new Radeon that's gonna, like,
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_23]: With all the problems you just went through with your graphic card, I think you should probably stick with the one you just, you know, you just finally fixed it so you can play your stupid Final Fantasy XI game.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: How do you like them apples?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we need to go to a break right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I need to have a word with Brad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, yeah, we're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we come back, we'll talk about some Bomani news, if we can dig any up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, the cage match.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, the FUs of the week, Ask Orange Lounge, and the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: All this when we come back from this break featuring more Dance Maniacs music, because that's what I feel like hearing.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_15]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for watching!
DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: I, I, I, I, I
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: After this song, we'll be having a Let Them Move Marathon.
[SPEAKER_15]: No!
[SPEAKER_04]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crap-free Bavani Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome back, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we are.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode number 103.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't supposed to be here tonight, but I was granted a reprieve.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not supposed to be here today.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get to leave tomorrow instead, so I'm hoping to check out some interesting things while I'm on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki had to do some surgery on the microphone here to get it to work right, but it's great now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jonas is fondling Loki's cock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, did you just put Loki's cock in your mouth?
[SPEAKER_04]: Jonas, what the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_23]: Watch out or his cock will bite you.
[SPEAKER_23]: His cock's a real pecker.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, I was having fun with that too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's not have fun with the cock.
[SPEAKER_24]: The only one you should have fun with is your own.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you said, Loki, you said you saw something local on DDR this week in the news.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did your mom say about it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't see it either.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard about it though.
[SPEAKER_03]: She basically said DDR was on the news.
[SPEAKER_03]: They said something about people losing weight playing the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it was a generic interview piece that every news channel has done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was Tanya in it?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a shocker.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: So everything, it's just basically the same story that's been going around ever since that Associated Press thing picked it up, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, this is bullshit.
[SPEAKER_23]: The media and parents and stuff, they don't fucking care about our video games until somebody goes and kills somebody and then blames it on Grand Theft Auto or something, you know.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, we don't make fun of them for being crack whores.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, what does that have to do with anything?
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyway, yeah, sorry, I just wanted to
[SPEAKER_23]: I digress.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it's just the old TV saying of if it bleeds, it leads, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: If it's not like a really horrible, depressing story, or causing violence in the streets or whatever, then, you know, it's one of those pieces that's saved for the end of the newscast to make you feel good.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an uplifting story at the end, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fat man fat no more thanks to video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who would have thought?
[SPEAKER_24]: Nobody watches the news that long anyways.
[SPEAKER_24]: They've watched the first ten minutes for all the bloody headlines, and then after that they wait until sports and they're done.
[SPEAKER_23]: I just figured it out.
[SPEAKER_23]: So they get lean, they lose weight, and they get in shape from playing this game, but then what's the deal?
[SPEAKER_23]: Konami's not releasing any more DDRs.
[SPEAKER_23]: So if you were going to get bored of DDR...
[SPEAKER_23]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_23]: People are going to get bored of DDR, and they're going to stop playing, and they're going to get fat again, and then they're going to sue Konami, because they didn't come out with any new DDRs, just like they sue, like, McDonald's for not, you know, for making people fat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Careful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Technicality, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you mean no new DDR arcade, but every news story has focused on the DDR home version.
[SPEAKER_04]: Almost all of them are talking about the home versions, and they are coming out with two of them this summer, or not this summer, but this fall, so, you know, you can't say that too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I can't, because I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_23]: The arcade DDR was the pinnacle moment for DDR.
[SPEAKER_23]: Stapler.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want my stapler back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Loki, yes, you have something to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw another video this week of In The Groove, and I have to say, it doesn't look that bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: This coming from you?
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't look... Well, here's the problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's before I saw early shots of In The Groove, and they've developed a lot further since when I saw it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It actually looks pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wouldn't mind it actually coming into an arcade, except, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean, look at what the options are out there right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have two fucking bootlegs floating around.
[SPEAKER_03]: One's a miscolored DDR Extreme, and the other one's like a DDR Extreme with like this overclocking on it, which is stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, I'd rather play in the groove than that shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, hey, bring it in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't spend $650 on these bootlegs and bring in the groove.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it actually doesn't look that bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: The interface is pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like what they've done with it so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it just looked very interesting, that's all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would still rather have a new Konami DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, okay, yeah, but at the moment, since there is no Konami DDR on the horizon, I'll take this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of like, it's like, can you go give me, hey, can you go to the fridge and give me a soda?
[SPEAKER_04]: All we got's diet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, alright, I'll drink it anyway.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, it's more like, your choices are George W. Bush or John McCain, which you'd rather have.
[SPEAKER_23]: John Kerry, I'm sorry, that was last fucking election or whatever, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_23]: You just totally lost it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Bill Clinton or George W. Bush, either one sucks to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Jamie wants to say, where's the other mic over there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw a funny bumper sticker day since you mentioned that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It said Clinton, he did it between two Bushes.
[SPEAKER_04]: On that note, I think we're going to go ahead and get into tonight's cage match, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about the cage match?
[SPEAKER_04]: The way the cage match works, for those of you guys who haven't listened before, you've got to be in our chat room to participate.
[SPEAKER_04]: OrangeLawnRadio.com, you pick a winner.
[SPEAKER_04]: Three songs, each host brings one to the table.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get to hear a clip of last week's winner, because you already heard it last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you get to hear two new songs in the entirety.
[SPEAKER_04]: You vote for your favorite.
[SPEAKER_04]: That favorite goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, with the Monty Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so let's get right into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last week's winner was brought to the table by Loki, and it's BT.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the song is called Kimo Sabe, and we figured out it is in one of those other harmonics games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's in Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number one, a clip of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: BT, Kimo Sabe, enjoy.
I rock creativity, I bust positive vibes from the west to Maui
Pull it back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that was song number one in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_04]: A clip of last week's winner, BT with Kimo Sabe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get into song number two tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number two is my pick.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I decided, you know what, I'd like to win a cage match before I leave town So I picked an artist that I usually tend to win this with And you know what, I do really like this song a lot It's my favorite by her that I think I've heard to date So let's hear it for Kylie's sister, Dani This is Dani Minogue with her latest single, I Begin To Wonder Enjoy, song number two in tonight's cage match Shut up Here we go, here it is
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: And every time I think I'm breaking free, these thoughts return to trouble me, hanging on
You're a sinner but you told me you're a saint Too fast I tripped and lost my way Can't believe what's happened to me, baby Cause everyday is the same day Different faces, no names Places I've never been before And everyday is the same thing Different faces, no names Places I've never been before
[SPEAKER_15]: All this time you led me astray Making love to you, I do
I'm really over you No time to think, I love death
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: All righty, that was song number two in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_04]: Danny Minow with I Begin to Wonder, and I'm wondering what you guys thought of that song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's start with, who's got the mic?
[SPEAKER_04]: Puppy, what did you think of that?
[SPEAKER_24]: It really does sound like one of her sister's songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, besides the fact that it was really boring, it was really boring.
[SPEAKER_24]: So yeah, a five.
[SPEAKER_04]: Five.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've heard that song before.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty repetitive.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's a 7.
[SPEAKER_04]: It gets a 7.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aaron.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aaron gives it half a lung.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lanky style then.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, of course I've heard that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Every time I'm driving in the car with you.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's not a bad song.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think it's pretty poppy, like most of Danny Minow's stuff, but
[SPEAKER_23]: Personally, I have to say I put the needle on it a lot better.
[SPEAKER_23]: A lot better.
[SPEAKER_23]: So I'll give that a 7.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, um... Jonas, your thoughts on that one?
[SPEAKER_13]: I begin to wonder why I'm gonna give this a 7 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, I just noticed your hat says you're fired.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that an apprentice hat or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's so funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now it's Aaron's turn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, well, it was not that great, I'm sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was kind of boring to the point where I took my testicle, put on my headphones, and started listening to music, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, on a scale of 1 to 10?
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably like 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: 4, alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was an easygoing, like, club song.
[SPEAKER_03]: I give it like a 7.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I give it a 9, because it made me very gay, as in happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I like that song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, song number 3 tonight is Jamie's Pick, and Jamie, you want to introduce your song?
[SPEAKER_04]: Where is she?
[SPEAKER_04]: There she is, here she comes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was on the administrative sound compilation, and it was by the... By the, what is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Lost Brothers.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Lost Brothers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the song because the song was in The Lost Boys, which is like one of my all-time ever favorite movies.
[SPEAKER_07]: And actually, it's actually like real samples.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not like somebody covering it, so it's very well done.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I will never, ever, hardly ever say that any, you know, song that I like that much is well done.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, then judge for yourself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you love the 80s, you'll love this.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Lost Brothers, Cry Little Sister.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie's pick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enjoy.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, quiet in the studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was song number three in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Lost Brothers with Cry Little Sister.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry about the ending there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It starts to fade into another track because I'm one of those nonstop dance compilations, so you have to disregard the last 20 seconds of that track.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, that was Cry Little Sister.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what everybody here thought of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course it's nowhere near as good as the original song because I can listen to the original on repeat, endless for days and years and months and everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: I give that one a 9.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's well done.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would have liked for them to do a longer one that actually had the lyrics in it, you know, but that one was still pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's enough to get that little bit of nostalgia pulled up in me and think of, who was it, Jason Patrick with those shades and that hair and Kiefer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Young.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, uh, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fucking cut myself on a wire.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, um, that was okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, I'd give it a seven as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, LankyStyle.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's a standard club song, you know, so I'd give it a seven.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, who else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Puppy.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can get over to Puppy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know, I wasn't really paying attention to the song, so I was drinking some pineapple soda.
[SPEAKER_04]: You make Kiefer Sutherland cry.
[SPEAKER_24]: Kiefer Sutherland was awesome in 24, and I loved that show, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But he was also in Lost Boys.
[SPEAKER_24]: What?
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_24]: I haven't, uh, they've had the, the box office season 2's been out for a while.
[SPEAKER_24]: But, oh yeah, oh yeah, the song, um.
[SPEAKER_24]: It didn't really catch much of my attention anyways.
[SPEAKER_24]: It seemed kind of mellow.
[SPEAKER_24]: Just because I don't feel like favoring one song over the other, I'll give this one a 5.2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Erin, VHG.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nah, it wasn't anything special.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'd be something I would listen to if I were driving, per se, but beyond that, I wouldn't really listen to it otherwise, so I'd give it a 6.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jonas.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll give it a 7.
[SPEAKER_13]: Same reasons.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of have to agree with Jamie that it's just not as good as the original, but I honestly wouldn't even put it in the same ballpark.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just the original is so great, that one doesn't have the lyrics.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get the point about it's kind of, it makes you think, when I hear that song, I think about how I want to hear the original.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's basically how it goes for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I give the original a 10 and I give that a 6.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's a clip of those three songs you can vote for one more time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number one tonight, BT, Kimo Sabe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number two tonight, Danny Minow, I Begin to Wonder.
[SPEAKER_04]: And song number three tonight, Lost Brothers, Cry Little Sister.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, now you can start placing your vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you're undecided, we'll try this out tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to allow a listener to come through on the Skype line and try to get people to vote for the one they think ought to win.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if anybody will bite on this, but as long as we have this new feature, we'll try it out and see if anyone wants to persuade people that they need to vote for a particular song.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can place vote now.
[SPEAKER_04]: NightRiders NightRiders NightRiders
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, your mic's not on over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your mic's not on.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, much better.
[SPEAKER_07]: People in Renfair garb on a motorcycle.
[SPEAKER_07]: This has got to be the biggest piece of crap I've ever looked at.
[SPEAKER_03]: This movie, okay, this movie has a scene where this guy's just driving down the middle of this free, uh, middle of this highway going, he's all, ahhh, ahhh, they're going down the highway, ahhh, they show like out in the distance or something, ahhh, all of a sudden, vroom, gets hit by like a semi-truck.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want them to do a new Knight Rider series, without David Hasselhoff.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: David Hasselhoff is loved in Germany.
[SPEAKER_03]: He owns the rights for Knight Rider.
[SPEAKER_03]: He bought them, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I guess that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody's going to call through on the skyline.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're a bunch of pussies.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: People suck for not calling the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll have chances later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody liked any of those songs, I guess, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are getting some votes, so we'll tally those up during the next break and let you know who won.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the meantime, let's go back and talk about some new DDR news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, this just came up today, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is interesting, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alloy Magazine is having a DDR sweepstakes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alloy Magazine, by the way, is one of those, like, girly magazines, like, Seventeen, and Cosmo, yeah, VHG's like, oh god, in fact, if we, if we go to, prepare to be really sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's cause, um, we, we, like, my sister and I used to have a subscription to one of those girly magazines, and every once in a while they send you, like, free subscriptions to other, or send you a free trial issue of another magazine, and one of them was Alloy.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I was like,
[SPEAKER_06]: Here are the top stories right now on Alloy.com Which fairy tale fox is dreamier, Chad Michael Murray and Hugh Dancy duke it out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're these dream kids, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it says, hey, get your movie on this weekend.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get your movie on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And right on the front page there, there's gossip about Colin Farrell and where Will Smith changed their naughty ways.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about who cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, well, this is why we care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Alloy.com is right now having a You Got Served Take It to the Streets contest.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: And you guys are saying, what the fuck does this have to do with DDR?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you win the grand prize, you win a PlayStation 2, a Dance Dance Revolution prize package with two dance pads and the game, a Vega 32-inch TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that's the reason to win right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want it for the Vega for 2DX.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the copy of the new Take It to the Streets DVD.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, and five first place winners get a copy of the Take It to the Streets DVD and DDR Max 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Game, so if you still don't have DDR Max 2, you can try and win it here on Alloy.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just look in between the Who's Dreamier polls.
[SPEAKER_24]: If it weren't for the fact that they had to include the movie You Got Served anywhere in this contest, it'd be worth entering.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take It to the Streets is where they show the choreography, it's like Darren's Dance Cruise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I own both of those, sadly enough.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's depressing, but hold on, I'm confused.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, it's You Got Served, Take It to the Streets,
[SPEAKER_23]: It's not going to buy you, or is it?
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_23]: She's talking about the Knight Riders movie, whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyway, so, is it a DDR tournament or a freestyle dance?
It's a contest.
[SPEAKER_23]: What kind of contest is this?
[SPEAKER_23]: Give me some information.
[SPEAKER_23]: Are people really dancing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, how do you enter the You Got Served contest?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, what is it doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, is it a sweepstakes?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, this is a sweepstakes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not like a tournament or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a sweepstakes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: All you do, basically... Oh my god, I'll enter it, because I want the TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you enter now?
[SPEAKER_04]: You just... You give them your information.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You give them your mailing address and stuff, so they'll probably send you copies of their crappy magazine, and you have a chance to win a Wega.
[SPEAKER_04]: What a deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do I get to tell them how I feel about the movie you got served?
[SPEAKER_23]: If you want.
[SPEAKER_23]: Because I got some things to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, everyone got served, but we got served... Yeah, a big pile of crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you going to serve you got served?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll serve chicken with a side of vegetables.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dancing movies are really just cheesy all together.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, who remembers Lombada?
[SPEAKER_04]: Save the Rainforest.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: Break-In was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Break-In 2, Electric Boogaloo.
[SPEAKER_23]: How about the sound of music?
[SPEAKER_23]: That was pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_23]: Those dances they did, whoa, that was off the chains.
[SPEAKER_03]: For a shizzle.
[SPEAKER_03]: The, uh, do not take us away to concentration camps dance.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was, that, that dance was just, like, awesome.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was moved.
[SPEAKER_23]: In my pants.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: You got served, Hitler.
[SPEAKER_07]: That, you know what, that was just, you were right, that was moving, as in bowel movement.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, this whole... Okay, I want to change the topic for a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: This whole, like, You Got Served contest being on Alloy.com kind of got me thinking earlier today.
[SPEAKER_04]: It reminded me of a post from LiveJournal, one of my buddies LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to embarrass them on the air because they might be listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: But somebody was asking me in their LiveJournal today because they're having problems where they're not gay, but they're getting a lot of guys hitting on them because they've got, like, that... They've got that metrosexual thing going on, so, like, people assume the guy's gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he's like...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I'm a DDR player.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does that make me gay?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that kind of just had me thinking about this stigma that DDR has with, like, the fact that if you're playing DDR, then you're either metrosexual or you're all the way gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you play DDR, you gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can somebody please explain that to me?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't totally see... I've seen some real...
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, guys I would not consider gay at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, they're not really gay or straight, they're just ugly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I've seen them playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, well, wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: G-Dog plays DDR, doesn't he?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's our new joke for the season.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think that one of the reasons why people, you know, like... What's the word I'm looking for?
[SPEAKER_23]: Like, they...
[SPEAKER_23]: Wait a minute, wait a minute, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: For the longest time, I was the only gay guy playing DDR in this town.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know it, you know it.
[SPEAKER_23]: At the time, yes, you were the- No, you were the only outwardly gay person playing.
[SPEAKER_23]: Everybody else was just a closet homosexual.
[SPEAKER_23]: And that's the word we're using today Of people who
[SPEAKER_23]: who don't get out of their house and don't get with girls and stuff, you know, because gamer geeks don't have lives, so.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, that is true.
[SPEAKER_23]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_23]: You see what I'm saying?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I still find it very funny just how many guys in the Bay Area were playing Patapata.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess, by the way, you guys, I guess we dropped for like half a second.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what happened, but... I don't know what the fuck that was about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, seriously, it was amazing how many guys played Patapata Paradise compared to girls.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because when I played, there were like
[SPEAKER_06]: 3 girls playing, including me, and the rest were all guys.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, that's just that bad thing about there not being as many girl gamers as there are guy gamers.
[SPEAKER_07]: The funny thing was watching how many guys played Deluxe and Oh Sole Mio.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, now that's another reason why people think they're gay, because of that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Doing the Deluxe dance.
[SPEAKER_06]: And those were like the two songs I kind of just didn't touch after a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just like, fuck it, I'm not playing those songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: And for some people, and I know a few people listening actually haven't seen any of these on Patapata, Deluxe has a move where you put one hand out to one side, and the other hand out to the other side, and then you shake your butt.
[SPEAKER_23]: And your hands are kind of in a faggish motion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your hands are held vertically.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, but to be more accurate, you should be pointing it down like this.
[SPEAKER_23]: And then there's Oh Sole Mio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where you do the little teacup-looking dance.
[SPEAKER_23]: The Oso de Mio has... You fan your ass as you walk to the other side.
[SPEAKER_23]: I like to call it the cock block.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, you're swatting something away from your butt because, you know... You have one hand pointed out to the side like you're waving and the other one waving at your ass.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, like, I don't want you, you're ugly.
[SPEAKER_23]: You over there.
[SPEAKER_23]: You're pretty attractive.
[SPEAKER_05]: I grab this one and wave this one away.
[SPEAKER_23]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's Robert Faces.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: But my point is, is that this whole, like, Alloy.com thing, this isn't helping, this image, at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, like, I'm looking at this page going, this is the gayest thing I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, yeah, seriously, I'm just, I'm waiting for, like, Madonna to start playing, and, uh, you know, Liza Minnelli.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even worse, Madonna remixed by Thundercast.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Madonna ends up in the next DDR, you all are going to start sucking cock.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm totally kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: We shouldn't be stereotypical.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you know everybody else is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody outside of this scene is.
[SPEAKER_07]: When have we ever been nice?
[SPEAKER_04]: I just have a question for all the straight guys in the room, which has everybody but me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I have a question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have any of you straight guys, any of you straight guys in the room,
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever not been called gay while playing DDR?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you talking to me?
[SPEAKER_03]: Have I ever been not called gay?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're like, Danny, you're so hetero!
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn you, hetero!
[SPEAKER_04]: Get out of my arcade, you hetero!
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me rephrase the question.
[SPEAKER_04]: You all have been called gay at least once while playing DDR?
[SPEAKER_04]: You've never been called gay?
[SPEAKER_04]: You've been called feminists?
[SPEAKER_04]: You were called feminists?
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you, like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Buy tickets to the Lilith Fair and start blasting Ani DiFranco and... And started joining Greenpeace and shit, what... Okay, for the whole time I've been playing DDR, I was never called gay.
[SPEAKER_13]: But someone was calling me a feminist or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have not, but most of the times I've been, there's been no one around when I've played.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, you remember... Not the Bay Area, where it's a little more accepted.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there's also, keep in mind, keep in mind, there's the Roseville Children, as I like to call them.
[SPEAKER_07]: The people that I have kicked out on a regular basis every time I go?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's that crowd that's more... Well, no, I had a group of, like, uh...
[SPEAKER_23]: Mid to early 20 year olds, a bunch of them.
[SPEAKER_23]: A bunch of them with one girl trying to impress this girl and they were calling me gay and they were like, he grabbed my hand.
[SPEAKER_23]: Who's gay now?
[SPEAKER_23]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_23]: He grabbed my hand and tried to pull me off the machine and I'm like, no, you gay.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, he's like, oh my ass is screaming for some action.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm like, uh, get away.
[SPEAKER_23]: Get away and let me play It's Ready Men.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh god, that was a...
[SPEAKER_13]: Speaking of that, I remember playing Random All with some dude.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's gay, and it ended up being It's Raining Men.
[SPEAKER_13]: He was like... He was grabbing your ass when he was playing?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, he was grabbing my ass.
[SPEAKER_21]: I wasn't sure if it was intentional, but... Hey man, just be flattered.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just nod your head, smile, you know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's like, ah, I don't like this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, effeminate would be the word.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is practically the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: We all know that Jonas was trying to say effeminate, but it was funnier that he said feminists.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I knew he was trying to say effeminate.
[SPEAKER_08]: I play DDR for women everywhere!
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say, I was like, whoa.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm going to get up on this DDR machine and burn my bra!
[SPEAKER_13]: Now if you want to see real gay, just look at the dynamite rave hand plant knee drop routine.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's a different type of gay.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's not gay.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, and if you yell at me, I'm going to take out my bloody tampon and throw it at you.
[SPEAKER_07]: And by the way, gay is not a negative thing, so stop using it like it is.
[SPEAKER_20]: Thank you, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: You people suck ass.
[SPEAKER_20]: Who's gay now?
[SPEAKER_20]: You are the one that is gay.
[SPEAKER_07]: You are the ball lickers.
[SPEAKER_07]: But seriously, for all the people who go, oh, that's so gay, you people are the hemorrhoid on the butt of social progress.
[SPEAKER_04]: I say that's so gay all the time.
[SPEAKER_07]: You say it in relation to things that may be associated with gay things.
[SPEAKER_04]: But see, I feel like I have an authority on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, like I have a wand and I can deem things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can say, this, gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's gay.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, okay, Rob and his immediate gay friends, they constantly say, like, terms that would be used to describe a homosexual male in negative connotations.
[SPEAKER_23]: You fucking faggot!
[SPEAKER_23]: Things like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love you too!
[SPEAKER_23]: See?
[SPEAKER_23]: And that's how we say, you know, hello and stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's like... It's like another...
[SPEAKER_23]: Group of people we know who use another word that is, yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, I'm going away from this topic, but here, have the microphone, faggot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to burn my bra right here on behalf of drag queens everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, you guys want to hear who won tonight's case match?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get to hear.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm very happy this song won.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course you are.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's your song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Danny Manero wins tonight's cage match in a very close vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: So all three songs pretty well represented tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a mercy thing right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the point is that I won.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now I don't have to pick a song for next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: It works out nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: We needed the violin music playing in the background.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm going to Pennsylvania for two weeks in front of my song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my poor heart.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I have a heart disease and I never learned to read!
[SPEAKER_04]: Be quiet.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey Rob, at least you're white, okay?
[SPEAKER_23]: So it's okay for you to go to Pennsylvania.
[SPEAKER_23]: You won't have to be threatened by all the hicks over there.
[SPEAKER_23]: What in the hell does that mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: Excuse me, hicks where?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pennsylvania.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, I hear hick and all of a sudden I'm thinking like, okay, what you saying about... Look, on the outside I may be white, but on the inside... You're a black woman, a repressed black woman.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the inside... Hey girl, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the inside I am blood and guts, just like you.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the outside...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we're getting a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should actually answer the Skype line once in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you want?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, can you hear us?
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, we're already getting prank calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, call her.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is your refrigerator running?
[SPEAKER_04]: You better catch it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Call you there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hey, there you are.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Turn off your BitTorrent!
[SPEAKER_04]: Turn off your BitTorrent!
[SPEAKER_04]: Turn off your, uh... Stop downloading the port!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: You there?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no torrent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_24]: Not much, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I think it's a lot of lag.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I gotta let you go, dude, because you got a lot of lag going on here, so try calling us back a little later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it'll clear up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for the call.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't catch it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see the name on Skype, but the names on Skype are different than the chatroom names, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chuck, I'll call you back later, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said he didn't have any torrents running.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just a bad connection.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently our show dropped earlier, so it might even be us.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: That might have something to do with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might have.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll leave the Skype line open a little bit longer, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody else wants to give it a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's call in and talk about the topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Change the subject?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Back to dick and fart jokes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, no, actually, we can take a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I do want to play this, because I haven't even heard this yet, but apparently, Loki did a new remix last night, and I didn't even know about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, what's up, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us about your newest remix.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was bored, and I saw someone made some stupid remix, and it's not even really a remix that they made.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was like... I know it wasn't Max Remix.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was like, I heard the other day Insertion and Ecstasy, and they sounded the same!
[SPEAKER_03]: So I decided to mix them together.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it sounded like crap, so, but, that got me thinking, I was like, hey, Ecstasy, I haven't used Ecstasy yet, and I was working on something before, and that just wasn't going anywhere, so I plugged Ecstasy in, and played that around, it's okay, my remixes are starting to become average now, and, yes, the DDR song, Ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this is like an average remix now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I worked on it for a couple hours and I was just like, eh.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a mediocre remix.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's mediocre.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's parts that are cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's just like bad transitions in a few spots that I have to... It's really... The song I was working with was hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this is kind of a tribute song to the song that got me into techno in the first place.
[SPEAKER_03]: 14 Hours to Save the Earth by Tomski, so it's a remix between that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Ecstasy, the 14 Hours Club Mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're going to check this out, and then we'll be back, and we'll talk about more stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_04]: For up to the minute Ramadian gaming news, discussion forums, and for access to the chat room, visit our website at orangeloungeradio.com Alright, we're back, Orange Lounge Radio, and that was Tomski vs. D-Complex, remixed by Loki there, Ecstasy, the 14 hours club mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you guys think of that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought it was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got to be honest with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think out of all of your songs, everything you've remixed, I think that is the one I would want to listen to more than anything else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no, I like a lot of his stuff, but I think I could see myself listening to that a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I love Ecstasy to begin with, but I love the last minute and a half of the song with the other song mixed in.
[SPEAKER_23]: I love how it makes you feel good when people touch you.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, wait, wrong ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I seriously... I think that is a better ecstasy remix than the one that was in Max 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, way better.
[SPEAKER_04]: That one on Max 2 sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I cannot believe that Konami isn't calling you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I realize that you're taking commercial songs and fusing them together.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shh!
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't tell him the secret.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I still think even with...
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still think, even your, like, Silent Hill remix you had earlier, where you're kind of remixing it on top of itself and stuff, and with enough public domain samples out there, honestly, because we know in a lot of DDR songs they're using public domain samples.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're public domain, or they're just, they're like sample kits from Acid, I swear to God they are, because I listen to so much techno music and stuff that you're like, wait a second, that's that song.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, one Easy to Dancer song, which is called, like, uh...
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh man, I can't remember the name of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like a long mega mix of like trance stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all commercial songs!
[SPEAKER_03]: No credit to them!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, you completely ripped them off!
[SPEAKER_03]: Great, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: But seriously?
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever that one program is.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Fruity Loose!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not making my song with Fruity Loose!
[SPEAKER_03]: How can they tell?
[SPEAKER_04]: How can they tell what program you're using?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it doesn't sound like MIDI.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what they like.
[SPEAKER_04]: They like MIDI.
[SPEAKER_04]: I honestly think you should just send it in anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if they say no, they say no.
[SPEAKER_04]: But honestly, that is better than half the stuff that was in... Almost all the stuff that was in the Balmati Star Remix Contest last month.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just don't have... Like, that right there is below my standards right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's...
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice, I like the parts in it, but I can't stand non-perfect transitions and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you're just a perfectionist.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you did that in one evening.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I did that in about three hours or a couple hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just sat down, I was listening to this really shitty... It sounded like someone just had two songs playing back-to-back and they just... They didn't even really remix them on top of each other with acid, they just kind of faded one into the other.
[SPEAKER_03]: or faded one in on top of the other one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just didn't sound right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, if somebody is going to reject your song from a remix contest because of the program you used, they are being ignorant.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is so ignorant.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, because you understand that, you know, mash mixes are not real remixes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, but that's because people fucking did Paranoia Cowgirl, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's funny, though, is I'd like them to tell the people that mash mixes aren't real mixes since, oh, wait a second, because I do think Acid, the site that actually produces the Acid 4.0 and stuff like that, guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: They have a whole remix contest section.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually recognized by many artists like BT and David Bowie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I was going to say, David Bowie, wasn't he giving away a car for some mashup contest?
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, no, his, um, yeah, it was not only that, but his, um, the mash mixes were gonna be featured on his CD, so, you know, I guess that's not very important, you know, but hey, go ahead, play with Fruity Loops, because you're better than I am, because you know how to program instruments in MIDI.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: So what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm not programming shit, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not to say that all the Fruity Loops remix stuff sucks, because there is some good stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's really good stuff out there, but there's also bad stuff too.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is really good too, and I think we need to recognize that mash mixes can be good when they're not stupid, basically.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: When they're not mash, insert Bambi song here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody out there uses samples, whether you guys want to recognize that or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know what, it's just, that's the way it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: People, but, you can program your own, like, you know, um... You can, like, remix, you know, you can, like, actually, you know, add, you know, synth on top of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I need to learn.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, once I learn the Fruity Loop stuff, I'll be able to do that much more with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and you should keep working at it, honestly, because, seriously, I think if you were just...
[SPEAKER_04]: If somebody were to give you money, and say, take a week, and take a DDR song, and put in public domain stuff, and original stuff, you would have an awesome DDR song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's the situation, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you were to actually, like, say, Konami went to, I want you to remix this song.
[SPEAKER_03]: What they'll give you is they'll give you, like, this song, all the samples that were in it, and all the arrangements that were in it, like, basically the 8-track, the digital track.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a lot easier to work with raw, you know, tracks than just, you know, everything in a composition, so it's a lot harder to do it that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why, like, when, you know, Punk Knight gave me stuff to remix, it would be an EJ, he'd give me all the samples that he used and the arrangements they had, so you can just go in there, rearrange it, and add your own stuff into it, and it's a lot easier and sounds better.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's, you know, they're not gonna just say, oh, we want you to take something that was on the soundtrack and remix it, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to hear the stuff from the, what was it, the DDROSX
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even know what the hell the... OSC or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I want to hear what their stuff was in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because if it's any good, you know, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's stuff that sucks too, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the thing though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't consider it a remix if you remake the song in Fruity Loops.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you take like synth and just basically remake the song, it sounds the same but it's a little different because you didn't quite get the right samples.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not a remix.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Waving your hand at it too much, going, eh, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was really good, personally.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, Skype line is open if you have a comment on that remix, or comment on anything we've talked about during this show so far, really.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll get around to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to get to the FUs in a little bit, and no, sorry, you will not be able to do your FUs over Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: The segment's too long as it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to not make it any longer.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, uh,
[SPEAKER_04]: Foon Team
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought that was it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dojinshi Sites
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so Food Mix Plus should be coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't really say what's going to be in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably just some additional songs and whatnot, but hey, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, actually, there might be some additional songs and edit steps, because I know they had edit steps on their website, so that'd be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Tourney Mix 5, I have no fucking clue what's going on with that, so let's take a look-see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Last thing I heard, they were in like sway votes or public sway votes or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I have no idea what they're doing, semifinals, finals.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the fuck is a sway vote?
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, okay, semifinals, they just finished that, um, now they're on, um, finals.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see what we can vote on, um, oh, I have to be logged in, fuck that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, um, so, yeah, they're in finals.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have no idea who won, what's going on, but all I know is Kimo Sabe did not make it, and that makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Did that Just Like Naoki song make it in there?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, actually, here's the songs that were considered in the semifinals.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, let's see, we've got Domo Domo Domo, the KCP remix, so... Whatever that is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just Like Naoki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Roppongi Canyon, it looks like it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, Lemmings, I think, and Pear Pear All Stars, One More Lovely...
[SPEAKER_03]: There was Look at the Heaven, Halloween, Speedy Mix, Kick Your A by Archowl Then we have Party for You, Holy Night Mix, Stronger, Yoju, Kokoro no Bushi Niwa, Nari Nari, whatever that is, I don't know Some like crap Konnichiwa, Arigato Another Kick Your A, I think this is semi-finals right here I think this is semi-finals, so Kick Your A
[SPEAKER_03]: One More Lovely, R.E.U.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's kind of sad that it's always a remix of like a Bomani song that, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's always like, I want a super hard song that's like, you know, ooh, it's something like what Money Ruler used to do.
[SPEAKER_13]: Didn't the rules say that it has to be like catapult?
[SPEAKER_03]: Eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're just being such dumbass idiots.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: As far as other stuff, really, that's been slow on all the, like, sites.
[SPEAKER_03]: Haven't really found any new, like, really good sim files or anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've just been playing what I had.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are some really cool tutorials, though, on DDR Mania X, especially stuff to make your skin look more, like, in the groove, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have, like, you know, the little, what was it, the...
[SPEAKER_03]: How well you did, and you know the little graph there, just like in Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have how you can put that in your sim, how to make a combo bar, which is kind of neat, and some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'll really help out your skins.
[SPEAKER_03]: So just look for those, they're really good tutorials.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's pretty much all with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can actually call us, and it's just like a phone call, except it doesn't cost you anything, it doesn't cost me anything, because it's all over our internet connection.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, do give us a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: But do make sure you close your torrents and have the maximum bandwidth possible before calling, because otherwise it messes up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so I guess, since nobody is calling in on the Skype right now, maybe we'll go to another break, then we're going to come back and do the FUs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Jamie, you have a thought?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I just wanted the microphone because it comforts me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why does having the microphone comfort you?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just does!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm happy because I'm in fourth in line to get the Megamix from GTA 3 for Rise FM, which has the song I'm looking for, Neo the One by Slider.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got a call on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're at least trying to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please say something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it us that slides really bad?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes, I am here.
[SPEAKER_04]: You there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Richie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Again?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_09]: I just had to call in again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just want to hug up all the air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody else wants to call in, so we've got you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you still have that torrent going?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I can hear you a little clearer now.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you have a comment on something?
[SPEAKER_09]: I just wanted to say something about remixes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Loki's remixes, I think you should, like, you know, like, submit them to, like, OC Remix or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they're really great, you know, it's like, you know, what he's doing with, you know, it's like, certain, like, songs and just, like, throwing, like, a whole new, like... Hey, Richie, speak a little bit louder so we can hear you, because... Sorry, can you hear me now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I can hear you now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just saying that, yeah, Loki should submit some of his stuff to OC Remix.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it sounds professional, really.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, like, I had one of my teachers at my school listen to some of Loki's remixes, and he was wondering, hey, do you know who this guy is?
[SPEAKER_09]: And I was saying, oh, it's...
[SPEAKER_09]: OC Remix
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you ever consider sending something like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: I would if I didn't use some other commercial songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the thing that's stopping you, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, it's true, it's true.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you thought about it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you hear me better now?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or is my mic still like... I can hear you a little better now.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, let's see, other than that, well, I mean, keep up the good work, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm looking forward to any new remixes you might have.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remix more stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for calling, Richie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, no problem at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: See you guys later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, have you thought about trying to maybe do something with public domain samples?
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm starting to go more that way anyways, because with this song even, I used a lot of those BT public domain samples that I got.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't you do one a while back where you remixed a song with other video game samples or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the kind of thing OC Remix would eat up, if it was video game music mixed with other video game music, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think I did.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only song that's sort of like just a bunch of different songs was that Dynamis one, which was like kind of eh, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty much like, I like the stuff...
[SPEAKER_03]: If I learned how to do, like, DMS files or something like that, you know, that'd be kick-ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, really, I don't have a lot of music theory and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never took the classes, don't know shit about... I mean, I understand, you know, structure of a song and stuff, it just... Didn't they say that Akira Yamaoka couldn't even read music when he started?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could've sworn I read that on some fan site.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's probably... It's like, I just need to have, like... Because I need, like, you know, some of the set stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, scales and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, really, if you listen to a lot of songs, they're the same scales.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the same structure, they're very simple, they just use really elaborate samples, that's all it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I mean, pretty much every single fucking trance song, you always have a four on the floor, and then you have some beat that's going at, you know, 12th notes, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's every single, yeah, it's every single, you know, trance song out there, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried last night to make another Revenge Neo song, and it didn't turn out very well.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was like, I tried, what was it, I was mixing that one, um, Revenge song from, uh,
[SPEAKER_03]: Poppin' Music, it was the one that sounds sort of like Exotic Ethnic, but not.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried mixing it with Exotic Ethnic, and that really sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: It did not sound well at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to get some sample kits and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just kind of weary to do that, because I have 30,000 public domain samples on about
[SPEAKER_03]: 20 CDs or so, 20 plus CDs, and I don't use any of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I use about two.
[SPEAKER_03]: Two out of those.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just have to kind of go through and look at all those samples again, because I had them all ripped to my hard drive and it just took up too much space.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, what we're going to do now, we're going to go to a break, and when we come back, the F use of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to get ranty.
[SPEAKER_04]: The chat room's getting mad at me because I'm calling them all pussies, and they're like,
[SPEAKER_04]: Skype doesn't work out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'll have Aaron call you a pussy instead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or she'll barf up along.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, actually, but some of them, I guess Skype only works on Windows XP, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that messes some people up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And why don't you have Windows XP?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, some people don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, there's Macs, Linux.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people still want to use ME, whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: If you have a Mac, okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: If you have Linux, okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: But if you're using any other kind of form of Windows, why don't you have Windows XP?
[SPEAKER_04]: Challenging somebody on their operating system, though, is such a nerd war.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're just waiting to get lashed at for challenging someone on their operating system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here comes the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here they come.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is, by the way, a certain build where you start off with Windows 3.11, build up through to 2000.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you take, I think, 3.11, upgrade that to NT, upgrade that to 2000.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's supposed to be the most secure way to run Windows.
[SPEAKER_07]: Much more secure than XP.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I know a lot of people who do it that way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway... Everything will still run.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway... Okay, so... And you remember what happened, you know... But I see that we've got a ton of people on our Skype list, so I know that there's more people than just the one calling in, so... It's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're gonna go... You just like saying the word pussy, don't you, Erin?
[SPEAKER_06]: And boobies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was the other word?
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back with the FUs of the week, which you can send over a private message.
[SPEAKER_04]: But please no FUs to Brad for his operating system rant, because I just don't want to go there tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's listen in on an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting.
[SPEAKER_17]: Do you want to be staffed by Hollywood?
[SPEAKER_17]: No!
[SPEAKER_17]: Do we care what people think of us?
[SPEAKER_17]: Do we want people to kiss our ass?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_01]: Extreme Babani Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's us, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are back, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we are, episode number 103.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty soon we'll get to use the other promo again.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, because Pump Up the Volume is doing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: When are you officially moving that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I start school August 16th, but I think I have an orientation the week before, so it's probably going to be either the first or second week in August.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, but this week you can hear Pump Up the Volume what night?
[SPEAKER_07]: Monday!
[SPEAKER_07]: Monday, Sunday.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what happens on Monday night at 7 and 7.30?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I actually have started my pre-show a whole lot earlier now because I usually just get bored.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pre-show's been now starting about 6.45.
[SPEAKER_07]: 6.45 to 7 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then around 7.30 I start the normal show.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's supposed to end at 10.30, but sometimes I just stay bored and keep going.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're basically just a radio whore.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm such a whore.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what do you do on that show?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's supposedly a request show, but nobody ever requests anything anymore except Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Angel does sometimes when she's there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But...
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you hang out in our chat room, like many of you are right now, you can request or spend any song that you want to listen to.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I've got access now to more music, so my library will just be growing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, in fact, I've been trying to start a segment on my show that's DarkSakura email, much in the vein of StrongBad email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where I answer your email.
[SPEAKER_13]: Will you talk with a voice like this?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to be doing the... Dear DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to be talking in the strong bad voice.
[SPEAKER_07]: As you take some stuff, add some more stuff, and answer the email.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to be doing that, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, just send me a private message on our forums.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hint, hint, hint.
[SPEAKER_07]: at orangechallengeradio.com or shoot me an email to darksakura at gmail.com because you can send it right to me or you can send it to our other email at orangechallengeradio at yahoo.com
[SPEAKER_07]: and I prefer having MP3s to OGGs, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can use them, but I can't play them on the station.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tuesday nights is Diversion, the Orange Launch Radio remix show.
[SPEAKER_04]: which will not be live for the next couple weeks because I'm not going to be in town.
[SPEAKER_04]: But do enjoy the great music on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll make sure to try and bump up the playlist a little bit before I leave town.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's some really good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some more people have been tuning in lately and just hearing what a great show that is.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you like Loki's remixes, there's tons of very talented people just like them out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remixing Mamani songs and we like to give all those songs a place to be heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Diversion is that place.
[SPEAKER_04]: 7 o'clock Tuesday nights here on the station.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wednesday nights are empty right now but I hope to have an announcement about Vanilla Sky when I get back from my trip.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Lanky Style?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's just picking his nose, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's picking his nose.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember, you can pick your friends, you can pick your nose, but if you pick your friend's nose, you're a big, gross, paraplegic, and they need their nose picked.
[SPEAKER_02]: God damn it, I'm doing them a favor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you need to, this is what tweezers are for, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: More interesting things.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't care about the handicapped.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just want to make that clear.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have a fetish for picking the nose of paraplegics.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: When did this show derail that quickly?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_08]: When?
[SPEAKER_08]: How about episode two when I wasn't here?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about on that Bart train?
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, there's some actual other Bomani news going on this week, and it's Bomani news that doesn't involve California.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do we have hot Bomani action?
[SPEAKER_04]: California!
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Lowe's.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lowe's is a big theater chain.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if they have any Lowe's here in California.
[SPEAKER_04]: California!
[SPEAKER_07]: I know what Lowe's is.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not Lowe's Hardware Store, it's Lowe's Theater Chain.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are hosting a Ultimate Film Fan Contest, and for whatever reason, being an Ultimate Film Fan involves lots of Sony PlayStation 2 video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they will be having these local events going on where you can play Karaoke Revolution Vol.
[SPEAKER_04]: 2 and, get this, DDR Extreme before it comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before it comes out, you'll be able to play DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_04]: And these are all happening on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going from Texas to Michigan to Jersey to New York, Massachusetts, Washington, that's about the closest it's going to get to here, Ohio, New York, Maryland, and Illinois.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is running from July through September.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you live in one of those areas, you want to get a jump on Extreme and you want to check it out and see what it's all about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: But Mel B wants me to pass this along.
[SPEAKER_04]: There will be a Konami booth at Comic-Con in San Diego this week, Thursday through Sunday.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the booth will be the most recent demos of DDR Extreme and Ultramix 2 for PS2 and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what do you think that's going to mean we're going to have next week?
[SPEAKER_04]: New song list!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, new song list.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you want to check out what some of the new songs on these demos are going to be,
[SPEAKER_04]: Thursday through Sunday, Comic Con, San Diego Konami will also be doing contests and giveaways So California doesn't miss out completely You know, I wonder though, why do people always leave out my home state with this?
[SPEAKER_07]: We need DDR contests in Alabama We do?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes People in the South play DDR too Skype line's open if you have a comment
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, we're going to leave out the Wayne's World jokes.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we'll get into the FUs here a little bit, but I still am trying to figure out why a movie theater would just randomly have DDR, but then I kind of think back to the Metreon, how they have the DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: What is Brad saying over there?
[SPEAKER_07]: We were making a joke about people calling.
[SPEAKER_07]: Someone was breaking into the Blondie song, and I was doing the whole sex line thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pick up the phone!
[SPEAKER_04]: Does that only air in this area?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or is that a nationwide commercial?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's nationwide.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's been on TV forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's always on during Jerry Springer.
[SPEAKER_23]: Pick up the phone!
[SPEAKER_23]: I love when the Sci-Fi Channel used to do Saturday Night Anime, and then they changed it to Saturday Morning Anime.
[SPEAKER_23]: And they always used to play those commercials in the commercial breaks.
[SPEAKER_23]: So they got Anime, which is considered cartoons over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we got a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got a call.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, don't interrupt me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I finish?
[SPEAKER_04]: They can hold.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I'm finished.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got a caller.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope I'm not interrupting.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello again, Sky.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's me, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Got a comment?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, just the random stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, in case you have any problems pronouncing Japanese titles or Japanese names, you know, don't hesitate to call me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which, by the way... You could ask me, but they never do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but you see, you're never here.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_23]: Excuse you!
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wanted to get the glare.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think it's much funnier to hear Rob destroy the Japanese language.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, isn't it funnier to hear me stumble through it, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's why Jamie doesn't bother to step in and correct me, because it's so much funnier when I fuck it up.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least you're finally saying Sakura right, sort of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, you can shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Sakura says... Wait a minute, actually... Wait a minute, hold on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been studying Japanese since I was nine years old, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: All I can say is my accent is already 95% accurate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you actually have Japanese in your blood, or have you just been otaku since birth?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, actually, I learned it by accident.
[SPEAKER_10]: How'd that work?
[SPEAKER_10]: Back in the Philippines, where I was actually born, there were a few channels, and then one of them is a Japanese learning show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Learn how to speak Japanese.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's where I got my accent and my grammar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you want to comment on besides your offer to correct me when I screw up, which is quite often?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it's not really a screw up.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just, you know, if you're having fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, Rob, he's so funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's so white.
Yes, he is.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello out there.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: But you might know me in the online world as Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: On June 23rd at 7pm Pacific Time, join DarkSakura and I for the Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, that's actually grammatically incorrect because you don't use and I, it would be and me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Here come the grammar police.
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, I'm double busted tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am like, because it's used as an object and not as a subject.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was two years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give me a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was when I was a radio amateur.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did Kansai... Oh, dude, Kansai Ben is like so hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just call me Ski.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, just call me Ski.
[SPEAKER_04]: That pisses me off enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't piss me off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Arigatou
[SPEAKER_07]: Arigato.
[SPEAKER_05]: You say arigato like we say arigato.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sonny Chiba is the man.
[SPEAKER_22]: What did he say?
[SPEAKER_22]: I forget.
[SPEAKER_22]: He's like... What did he say after that?
[SPEAKER_22]: Very good!
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: I think what we need to do is go into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_08]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_08]: My favorite part!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, remember, we only have a half hour show left, so let's try to keep this a relatively good length here.
[SPEAKER_04]: So here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go, we're going to start it off.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, are you ready?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm ready to be ranty.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, you ready to go?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, you can... Where's the ferret?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, what... Ow.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do we do during the F-U's of the week?
[SPEAKER_08]: We throw paper towels at Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: I already did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, I need that ferret.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't wipe it on your... F you to wiping the ferret on your ass, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Throw it at Rob now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, eh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Give me that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: You get that ferret thrown at your head.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob gets a ferret thrown at his head.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to all you people for distracting me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, ferrets.
[SPEAKER_07]: Those people Anyway, F you to distracting me Because I've been so easily distracted all day And F you to being fatigued all damn day I'm trying to go out and spend a day with my fiance You know, spending money, which I consider highly romantic Because money is the way to win my heart Sex has nothing to do with it, it's money
[SPEAKER_07]: No, money is a meme.
[SPEAKER_07]: And sex is just the stuff that happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sex is what you get when you give me money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, are you saying that I am a whore?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't say anything, you just did.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then Rob's the whore, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's the story of my life, anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm really not that shallow, by the way, but still.
[SPEAKER_07]: We were going out, we were going laser disc hunting today, because I found the Beauty and the Beast Work in Progress laser disc, which goes for like a hundred something dollars on eBay, for ten bucks last night.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I was going back to buy more laser discs, and I
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I was getting so tired, and Dan's like, let's go to Tower Books, so I can sit in this chair and read a book about Pac-Man merchandise for an hour, while his poor, poor, poor suffering fiance has to go to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's no public bathroom at Tower Books.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm here, okay Dan, hurry up, okay Dan, hurry up, okay Dan, hurry up, okay Dan, hurry up, and finally I'm like, get your ass out of the chair!
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to go to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: It wasn't really like that, but we... Yeah, it was the Pulte emergency.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was about to do the dance.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, another FU goes toward people who... SUV drivers in general.
[SPEAKER_07]: There are, I have to say, a few people out there who know how to responsibly drive their vehicle and then there's everybody else who ruins it for the few who do.
[SPEAKER_07]: You people do not need to be driving a vehicle that big, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why I want my freakin' rebuilt Humvee with an assault rifle built onto it so I can gun your asses down and drive over you in my armored vehicle and not have you all in my way.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I will stay in my lane
[SPEAKER_07]: and abide by the speed limit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: And my gun will be on a torrent, yeah?
[SPEAKER_07]: So I can get the people who are trying to get behind me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aw, you tailgate my ass, you're dead too.
[SPEAKER_07]: The road, okay, I just need my own road, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: I need the Jetson's car so that I don't have to deal with traffic.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need my own jet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob, I want a jet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe that's why I want a jet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll make a note of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another F you goes toward my schedule for being so damn busy this week that I haven't been able to get to the gym as much as I wanted to.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was supposed to go running today.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was up so late last night.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another F you goes to insomnia because I have it really bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another F you goes toward money for not having much of it, distance for it existing, and
[SPEAKER_07]: Not being able to go where I want to go, or see who I want to see, or do what I want to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another F you goes toward the general attitude in this state, because I'm getting really sick of it, and I really, really need to just get back to Alabama for a week so that I can be around people who are relatively polite and have good manners, at least to your face.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just, it's just been kind of a, and it's going to be a crap, yeah, another FU to peak season at my job.
[SPEAKER_07]: All of you people who are trying to go to school, and I guess that's including me, you know, try calling your financial aid office instead of calling me first.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even though they probably don't know what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and a big FU goes to ARC's financial aid office.
[SPEAKER_07]: Learn the freaking student aid process and tell it to other people.
[SPEAKER_07]: If one of you is going to say something to somebody, make sure all of you are saying the same thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Instead of one person saying thing A, one person saying thing B, just stay on the right page.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stay on the same page.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least be consistent with your information.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's really, I guess, about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've gotten the angst out.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're currently...
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the ferret likes it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I bet Rob doesn't know what I just said.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, because I was saying goodbye to Brad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, bye Brad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Meanwhile, Loki's cock is just stiff and erect.
[SPEAKER_04]: Half hour show, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Half hour left in the show, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I'm done?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just said I was done and you were ignoring me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, F you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, uh, Logie's turn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I forgot about that song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any... Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, anyways, um, fuck you too, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: to RadioShack because like if the computers break down you start to panic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aren't you supposed to be there to know how to fix things?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I thought that's what RadioShack was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just fix things, sell me satellite dishes and cell phones.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and batteries.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, so you suck and F you to stupid SUV drivers because you suck and you can't drive your SUV.
[SPEAKER_03]: You think it's like a race car or like a highly maneuverable car or...
[SPEAKER_03]: A car that will just, you know, let go of the wheel and it will drive in the lane.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's not a compact car.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, it's no, not a, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: It just sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't drive an SUV if you don't have kids or if you're driving alone.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should have another car for driving when you're alone.
[SPEAKER_03]: It should be a one person car.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not this car that can hold 50 people.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't see bus drivers driving buses around aimlessly without anyone in there and parking in compact spaces.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do not expect you to be doing the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: So please, do not park your SUVs in compact spaces.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like you.
[SPEAKER_03]: and those stupid fuckers that park on the line.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just because your tire's on the line does not count.
[SPEAKER_03]: It needs to be in the line.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I can't open my door when you're on the line and the person next to me is on the line.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or over the line because your SUV's too big and you're parking in a compact space.
[SPEAKER_20]: God, you people are so stupid.
[SPEAKER_20]: You won't walk the extra few feet because, oh my god, all that SUV driving has gotten me tired and if I have to stand this heat for any longer, I'm gonna die!
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, fuck you to stupid kids with laser pointers in movie theaters.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're not funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: And no, you cannot destroy the robots with laser pointers.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just does not work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, fuck you to stupid previews before movies, because, you know, that's just delaying my movie-watching time, and I really don't want to see another preview for The Manchurian Candidate.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will not see that movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a remake.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I wanted to see the movie, I'd watch the original.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not with Denzel Washington.
[SPEAKER_03]: And finally, finally, finally, um, fuck you to the goddamn people at Roundtable, because I go there to get a lunch buffet, and they have to be jackasses and go, I don't want to make pizzas for the buffet!
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, don't offer a buffet if you don't want to make pizzas for the buffet!
[SPEAKER_03]: And then you think you're so smart, I'm gonna make a vegetarian pizza!
[SPEAKER_03]: Eh, I'm cool!
[SPEAKER_03]: So I had to wait, you know, forever for them to make goddamn pizzas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just pop in a couple pepperonis.
[SPEAKER_03]: They take less than a few seconds to make, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: And stop whining.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I swear to God, it's not like, you know, you're gonna be there forever.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm done.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, my FU goes to stress.
[SPEAKER_04]: especially before this trip I have to take by myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a hard time going to the bathroom by myself, let alone having to travel back to the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't give me a funny look when I say that, Aaron.
[SPEAKER_04]: Girls go to the bathroom together all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know...
[SPEAKER_04]: I just, I don't, I'm really distressed about the trip, and yeah, but, you know, what can you do?
[SPEAKER_04]: And F you to the fact that I'm going to miss all the good TV shows while I'm gone, because I do watch all my TV through BitTorrent, and I'm not going to be able to do that while I'm out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And F you to the fact that I wasn't able to get a laptop for my trip, so I will have absolutely nothing to do at night, except masturbate.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's alright, because I'm going to get a lot of that done, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: But Aaron, I can safely say I won't be thinking of you when I do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So allow me to be the first CDR male to tell you that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will not be thinking of you when I masturbate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, sometimes I wish Loki was my Doug 24-7.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll be thinking of that comment right there, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a good thing you didn't hear it, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I had other FUs, but I forget what they were, so I guess we'll just move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's hear from other folks in our studio right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll start it off with ViolentHyperGirl.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, F you to the stupid fanboys who publicly post on forums saying they want to have sex with me.
[SPEAKER_06]: PLEASE!
[SPEAKER_06]: KEEP IT TO YOURSELF!
[SPEAKER_06]: IT'S A FUCKING PUBLIC FORUM!
[SPEAKER_06]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_13]: Desperate people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, if you want sex that badly, go find a whore!
[SPEAKER_06]: Or go masturbate or something!
[SPEAKER_06]: And not to my routine!
[SPEAKER_06]: My CBDL routine does not constitute as porn or masturbation fodder.
[SPEAKER_06]: It should actually be illegal because I was under 18 at the time.
Pedophiles!
[SPEAKER_06]: Second F you goes to Audio Taco at AX.
[SPEAKER_06]: You smell.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please shower.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't kill you to take like 10 minutes out of the day to shower, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why people go to cons, is to not shower.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're talking about the lobby boys, the ones who sleep in the lobby, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or even the people with hotel rooms, I mean like...
[SPEAKER_06]: For those who didn't hear Jamie's comment, she said, it's Anime Expo, what are they going to miss?
[SPEAKER_06]: The sucking?
[SPEAKER_06]: And honestly, you have no chance with any girl, Japanese or Asian or white.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't fucking shower.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, you know, you might raise your chances just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just a little fucking bit.
[SPEAKER_20]: Now, now, last fan of Akana, I saw boob.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was that from?
[SPEAKER_13]: Real boob, not fake boob, not drawn boob, real boob.
[SPEAKER_13]: My boob.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was that from the fat Mai that was walking around?
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, please, don't suffocate us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another SU goes out to physics, for obvious reasons.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have to really state why.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, just physics.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another SU goes out to being sick, but I honestly kind of don't care because I was helping out a friend who was sick.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I knew what I was putting myself out in front of, so I kind of accepted the responsibility for getting myself picked.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, um, let's see, I can't really think of anything else other than the fanboy issue, which I could go off on for hours and hours at a time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but, uh, yeah, I think we can move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, Jonas.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hold on, let me touch the car first.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, I'm sorry about that, I'm sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, the first F he goes to in Zuma of 469 for almost screwing my tournament up in June 25th and the 26th.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who the hell do you think you are trying to control my tournament?
[SPEAKER_13]: Who the hell do you think you are saying, ooh, the pet detailer doesn't work?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, get used to the fucking pads.
[SPEAKER_13]: These are the best damn pads out there in Sacramento, in case you haven't been there, Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: And quit your whining about for one and a half hours you delayed the whole tournament.
[SPEAKER_13]: Everyone was bitching at me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those pads are so squeaky clean that I can see Aaron's image in them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, Jonas.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, the next interview goes to this bitch at work, well not, well it says some bitch customer, who's saying, OI!
[SPEAKER_13]: You're a freakin', I'm a good woman and you're just a fuckin' worker just getting minimum wage.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who the fuck do you think you are calling me a low-class person?
[SPEAKER_13]: First of all, second of all, we kicked everybody out of the track because, this is during my previous island as I worked there, this,
[SPEAKER_13]: First of all, your kids can't drive for shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: This has no bumping.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you're accusing my ass trying to get me fired?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I'm gonna kick your ass if I have the chance.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have a whip on my car, all spiked up in braids.
[SPEAKER_13]: Does it have braids, Aaron?
[SPEAKER_13]: They could, eh?
[SPEAKER_13]: How long is the whip?
[SPEAKER_13]: Damn!
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, and I'll give another F you guys to someone who spiked up my freakin' strawberry daiquiri drink.
[SPEAKER_13]: You put a hell of vodka in it!
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I mean, there's no strawberry daiquiri in it, they put like some nasty type of vodka in it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know it's kind of, it's not the Smirnoff version, it's like some other vodka.
[SPEAKER_13]: I accidentally spit that out in front of my parents and stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: while eating a delicate dinner during the cruise and I see to my skin because when one side is hella dark and the other is hella white no matter how many times I go to the pool it still remains the same thing oh really?
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, I'm kind of heated up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, FU for time being wasted for my other FUs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll continue the FUs next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Puppy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said two weeks, two weeks, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, don't forget next week won't be here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Puppy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, since time is short, I'll make this quick.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck school, fuck my car, fuck funerals, fuck the funeral across the street, fuck the number zero when it's alone, and, um,
[SPEAKER_24]: Suck the mold, and fuck my refrigerator.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get to our chatroom FUs then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Started off with Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Knight says, let me start with a big FU, and that's for my car to go kerplunk on me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ended up having to catch a ride to work for the weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another for being a broke-ass mofo, and finally work, that is all.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Angel says, F you to Skype for freezing while trying to run on my system.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to QRO for giving me sprite errors and other continuous errors spontaneously while I'm trying to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to feeling like I'm fully packed but then thinking I'm still going to forget something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meh, I guess I'm done.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I can sympathize with thinking you're packed when you're not because I'm having that same problem right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Vid Palace says, F you to this horrible retainer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't say anything coherently when I have it on.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Too bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had braces.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have the retainer now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Deal with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We all had to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Screw it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I stopped wearing my retainer after three months.
[SPEAKER_04]: And look at me now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got all three of my teeth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Flerone says, F you to the official PS2 headset.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got Karaoke Revolution this weekend and the headphones are crappy.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Xbox headset is actually decently sturdy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually thought the KR one was a little better, but, you know, potato potato.
[SPEAKER_04]: VXJasonXV says, my one and only FU.
[SPEAKER_04]: FU to people who show up almost an hour after the tournament was scheduled to start and starting about one and a quarter hours late.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and Rychan is passing one along too.
[SPEAKER_04]: FU to other girls who repeatedly try to hang all over your boyfriend.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even more so when it's right in front of you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then that's when, you know, you just take your hand and ask them what the five fingers said to the face
[SPEAKER_04]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: EvilNowQ2DX says, F you to Noria for singing Sylvia Drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: That song's been in my head for the past four days.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and one F you to commercials before movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to the 20.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck the 20.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got 20 for you right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: John Field says, I guess my only FU is that connection was too short.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and FU to claiming that Mega Man Anniversary Collection has remixed music when all it's using are the music tracks from Power Fighters slash Battles.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_24]: It does have remixed music.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was the overclocked one.
[SPEAKER_24]: There was a bunch of remixes.
[SPEAKER_24]: If you change it to Navi mode, it's all remixed music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's all the FUs right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some folks wanted to comment on some convention things you were talking about, Aaron.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm going to open the Skype line back up since we only have a few minutes left in the show anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe some folks have comments on who knows what else.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're just going to kind of finish up the show with a little bit of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I think there was some Anime Expo commentaries.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody wanted to add.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've only ever been to like one anime convention in my entire life.
[SPEAKER_24]: Ditto.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it wasn't Anime Expo, it was a little one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Richie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Richie wants to... Richie's back on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: He wants to talk to us about an Anime Expo story I think that Aaron brought up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what's up, Richie?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, nothing much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just a couple of horror stories from AnimeCon this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um... Well, yeah, just... Okay, what do you want to tell us about?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, buddy, hey, buddy, you're skipping up a little bit there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop your torrents and stop your Winamp for a second.
[SPEAKER_04]: See if that helps.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what the hell's wrong with my connection.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can hear you now.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I just want to say that, yeah, a lot of the guys there didn't know what the hell the concept of a shower meant, so it stinks like high heaven over there.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least my roommates still were like... Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: ...every day and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And other than that, well, other than, you know, like, stinky idiots, you get drunken idiots, too, who ruin everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if you heard about this, but, uh, on Saturday night, Sunday morning, we had to close down the convention center, because, uh... I was there, that, I was there.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was the toilet, didn't you remember what happened, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, somebody, somebody, what happened that night, for people who don't know, um, in the arcade, in, uh, the Fanime 2004 convention, somebody decided to, like, blow up the toilet.
[SPEAKER_06]: and ended up flooding that whole second floor of the convention center so they had to close the arcade down which is like almost the only thing to do in the middle of the night save for like the video rooms yeah and uh if I can add to that I was staffing the arcade during that shift so like they had me pull they had me pull con security you remember you remember how tired I looked Erin yeah they took all the arcade um workers and uh what they did was that they made them work security to make sure nobody went into the upper area
[SPEAKER_09]: and you saw how tired I was.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I was up listening to Nami Tamaki for like how many hours straight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, actually at Fatime too, they played the same Nami Tamaki CD for all four days.
[SPEAKER_09]: All four days.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was hell.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I was starting to sing along to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was crazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Other than that though...
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, and if I could put in a plug for another con that's coming up, Chinatown Anime Fair in San Francisco is coming up September 11th and 12th.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ten bucks to be registered.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go over to JTAF.com to pre-reg.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Check out the site.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got a few guests of honor you might want to check out.
[SPEAKER_09]: And hope to see you all there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got to get going, Richie, but thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, no problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll see you guys later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care, bud.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so that's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got to start wrapping up the show here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts, starting off with Jonas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Erin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well, the thing, oh, I just wanted to add one thing that really, really sucked about Anime Expo was that I guess since the con's been held there for so long,
[SPEAKER_06]: They well knew about the BO, so what they did was they turned the AC on really, really high.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you walked through the convention center at night, it was at least 65 degrees in there, if not lower.
[SPEAKER_24]: No sweat, no BO.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final thought from Puppy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, Loki's cock really is big, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Jonas, do or die, final thought.
[SPEAKER_13]: It tastes very good, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm taking that cock back to work and I'm leaving it there.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought is listen to the Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need people to whore up our listening hours because our ratings have been dropping and that makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, final thought?
[SPEAKER_07]: Tastes great, less filling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last word of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Erin really wants it, so why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: One word that sums it all up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Erin, what is tonight's... Well, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got to make sure our outro is ready to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Erin, what is tonight's final word?
[SPEAKER_08]: Movies!
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you'd like to leave us a comment, send us an email at orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have not had sex in almost two years.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I think once you hit two years, you automatically get your virginity back.
[SPEAKER_19]: You get to start over.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I'm about to.
[SPEAKER_19]: What is wrong with me?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm just going to have to trick somebody into doing it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Use trickery.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to have to cover with leaves and hope somebody falls in.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's going to be the only way!
[SPEAKER_19]: I think I would be really hot if I didn't talk.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's my problem.
[SPEAKER_19]: I just have a big mouth and I just say the wrong things.
[SPEAKER_19]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Like, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_19]: I try.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have one pickup line, which never works.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is what I do.
[SPEAKER_19]: If I'm at a club and I see a guy that I like, I'll smile.
[SPEAKER_19]: And if he smiles back, I feel comfortable.
[SPEAKER_19]: And when I feel really comfortable, I'll walk over and I'll say, Stick it in!
[SPEAKER_19]: So, as you know by now, I'm Korean.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't have a store or anything.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, not anymore.
[SPEAKER_19]: I look very Korean.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have very typically Korean features.
[SPEAKER_19]: I look like one of those girls that you would see in a Korean grocery store on a calendar.
[SPEAKER_19]: Holding a box of soy milk.
[SPEAKER_17]: Drink by the soy.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's good for you.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have a Korean name.
[SPEAKER_19]: My Korean name is Moran, which is a pretty name, but you have to understand I've heard my mother scream it from across the hills.
[SPEAKER_19]: Moran!
[SPEAKER_19]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sure you can relate.
[SPEAKER_19]: When I get famous enough, I want to have my own fragrance and have it be called Moran and have the ads be old Asian women coming out of French doors like in the Ego East ad.
[SPEAKER_19]: Moran!
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't you think that's sexy?
[SPEAKER_19]: It's just, it's so hot.
[SPEAKER_19]: My mother is convinced that everybody in show business does drugs.
[SPEAKER_19]: She's like, oh, you cannot go to the club because they take the drugs.
[SPEAKER_19]: The people, they take the cocaine.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then they take the D, what is it, the D, the L, the D, the D.
[SPEAKER_19]: Mom, it's LSD.
[SPEAKER_15]: How do you know that?
[SPEAKER_19]: My mother has a problem with blind intersections.
[SPEAKER_19]: She will sit there for a very long time and rant.
[SPEAKER_15]: They never give you a chance!
[SPEAKER_19]: So since I was about 10 years old, almost all of my friends have been gay men.
[SPEAKER_19]: And my mother would give me phone messages from them when they would call me when I lived at home.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, Scott called.
[SPEAKER_19]: Is he the gay?
[SPEAKER_15]: Is he the gay?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, godmom, I don't know if he's THE gay.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's a lot of pressure to be THE gay.
[SPEAKER_19]: All of that resting on one guy.
[SPEAKER_19]: He has to do the parade all by himself.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm here!
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm queer!
[SPEAKER_19]: I guess I'm the only one.
[SPEAKER_19]: My parents are very conservative, but surprisingly gay positive.
[SPEAKER_19]: In the late 70s, we owned a bookstore in San Francisco on Polk Street, which then was a huge gay mecca.
[SPEAKER_19]: And my mother, for some reason, was in charge of the gay pornography section.
[SPEAKER_19]: So every day as we walk over there, I don't know why we have this booth!
[SPEAKER_19]: The most harrowing experience I ever had with my mother was one time I wanted to go see this movie with my friends and she would not let me go with my friends.
[SPEAKER_19]: She had to come with me.
[SPEAKER_19]: So I had to go see The Wall with my mom.
[SPEAKER_19]: Halfway through the movie, somebody actually passed her a joint.
[SPEAKER_17]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know why they give this to me.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's so... I... I...
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you very much for listening and we'll see you next week.
That's what I would play for anybody who wants to know what Margaret Cho is all about because that just sums it all up right in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we are in the afterbirth, and we'll open up the Skype line for any calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there were a couple people that missed the chance to call during the show, so we'll give them a chance right now if they want to call in.
[SPEAKER_07]: But guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't talk to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, why?
[SPEAKER_04]: You leaving?
I'm leaving.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, bye, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for coming, of course, as always.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Studio Dark... I feel a little warm.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to be in Studio Dark Sakura next week, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: If we can fit people in there, because there's a bunch of boxes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie's got a lot of boxes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, we've been, we had to take all of the boxes out of Dan's mom's garage when she moved.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we have them all piled up in the upstairs room.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the downstairs is taken up by pole position cabinets for the main machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, we'll have to be creative.
[SPEAKER_07]: People are going to have to sit on boxes and sit on the floor, but we'll be able to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm going to miss everybody next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll miss you too, but my aim's improving.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish I had Skype in Pennsylvania.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not that you've got the Skype thing set up, but we'll get it set up sometime.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not on the show, but I can't get it to work with the broadcaster I use.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's the only reason we can do it now is because I'm using a different broadcaster.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're going to have to show me how to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I might have to work that out someday.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the other broadcaster because I can talk over music where my sound card doesn't normally let me do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stupid piece of crap, Vio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I'm going.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye!
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good one!
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey Sky, this is John Fields.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: Not much.
I'd just like to say a couple of words.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went to my first... Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a couple of words.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: I went to my first anime convention this weekend, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was held right on my campus, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: And what was that all about?
[SPEAKER_11]: It was Kineticon, and it was a really fun experience, but I think I kind of blew it on the anime, because I really didn't actually go to see any screenings.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was stuck playing video games the whole time.
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of video games were going on there?
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually got to play Papa Music for the first time there.
[SPEAKER_04]: How did you like it?
[SPEAKER_11]: It was a very fun game.
[SPEAKER_11]: It makes me want to pick up the controller and play it at home or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a fun game to have.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should pick it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Call during the show sometime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, no problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: We missed a call in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no call waiting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there's no call waiting or anything and I can't conference thing or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I have to remember to put it back in Do Not Disturb or else everybody will call at once.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is of course what always happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: You sit there and you wait forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember guys, if you want to call, just get on the Skype line and give us a call and then everybody will call at once.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh well, what can you do?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll leave it up in a few more minutes, and then I'm going to pull the plug for... We got the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_03]: I finished the wiring on my main cabinet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Meaning, all I got to do is plug shit together, and we'll be good to go.
[SPEAKER_24]: And the TV, and yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, I think we are going to... Oh, here comes another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up, you're on Orange Silence Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Ton!
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, first rule of radio, turn down the radio when you're on the radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, oops.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're all learning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, it's amateur radio on our end.
[SPEAKER_04]: We expect it to be on your end too.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_18]: Eh, nothing much.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just wanted to say hi.
[SPEAKER_18]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_18]: Uh, Ton Dork.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dork!
[SPEAKER_18]: Dork.
[SPEAKER_18]: Unfortunately, the Skype doesn't let me type four characters in my name, so I had to type Mr. Urkel, which is my LJ name.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's a good name, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was a dork.
[SPEAKER_24]: It fits.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, it fits.
[SPEAKER_24]: It works.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, well, hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you have a comment on anything for tonight's show or anything?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want to ask Puppy how he thinks of Destiny.
[SPEAKER_24]: You're asking me that again?
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, you requested it.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, you did.
[SPEAKER_12]: She specifically said that.
[SPEAKER_12]: When did she say that?
[SPEAKER_12]: Check her last LJ post.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, LJ drama.
[SPEAKER_24]: One of our friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see, LJ drama.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's a good chance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, there's a good segue for me to plug the LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_04]: LiveJournal Community, Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: All one word right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And no drama on our community, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you look at the friends page with all our members, you can get plenty of drama from all their journals.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fabulous.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's really good for killing time to read up on LiveJournal drama.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, thanks for giving the show a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later, Dork.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, call during the show sometime.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: See you Skype is fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Click.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I like the little clicky noise it makes when we hang up on people.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're out of here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of done with tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll leave this open a few more minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know Angel was really trying to get through, and I don't know what happened, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll be uploading my two new remixes, the Ecstasy one and the Room of Angels one, probably tonight, actually, for other reasons.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to be able to let our listeners download it, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the number one reason.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, they can listen to it before everyone else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'm going to set up a post-show here right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, this was really popular last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We played some stuff from the Ministry of Sound Compilation, the annual.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm going to do that again, except we only got through disc one last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm going to just go ahead and start it off with disc two tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I'm turning into Aaron here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so lovely when it's sunny