Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts?
DarkSakura
Sky and the Low Crew
Tonight, October 16th, 2011
Street Fighter X Tekken gets a release date
has Sony Playstation Network information been compromised again
and a date is set for the new Xbox Dashboard
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet
and welcome back to another week of the show
where every gamer has a voice
Orange Lounge Radio
It is episode number 432
for this October 16th, 2011
My name is Rob Roberts
and I'll be joining you over the next few hours
with my awesome co-hosts
First off, the one and the only DarkSakura
Jamie Summers
Hi
How are you Miss Summers?
Caffeinated
Mildly caffeinated
as opposed to extremely caffeinated
Yeah, because I had to decaf coffee
but there's some caffeine in it
Yes, a little bit
It's decaffeinated but not uncaffeinated
Enough to bounce the headache
Say hello as well to tech master Loki
Hello
Who I notice has brought dinner of choice tonight
an entire pizza
Is this triple bacon? Quadruple bacon?
Triple bacon with Red Bull
What a very nerd powered dinner
I love it
Alright, we do tape live every Sunday night
at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
right after the Bobby Black Wolf show at All Games Radio
www.allgames.com
Join us in our chat room if you are listening live
chat.orangelaunchradio.com
After all, we are the show where every gamer has a voice
By the way, speaking of Bobby
who comes on, of course, before us live every week
he had a great interview tonight
and if you don't listen to his show
you really should check it out
go look at it on iTunes or whatever
because he had an interview with some of the famous voices at Valve
including Dark Soccer, one of your favorites
GLaDOS was on the show tonight
so it was a fun listen
so I guess he ran into them at an Atlanta based convention
Does that mean he's going to have new bumpers?
I would think so
I would hope so man
He's not going to have new bumpers because of that
I hope he did get something out of that
He better
Can you record a bumper for my show?
What I liked
I will be 100% honest
I didn't hear the entire interview
because we used Bobby's time to get some set up
and some stuff of our own done
but I heard about half of it
and one of the questions that I liked was that
he asked them if they'd heard the
commercial for the iPhone 4s
that had GLaDOS' voice over it
we played it on the show last week
and he had heard
because they're a husband and wife
and the husband had heard it, but she hadn't
but he was trying to explain it to her
and it was kind of funny
He had that voice modulation program
because that was dead on
I'm sure it's doable in Adobe Audition
not too difficult
He'd probably just Google GLaDOS Adobe Audition
I don't know, probably a way to do it
Bobby, by the way, is in our chat
He says two new bumpers
Not one, but two
Alright
Let's see what else is going on
in our worlds today
I want to mention this
Usually we have a little chatter here at the top of the show
before we get into our gaming weeks
and I was specifically asked
to mention this to you, Loki, tonight
I've been waiting to tell you about this
Miklotov gave me a call about
two hours before we went live tonight
and he works in gaming retail
and he sells video games
He wanted me to tell you about
a game that came out today
Skylander Spyro Adventure
I saw the ads for that on YouTube
Apparently
if you've been listening to the show for a few weeks
I know Loki is a huge fan
I love it
Alright, quickly reiterate for us
What is this game and why do you hate it?
This game is basically
everything that's wrong about Activision
all lumped up into one game
It's basically Activision taking
Spyro, a franchise that was beloved
years ago
turning it on its edge and basically
making it this thing where
instead of having download content for the game
you're going to have actual physical
add-ons that you buy
as in the little
I wouldn't even call them toys or figurines
that interact with this thing they call a portal
so you basically stick these little figurines
on this little portal device and you get to play
I'm playing this trailer here that I'm not exactly sure what I'm going to see here because I know very little about this game but I guess this is something like
I would buy that for a child
That's more like a morning star
It's a character
It's basically a character
You get these characters
that you can play as
It comes with three including Spyro
Spyro by the way looks like he's
extremely angsty and emo now
He's just ridiculous
Doesn't look anything like the old Spyro
It's just basically a platform hack and slash game
but the game requires you
to switch between these different types
of characters based on different elemental
powers that they have
so like fire characters can't go underwater
and vice versa
so you have to keep switching characters
in order to finish parts of the game
but there's thirty fucking characters that you can buy
for this and might I add
they're all eight dollars
can you imagine if DLC out there
for your favorite game and hell
even Marvel vs. Capcom 3
which had really expensive DLC
it was like five bucks a character
I think
eight dollars for each individual character
or you can get like a three pack I think
maybe twenty bucks or something like that
it's just, it's ridiculous
but they're aiming this at
kids because they did really well with
their stupid toy titles like
Zuzu Pets and
Squinkies and they have a whole
bunch of them coming out this November
but I hate it because one
it's difficult
to sell
kind of on the back side you don't really see any of this
but the way they had us set
up the items and
buy it and stuff is retarded
and um
honestly this looks like another Tony Hawk
ride or you know
something like that
it's just, it's a peripheral game
that's just not going to work and on top of that
you know because they're really trying to attract everybody
it's eighty dollars to buy
it on any platform
including 3DS, eighty dollars
well Mieglatov
wanted me to tell you it's selling
like crazy
apparently they are already sold out
of all, like it just came out today I think
they're already sold out of it on like every
platform but the Wii, most of the
characters are already gone, it's selling
like crazy apparently
well fantastic
and I know that was my reaction
too I was like great, that means
it's going to end up maybe, maybe
still too early to tell being the must have toy
this Christmas, oh well they've already, they're already
in bed with Toys R Us and they
worked a deal with them where they get an
exclusive three character pack for
you know that title being placed on their
hot fifteen toy
titles of the holiday, so yeah
that list is trusting
whatever, you know what
cool, if it does well for them
awesome, but I just
I've asked first off
how many did they bring in because
you know, selling out, trust me
with the quantities that my
customers are buying, selling out
wouldn't be that many titles
alright, I've got to go to our chatroom
at chat.orangelaunchy.com, after all we are the
show where every gamer has a voice and not every gamer
necessarily agrees, going to our chat
rooms, ShadowNextGen says
Skylander Spyro Adventure is the first good
Spyro game in a while, I'm reviewing it right
now and it's a lot of fun
you can beat the new Spyro game
with the three included characters
you are not required to buy anything else
and he also says
Spyro is seventy dollars not eighty dollars
sixty nine ninety nine
you're wrong Loki, you're very
wrong, oh I'm sorry
alright
and DarkTetsuya says I'd be willing
to bet that it sells a million copies
invoking an old
OLR joke from yesteryear
so there you go
I don't know, like that little clip
I looked at didn't look terrible but
I can see where
especially on the back end point
it's probably really annoying where you have
like all these different peripherals
that are going out there for this game
I'm sure this is very uninteresting but let me tell you
how they have it so that you have to order this
yes please start off our show tonight with something completely
uninteresting, ok well anyways
so they sell these twelve characters
this is their first wave of characters that they have
out right now, ok so twelve
different SKUs that you have
but then there's this generic
SKU that represents the full case
but you have to order that generic
SKU by how many characters you want
so it comes twelve to
a case, so you have to order twelve
so it makes it look like, in our system
that you're receiving twelve cases
instead of one case with twelve characters
in it, because it's fucking back asswords
so
I just, I hate that
so it sounds like a lot of your frustration with this game
really has nothing to do with the game itself
it looks terrible, ok, they showed it to me
they showed it to me, I actually got to
play a little bit of the Wii version
and I was just unimpressed, I was just like
big fucking whoop, oh good
why do I need this stupid portal thing
why couldn't this have easily been done
in game without any of these extra characters
oh I know why, because Activision
wants to get in the toy business, because they think
hey, if we can convince stupid parents to
buy these eight dollar pieces of crap
for their kids
then we're in the money
to be fair, it's a good idea
I mean isn't that every Christmas
trying to convince parents to buy an eight dollar piece of
crap for their kids? Yeah, pretty much
but I'm just saying
you're a parent now, would you consider
buying it? No, I would not
you already knew what I was gonna ask
I would not, and you know why? Because it's not a fucking toy
a toy does something
a toy would be something that you could play with
outside of the game, like
ok, if they were action figures or something
like that, like a GI Joe
or Ninja Turtles or whatever, they actually moved
did something, then that's fine
then that's cool if they, you know, worked with the game
and you could play with them outside of it
I could see that worth eight dollars, but they don't do anything
will Josh only be allowed to play with toys
from the 80's? No, he will not
be allowed to just play with toys from the 80's
but I'm just, I'm not gonna buy him something
that doesn't, like
a statue that has no articulation
ok, maybe a little bit of
articulation with these, I don't really know if
maybe their arms move a little bit, but
they're stuck to a base
and
yeah, I know, you know, back in the days
you know, there was the green plastic
army men, and those were also stuck to a base
but you know what, they weren't fucking seventy dollars
either
or eight dollars
alright, is he allowed to have, uh, Tron
toys? Cause maybe I'll, uh
well he's probably too young right now, but maybe in a couple years
right now he just likes books
he likes books, he likes books
uh, we, uh, brought down
out of the attic, uh, Teddy Ruxpin
and uh, Grubby
and um, I actually, we popped
in a tape last night, man, it still
works? It still works! Wow!
Oh, it's, it's in great condition
I kept that in great condition, and we also have
Grubby, and I just had to find a
cable to run to, uh
it just needs an audio cable so that they both
talk, but he thought it was cool for a few
minutes, and then he went and
I don't know, was trying to steal
the iPod. Well, a kid his age
is supposed to have a short detention span, that's what happens
but yeah, I still, you know what
despite the fact that they sold well
in Miklotov's store, I still hope
it fails. Why?
Because I, I hate Activision and their
experiments to try to capitalize on
I mean, seriously, they're trying to run
this franchise into the ground, they've already tried
with a few games already, and
now it's just like, whoring this thing out
it's Spyro and friends, I mean
take Spyro out of it
I mean, seriously, just take him
out of it, I mean, he's not a draw anymore to these
games. I, I do want to move on past the subject
but I gotta say this one other comment from Shadow
Next Gen in our chatroom at chat.com
because I gotta say this does sound pretty cool
Shadow Next Gen says, Skylanders
Spyro's adventure is also cross-console
kids who have a 360 can bring the character
to their friend's house and play on the Wii version
with all the progress that they had on the 360
version, and I gotta admit, that sounds kinda cool
Loki's giving me a
blank stare, he doesn't care
I don't care, I really
don't. Alright,
fine, alright, and Tigerclaw
suggests, put a tape of OLR recorded
on it and watch Teddy Ruxpin talk
like everyone. I don't know if
daddy would necessarily want
Josh hearing him, some of the rants
he does on this program. And also
I don't fucking have a tape recorder anymore
so how would I do that?
I mean, seriously, I'd have to go to my
sister's house and she has
my old, like, stereo system
I think it has a tape player, I'm not sure if it works
anymore because that's usually the first thing to break
I actually, I had a huge old
boombox when I moved this last time
that had tape recorders in it and everything
I fucking threw it away
like, I didn't even try to sell it on
Craig's system, I can't. She uses it for like
a little, you know, cheap ass surround sound
system or whatever, but you know, those
the tape recorders are always the first things that break
on those, it's like the door falls off
or, you know, just something doesn't work
it eats tapes, you know
I saw a great
picture on Facebook
earlier in the week, or maybe it was last week
it had a little picture of a cassette tape
pencil and it said, if you don't know what
these two items have in common
then you're too young
thought it was funny
it was an old people joke, alright
moving on
not so light-hearted news, in fact this is
kind of sad, and it sucks that I'm having
to do a eulogy two weeks in a row
but that's just unfortunately the tech world
has lost a lot of great people in the past couple weeks
and this week we lost Dennis Ritchie
and you may not recognize
the name as readily as you might
say Steve Jobs, who we were talking about last week
but Dennis Ritchie
obviously had a direct impact
on pretty much everything
in the video game world. Why?
Well, if you didn't know, he only
like wrote the C programming
language
that's kind of important because like
every programming language out there is
just about, anyway, like some type of
derivative
derivative, thank you
I don't know why the words gave me, of C
so I even learned
a little bit of C++ when I was in college
I actually originally studied to be a computer programmer
but
it wasn't really free
it worked out terribly and I actually
this is the ironic thing, I actually blame my teacher
I had a horrible, horrible
professor and I don't think
I went to a very good university either
you know
and granted there was some things going on in my personal life
I can't scapegoat everything, a lot of it is
my fault too, but let's
be real, computer science was just not for me
ironically what do I end up doing now for a living
not this show, that's not my day job
trust me, but the job I had that pays
the bills, I'm a teacher
in a corporate environment so I teach
adults much like the professor did so it's
just kind of ironic that that's where I ended up
but anyway
I don't want to get too far away from the topic at hand
obviously we have to tip the hat to Dennis Ritchie
who created C programming language
also was a
co-creator of the Unix operating
system, which is a huge deal
he passed away this week at 70
years old, CAUSE is
undisclosed at this time
so
I think we're ready to move on to our gaming week
I think CAUSE was sadness from hearing that Skylanders
is coming out, stop it, stop it right
now, it's terrible, don't joke, alright
moving on, Dark Sakura
how was your gaming week?
I played stuff other than WoW
oh my god, congratulations
everybody give Dark Sakura a round of applause
yay, woo
well when you came in I was playing Castlevania Symphony of the Night
because we finally got it working on the system
you sure were
and of course I was screaming because
dammit it's not, you know, playing it on the Playstation
and I walked in the house and I said
what is a man? and I threw a glass on the ground
and Dan got very angry
especially since it was our glass
and I called him a miserable
little pile of secrets
he just said, bitch, clean that up
pretty much, yeah
we also played
Guardian Heroes today, we got the demo
and then Dan proceeded to go
wait I want to play Radiant Silvergun
and decided to play Radiant Silvergun and the demo was like
half a level, it's not even
worth
doing, at least, you know, the first
stage is what you can play in Guardian Heroes
so
we kind of got our Saturn
on, I guess, on the Xbox
and then he played through a whole bunch of After Burner Climax
and that was it
good times, so it sounds like you had an Xbox Live arcade party
kind of, yeah
kind of, yeah, alright, moving on, Loki
how was your gaming week?
um, playing more Grand Theft Auto
and um
I'm playing Earth Defense Force
this week, more Dead Rising 2
off the record though, are you feeling okay?
no, I just didn't get
around to playing more
Earth Defense Force because I was
playing Dead Rising off the record
and it's alright, it's
you know, I know a lot of the
complaints that other people have because I didn't really
play through Dead Rising 2
playing through sandbox mode, it's kind of relaxing
actually, although I still don't
understand why zombies are easily
killed by guns
but people are not
for some reason, there is like
it was great because there was a part in the sandbox
mode where this bride's like, help, help
so you go up to her and then she starts shooting with
a gun, so I pull out
a shotgun, you know, because what wins in a gunfight?
a bigger gun
so the shotgun
to a zombie will literally cut it in half
it will just sever the body
in half and make it explode
whereas this woman, who is
a bride, can take like eight
rounds of a shotgun to the face
that doesn't make
any sense to me, out of all
the game, I mean, completely unrealistic whatsoever
I just don't get it, why are the crazies
you know, more armored than
zombies? I think, granted, the zombies
are dead already, but
I mean, shit, it should only take a couple
of shotgun rounds, and I understand you want to make it
difficult because they're like boss characters
or whatever, but
I don't know, just put more of them on
the screen or something
but it's a fun game
my character is currently dressed up like a cowboy now
because I'm still
going through every single piece of clothing I find
I pick it up
is this the game that has the protoman costume I was
reading about this week too?
even though Capcom hates
Mega Man
that's why it's protoman, not Mega Man
oh, touche
alright, well if that's it for your gaming week
my gaming week was a lot of
games you would not be expecting me to play
I played a demo
I hate basing
my assumptions of games off the demo
but let's be real, it's what a lot of us are doing
in this day and age of digital download
and I downloaded the demo for a game
I was interested in at first because I love
this series, Burnout Crash
is the game I downloaded
and I like Burnout an awful lot, the whole series
is really fun
and the crash mode in
Burnout Takedown 3
that was fun, it's awesome
and when I heard they were making a whole game
based on that mode, I was really excited
and so I downloaded the demo, I played it
and it was the most uninteresting game
I think I've played in a very long time
I'm sorry to say
but the whole switch to 2D
was just really boring
and how can a game
about explosions and crashes
and everything be boring
but it's like, I don't know, suddenly I feel like it's
this really slow moving
puzzle based game
and for those that haven't
played Burnout or know what the crash mode
is, basically it's all about creating
these huge explosions
and you can press a button to blow
up your car, essentially
and as you fill up a meter, you can blow up your car
again and again, you're causing these big
chain reactions and pile ups, and I know that sounds
really exciting, but in a 2D
Xbox Live Arcade title, it was just
it was really boring
I was so not interested in the game
after just, and I tried
I played through the whole first little demo and everything
I just, I don't want to drop
$15 on this, sorry, so
sorry Burnout, just not a fan
of the crash arcade, sorry
I would love to play a game
that was like actual racing
crash mode though, because that was a lot of fun
in Burnout 3, and I can see where maybe
somebody thought on paper it was a good idea, but it's
not, sorry
I also played
NBA Jam on Fire edition
which, you know what
I miss about the original NBA
Jam, the fact that it only had three buttons
and I don't know, like I tried to play
this new NBA Jam and I was just like
my characters were not doing anything I wanted them to
do, and you know, granted
you do not associate me
with sports games titles often
I'm not really an expert on them
but there are a few sports game titles I do
enjoy, and most of them have to do from when I was
younger and so forth, like
things like Blades of Steel and the original
NBA Jam, so when I heard there was a new one I wanted to play it
I damn near bought the one that was on the Wii
I'm so glad I didn't now, because I don't know, I just
didn't have a lot of fun, but I think
that would be a game that would be more interesting
when you're actually in the room with other people
because that was the other great thing about NBA Jam
that's the game we all played, you know, at
sleepovers and stuff growing up
when we were at the arcade, so
I think to sit there and play it by myself was
a little bit of a snore fest, especially when I was just
getting frustrated with my characters, and I was just like
eh, I'd like to go play something
else now, thanks
so, um
then the other game I played this week
so
I spent quite a bit of time
this week with
Final Fantasy XIV
I, after the phone call
last week, Mikolatov
pestered me and pestered me, and
finally I decided to buy the game on Amazon
because I found it for like 25 bucks
new, because you know it's pretty easy to find right now
and I got
the game, it took me
a while to install, that was the first
thing that pissed me off about it, because my
DVD was borked or something where my drive
wouldn't even read it, I had to dump all the
files to Alan's computer, because his drive
could read it, transfer it to my USB
drive, then install it off the USB drive
then it had to patch
so four hours later, I'm finally in this game
and I'm playing it, and
I will say this, you know, obviously we've
razzed the game quite a bit on the show before
because it was a dreadful launch, and nothing
is ever gonna change that, it's always gonna
be looked at as one of the most
horrific, horrible launches in gaming
the question I think that's on everybody's mind
now is, is the game any better now?
and I would say the answer is, yes
actually, the game is a lot better now
it's, the combat
mode makes a lot more sense
the game itself
graphically is really good looking
just
really gorgeous looking
sceneries, and some of the cutscenes
are really good, especially in the beginning
here's where the game suffers most now
at this point, is that I think
the game's biggest problem is that
like 11, it is really
not friendly to new players
and I think they've tried to
improve the tutorial a little bit
because I sense that there's been some things added
with that, but there's still a lot of
what the hell do I do now
going on in that game? it doesn't
really quite handhold you the way
that WoW does for the first few levels
and I had to take a lot on myself
to go research wikis
and fan sites devoted to the game to figure
out like, how do I get better
armor?
or where is the damn
auction house? you know, like these are things
that the game doesn't really help you with
and I realize that a lot of people
that are gonna defend Final Fantasy 11
and Final Fantasy 14 are gonna say, well that's
part of the game, these games are not WoW
you're supposed to figure these things out, that's the challenge
and I'm here to tell you, most people aren't
gonna fucking have the patience for that
that's fine
if, you know, the select elite
smart few wanna, you know, go ahead and
be all into it or whatever
but without a significant
amount of people supporting the MMO, the MMO
is not really gonna last
I definitely notice
there's a lot less people playing this game than there was
Final Fantasy 11 when I was playing it, I noticed that
right off the bat too, the server seems
a lot more empty than 11
but to the game's credit, again
it's gorgeous, the battle system's
interesting, I like what the
I really like how they've handled
the mixture of jobs now
like if you level one class
like a conjurer and then you level another class
like a Thermaturge, you can take
the spells you've learned as a Thermaturge and apply
it to when you're a conjurer, so it's like
you're building, everything is like your own
custom class that you've built of spells
and abilities mixed together from the other classes
that's cool, I mean, so
there are things I do like
about the game and where it's going
that reminds me a little bit of
7, remember with 7 you, you know
you'd get the different spells
from the
what was it, Espers? Is that what they
called them? I don't remember
Espers or whatever and you would
apply those in there and then
you can transfer those out and learn something else
it's kind of like that and you can
basically at the end, everybody had everything
the guild levs
or the little questing thing that they put
into it, you really can
do a lot with a very limited
amount of time, like I have noticed
you can get in there, do some levs and you know
you've gained some experience and you feel like you've done
something for the day and that's kind of
nice, like that's something 11 never really had
is that you had to sit around
find a party
okay, maybe we'll gain some experience
hopefully somebody does that, I mean
even as a white mage
sometimes you'd struggle a little bit
but the nice thing is there are things you
can do by yourself and the things that
they've done, especially with the crafting
the whole fact that crafting is its own
job system with its own quest even
I thought I was
going to really hate that at first, but I realized
it gives you so much to do
playing alone
that 11 never really had, at least back in
its heyday, keep in mind my frame of reference for Final Fantasy
11 is up until about
Treasures of Aurgon, I never played after
the Wings of the Goddess, well I played a little bit
of that expansion but never the
Abyssia or any of this stuff, like level sinking
I was already gone by the time that came out, so
keep in mind my frame of reference is a few years dated
in the game
now here's the other thing, and I know you guys
are probably waiting for me to mention this because there's been a lot
of talk about this this week, Final Fantasy
14 had a lot of major announcements to it
this week, one of them being, of course
the day the game shows up in the mail
for me, what's the big announcement?
We're going to start charging monthly for this game
hahaha
alright
and then they were previewing a lot of what they plan
to do in 2.0, and granted, a lot
of it sounds really cool, it looks sexy
as far as, the screenshots look great
they're incorporating the old school
Final Fantasy more into it, which I
think is great, I really like what they've
got planned out for Final Fantasy 14
2.0, it's going to be very
interesting and almost something unprecedented in
gaming, where can this game be
rescued? And it's going to be
really interesting to see if they're successful or not
but the fact that they're
going to start charging people when the game
is admittedly halfway done
is a little weird to me, and I'm going to be honest
right now
at this moment, in my point of mind, if they were to
start charging for this game tomorrow, probably not going to
pay for it, I'll enjoy my 30 day trial
period, and then be done with it. I got a lot going
on in Warcraft and other MMOs that I play
But, and it's not even
going to be done until what, 2013?
The end of 2012 I think is when the
big, big expansion is supposed to hit. Okay, 2013
But, well, here's the other thing too
you have to remember Final Fantasy 11
it didn't come out in America at first, it was only out in
Japan, and when it came out in America
we essentially got Final Fantasy 11
2.0, because we had Rise of the Ziller
included with our release
when it came out, so it gave them time to work out the
kinks, but now that that didn't
happen this time, and everything was kind of released
at once, it does make me feel like I'm still playing
this big alpha or beta test of a game that's not
done, and now they want to charge me for it?
Like, I realize they're trying to
recoup on some massive losses
on this game, but
Not my problem. I kind of
think they're in for a rude awakening
Like,
the amount
of failure of this game
is just
whew
It is epic fail
in every sense of the term
Now, I think it's going to be really neat if the game
can salvage itself, and I gotta
be honest, a lot of what I'm seeing online
and a lot of this plan, and I
like that now they're being
open with their customer base
Now they're talking more, now they're laying out a plan
Like, I think they realize they've fucked up in a
big, big way
I mean, for the president of Square Enix to say
this game tarnished the Final Fantasy
brand, one of the biggest
and longest running franchises in gaming
history, that is like
not something to just blink at
That's huge
Especially a Japanese company to say that
So
But I think if the game
kind of keeps moving on this path
I mean, it's definitely gone in the right
direction
Real quick, sorry, I listened
I went back and listened to how I first
described my Final Fantasy XIV experience
and I called it fucking garbage
That was exactly how I reviewed this game when I played the beta
It is no longer fucking garbage
But it's not an amazing
game that I want to pay money to play
every month. It's
It's pretty good. It's alright
It's on its way. It's getting better
But, see, what's the point if, like
why would I start paying for
this game when they're like, oh, it's not
really going to be done until next November
or, you know, the end of
the next year? Okay, well fine
I'm not going to pay for it until the end of next year
That's when I'll pick it up. It's like
why even announce that and then start charging?
All you're going to do is just get people to
quit. I mean, you may get a few people
that are die hard that are just going to
I'm going to level up my characters while we're doing this and stuff
while you're working on it
But I think a lot of people that were just like
oh, well, it's free right now. I'm just not
going to pay for it. But now that they're going to start charging
I'll just wait
and play something else and then I'll come back to it
in a year or so
But at that time, who the hell
knows what Blizzard is going to have at that
time? I mean, fuck, how many more
MMOs are going to come about
by the time that they're ready to launch 2.0
It's not going to matter
And a really good one is going free to play
And we've got
Swartar on the horizon
at the end of December. We've got
Guild Wars 2 next year that has a lot of people
riled up. There will
be a WoW expansion. By that point
Blizzard will have announced their next
MMO
Yeah, you're right. It's getting a little crowded in the MMO space
I think what's going to end up happening is it's just going to go
free to play. It's got to. I mean,
that's the trend right now and a lot of these
suffering MMOs end up going that way
But then again, they're Square Enix and they're fucking
stubborn, so maybe just
let it rot and die
I would love to read
a behind the scenes book on Final
Fantasy XIV. Like, this is a
this is a game for
better or for worse, this is a game that will go down in history
Absolutely. Absolutely.
And we're watching it unfold right now
Alright, let's move on
to some quick housekeeping
before we get into the gaming news for the week
Quick, quick housekeeping. Please add us on Facebook
be our friend. Facebook.com slash
Orange Lounge Radio. We're also on Twitter at
Twitter.com slash O-L-R and
got to say this, don't forget to
vote for us in the podcast award. We are a
finalist for best gaming podcast
at www.podcastawards.com
We won this award
the very, very first year
which was 2005 and
Dark Sakura now has her duffy hat
sitting on the trophy. Yes, I do.
I'll take a picture.
Yeah, we've got that and
we would be honored to win it again
but there are a lot of great shows
in the finals but the promotion
that we could get for winning would be
great and as you know
we don't have a lot of big dollars
or ways to advertise our program
We don't have any big dollars. Yeah, actually
we have no money whatsoever so we really
rely on word of mouth as we say at the end of every show
so please, please, please take
a moment to go vote for us in the podcast
awards and don't forget you can
vote every day between now and the
24th? 27th.
27th, thank you. And the winners
will be announced what, early November probably.
I don't think there's actually an award
ceremony this time though. I remember the first year
Dark Sakura went to an award ceremony where she sat
behind him. I was so sick too.
But um,
yeah, we would be honored to win again
and it would be pretty cool. I think we would be the only show
to have won the award like what, six years apart?
But, you know,
it's been an honor just to be
nominated. Alright.
That being said, we fucking
want to win. And also on
Facebook you can check out
we've got a little banner
art thing that you can put in your signature
on whatever forms
you happen to visit and stuff to help
promote, you know, voting.
Don't, don't spam people, but
at the same time, like, please, people you know
like, tell them, like, we, we really
do need every vote because
every show, and you probably,
you probably have a couple of the podcasts that are finalists
in your listening rotation, as you should.
There's a lot of great shows that were nominated.
Um, and there, you're probably gonna be hearing
this to death throughout the next couple weeks.
But, you know, it's, it's really
um, promotion from winning
it can't be beat. So,
it'd be great. Alright, uh,
let's move on and talk about the
gaming news. So,
Loki, why don't you start us off.
Um, of course you know there's a new fall
dashboard update coming to the Xbox 360
to kind of make it look a little bit like, uh,
Windows 8 or, um, you know,
the Windows phone and that kind of stuff. Personally
I think it looks stupid, but, you know, whatever, that's
I don't really have a say in it. I got an
update, you know, on the 25th of November
when this actually goes live.
Apparently it's gonna be using a modified
version of Silverlight
if you care to know how it works.
Honestly, I don't really
care myself, but it's supposed
to, you know, do a lot of integration. Obviously
they're gonna have, you know, more Kinect support
and, um, you know, the live TV
stuff. Also, you're gonna be able to
do the, um,
you know, the, uh,
Bing searches and all
sorts of stuff to find different content on there.
And, um, I believe there is also
a, uh,
if you wanted to, I decided to
opt out of it this year. Um,
a beta participation to,
you know, test the dashboard early.
Uh, honestly wasn't a big fan of
having to update twice a day every single
day until the launch of the actual dashboard, so
I passed on that.
But, uh, that was available shortly
and I believe, uh, the
submission, uh, for the beta program
has been closed already. And,
um, yeah.
And of course, you know, for those keeping
track, 25th also is Black Friday.
So.
Busy, busy, busy.
Oh my gosh, that's rolling out on Black Friday?
Yup. That's a recipe
for disaster.
Maybe. That sucks for those employees.
Cause you know Microsoft's gotta be fully
staffed for a day that something like that goes live.
They'll have to work on Black Friday.
Well, they will at least have
their stomach full of turkey.
And, uh, they will be, uh,
be ready to take those. Loki always looking
at the bright side. You know what,
you know what an awesome thing to do is on Black Friday?
Go to a theme park.
Cause they're empty. I don't know about Disneyland.
Disneyland's always kind of the exception of the rule, but I will say, like,
I went to Magic Mountain a couple years ago, it was empty
on Black Friday. Black Friday and Super Bowl Sunday.
Best days to do that stuff.
Anyway.
Uh, as far as the fall dashboard goes, are you
excited for this? No. That's about to roll. No?
No, I hate the way it looks. You don't like
it? I, I dislike it.
Windows 8, you know what, when that comes
out, I am fucking turning this shit off.
So it looks like back, you know, back to
Windows 7, 95
XP, whatever you want to call it.
You know, I don't like this crappy,
oh look at all these panes of information.
Yeah, you know what panes of information are?
It's more advertising space.
That's all this fucking is. And I
don't care about the ads that are on there already.
So why would I want to see more of them?
There are things I like and things I
don't like. Um, but as far as the
dashboard goes, I, I, I
have not been a fan of NXC
or whatever this current one we're on is called.
I just, I hate the way it's laid out.
And I like the fact that this new one is
going to have all the searching built into it for
like, hopefully it works for like options
and things like that too. Like, change
my gamer pic. I hope I can
yell that at my Kinect and it'll understand me.
Um, because like honestly
part of the NXC and part of the frustrating
stuff in that is that you
sometimes like honestly can't find
the one simple thing you're trying to change in your settings
because they're like all over the place. So
hopefully this has that a little more
streamlined. But as far as like being like a
streamlined entertainment box,
well shit, that's where they're all going now anyway.
But I think the next, the next
generation of consoles, just
you wait how streamlined
those things are going to be with your other
entertainment stuff. You know, but see, I'm, I'm cool
with the fact that they're going to have content on there
and I would, I would like to
believe that it's going to be free, but I don't like the fact
that it's tied in with like my cable provider
because I mean granted
right now with Comcast I have the most basic
basic basic cable possible. I don't
think I even have on demand or anything like
that, but I don't want
to have to have Comcast cable
in order to access, I mean I would love to get rid of
cable period. Keep the
internet of course, but and just have
access to this stuff.
Maybe not necessarily the stuff that's on
Comcast because if I want to watch on demand
Comcast stuff, I'll just
go to Comcast
and watch on demand. I mean there's a ton of
different ways to do that. I don't need to actually
hook up my console to do the same thing you're going to do on my
TV. It just doesn't make any sense.
I've actually really given thought to just cutting
my cable loose because I just,
I barely watch any TV.
Ours is linked to our internet so
Well yeah, so is ours, but I mean
still if we could even save 20 bucks a month
shutting it off. That's the thing though is as we did that
we cut out phone and we also cut out
cable, well we were going to
cut out cable and just keep the internet, but they had a plan
that was $2 more for cable.
It included, so I was like okay fine
we'll do cable too. It's a good thing
too because my plan was, oh I'm just going to get one of
those antennas and hook it up. Yeah I bought one of those
antennas last night, they fucking suck.
They do not tune in shit. And so
I got nothing and the only time I did get to
tune in the channel it was so messed up.
When you have cable internet you kind of have to
have at least basic cable, right?
I don't think any of the companies will sell you.
No, you can get just the internet.
Really? I always thought you had to have at least
It's more expensive, but
Like local channels plus CNN, bare minimum.
No, you don't have to, but
like I said there is a deal that they have right now
and you can get it for I think
they gave it to us for about $2
more a month and I was like
you know what I can do that and
since Comcast doesn't have any
contracts it's like well fuck at the end
of the year just cancel so
or at the end of one year it's time
we can just cancel so who cares.
Ron's 006 in our chatroom at
chat.orangestop.com says they know
people don't want cable much and so
they will bundle it to force people to buy cable
to get internet. Yeah, I think that's exactly
what's happening.
I'm sure these companies know. Well all they're doing is
raising the prices of, you watch
they're going to start raising the prices of a lot of
internet. Alright, well let's
move on to some other gaming related stories and
speaking of rising prices
these next little few stories
have to do with the online pass. Yes, that's
right. What once was Project
$10 is now becoming the standard
and if you don't believe me look at what they're doing in some
big releases coming out.
Catwoman in Batman Arkham
City, obviously this is a huge release
that's out, what, this week? Is this week?
Tuesday. Tuesday.
It's actually on my friend's birthday. Big week.
Well Arkham City is coming out and
here's the deal, if you want to play as Catwoman
you need to have an online pass.
One of them will come with
the game of course and you buy it new
that's the whole deal is that you always do get it
included new but if you end up
buying the game used you will have to
purchase the VIP pass for
800 Microsoft points or
$9.99 on PlayStation Network so
you know 10 bucks or however you slice it there.
They are quick to say that
playing as Catwoman is not required
to complete the game but
come on we all want to see Catwoman in
that outfit. Not entirely true.
Well there's more, hold on, hold on.
There is something else going on there too
and that is a deal with
a company called
the Evil G
which is a major major major
gaming retailer in America.
Yes. We call the Evil G
and apparently there is an agreement
with Evil G where
supposedly, this is an internal memo
that all customers that will purchase
the game used there
will be given a free code that will be
on the receipt. So
in other words Project $10
won't apply if you buy the game
used at this one retailer
who has their hand
firmly on the balls of all gaming
publishers around the world. I bet you
you're going to see there's a lot more titles because they have
they have the strength and buying power
to say listen bitches you're going to
give us codes for all these games.
And that's how they're going to get around it.
Does that hurt?
Everybody else.
Or if you're like me
who gives a fuck
about Catwoman. But here's the gross part about it.
It's already on the god damn
disk. It's just locked away behind
a code because they're assholes
is what it is. So you know what?
Fuck them. Don't buy the game.
Either don't buy the game
or just don't fucking play as Catwoman.
Who gives a shit? Tigerclaw in the chat
room points out there are Riddler trophies
that you can only get with Catwoman. Exactly.
That was the part I was going to bring up.
Yeah. So if you want 100% complete.
You gotta play as Catwoman.
Now granted if you buy the game
new you're not losing any of this.
You're not going to lose it. It's that but
you know this is just
that trend and by the
way speaking of trend
Electronic Arts
mentioned this week that Battlefield 3
will also have an online pass.
Battlefield 3 kind of a big game coming
out pretty soon. Just a little
title you might have heard of it. Battlefield 3
right? And this was all confirmed on
Twitter.
A user tweeted a guy working
for EA. Do you need to buy a
new Battlefield 3 to pay on Xbox
Live? And the response was you can
purchase an online pass for a used
copy. So I mean as if it wasn't
confirmed that this shit is now the norm.
And it's the first game that they've done
that it's not a sports game either.
Oh. I did not pick up on
that so. And
obviously going to be a huge huge
title no matter how you slice it. Yeah. I'm not surprised
and I think that mainly is just to stop
piracy because it's going to be a big game
that's going to be pirated. It's also and to be fair
you know for what it's worth this is also going to be
a big title because you're going to have
tons of people who buy it new
and they will not this will all be
transparent to them it won't matter they get the code with
the game. So
it's only for those people that are waiting to save a few
bucks by buying a used copy that won't really
be saving any money. Well just wait a little longer and I'm sure
by then GameStop will have the code for
you for free you know.
Because they've worked out some sort of deal.
All right. Shadownext
in chat says buy a game new and support
the industry if you do that the online passcodes
are not an issue. I'm sorry once again
yeah I understand buying new and stuff it
supports the industry and stuff and I hear
people saying well if you buy used
the developer doesn't get any money
listen you stupid idiots
okay. The developer gets paid
when they fucking press the goddamn disc
it can sit on a goddamn warehouse shelf
in EA, Activision, you name it
and the developer is still getting
fucking paid for that shit. So the
fact that they're complaining that
we didn't sell another
new copy now our servers
gonna go down because we have less people
paying for it. No listen there's
exactly the same amount of people playing on those goddamn
servers as new copies that were sold.
You can't magically create two copies
out of one without you know some sort
of piracy. So I'm just so
and I think we all agree that
piracy is a no no. Yeah piracy
is bad but that is really the only thing
I'm sorry used games do not eat
into that.
It's just it's so stupid.
I'm with you and I'm not.
Here's my whole thing and again it's
the movie industry and I think what's good enough for the movie
industry is good enough for gaming and the movie industry
hasn't like died because of used games.
And you know there's always gonna
be game rental services and things like this
and I think there's just there's enough people
that want these games new the day they
come out. Yeah but see there's a lot of stuff
you don't understand preordered Skyrim
you know there's a lot of things that you don't
know about the movie industry too. They don't like
used product. In fact red box used
to have to you know they used
to sell off their used movies when they were done
renting them and then you know those would get
in turn sold to stores or whatever to
be bought. And now through the
exclusive deals in order to get the product into
those machines even though a lot of them are really terrible
deals they have to destroy all that product
because they're afraid of the used sales
eating into their new sales. And the same thing actually
happened with the original runs of Hummers.
It's just like... No seriously
not the Hummers but the Humvees through the military
the first run of them you could
convert them into Hummers for sale.
Wow. But then they actually
when they decommissioned them they had to destroy them.
So that they wouldn't be sold.
Same thing goes with
Warner Brothers for example Warner Brothers
they just instilled a 60 day
rental window on all titles.
That's for everybody.
You know before they used to have it
where it was just Redbox
and stuff now it's everybody and I heard
something I think they may even do at some
point it's going to be six months once
the rumors is going to be
turned into six months once
all these contracts are up.
Yeah they hate
the used industry but they're the only ones
so far that are kind of going to the
extreme. But once
again though I'm sorry I don't
yeah I understand that people
buying used or whatever
are going to be
affecting the amount of new copies that a store
brings in because if you have like 60 used
copies you're not going to be bringing in a lot of
new copies and so yes that would eat at your
bottom line a little bit. But
the people that sell back those used copies
take that money to buy new fucking
games that you may be producing.
So the fact that you're just
stopping people from buying new games
there's only a finite
amount of money these gamers are going to have
and if you're taking away that avenue for them
to sell it back used and
trade in to get a new game that you might be
making so that you can get your fucking commission
check then people are going to
buy less games overall so
you're just hurting yourselves. That's really all it's
going to end up being. I guess
at the end of the day most of the
games I buy I buy new so it really
doesn't end up affecting me but she kind of
can't help but go
they're going to make a buck wherever they can.
But am myself directly
is this going to change my game buying habits?
Probably not. But I will
say that there's like I kind of
noticed that this year I really am cutting
back and maybe it's just the economy or what have you
I really am kind of cutting back on
the games I plan on buying new. Like
I go back a couple years and
there you know I probably would have bought a lot of games
over the holiday
season but this year I really can't
think of a lot that I'm going to buy. I'm not even sure
I'm going to buy Dance Central 2.
Like because I'm really questioning like am I really
going to play it that much? Probably not.
So I'm only buying those games
I know I'm going to play a lot.
And that would be Skyrim
this year. Final Fantasy 13 2
next year. You know kind of a lot
of the big RPGs.
So I don't know.
Saints Row the Third.
That will probably have enough. See that's one of those
games where I might want to check it out used.
That will have a pass I'm sure but here's the best
part about Saints Row the Third.
Welcome they've got system link. I don't need to go
on your fucking internets.
I'll just play it local.
I don't need your internets.
Alright let's move on we've got lots more stories to tackle
Dark Saga.
There's actually something on my oh there we go.
Something on my microphone.
How about Wii stuff? The new
Wii bundle. Wii!
It's going to have new Super Mario Brothers
but it's going to lose something very important
to a lot of people. GameCube support.
No more GameCube. Sorry.
We're pulling a Playstation.
So this is like our version
of what Europe got
at the Gamescom or whatever right?
Pretty much.
It is going to have though
actually the system itself
is black.
It has a black Wiimote Plus
and a nunchuck and
a Super Mario Galaxy soundtrack.
And it's going to be out on October
23rd for $150 bucks.
Isn't $150 bucks
what a Wii cost right now?
Yes it is.
Alright. And they say that
the Mario Kart bundle is going to
still be available along with the new one.
Is that true Loki?
You're like half shaking
half not. Yes it's true.
I think they're going to sell the old ones until they run out of stock.
I'm not doubting what Dark
Sakura is saying but I'm like okay really? Is that really
the long term plan? Is that really?
Dan and I back in the day
went through the entire
supply of
PlayStations, DualShock Systems
at KB Toys
by where I worked
so that we could find the one with the port in the back
because our old one was dying.
People are that anal
and will try to find the ones
that have got what they want in it.
People still want a Playstation 3 that will play PS2 games.
I've got one. I have one
that will play PS1.
Well they all play PS1. I know but mine will play PS1
PS2. It's
the whole thing.
Which one of the games I didn't mention I played this week
I actually put in old school PS1
games on my Playstation 3.
One of the random games I played this week was like
the 30 Activision game collection.
Oh my god. Like going back and
playing it now I'm like god this is some sloppy
ass packaging and like what are these like
LSD influenced title menu graphics?
Like I can't even. You know what
I've had the urge to go back and play? What?
Jumping Flash. Like
plug it in and go play it like in the front room.
Awesome. And give myself a seizure.
But yeah. So
people will
they want the old one look at the old one. They don't care
then. I mean it really doesn't matter to me
I've got a GameCube. But
it's nice you know having it all in one.
I hope at this point
everybody who is interested in this
kinda already got
a Wii. Like I can't imagine there's gonna be
lots of people that are like left out in the cold
so to speak.
But it's still weird
like the math behind it is what's weird
to me. If it's cheaper it'd make like
$129 or something or $125.
Even a $20
cut in the price tag would have
helped you know like make this
make sense. Or like
new Super Mario Brothers and maybe
like Super Mario All-Stars or
something like that. You know that limited run game or something.
Well there's a little bit more and actually this is
for Europe specifically.
In November there's gonna be a bundle
that's Mario and Sonic at the London 2012
Olympic Games and it's
blue. But it's the same
GameCube free
edition.
The horizontal. The vertically challenged
Wii. Yeah. Essentially.
The
Wii.
The not so Wii. I just I don't
understand
it's the PSP Go again.
It's like hey we got this new
system that's coming out and it's got less
feature. No it's not that bad. It's not that bad.
Again I think most people
that give a hoot about GameCube compatibility
already got one. Like
but still the math just doesn't
make sense. If you're a gamer
they're literally cutting it out for no
reason than maybe they plan to sell
the games on the Wii U.
Which I'm sure is the that's really
the long term thing we're looking at.
That's why they're cutting it now. Because they know on the Wii U
they want to sell the GameCube games. Just wait.
Just wait. Oh it's gonna happen.
But
it's still though. I mean if you're looking for
you could probably just get the Mario
Car thing. And hell I'm sure you could probably
if you really didn't want Mario
Car you could probably trade it in someplace and
get New Super Mario Brothers. I mean
I'm sure a lot of stores have it. It's
a popular game and I'm sure
a lot of people have traded it in. But
just
I don't understand.
You might need the GameCube controller for something else
later on. Here's a
crazy random question. Do you think these new
Wii's are being done to combat a lot of
the modding that people are doing to their Wii's?
I think so. Because I think a lot of that modding
stuff runs off of files
that were part of the GameCube.
Like the Dole files or
whatever. Now
I'm understanding why
they just are slowly taking that out. Like
if that's part of it. That
makes a lot more sense now why they've removed it.
It's akin to
PlayStation 3 deleting the other OS
support but without all the hubbub. Because
you know
this is a physical thing. Nintendo can't
come to my house and take the GameCube compatibility
out of my existing Wii.
Yeah. Or they couldn't but that wouldn't be
good for them. Yeah. Not a good idea.
That would require
releasing
like an online patch which
Wii is very limited in what they're able to do.
Yeah.
Alright. Anyhow. Let's move on
with some more news, Loki.
So they're gonna have some new
as you may remember the Halo
HD remake. The Halo
Combat Evolved Anniversary Edition.
They're gonna be doing some sort of
like. Oh I'm sorry.
I'm reading the wrong story. Stupid me.
I was like what the hell are you doing Loki?
Let's talk a little bit about
the PlayStation Network.
The OLR host compatibility has been
removed out of Loki in the most recent
upgrade apparently. Yes. Exactly.
So there's
not really
the PlayStation Network hasn't really been compromised
but some of the data or
whatever that was grabbed from
the PlayStation Network the last time
has been used to try to compromise
the PlayStation Network again I guess.
So basically a lot of user accounts
I wanna say it was like 75,000
or something like that
were locked out because
people have been trying to attempt
or attempting to sign in using
login and password information that were
obtained of one or
more compromised lists
from other companies sites or sources
so I guess they're like trying
to login using your
Hotmail, Google or whatever
sites happened to leak
out some information
and I'm wondering if maybe that has
something to do with also
the Xbox Live users
which we're still getting a lot more of those now
finally being reported.
Much like
Sky had a problem with
people breaking into his account
and spending money on FIFA shit
there's been a lot more people
talking about it and
Thank you Gaming Press for covering this a month
after it was news. Yes
Ars Technica actually started
reporting a lot of people
actually
telling them that say hey
my game account was hacked and
they bought
FIFA 11 and also
the Gold Pass or whatever
spent $100 on my account
and there's been a lot of
other things people are starting to see
FIFA 12 and
purchases are kind of related to that
and
of course sure enough
all of my Microsoft points that were stored on my
Xbox Live account had been spent on
in game items for FIFA 11
I don't own that game, hell I don't even like
soccer games and whoever spent
my Microsoft points had tried to purchase more
presumably when the purchase failed
they abandoned my account and went to steal from some
other unsuspecting gamer
and yeah I think that's kind of the case so
of course you know change passwords
hopefully that's enough
and of course Microsoft
when pressed for a statement
they were saying we do not have any evidence
of the Xbox Live
service that has been compromised
we take our security of our
service seriously and work on an ongoing
basis to improve it against
any evolving threats
however a limited number of members have contacted us
regarding unauthorized access to
their accounts by outside individuals
we are working with our impacted members
directly to resolve any unauthorized
charges to their
accounts as always we highly recommend
our members follow the Xbox Live
account security guidance provided
at Xbox.com slash security
What a lovely sanitized response
from the Xbox media relations
department what a lovely
sanitized response because some
could mean a million
I mean I get it Microsoft does not
want to panic on their hands like what Sony had to
go through but you know they're trying to
poo poo this and make it sound like it's not that many people
when I've known at least
at least 12 people that this has happened to
And you just read the comments and like
Do you know how many people I've known that have had their PlayStation accounts hacked?
Zero
And I mean hacked for like money
or false charges
And you know on this story there's
109 comments and a lot of them
are saying
yeah hey are any
let's see here
um
where we go here
my account was hacked yesterday I'm getting the standard
25 day lockout treatment I'm also
disputing the charges on my
credit card
see here on July
10th the same thing happened to me
um
let's see here
a couple of people I know
have had this happen
so there's a lot of people that are like saying
hey this has happened to me and stuff and that's why
you know they even kind of made a comment on the story
hey uh
you know there's been a lot of people that have been writing us saying
hey the same thing has happened to me
so yeah it's a little bit of a pattern there
a little bit gotta figure it out
cause
and why is it FIFA players?
And why is it 30 days that your account
remember guys I didn't play my Xbox for a month
and I made some purchases
on Playstation 3 instead during that time of things
I might have bought on the Xbox 360 instead
you know so just
I think their whole process
needs to be fixed that's another big problem
Microsoft does some very shady
online things that they do you know not just
there's the whole credit card removal thing too
anyhow
as a pain in the ass I refuse to give them my new
card I will not give them my new card
info cause my last one just expired they will
not get my new one they'll still try to charge it though
and then when
they will still try to charge it good luck
they will
they will lock out your account until you
give them a new card so you need to cancel
I will close my Xbox account if it
comes to that I'm going on record
saying that they are not
getting my new credit card number if they
were able to
I will turn in my seven year
whatever it is Xbox Live membership
I'm done if that's the
case let it be known
there's a lot of stuff I see where people will
change their credit card and then
they'll cause they'll try to renew
and then it doesn't auto renew and so
they give them a new card to charge it and then
they'll charge another year on there and they get two
years instead of one
see that shit's shady like there's
there's a lot of shady shit going on right now
in all this Xbox
Live stuff and I think we need some answers
and stop with this
corporate speak
you should be able to get out of that stuff
this is why people are fucking mad at corporations right now
by the way not to go on a tangent that I
really don't want to go on on this program but
this shit is why people are mad
this is why people are mad
yeah because you can't take out your credit card you have to call
their customer service to remove your credit
card information off your account I don't
think that should be I think you should be able to do it
right away just delete it right out
oh boo hoo you can't get the
can't auto renew because it's so fucking hard to
remove your you know account information
alright moving on to a story that you didn't
hear anything about just 10 minutes ago on this program
some changes are coming to Halo
Anniversary talking
about the Kinect functionality some of the details
came out this week at New York Comic Con
there's going to be the feature to
analyze enemies
meaning that you can like actually talk to your
Kinect and go into the library
or something like that and look at I don't know
your enemies I guess
lore or something I don't know
what do you need to know about Halo enemies
shoot to kill, shoot to kill
enhance, enhance
and now you're going to be able to shout grenade
and your character will
throw a grenade
amazing and reload weapon
we'll also do that too oh that's so much quicker than
pushing a button how many times can you shout
grenade versus how many times can I
push the button this is just all
showy shit that you'll
never use well it's just like the past showing
your friend like look at this grenade
oh and this is only
possible through Kinect
they even said oh you can't do this
with like a headset this is only possible
through Kinect who gives a fuck
and also you know
before this the
only other thing that they said that you could use your Kinect for
was switching between classic
and HD mode I want
to play classic I want to play HD
why would I need to do that on the fly
who cares
that's not a full price game
so
alright that's
again Halo anniversary edition
like in another year probably would have bought
the game new but this year just not
not enough into it
to really want to buy it sorry
maybe I'll rent it
there won't be an online pass
because it's Microsoft huh
and if they try to do the online pass they're
going to get really they're
in a tricky spot
they're already charging for an online pass
and have been for years
alright anyhow Dark Soccer what do you got
for us how about something
that makes me particularly giddy
a release date for Street Fighter
cross Tekken
it's going to be
on PS3 and Xbox 360
on March 9th
and it revealed that at
New York Comic Con
so that's pretty cool information
as far as other
stuff that's going to be it's actually just confirmed
for the US is the
build it yourself arcade cabinet
bank a prequel
comic by Udon 36
let's see
pre-order packs and a bunch of other
stuff 9
exclusive gems only available for
pre-ordering and
gems when you pre-order
a bunch of stuff
so yeah
it will be out in March
this game's coming out sooner than I thought it would
like I don't know like I just kind of assumed
this was going to be like holiday next year
but I guess the game is further along than that
I don't know just kind of
they also announced another character
Rufus
oh god the big guy from Street Fighter 4
it was only obvious
since he was in the cut scene
yeah he was in the cut scene
I mean come on there's like
a million Street Fighter characters I can think of before
Rufus but I guess he has his fans
whatever
yes he does all three of them
that's it
alright let's travel around the world
and talk about some release dates as soon as you know
this week
today Skylander
Spyro's Adventure came out
PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii
3DS and PC
try not to sound too excited
I am thrilled thrilled
that the game is coming out
Professor Layton and the Last Spectre
that's coming out
on the Nintendo DS
Batman Arkham City
on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360
this week Ratchet and Clank All for One
on PlayStation 3
Naruto Shippuden Ultimate Ninja
Impact on PSP
Family Feud 2012 edition
on Xbox 360
Jewel Time Deluxe on the Nintendo DS
Minute to Win It
on the Xbox 360 for Kinect
The Price is Right Decades
on the Nintendo Wii
also Family Feud on the Wii
as well
I Spy Castle
from Scholactic
yeah this is Scholactics
that was
on Nintendo DS
Bigfoot King of Crush on the Wii
I didn't even know Bigfoot
was still around
Rocksmith on
PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360
and also if you really want to you can spend
$200 and buy a bundle with an actual
electric guitar in there
Power Up Heroes on Xbox 360
for Kinect
Everybody Dance on PlayStation 3
from Sony
The Sims 3 Plus Pets and also The Sims 3 Pets
coming out on PC
and then The Sims 3 Pets on PC
or PS3, Xbox 360 and
3DS
1001 Touch Games on Nintendo DS
Pets, Puppies and Kittens
on Nintendo DS
and
Jungle Speed
on the Wii
and let's see here
Tropico 4 on Xbox 360
and
Ben 10 Galactic Racing
that sounds terrible on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360
Wii and DS
Jane's Advanced Strike Fighter
that's on Xbox 360
PC and PS3
Holy crap
why is there so many damn rugby games
coming out and this one also again
exclusive to GameStop for some reason
Jonah Lomo
or Lomu Rugby Challenge
I mean seriously, is that like the third
or fourth rugby game that's coming out on
Xbox 360? Wasn't one of them like exclusive
to Evil G2? Yeah, the last
one from 505 was
they were exclusive to
Don't get your own, rugby's cool, but
It's cool, but that's a lot of games
I bet there's more games than there are football games
or basketball games
Let's see, Pokmon Rumble Blast
on the 3DS
The Haunted, The Hell's Reach
Wait, what do you do in Pokmon Rumble Blast?
Is that just
I think it's like the Pokmon
Wasn't there a Pokmon Rumble or Arena
game or something like that in the Nintendo 64
GameCube? I think it's just like a fighting
game, sort of
with Pokmon characters
I don't know, I don't play Pokmon
What?
It doesn't matter
Just curious
It's the only 3DS Pokmon game that's coming out
There can be a lot of Pokmon
It's like saying, you know, Mario Tennis
is the only Mario game available this holiday
And that's it
That's everything
Let me travel to Japan and talk about some of the stuff
that's coming out in Japan this week
Starting off on the Xbox 360
Dead Island gets a
Japanese release this week, as well as
Deus Ex Human Revolution
FIFA 12 World Class Soccer
Hacking Extreme, okay I added the last part myself
NBA 2K12
Excuse me, all out on Xbox 360
in Japan this week
Moving on to the Playstation 3
I imagine you'll see a lot of that same stuff
Just on the Playstation 3
Yep, Dead Island, Deus Ex, FIFA 12
NBA 2K12
There are a couple others though
Ratchet and Clank, all 4-1
And Gekkejuban Macross F
Sayonara no Tsubasa
Hybrid Pack
That is coming out this week
What is this? Is this like a
Oh, it's the movie and the game
That's why it's a Hybrid Pack
Yeah, it's the movie and PlayStation Network game
Yeah, it's like a Blu-Ray
So it comes with the Blu-Ray and it comes with the game
It goes with it, so it's like an all-in-one pack
That is out on the Playstation 3
this week
Going to some other systems
On the
Sony PSP
We have FIFA 12 is there as well
And Naruto Shippuden
Naruto Impact
Cause you know it's just not a week without a Naruto game
coming out in some form or another
Also a brand new type of memory stick
I guess a 4GB one
Is this with branding on it?
Yeah, this has some branding for Uminico no Nakakoro
Lastly
Trying to go to the 3DS real quick
and see if we have anything over there
No, the 3DS in Misty Pink
is this week, remember the DS
for girls is this week
And the Japanese
version of Tetris on the 3DS
is out this week
That's it
How about the UK, DarkSakura?
On the 19th we have Beat Hazard Ultra
and Dungeon Defenders
Ratchet and Clank all for one on PS3
Worms Crazy Golf
The Sims 3 Pets
So looking forward to that
That was actually on the 20th, my bad
On the 21st we have
Adventures of Tintin, The Secret of the Unicorn
and Captain America
Super Soldier on 3DS
FIFA Manager 12, Football Manager 2012
Which of course is real
football and not the crap that they call football over here
Jacket Alliance Back
in Action, Jonah Lomu Rugby
Challenge, Naruto Shippuden 3D
the new era on 3DS
and Naruto Shippuden Ultimate Ninja Impact
Tetris Axis
Naruto for everyone
Tropico 4 and
Batman Arkham City
That's it
Busy week over there
Just a few more stories for you guys
and then the classic game of the week
But first, Loki
Microsoft has bought Twisted Pixel
Of course they just recently put out
a few games for the Xbox 360
including Explosion Man
and The Gun Stringer
also Ms. Explosion Man
and
basically Microsoft is a very big company
Twisted Pixel, a relatively
small developer
We're very interested that they get to stay
who they are and they get to retain the
magic that they have as a
small indie and also we'd like to
leave the golden goose alone so to speak
So basically they're going to
be able to do kind of what they
want but still have some financial
backing to go with that, maybe some
better projects because they'll have a little bit more to
work with
So that's kind of cool because they're definitely a unique
developer
I mean it's not too surprising, I kind of
already thought they were in bed with Microsoft
because hasn't all their shit been exclusive anyway?
Um
I don't know about that
I think they had some stuff that was
on PC but
yeah, I think for the most
part it's been exclusive to
Microsoft, probably the Microsoft
Well PC still counts if it's for Windows
Yeah, that's true
So they can still develop for that
Um, I'm wondering
if they're about to be trusted with some big
Microsoft franchise to make a game for that
Or I don't know, maybe Microsoft
just wants a piece of it You just don't have a lot of big franchises
anymore though, I mean
the thing about it is just Halo
and Forza
and Fable I guess
but they're not touching Fable I know that
Um, who knows
there could be something new in the works They could make anything
better than Fable 3, that'd be great
A new cameo game
It could be something new for the new system too
you know, there's got to be
stuff under development for the new Xbox
and we've heard a lot of rumblings about that
you know, whatever it may be, so maybe
because these guys did
you know, Explosion Man and all that
they're tasked with making some
must have game on the new system
who knows, who knows, just throwing it out there
I mean there's always new franchises, they can come up with
something unique and brand new
so sequels
Alright, let's see
one more story for you guys
for this half of the show and that is about
Ubisoft delaying a game
called Rocksmith
You familiar with Rocksmith?
That's alright, a lot of people aren't
Rocksmith is the game that like, it has like the real
guitar with it, which I kind of thought
Rock Band 3 was supposed to kind of cover that
but I guess Rocksmith
is supposed to be more like you actually
see the frets on the screen, it's a lot
lot different kind of the way it's presented
Oh, I think this is the game my friend was working on
Oh really? Well, it's been delayed
and now it's going to be launched in 2012
in Europe, and I guess
this is because of some complaint
that was against
Ubisoft
Yeah, filed by a band named Rocksmith
Oh, how funny
So I guess now there's a whole ugly thing that's got to be
settled around that
Court documents say that the dispute could
go through February 2012
so until that's resolved
this game is delayed
Unless you happen to buy a PS3 version
which is region free
Oh, okay
I mean, if you're really in a hurry, but
Is the game not coming out here in America?
Yeah, it comes out next week
It's just, you know, we don't have a band named
Rocksmith over here, and they're over in Europe
There you go
Alright, well, let's stop talking about
these newfangled games
and let's go back to the classics
Every week on this show, Darkstalker
dives into the gaming vault and finds a game
that she thinks, hey, listen
you kids and your Rocksmith
you need to go back and study
this classic game from the archives
the way games used to be
Darkstalker, what's the classic
game of the week?
Castle of Illusion starring Mickey Mouse
because we talked about it last week and I started
thinking about it, so it's this
In Japan it was known as
Castle of Illusion I Love Mickey Mouse
Great Wonderland Castle Adventure
Really long name, huh?
And it came out in 1990, and it was on
the Mega Drive slash
Genesis, developed by Sega of Japan
and it was
one of the
parts of the games that were released
right before Sonic Hedgehog came out
And I love this game, so
shut up. It's a side-scrolling
game, and you play as Mickey Mouse
and he has to save Minnie from
this evil witch named Mizrebel
who wants to steal Minnie's youth
because Minnie apparently is
young and pretty
And who I believe was not actually
a Disney villain otherwise though, right?
I don't think so
This is interesting that they didn't use
a quote-unquote real villain, but anyway
You know what?
No villain is as awesome as Maleficent
the damn diva
So, moving forward
You play in the castle, and you have to
defeat different enemies and bosses by jumping
on them, which makes you jump higher
And you get apples and marbles to use as
projectiles, and you get health
boosts and extra lives or
bonus points, and then after you beat the
boss, you're given a gem. When you get all
of the gems, you build a rainbow bridge
that lets Mickey walk into the castle
so you can fight the witch in the tower
And her, uh
Now, I need to double check this
reference because it says that her younger version
looks like the evil queen
from Snow White
It does kinda look like
Yeah
Who knows? Maybe it is her
It also did come out on the Master System
but they redid it
And so the Game Gear version is actually exactly
like the Master System version because it's one
of the ones that ran in Game Gear
One of the Game Gear games that ran
in Master System compatibility mode
So, um
I mean, there's not really a whole lot to say about it
It's a cute game. It's got some good challenge
to it. It's fun
Um
I mean, Rob, you're looking
at it, right? Yeah, it's a fun little platformer
You know, I didn't own a Genesis when I was younger
But I do remember, I remember there was kind of
a stink because this came out around
maybe a year or two after the NES
had Mickey Mousecapade
Which was kind of their big game
And Capcom had the Disney license for Nintendo
though. They weren't really putting stuff out on
Genesis at the time. In fact, wasn't Capcom's
first Genesis game, the Street Fighter
Championship Edition? I think it was
I think so. I seem to remember that
from my gaming history
Well, the Street Fighter 2 came out before
Championship Edition
Well, no, but remember the Genesis one
The Genesis got the Championship Edition
It was like a big freaking deal
But then the Super Nintendo got Turbo Championship Edition
So it kind of went back and forth
But anyway, my point is that I do remember
this game. I never played it when I was younger
because I didn't own a Genesis
But I remember wanting to because I thought
Gosh, this game looks a lot better than Mickey Mousecapade
Which actually was a pretty sweet
NES game. Yeah. I don't know if you've done
that as a classic game of the week before, but if you haven't
it should be someday. Well, this one
actually, I don't know if I've ever told you about
the week I traded my SNES for my friend's
Genesis and
Master System Converter
This is one of the games I borrowed
Oh, nice. And I had
a field day with this game
I loved it so much. I mean, there's
so much more to do. I mean, not just
you had the, you know, the
jumping boosts and you had swinging
from vines. Just graphically
this game was really pretty to look
at. You have to remember again, guys, this was a long
time ago this game came out. But some of these
environments, like this level that we're watching
Mickey in here on the YouTube right now, in
this like spider web
where he's floating on leaves
Like for a game of this era, it looks
fantastic. It's like paintings
You know? And that was the first thing
that really got me is just like, oh it's
so pretty and look how rich the colors
are and blah blah blah blah blah
You're climbing up a tree
I think this is a very important Genesis game. It really is
Well, um
There was a sequel
Sorry, I was just going to say weird that it's never shown up on
any collection. I mean, I understand probably the Disney
licensing probably has a lot to do with that
Well, now they've licensed, though
Disney took the license for Castle Illusion
Oh, that's right. That was recent
I remember that. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay, okay
And we don't know what they're doing with it. Right, right
Right. Probably just sitting on it for a while
I hope there's like maybe like a
newer version of this coming out. That'd be awesome
Well, let me go a little bit
further then. Sure, sure. Okay, well
first of all, there was a sequel named Land of Illusion
that came out of the Master System into Game Gear
and then Castle Evolution was re-released
in 1998 in Japan as
the Sega Ages Mickey Mouse and Donald
Duck on Saturn
and that also included Quack Shot
which is a very
interesting game on its own, too
So, uh, there you go
It did have a re-release in Japan
Alright
Very cool
There it is, your classic game of the week
Castle of Illusion starring Mickey Mouse
for the Sega Genesis. Nice pick
Thank you. Alright, that's gonna do it
for part A of our big show tonight
but don't go anywhere. We're not done
We've still got half a show to go. We've got a lot of news
coming out in the next half of the show
and gonna get to your emails as well
at mailbagatorangelaundry.com and
twitter topics and hopefully, I'm hoping
some people will call us that went to
our Comic Con cause I know we've got several
people that went cause I wanna hear about
Bungee Ferret Tossing which by the way, did you
did you see the art on twitter?
I don't know if you've seen this. Sorry. No. Some art was
released of the main character
in Bungee Ferret Tossing officially
now named Fernando of the French
Canadian Army. Yes. So
I will, uh, you haven't seen that fan art?
I'm gonna look. I'm gonna go to
YYR's twitter. He's like, it's like
YYR underscore or maybe the other way
around, underscore YYR. It's one of the two
and he has the artwork in one of his previous tweets.
It's awesome. So anyhow, we'll talk
with you guys in the skype line as well
as plenty more news when we come back with more
of Orange Lounge Radio. Don't go anywhere.
Welcome back everybody to Orange
Lounge Radio. We are
live on this Sunday evening.
October the 16th of 2011.
I'm out of breath. That was such a fast
break. Where we're
of course taping another episode of our show. Episode
number 432 to
be exact. I was showing
Dark Soccer the picture of Fernando
during the break from Bungee Ferret Tossing which
I guess we're gonna get some calls during part B.
Some people are already private messaging
me in chat wanting
to talk about the game. So we're gonna hear more about it
later. But. Awesome.
Do you approve of Fernando?
I do. I do too. I'm gonna have to draw.
My favorite is the ferret with the tongue
hanging out of his mouth like ahh dead ferret.
I feel like drawing the ferret.
The question is when's Ronma gonna
cosplay that?
It's just
a matter of time.
Alright look. You're gonna have to bulk up
for it though cause Fernando looks pretty ripped.
So I'm just saying. I don't think
it's gonna be that hard for Ronchon. He was a
marine.
Alright. Let's move on to some
rapid fire news. Every night we like
to or every night that we do a show anyway we like to
go through some news quickly cause we don't have
a whole lot of time. It's not a six hour show.
But we do want to bring to your attention
a few other things going on in the gaming world.
We do need another marathon show. Speaking of marathons
I gotta mention this. I can't believe I didn't show all this
somewhere else. I need to mention this. Need to need to need to.
Extra Life happened this past weekend
and congratulations. They
broke a million dollars. That is outstanding.
And I know we had some members of the
OL army that participated in Extra Life.
So. The moment you announced that Shermie started
licking her bed in excitement. At least
she didn't shit the bed. That's good. So she approves.
Like licking is like shitting is for the tester.
Now she's licking her pond.
Well she was until you decided to look.
So she approves of the fact that Extra Life
raised that money. That is flippin
fantastic. And I'm sorry we couldn't participate
ourselves but you know we are
thinking about charity in the back of our mind
and maybe what we can do later on.
Also speaking of charity
the date for the new Umlaut I think
was announced previously but
just to reiterate it's December 8th this
year and it's gonna be flippin
huge. Like I
can't say too much. I may or
may not know some things
but it is on Thursday December 8th and
it's gonna be awesome.
Awesome.
So if you are like anywhere remotely near
the San Francisco Bay Area you need to make plans
to attend. If you are
nowhere near the San Francisco Bay Area
you still should keep the day open.
Just saying. Moving on.
Let's go through some
quick quick news. Loki.
This is quite appropriate and I'm actually kind of
psyched to play it cause this is more of a puzzle game
than it is a crashing game.
But Burnout Crash is gonna be
coming to the IOS both on
iPad and
iPod or iPhone
or whatever. So you can
check that out. I think that's actually
a pretty good fit for it because
yeah like you said it's more of a puzzle game
and kind of disappointing.
But still fun. Still fun.
So check that out.
No word yet on when it's coming.
This holiday season they say.
Anytime between now and the end of the year.
This is kind of cool.
There's gonna be a free to replace
Shadowrun game coming.
And it's an online
MMO. I guess originally
you know I guess
the game was supposed to be inspired by Counter Strike
but now it kind of
I don't know it's more top down. It looks to me
like one of the old
Fallout games or something like that.
They're calling it kind of
Baldur's Gate with
Jagged Alliance but
I think it's awesome because honestly
the last Shadowrun game that came out in 360
was terrible so this
this is more like it.
And it's free to play so
cool. And it's being made by
Sixth World I guess.
I don't know if they're
no Sixth World was the last one
I'm sorry. Cliffhanger is the one that's
putting this together now.
Oh god. That's gonna be awesome.
No word yet on what's coming out but
Shadowrun definitely has its fans.
And you know there's been some hit and miss games
in the Shadowrun universe so this sounds neat.
It looks cool. I mean it could be a franchise
if done well. It would be
successful so. Neat.
And then last but not least of course
PopCap. They're always
putting out gamer
crack if you will. They have a new
game coming out
called Popcorn Dragon.
And in Popcorn Dragon you
shoot fireballs to make popcorn
that a dragon then attempts to eat.
They're saying it's kind of like a popcorn
fruit ninja with a cute mythical beast.
That sounds so PopCap.
Like when you describe it I'm like god
that just sounds like a PopCap game.
To be fair I don't think we've really
heard of anything that that studio has done for a while.
I mean their last big big game was Plants vs.
Zombies. That was some time ago.
Well they have to port it to every single platform.
Bejeweled 3.
Oh yeah shit I forgot about Bejeweled 3.
You're right you're right you're right.
And then it wasn't technically PopCap.
The spinoff studio.
I really wish they'd do more stuff because
unpleasant horse is fucking amazing.
But
yeah they had a few things.
This looks alright. It looks like it could be cool.
And I do like
Popcorn and dragons.
So it'll be worth checking out.
That's the quote they're gonna put on the box.
If you like popcorn.
I do love popcorn and dragons.
It just made me think about having
a little pet dragon and watching a movie
and going dammit I want to pop
this popcorn.
Who doesn't love popcorn
and dragons? Terrorists that's who.
You know what I don't like popcorn.
Really? Because the corn kernels get stuck
up under my gums and it hurts.
Without fail.
I guess that's a fair but you like dragons.
Yes.
Because dragons will smite my enemies for me.
So you're not completely evil.
I guess I can see that in Popcorn.
I do get annoyed with popcorn kernels too.
Would it be my weakness?
And people at work who can't cook popcorn
with dam.
And end up making the whole building smell like
burp popcorn.
I love burnt popcorn.
I purposefully burn my popcorn.
Just say her.
You are the office asshole.
My desk was like
two rows from the break room.
So it would smell like this burnt shit all the time.
Whereas I was perfect.
And I had
our crappy microwaves.
You were perfect?
As for popping popcorn at work.
I had our crappy microwaves timed
that I could always do the perfect
container of popcorn with only a couple
of kernels left at the bottom and nothing burnt.
The end.
I follow the directions
completely but I know when to pull
it out so that it has...
You know when to pull out?
Yes. I know when to pull the popcorn out
of the microwave.
Oh you.
You adolescent
children. You know how to pull it out when the explosion
is just right.
Hey I don't want to singe anything
in there so.
I have to make sure. With that dragon of yours.
Cause you know.
Cause if you leave it in too long
it's just gonna be waffen smoke
all over the building so.
You just have to know when to take it out.
And then it stinks all day.
Exactly.
This is the clip I want them to play
at the podcast awards.
But yeah.
What started it was
I had bags of
non buttered popcorn that people gave me
and it was just nasty.
You have to burn it a little bit to give it a little bit of a
smokey taste to it.
Just enough.
It doesn't smell too bad.
Okay as gross as the story is
and as non-video gaming related as the story is
I have to tell it. I'm like kind of the opposite
of you Loki. Burnt popcorn
not really a fan. But what I'm a
total fan of and can't get enough of
are like the barely popped kernels.
Like the kernels that have popped a little bit
but are like
not all the way popped.
I will pull a microwave. I'll pull out
early.
Just to get a bag full of those
because those are the
delicious kernels in my opinion
are the ones that are like barely popped. Of course they're also the worst
for your teeth but whatever.
So. Alright.
Moving on to non
dragon related things.
Only us can you know
take a pop cap game and turn it into
pulling out.
Alright moving on.
Do you hear these sounds in the background?
This is the sound
of BurgerTime on Xbox Live
Arcade.
That's right. BurgerTime Xbox Live Arcade
it has a release. It is November
2nd is when this is coming out.
And look it's kind of an old
OLR in joke. It hasn't come up a lot lately
but I really defend the old
arcade classic BurgerTime
is vastly underrated. It's a great
game. I actually
contrary to popular belief I don't really believe
it's like the best arcade game ever made.
But it's a fun one. And it's underrated.
And I have to admit this looks pretty cool
what they're doing with the whole like round
platforms and the graphical upgrades.
Hopefully it retains some of that charm of the original
and I'm really excited to try multiplayer.
So I will get to do all that
on November 2nd because that's what
the release date is according to Monkeypaw Games.
Who's making it?
Infinity Blade of course very popular game
on the iOS platform. I have yet to play it.
I don't know why I've been dodging it.
But very popular.
It is actually going to be coming to arcades.
That struck me as very interesting.
But Infinity Blade FX
is making its way to
I guess Dave and Busters
and other
types of facilities
like that. So it's kind of cool.
Apparently though they have other games that they've
ported with us like Fruit Ninja.
Flight Control is the other one.
Any game that has a big old
touch screen they say 46 inches
is going to have this.
They're saying it's going to be in all
57 Dave and Busters locations
of which we have a brand new one here in Roseville
not too far away. So Dark
Sakura we might have to go to Dave and
Busters on assignment for the show.
Ok let's do it.
We'll make that sacrifice. By October
28th so we'll have to go just after that to
make sure that the game is there. And then I can finally
play Infinity Blade be it in arcade form.
One other story before
I turn it over to Dark Sakura and that has to do with
Leisure Suit Larry. Ok look before
they ruined it like 5 years ago
with the versions that were on the regular Xbox
and Playstation 2. Leisure Suit Larry
was kind of an epic game like
back in the day. Not actually by Epic
it was by Sierra. But anyway it was a great
adventure game back in the day. Well Leisure Suit Larry
in the land of the lounge lizards
is being remade.
That is the original game in the series.
They're remaking it with an HD
upgrade for the series 25th
anniversary which is coming up at the
end of 2012. Surprisingly
enough it's not Telltale doing
it. Which I would have thought
point and click adventure game surely this is
Telltale is doing. No it's actually being done by somebody
else. It's being done by Replay Games
and this is very important. Al
Lowe who did the original
series this has his blessing
and he's working with them on it.
It should be noted the games
that came out within the past 5 years
he had nothing to do with. And in fact
he was kind of a bitter
betty about them and I can't say I blame him.
In fact listen to this quote
to EGM that he said
quote I'm overjoyed to see Larry released
from his digital dungeon after all this
time and be placed in the hands
of someone who understands him and
wants to see him brought back to
the forefront by people who love him and
understand him. That's what we call
subtly throwing shade.
That's also a little redundant.
A little bit but. Well you may remember
that Leisure Suit Larry before was released
by Venvedi
Universal who put out wonderful
franchise killing games
like the Spyro series, the Crash
series and of course the Leisure Suit Larry
series.
Thank you and guess who bought Venvedi
Universal? Activision.
See where we're going
here? Well they must have not optioned to
continue this series and after the last couple games
I can't imagine why. So now Replay Games
picked it up. What's cool about this, Replay
has said that if they're successful they're
going to keep doing these HD updates
through all the original games.
So that's kind of rad.
They're also planning on some new games.
So let's just hope it
doesn't suck.
Moving on, DarkSakura.
Well, how
about some stuff about the Nintendo DS?
No, I don't want to hear it.
Okay. There has
been over 50 million
units sold in the US.
And this was
numbers presented by Nintendo.
That's 7 years
post launch, still selling, and
like I said, 50 million
units. I wonder if that includes 3 DS's
because technically it's kind of part of the DS
family. It says and its variants.
Okay, there you go.
Also, for Ultimate Marvel
vs. Capcom 3, there
is going to be a playable Galactus mode.
That's pretty cool.
You can just have him
smack people with his bitch slap and
his flick attack, I guess.
You know who else I saw on there, by the way?
Phoenix Wright. Yeah, I heard about that too.
Phoenix Wright's in it.
Pretty cool.
Is it bad that I thought he was in the original one?
I did not play the original one.
They put in Frank West.
That's awesome. Frank West is
awesome. I love that character.
I mean, that's kind of a why, except
I guess he's pretty cool, you know.
And then last but not least, Star Wars
The Old Republic has a European
release date. It will be out on the 20th of December.
Two days earlier than
it was announced. Yeah, I was going to say they bumped it up a little bit
because it was supposed to be a
variance. Just a teens.
In MMO speak, three days
is a big deal, so it's nice that
Europe got parity with that.
In fact, the 20th for
them starts earlier than it
will for us, so now we're getting shafted.
Oh, Rob.
Alright, it's just one day.
It's not a big deal.
Alright, so
let's get back into some more long
form news. Of course, coming up
later in the show, the mailbag at
mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com is where you can always send us
emails. And the FUs of the week coming
up as well as Twitter topics. Make sure you
get those in because we will read Twitters
while we're waiting for calls
at Twitter.com slash
O-L-R. So get those all in right now.
Loki. Unfortunately,
you know, when you're a game
studio that produces
all the Harry Potter games
for the movies, and then the movie series ends,
what's
left for you than
to just, you know, go under?
I actually have an answer to that, but I'll let you
finish the story. Yes.
Apparently, the
Bright Light Studios is now
under a formal
under the formal
consultation process
and they basically
the employees that are impacted
will be considered for other positions
at other EA studios
including those in the UK.
The UK is a vital center for
of game development
for EA and we intend to maintain
a strong presence there. And of course
you know
the last few games that they put out and kind of
ehhh. But you know
the movie tie-in games weren't really
they don't have a high bar to hit
but even then they missed those. So
maybe it's
for the best. I mean it sucks
that people are out of work, but come on man
maybe they'll reform
with some better hands
leading the brigade. You know sometimes
sometimes that's the silver lining that comes out of
these studio closures is that you know
they'll reform with different
direction and that could be a good thing.
The one thing I do want to say about this though
to answer the question, what could they be doing now?
A Harry Potter MMO?
Like. I would not want them
doing that. Well yeah and maybe this is
for the best. Like it sounds like based on
the games that they've made and I've played some of these games
they're not that great.
They should
put it in more capable hands if they're going to do a
Harry Potter MMO but seriously I'm not even
that into the Harry Potter universe. I still haven't
seen a single movie past the third movie
and I really haven't read the books.
I would
try this game in a heartbeat because
that universe would just be fun.
It's meant for a video game. Another game
that they created that
also was terrible. Create.
What the hell is that? It was supposed
to be a thing that was going to take on Little Big
Planet. Came out last year. No one gave
a shit about it. Was that the Xbox thing? It was
Xbox, Playstation 3 and Wii.
Terrible! What was
Microsoft's answer to that? Didn't they have something?
Oh that was also terrible. That ended up being an
indie games thing didn't it?
It was not Zubo.
Was it Zubo? I don't remember. I don't know. They also did a game
called Zubo on the DS but
yeah I don't remember.
The other thing I want to say about
Harry Potter. Pottermore.
There could be game material in there.
I don't know. I just
I don't know. I would really like to
see an MMO come out of the Harry Potter universe
but it does need to be done right. Don't
do a shitty MMO or people are going to be upset.
So.
Alright. Anything else before I move on?
Yeah but it's a tangent so I'm not going to go there
right now. Alright why not? I'm going to start another story
so go ahead. Go for the tangent. I forgot to mention
since it wasn't really my gaming week
and one of the reasons why I didn't play a lot of games
this week because I was reading Ready Player
One. It's fucking amazing.
Oh yeah that was the book you were talking about last week.
I'm serious. Any of our listeners
for the show this book is for you. I mean
it's absolutely without a doubt
for you. Can I get it on Kindle?
Yes. Maybe I'll check it out.
Dude I mean
not the spoil stuff but like
be careful.
Okay I'm going to spoil one thing but it is kind of cool.
The very first challenge
that this guy has to go through to get this
because you have to find three keys and unlock
the gates to find an easter egg
that basically gets you the
assets of this company. This guy
is like a multi-billion dollar thing.
So it's a little bit like Charlie and the Chocolate Factory
with the treasure hunt and stuff like that.
He has to fight a lich.
Is it the lich king?
He has to joust the lich
and the uh
it's like I forget the dungeon
it's some dungeon from Dungeons and Dragons.
Is it the lich from Shadowgate?
Not the lich from Shadowgate. But he has to fight him
he has to joust him
on the old arcade game
joust.
I knew something was coming with that.
Seriously it's a fucking amazing
book. You said this has been optioned for a movie right?
It has been optioned for a movie.
Warner Brother bought the rights last year.
I'm serious. Go check this book out
now. It's great.
Speaking of movies and all that stuff
I have to get this out there.
You know how like I talked a lot last week about the
various shadow casting stuff that's going on in town
you know I did Repo last week
and there's Rocky Horror of course is the king
of shadow cast movies and I think there's people
that shadow cast other movies too. Do you know what
shadow cast I believe
I have heard rumblings of this and I think it was on a
website somewhere and it was in the paper
in an article on the group here that does
a lot of shadow casts. Do you know what movie they're planning
to shadow cast next year here in Sacramento?
What? Scott Pilgrim vs. The World.
Awesome!
And now you know the movie
when I first saw it was only kind of eh
but thinking about seeing
that movie in a group of very
like minded individuals who are going to be there
for the sheer cheese factor of it I actually think
it's going to be pretty fucking awesome.
So. But I'm serious.
Go. I don't read books
a lot. I mean hardly ever.
And I couldn't put the book
down. I had to read the whole thing straight through
until I finished it. And it's just
it's seriously
if you're a fan of the 80's stuff, if you're a fan of
classic video games, if you're a fan of
just cool like kind of
where's the internet going to go? That type
of thing. And you got to read
this. It's just amazing. Anyways.
So that's my tangent there.
Moving on to some other news.
Oh let me play this way. No you're done.
No no this is cool. The
writer of this. He did a movie of
Fanboys. He wrote the script and everything
for that. Oh god I've heard about. Okay.
I haven't seen that movie but I know what it is.
The guy. He drives around
in one of the cars
the avatar in this game
or this universe drives
around. It's not like a blue avatar.
No like he hits this
avatar in a virtual world type thing.
He drives around or flies
around I should say. And DeLorean
that has
something from Buckaroo Banzai where it allows
them to travel through matter. Also
has the Ecto-1
logos and stuff on it. Also has a light
bar from Knight Rider and Kittencider.
And this guy fucking drives around in
a goddamn DeLorean that has all that shit
on it. Well obviously not the time traveling
and the matter thing. But
he drives around a fucking DeLorean
with the kit and the light
bar and everything.
An actual car to all the book signings he goes to.
It's amazing. ActDeft once again wants to know
the name of the book. Ready Player One.
Alright just for you Loki. I will
try to get the author on the show. Why not?
Sure it's
amazing. It's a great book. Why not?
Alright. Moving on
I want to talk quickly
about this. A video game
soundtrack. But not your typical video game
soundtrack. It's a video game soundtrack by
the London Philharmonic Orchestra.
So this is pretty cool.
They're actually going to be putting out a
CD called The Greatest
Video Game Music. It will be
21 tracks with music that
encompasses like 30 years
worth of games. Super Mario,
Angry Birds, Metal Gear
Solid Sons of Liberty, Fallout 3.
Awesome. There's a
sample available online. It's
Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2
theme. And they actually have a clip of it
available on SoundCloud
that you can check out under username
kwahl. Let me play a quick little
clip here of
this. If I can kind of skip ahead in the song here a little bit.
I can't change the volume on this but usually these
classical songs are a little
quieter anyway.
You kind of get the feeling, right?
Here we go.
That's the London Philharmonic Orchestra doing that.
So that's going to be awesome.
Available wherever
you buy CDs. You know, Amazon, iTunes
what have you. Alright. Let's go
to the mailbag. Every week you guys send us
emails at mailbag at orangeloungelaunge
radio.com
Dark Soccer is going to read some of her favorites
right now. Mailbag at orangeloungelaunge radio.
All two of them. Two?
Yep. First one comes... I'm firing the
listeners. First one
comes from Ian. Hey guys, long
time listener, first time, I don't know, emailer
whatever. I'm not sure if
you guys knew about this or not but
over the DSiWare store
you can
I guess you can get, the word get was left
out. Legend of Zelda Four Swords Anniversary
Edition for free. Hells yes.
I'm not sure when it runs out but you better
act fast. Actually, I have an answer for that.
I was aware of that.
It's pretty big news in the DS world if you're a
3DS owner. And absolutely it's free.
You literally have no
reason not to get it. I haven't done it yet.
Unless you don't have the 3DS.
February is when it will not be
free anymore. So it won't be free forever.
I don't have a 3DS.
The good news is those of you that get them at the holidays
will, you know, which I imagine
a lot of people are going to find 3DS's
you know, under their Hanukkah tree or whatever it is
they will
you'll be able to still get it through February.
Next email?
Why not?
Hello peoples.
And this comes from Retertainment.
There's a story that broke
this week that just seemed to stick out my mind.
Why men are in trouble.
Okay, I'm going to click this.
Men are always in trouble.
Because we won't man up.
The reason that this story sticks in my mind
is because we pull out the popcorn too soon.
I don't know about you, but
I tend to tune out people who nag me to do things.
It seems that no matter who it is
or what it is about, whether they
or it is substantial or not
if you nag me, I tend not to pay attention.
I tend not to pay attention
to what you are currently saying
or what you have said and will say in the future.
So when William Bennett, President Obama
or my mom tells me to get off the video games
five hours a week, get yourself together
get a challenging job, or get married
I tend to put that in the bottom of my to-do list.
Stay black, Retertainment. This message was crafted
while watching a news podcast on my Apple TV.
That's just called having a rebellious nature.
You don't want to do
what someone tells you to do. Someone says
do it, you want to do something else.
That's actually very common. A lot of people
kind of have that rebellious nature.
Right? Well, I'm just
kind of glancing this over and...
Is this an opinion piece?
I noticed this on CNN. Yeah, I think it's an opinion piece.
By a dude.
It is. It's by a guy here.
Eh. Don't care.
Thank you. Thanks for your email.
I was trying to read over your shoulder.
Oh, you can get in the email and read it yourself.
I'll read it and be more educated.
Do I look like your correspondent?
Now who's nagging?
I'm not nagging.
It's written by a guy who's literally from the middle ages.
Oh, you read it?
Yeah, he's like, he's super duper...
Thank God someone's educated on this program.
He's so fucking old and he just like
he complains about all this stuff.
Back in my day!
No, I actually put a comment on my Facebook
if you want to link the article. I'm like, yeah, this article
is missing a lot of, back in my day
and get off my lawn. I mean, because seriously
that is what this is complaining about.
They need a medal. Those people need
to go to the military and fight for their
country and blah, blah, blah. This is the
problem with people. They sit at home and play
their Xbox instead of getting a job.
It's like, oh my
God. I mean, seriously.
Okay, well, how about this?
Okay, I'm going to put it this way. This is a military angle.
Now, would you go to work
for a place that you knew was in
debt and charging more debt?
This
is going to get political. I already know where you're going.
But I'm just saying, would you?
If they offered a great retirement plan, I might.
Touch.
Gotcha!
However, if the company was in
debt and started laying off people
before you could retire.
I think, logically,
any profession you go into, you would think
about the longevity of your job, absolutely.
So then why would it be a good idea
then to go into the military when
the entire, the last
couple of wars have been waged on
a visa?
He's
one of the people that's wrong with the problem.
He's probably one of the 1% too.
I don't want to say anything negative about people
that choose to go into the military because
it's a thankless job that
not everybody's brave enough to do.
No, that wasn't my point. I'm saying in response to this guy.
What makes it attractive
if, now I understand
going in for patriotic, that's one thing.
Or going in because, you know, it's a good option
right now. It's kind of a good,
to be fair, it's
a really good substitute for
school. I mean,
I know that sounds like really fucked up, but like
that real world experience, because people
do a lot in the military. Well, I even
considered going into the reserves
for the Air Force.
But the whole, the whole
thing is, is that he's bringing this up
but what he's not looking at is that
is there really going to be a future
for more people involved if they can't afford
to pay the people involved?
If we're just charging up more debt.
I think that this guy's one of the old schools
who's part of the problem.
You make it sound like though that we're paying back
the debt.
We can borrow as fucking much
money as we want. That's the problem.
That's the problem. They're not paying for
the debt because we're not having a raise in taxes.
We're not rationing,
we're not doing any of the stuff that they've done in past wars.
This world's going to hell in a
handbasket. I bet you anything would have
more jobs if there were, um,
if we were actually working to fund this stuff ourselves,
not outsourcing everything. Well,
that's a whole nother Oprah. I wasn't literally
saying though that he was telling people to go into the
military. I was just saying that he's, you know,
of the mind of like
old, old, old people. I know that mindset
though. Just like very stubborn.
He thinks, oh, it's a new thing. Therefore,
it's the cause of all problems. If it wasn't the comic books,
the rock music, the
drugs and more rock music,
I mean, or maybe rap music.
Um, yeah.
Wasn't it, and I'm
going to horribly misappropriate this
quote and hopefully not disrespect
somebody who recently deceased, but
wasn't even Steve Jobs who said
something about like drugs was
one of something that really like
the, like, like the one time he did it
was kind of like a life changing thing.
Not necessarily in like a negative way, but that
it was something that
I shouldn't have opened this box.
I tell you what, we would be missing
several classes. Not that I'm
condoning drugs. I'm not condoning drugs.
But I'm just saying, you know.
Keep in mind, think of how many
classic masterpieces would be missing if
not for Ebsynth. Sometimes
people who are a little rebellious
cause us to think a little
bit differently. I guess that's really my point.
That's, that's exactly it.
Think different, right? Touche.
Except that's bad grammar, and I can't
quote that. Shush. Alright.
Moving on. Uh,
that's it for the mailbag, huh? That's it. I said
this too. I guess that, this would be a, well, I
wasn't listening, because all I was hearing was
nagging.
Rob. Rob. Rob.
What a good opportunity to go to the FUs
of the week.
What?
And the whole market
thing is really coming back
to, it's really, and I told you
guys before the show, but it's really
playing a personal role in my life
and it's
ridiculous. And, uh,
I really want to
give a big FU to people
who try to argue
against
something that they don't believe in
by using, um,
fallacious arguments.
Like, number one. But using
fallacious is okay. That's fine.
But you know what I mean.
Like, trying to discredit the person
talking about something by saying that,
you know, by trying to insult
them, or by using
you know, sensationalist
words or trying to show that
you know, an issue is
skyrocketing, or throwing
someone off the path to try
to make themselves seem like they know what the hell they're talking
about when they really don't.
You know, if you don't know
if you feel a certain way just
because you feel that way
or, you know, you have
an opinion based on a feeling,
just say that. But if you don't have facts to support
it, don't inject your shit where
you don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
The end.
Loki!
Fuck you to, uh,
being invited to
the Saintsboro Hollywood
pre-launch event the day before
it happens, and yeah, it's
just kind of hard to
justify paying $400 for a
goddamn ticket or driving, you know, a total
of like 12 hours to and back
from LA to go play Saintsboro
for three hours. I would have been in the car.
I don't know, Loki.
Yeah, but see, I have a wife to contend with
as well. Yeah, that's true, that's true. Um, but, you know,
hey, if they were going to fly me down or something like that,
that's cool. But see, here's the thing, it's like
not that I would really want to rub elbows with
you know, Lindsay Lohan or anything like that
down there, but they had
a bunch of people, you know,
all the photos are people, you know,
taking in the free alcohol and
taking pictures and dancing and stuff like that, but no one
fucking playing the goddamn game was like
God damn it, they're playing the game!
I was like
all you people don't give a shit. Lindsay Lohan
doesn't even fucking know what Saintsboro is.
She was really there.
Was that the one where they got the picture? Yes, it was the one
right there. That is the one.
That is the event that she was at.
I don't know what the fuck Saintsboro is.
They're paying her to be there. She's just like, somebody gives a shit
about me? I'm so there.
They had, what was it, they had one of the
Kardashians or something there, but not
any of the famous ones or something.
I don't remember who it was, like Rob Kardashian
or something. Isn't he the one
that's on Dancing with the Stars? Yeah. Who was?
I don't know who the fuck he is. But, uh,
you know, it's just like all these people, like, I wouldn't
know who the hell they are. And then they're like,
so, but, my guy at KHQ
is awesome though, for at least sending me the invite,
you know, I was like, he's like, I just found out about this
yesterday, and I'm like,
yep, pretty much can't go there, so,
well, but I keep
tabs with them to see if there's something in San Francisco.
I gotta say, I'm fortunate in that,
you know, if something were to come up,
like, let's say, BlizzCon's coming up
this weekend, and like, if I could somehow swing it
with my work, or even if I couldn't, like,
if the event was on a Saturday, I'd be in the
car Friday night. No, I
would've- Allen would be like, can you take me with you?
I, I seriously, well, the only
reason I know is $400, because I looked at prices
and tickets, and it just, it was not gonna happen
even, even if I was able
to pay for that, the flights just went-
You got a family to think about now. And the flights just didn't
jive, and you would've had to, I would've
had to drive 12 hours for the playoff, 3 hours
worth of a game is coming out in a few weeks, I mean,
I would normally
do that, if, you know, I had no restrictions,
but, I, you know,
I'm not, I don't make
enough for $400, I can just
blow away.
Alright, fair enough. Um, my FU of the week,
I, I don't have a lot of serious stuff.
Things are going relatively well, all things considered.
So, FU to, um,
I would say FU to the traffic up in Apple
Hill yesterday. Like,
in the fact that all of the roads up there are only one lane
with stop signs. I mean, I get that it's supposed to be
all rural and country, but, there comes a
point where you just admit you need to build
a better off-ramp.
That's it.
Uh, moving on to a couple more
news stories for you guys, and then, of course, Twitter
topics in the Skype line very, very soon.
Loki. Uh, this is kind of exciting.
Not in the way you probably think, though.
Um, Grand Theft Auto 3 is
having its 10th anniversary.
So, Rockstar is celebrating
by porting it to the iOS
platform. Uh, this would actually
be the new iOS stuff.
The iPad 2 and iPhone 4S
are gonna be the only devices that are
supporting it, at least on the Apple end. Android
phones are also getting it, uh, Droid X2
HTC Evo 2.
LG Optimus 2X, uh,
Motorola Atrix, and Samsung
Galaxy S2, as well as
Android tablets, Acer, uh, Icona,
um, the Asus E Pad,
Motorola XOOM, and Samsung Galaxy
Tab 10.1.
Um, so, that game's
gonna be ported there in HD graphics
and stuff like that, of course, you know, some
unique gameplay stuff there, but,
I don't know, I think it'd be pretty hard to play
on a, uh, system. I'm just excited
about the fact that they're doing that, cause that means
that, you know,
sooner or later this is coming to
Xbox Live Arcade and Playstation Network, I mean,
come on, they're putting in the work to do it now,
they're gonna do it. And,
once this comes, then Vice City and then
San Andreas, and that's just gonna be amazing.
Um, one other ridiculous
thing though that they're having is they're having a 1-6
scale, uh, action figure you can
buy, uh, Claude
from the, uh, hero, I guess
of the first game, and of course,
comes with outfits and guns and stuff like that,
for a hundred and fucking fifty dollars.
Not worth it, but, uh,
if you're a really big fan, and I'm a huge
fan of Grand Theft Auto, but I'm not paying
a hundred and fifty dollars for a fucking toy.
No.
So.
Oh well. It looks neat though.
Uh, yeah.
I, I guess, uh,
any extra money they can get out of that
franchise, they will, right?
Uh, exactly. Um, I, I would
be, I would love to play the game. Apparently
though, they're gonna be porting the game later on to
other, um, platforms, you know, like the
just the regular iPhone 4 and stuff like that,
but it's not gonna be as pretty.
Um,
and it, I do think that, uh, it does
support some of the blue, uh,
maybe some of the Bluetooth controllers and stuff like that,
so that'd be kinda cool to actually play with buttons, but
I really just want it to come to
Xbox Live Arcade. Really, I would just say
skip 3 and Vice City, just,
just bring San Andreas. San Andreas
multiplayer, you don't even need to put out a grand theft of
five anytime soon. People would eat
that up. Alright.
Uh, moving on to Apple
related news, other iOS news,
uh, this has to do with Game Center,
which got some minor upgrades in the whole
iOS 5 thing, uh, but nothing
really to scream about. I mean, yay, it
shows you your total achievement points now in comparison
to others, and you can have your own little
picture. Whoopee. But
you gotta wonder if maybe there was other
stuff that was supposed to come, because some patents
that Apple had filed, uh, was talking about
avatars, uh, little avatars
on Game Centers, you know, where you could, like, have little hats
and hair, pretty much the exact same thing,
you know, with the, uh, Xbox avatars, and the,
the me's on the Wii.
Uh, that is apparently something that Apple
was, or is looking at
for Game Center. Uh, the patents were originally
filed in April,
but obviously we didn't see this in
iOS 5, so either it was scrapped, or
who knows. Uh... You know what those remind me of?
They remind me of the little figures,
or the characters from, uh, Tiny Tower.
Oh, kinda,
yeah, cause Tiny Tower kinda has that thing going on
with it, but, um, I, I gotta say
honestly, this is just, okay,
it's just another version of the me, you know,
avatar somewhere else, woohoo.
So, whatever. Game Center's
kind of, uh, I don't know, there's
just not, not a lot to get excited about
with Game Center. I mean, I get that Apple's
kinda trying to, like, like, standardize
things, but you look at what's going on with things
like Open Feint, and you're kinda like, wow,
there's, they seem to be pushing the envelope a lot
faster, and doing other, you know,
exciting things with it, but the problem with Open Feint
is that, because it's not
tied into the iOS, it kinda
sometimes can get in the way, and is distracting,
and a lot of games really push it, when you're like,
you know what, I'm just, I'm not interested in all that.
So, I don't know.
This is something I've noticed amongst my iOS gaming.
Alright,
DarkSakura, what do you got for us?
We have a few things, well,
really just one thing, but it has to do with, uh,
Eve Online. There is, um,
an offer going out
for lapsed Eve Online
users to save money.
So basically, if they reactivate
their account, um,
they pay $4.95 for 30 days
instead of $14.95.
So, I guess
it's just to get people back in for
that month and see if it keeps them hooked.
It's very interesting.
Well, I'm sure when
there's all these other MMOs going on,
you know, and of course, launches coming up
like Star Wars and so forth,
you know, these aging
MMOs have to do everything they can to kind of get
people to look at it again,
you know. Yeah. But of course, Eve has
that whole spin-off coming to the PlayStation 3
they were talking about at E3. That's true.
So, that is right there. It's probably gonna get
a lot of people kind of looking back at Eve, I'm sure.
Possibly.
So, Sony is apparently looking for,
um, or possibly
mulling around, if you will,
an idea where people
can actually
get a discount on purchasing
UMD games
on the Vita
if you currently own the actual
UMD game.
This is coming from the Japanese language fact
that's posted, I guess,
on Sony's PlayStation website.
They're saying that the fact
notes that they're considering a service to offer
PSN versions of UMD games
users
own for a special price. This is in
the confirmation, obviously, but
it's something that they're considering details
of the service will be announced later.
I don't know how the hell they're gonna be able to do that, but
maybe you have to pop it in your
PSP and it
recognizes it's there or something like that.
I don't know how that really
works, but, uh,
yeah. It says, I guess,
also it says that the Vita will
play all downloadable PSP games
except for game
archives, which I guess
is, um, the
Japanese label for the PlayStation
1 classics, Neo Geo games,
and retro downloads.
So, you're not gonna be able to
play your PlayStation 1 games, I guess.
But maybe they're gonna have a
different way to play them later on or something.
Oh well. That's too bad.
Uh, not surprising,
though. Well, it's hard to
port out the backwards, you know.
It's akin to the whole PlayStation 2 games that are now
showing up on PlayStation 3. You know, I don't know.
It's kinda what it reminds me of.
Alright, one more story for you guys.
Then we're gonna open up the Skype line at
1877 Game OLR or a username on Skype,
Orange Lounge Radio, and this has to do with
the game in the world of South
Park. You know, South Park gets these games
once in a while. In fact, they had an Xbox Live arcade
game. It was the Tower Defense game, and I
can't remember the name of it. Let's Go Tower Defense
Play. That was it. Uh, that was out,
what, about two years ago? Well, a
new South Park game was announced for Xbox
Live Arcade. It's supposed to be coming out next spring.
It's called South Park, Tenorman's
Revenge. Do you remember
Scott Tenorman? That was the character
where his parents were chopped up, and
Cartman fed the parents
in the chili to Scott Tenorman. That was one of
the most fucked up episodes of
South Park that there was. What was the play on
Titus, right? One of
those movies that had come out around
the same time, and it was
one of those so sick
it was funny. Yeah.
Anyhow,
I guess it was being shown
at Comic Con, and some
screenshots have come out of it.
It looks like it might be a little more of a platformer.
They have a trailer for it. It's actually
pretty cool looking. And ManBearPig is in it.
Oh, is there a trailer? There is a trailer for it.
Let me find it.
It was pretty
cool looking. It looks like a
four player side-scroller
game. Okay, here we go.
Got a trailer here. Let's take a look.
Is he building a robot? Oh, I see.
Begin ginger vacation.
Nice.
There's some gameplay.
It looks like it might be four player simultaneous.
Yeah. It's kind of what it looks like.
You can play as the goon.
That might be cute. A lot of those
South Park games are kind of dopey.
God, there was one that was especially
terrible. What was it on? I want to
say it was on the Nintendo 64.
It was some South Park kart racing game.
Not even that. That was pretty bad too.
There was like a first person shooter game.
It wasn't a kart racing game. It was a first person shooter.
It was really, it was a special kind of terrible.
Like, it was
really bad.
So yeah, hopefully it's better than that.
Alright.
Oh, even TigerClaw in our chatroom at chat.ornsauceready.com
just brought that game up.
The N64 game and Rama's like, I remember that.
Yeah, I'd like to forget that that ever happened.
Thanks.
Alright, Skype line is open. 1-877-GAME-OLR
or our username on Skype is
OrangeLoungeRadio if you want to give us a call.
Talk about anything that we've talked about tonight
so far on the show or maybe something that we
missed that you were hoping we would talk about.
I don't know. Meanwhile, going to
some Twitter topics.
Which I'm signed into the wrong account.
I was about to read tweets that were sent to me.
Not to the show.
Oh Rob, you're being a diva.
Are you reading my mother's Twitter?
No.
Alright.
Going to some tweets. We have a couple tweets here
from TigerClaw305. He always likes to
tweet us some stories that
otherwise might slip through the cracks.
The first one that he tweeted us is about a
Spider-Man video game. The Amazing Spider-Man
video game coming in 2012.
It's supposed to be open world.
And I guess there's teaser posters all over New York Comic-Con
about it. Obviously the new movie
because they're rebooting the franchise
that wasn't that dead. But whatever.
They're rebooting it in 2012.
So that's on it's way. They also have a trailer for that too.
Is there really? Let me see if we can
find. Well, hold on. Because we're getting a call.
I'll look for a trailer for this
while we take our call. But we do have
a call coming in. So let's go do it. Hi, you're on
Orange Launch Radio. Who's this? Hey, it's DJ
Ron Mess from Anime Jam Session. How are you
guys doing tonight? I am Fantastic Rama.
How are you doing?
I am tired. I am sitting
here pouring over photos,
pouring over videos, and sipping
my spiked apple juice.
Now you were at New York Comic-Con
this weekend, right? Yes, I was.
All four days. And are you working on your Fernando
cosplay?
No. And screw you
Loki. No. No.
No. No.
Alright. You know we
just gotta give you a hard time.
Besides, I have a Buddha belly so that ain't
happening anytime soon. Alright.
Well, how was the con? Tell us about
it. Okay, first, I gotta ask. Did you play
Bungee Ferret Tossing? Yes.
Yes, I did. And, um, we do
have a demo video
up. Woohoo!
And I just posted it in the chat
room. Was this blessed by YYR?
Yes. Yes, it was.
Okay, just making sure. Alright. Plus, I am
also press so, you know.
Oh, I see. Oh, you're a press.
Oh yeah, because you're Anime Jam Session.
Alright, let's see what this is.
Action.
Okay, first off, you wanna cut out
the guy that says action. You do know that, right?
You do realize I'm up
here rushing trying to get the video
online. Alright, alright,
alright. I love the poster in the background
too. How long is your snake?
That's also, he also
has it as a shirt. Clever.
Clever. We're going to check
out OLR's exclusive game
Bungee Ferret Tossing.
Were
you playing this in a hardboat?
Oh, we're watching it.
And so you're
kind of moving around on the helicopter. It doesn't look like
things are going too crazy on the ground right now.
Oh, there are the ferrets.
It's kind of interesting
this strikes me as like a
mix between like a twin stick shooter
like Geometry Wars where you're trying to dodge
all the bullets. But yet
it's a whole different
element. Like you don't shoot the same way.
It's like this mixture of
defender and Geometry Wars.
We can't fix the chopper in battle
so be careful. Now the blood
splats aren't really coming through very well on this
video but still.
Nice. Triple.
Very cool. Tell us
a little more. You can see the ground is all bloody. That's awesome.
Tell us a little more while we
watch the rest of this game play
video here.
I have to say that is one of the most bloodiest
8-bit style video games I
have played in a very long
time. Which is a good thing. If it has our
name on it, it better.
Awesome.
What else did you see in New York Comic Con?
Some other stuff but before I continue
if you notice
the ferret that
Fernando is tossing looks familiar
if you follow Naruto.
Really? Oh is it?
That is hers isn't it?
Yes it is. Awesome.
Well of course
it's a video game.
There's got to be a Naruto reference in it at someplace.
But there's a kill counter.
You killed
21 terrorists. Oh 22.
Nice.
And a few ninjas. What else did you
see at the con over 4 days?
Final Fantasy 13 2.
Oh nice. How was that?
You can jump in this game.
It's about freaking
time.
I thought Square Enix didn't know how
to handle jumping.
I played the
demo. It was pretty fun
and I hate to say it
I am not saying this as a
360 fanboy. But they did
have the 360 and the
PS3 versions both sitting
on display. Same model
TVs. And looks like
the graphics in the 360 version
looks a little bit sharper. A little bit crisper.
Interesting. Because usually
you would think with the whole Blu-ray stuff that it
would look a little better on the Playstation 3.
Pretty much. And I was kind of shocked
by that. Very interesting.
What else?
Any other games that you got your hands on while you were
out there? Like maybe Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom
or whatever else they were showing there?
I could not get on the line for that.
And one of my staffers who was covering
games, he got sick over the weekend
so he could not finish up all the game coverage.
Oh no.
But here's something interesting.
Now, I've
ran into some friends of mine and they're
all dressed as characters from
Mega Man Legends. Right. Oh boy.
They actually went to the Capcom
booth and protested them
canceling Mega Man Legends 3.
They should have
occupied Capcom. Yeah, occupied
Capcom. Is that what was going
on? One of them
actually had a sign. I might have taken a picture
of it. Occupied Capcom. Nice.
We are the 99%
of gamers that want a new Mega Man game.
Nice.
And they're all walking around
the convention center trying to
get people to follow
with them. And I saw one of them
and I said, you do realize
it's not going to happen, right?
And they're like, you shut up, it'll
happen! And I'm like, sure it will.
Sure it will.
It's going to be a lot harder once
certain individuals have left
Capcom, but okay, okay.
Yeah, pretty much. Nice.
But they didn't get thrown out of the booth?
No, not at all. That's good.
I was thinking maybe there was going to be some drama,
some throw down, some cops called.
No, no, no.
We were too far away
from that. I see, I see.
Alright.
Well, I don't know what else to ask you about the con.
Anything else you want to share with us tonight?
Uh, let's see.
Well,
I would say
cosplays. The most popular
gaming cosplay I saw this weekend
was pretty much
Link, Mario,
and Peach.
So just kind of your traditional Nintendo
characters. Very traditional.
Yeah.
Also, there's this one guy, he cosplays
the red trainer from
Pokemon. He actually was walking
around the convention center with his
bike playing the Pokemon theme
as you're walking through as you're playing the game.
That background music. Oh my god.
Nice. I thought that was pretty
cool. Sounds pretty intricate to me.
Eh, he's one step
up. I would be too lazy to do something
like that.
At least you're honest.
Pretty much. Alright my friend, well do you have anything else
you want to share with us tonight before I let you go?
Uh, not now,
but I think I'm waiting
on a response from somebody
to hear some other interesting information. As soon as I hear it,
you'll be the first to know. Alright.
Hmm. Interesting. Alright. Keep me posted.
Will do. Alright. Later buddy.
You got it bro.
1877 Game OLR. Our username
on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio if you
want to give us a call. I'm very appreciative of
the video of Bungee Ferret Tossing since we weren't
there to play it. I'm excited that
it's only going to be a dollar.
That's a bargain price for a game.
I love that YYR is doing that.
Really is a labor of love for the craft
of creating games. That's awesome.
Back to the Twitter at Twitter.com
slash OLR. Another tweet
coming to us from Tigerclaw
who links us to this article on
Gamasutra
about a mobile game
that promotes social network safety
for children. I thought we had something similar
to this last week, but I don't think it's quite the same thing.
Because I think this one is now an iOS
game that's coming out and it's
about Be Seen, which is like a
network. And I guess it's like telling people
not to share all their personal
shit online.
You know what I mean?
You know, because some kids don't really know better.
Right? So
you got to teach them how to handle
social networking appropriately.
So.
Alright. Let's go to another call.
We're getting more calls on the line here, so we'll go to another one.
Hi, you're on Orange Challenge Radio. Who's this?
Hey, it's CD Thunder. Hey, CD Thunder.
What's on your mind, buddy?
Not much. I have a couple of things I'd like to talk about.
Alright. What's up?
Well, I went to the
mall today and there's an arcade
game that I just couldn't stop playing. I was like,
oh, man, this is so good.
I got to keep playing. You know what I mean?
Yeah, of course. What game is that?
I'm not sure if you've heard of it. It's called Paradise
Lost.
I don't think I have heard of that. Tell me the
set up for this.
It's basically you're
the survivor on an island
and you go from gun to gun
and just mowing down all these guys.
That's
all you pretty much do. And then you
get these different bosses, like helicopters
and stuff.
So it's
pretty basic. But there's one
boss that's called the Chucker and it's this
mutant looking thing that
just throws
exploding barrels at you. I'm finding
that this is apparently Paradise Lost
is a arcade version
of the series Far Cry
and specifically Far Cry Instincts.
So now the way you're describing the game kind of
makes a lot of sense. So this is some type
of like port to it, I guess.
It's a rail shooter arcade game port
of Far Cry Instincts and
it was made in 2007
and I guess it uses hardware very similar
to Aliens Extermination. So
kind of neat.
Well, it would be kind of cool if
they actually put Paradise Lost on the Wii
or some other system because
it's just a lot of fun.
It's very addicting. Well, just so you know,
if you do really like the game, you might want to check out the
Far Cry series. Far Cry Instincts was on
the original Xbox, not the 360
but the old, old Xbox.
It was actually made in like 2005.
So if you like those type of games, you know, you
like that, you might enjoy the Far Cry series
which, you know, they're still making
those games. Like Far Cry 3 is
coming out
next year. I don't think it's out
yet. No, it's definitely not out yet but it's coming
out soon. Wasn't that the one they were showing the
big trailer for and it was like really
creepster looking. They kicked the guy down the
cave. Was that Far Cry? Or am I mixing it up
with another series? I think it was.
I think it was.
I don't know off hand. Anyway, sorry
CD Thunder, don't mean to digress. What else did you
check out?
That was the only arcade game that
I want to talk about but
the next thing I'd like to discuss is what
I think would make a really good game.
Alrighty.
I'm not sure if you agree with me on this but
what if somebody combined House of the
Dead and CarnEvil and put, and made
them, made it just one game.
That would already be House of the
Dead. House of the Dead.
How so Dark Sakura? Because it's kind
of like the shooter and everything.
Or maybe I'm picturing in what
CD Thunder is describing like an
evil carnival maybe. Like a
possessed, I guess that is carnival
isn't it?
Well the thing is
I think carnival just needs more zombies.
The thing is
you go through the House of the Dead
and along the way you find this girl
and
you rescue her and she'd be
tag along with you throughout the
entire rest
of the game and then you think you're done
and then one of the evil
characters from the CarnEvil
game comes out and
kidnaps her and then you have to go
in there and rescue her.
So it'd be one long game instead of just
two separate ones. Well you should
tweet the idea to Sega because
anything is possible through Twitter. That's something we've
learned very recently.
Alright.
Well, CD Thunder buddy I'm gonna let you
go so we can get more calls. Do you have any final thoughts?
Um
Is it, can I plug something?
Okay.
It's another gaming
podcast. It's called 4 Player Podcast.
It's really
good, not that I'm saying that
I'm not saying that this one isn't really good
but it's another really good one.
No, I'm familiar with
that show. It is a fine show
and I think some of their folks follow me
on Twitter and vice versa so
they do a lot with the Justin TV
integration which is something
we kinda used to do but our radio
show is not that exciting to watch
so getting a webcam back here hasn't exactly
been a high priority for us but they're a little
better at integrating all the video, the actual
gameplay and all of that so
Well if you had a webcam everybody could see
Shermie.
Maybe we just need a Shermie cam. We'll put
a camera under the table and you can see
my feet and Shermie. We'll think about that.
That's a good suggestion. Alright, later buddy.
Bye. Bye.
1877 game OLR or a username
on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio if you
wanna give us a call and
I think we're out of tweets.
Not a lot of people tweeting us this week.
Although I will say this. This actually came in earlier
in the week. Zushi13
had tweeted us saying, I got to play some bungee
ferret toss. It's a really fun game.
Oh,
13forever tweeted us
saying, Sweet! Scribblenuts for iOS
Scribblenuts. Scribblenuts
for iOS is real and ready
for install and tweets us that yeah
Scribblenuts came out on the iOS this week. I remember
seeing that in the app store. Now my
iPhone broke this week.
My sleep button no longer works
and it's really
killed my desire to spend a lot of money
on iOS products right now
especially when I can't get a new iPhone until January.
And I was talking about this a little bit on
Bobby's show but
you know I'm not exactly in a
rush to replace my iPhone. In fact
now I'm thinking maybe I want a different phone.
But yet I've spent all that money on apps.
I don't know what to do.
I guess we'll just
take another call. Hi you're on Orange Lawns Radio. Who's this?
This is Shane. Hey
Shane, what's up?
Not a whole lot. I just wanted to
say the word Skylanders so I could
hear the rant that Loki went on earlier
than I missed. That's your fault for not being here at
6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern.
I had a work thing
I had to go to. It was pizza.
Like I was going to pass up pizza.
Well, Loki?
Heard he made a rant.
I'm just saying, you know
yeah it's cool that your store sold out
of them or whatever.
I hope those four copies
went pretty fast.
I had more than four copies. I had like
eight on PS3
eight on 360, eight on Wii and four on
3DS and then all the little
freaking boxes of the single
figurines. Do you have games?
I mean that eight doesn't sound like a lot.
Of course granted you're in Kansas but
I'm just saying it's six because they came
in case slots of six so
that's only one
case of each. That's not a lot.
I'm curious if there's other games
that maybe have the potential to sell eight copies
in a day. I mean that doesn't sound like that many.
Well across multiple
systems on a Sunday release
that's not a Nintendo game is
pretty significant. I'm optimistic
that they're going to fail still.
Although I did see a review
from some site. It's the
only review that they have right now that's like eight
out of ten.
Like Kotaku for example
they're like, I think this concept is pretty awesome.
Yeah, you think it's pretty awesome because they sent
you five fucking copies of the game and all the
toys. Well this looks like fun.
The kid in me wants to open
this up.
Okay, fine, whatever.
But reading the feedback from
people that are looking at the trailers and stuff
they're like, what the fuck happened to Spyro?
What have they done to this guy?
It's pretty mean now and like the
3DS one comes with a black version like
an evil Spyro or something.
And that was kind of
cool looking but he still didn't look like Spyro.
Let me kind of
turn this on you and ask you about something that we
also talked about in the beginning of the show. No, yes.
Because last week on the show you were here defending Final Fantasy
XIV and saying I should play it again.
And I did. And I talked about that
at the top of the show. Which you said was pretty
negative sounding. Well, it mixed.
I would say I gave it a mixed review because there are
things I like about it. Like the
whole way you can mix and match
your talents. And I thought there's so much
more to do for a single player now.
And I realized that a lot of the crafting
jobs are really there for the single player
experience. Like you're not exactly going to party up
to go do botany together.
Like that's really part of the single player game.
Ooh, but we should because that would be hilarious.
But my
real question for you is
and then just so you know the bottom line is it's
better and it's much better than fucking garbage
which is what I called it last time. But
I'm not going to pay the monthly fee.
And that was the news that came out this week is that
now they're charging a monthly fee for Final Fantasy XIV.
You didn't know that last week. What's
your reaction to all the news about Final Fantasy
XIV this week?
In regards to the monthly fee
I feel like it's way too early
and I also feel like that's
not what the dev team
was going for
because recently in a post
they said that the game's
only like halfway to where they want it to be
and they weren't going to start charging a fee till it was
100% that way. So clearly that came
from the top down.
I don't feel like
it's really ready for a monthly fee
but I will pay it because I am
having fun. And
in terms of like the other things
they announced like completely rebooting the game
again, I'm actually kind of
excited for that because the one fake little
screenshot they made looked really cool
and they're adding classes I care about
and it's more Final Fantasy now.
It sounds like
really Final Fantasy XI
II with all the changes
they're doing. You know I got to admit from that
screenshot I don't know why but I was thinking
like it looked like Phantasy Star Online
with Final Fantasy characters. That would be
amazing especially since we
probably aren't getting Phantasy Star Online 2.
It was one sexy looking screenshot.
It is a concept
I mean it's not until
it's in my hot little hands.
And it seems weird to me that they're going to make the graphics
look better yet allow the game to run
on lower end PCs. It's just about
optimization though from what I understand.
This game is horribly optimized for
anything. Once again though
we're talking like a year's time
that this thing is going to be
fully rebooted. I mean
I just can only imagine
the games are going to look still even
better than they are now.
To me it's almost
like the
Wii U I guess. You know how they're kind of late
to the game with everything and it's like
oh look we're pushing these HD graphics
that everyone else has been putting out for like
years now.
It kind of seems like to me.
But it still looks sexy.
Will it be good enough for me to play?
Well it does have the uniqueness of being a Japanese MMO
that's pretty big here in the states.
You know at least Final Fantasy 11 is.
You know and there's not a lot of
Asian in general no matter what
country MMOs that do
very well here. Most of the MMOs that are doing
well here are developed by
studios that are here. Like WoW
of course is the big one developed by Blizzard.
So you know I don't know.
I guess
that was really all I wanted to ask you was about
Final Fantasy 14 and where you're at with that.
So are you going to be paying for WoW and Final Fantasy
14 or are you saying you're like
into 14 so much you might cancel WoW?
Yeah I might.
It depends on what Blizzcon says this week.
And
how fun 4.3 is.
Also when it comes out
because who knows how long that is. But I'm just sick of
you know grinding rep in
Firelands and
jumping. So Final Fantasy
14 is something pretty and distracting right now right?
Yes. And it's still free
because they said they'll give us ample
notice of when it actually goes to pay.
And I'm guessing it's more
like early December instead of
late November. So I still have like
two months. I'm wondering
how my 30 day trial is going to play into it.
I totally am going to get screwed with that.
Like my 30 day trial will be up and then the
fee kicks in. It's like I didn't get
shit. I didn't get shit
like everybody else got. Oh well.
Oh well I'm part of that too. I mean I've only been
playing for what a week longer than you? You didn't
even buy the damn game. It was conked to you.
That's true. So shut up.
I didn't get it for free.
I paid 25 bucks for it.
I paid half what most people
paid for it new but I still paid 25 bucks
for it. And then my DVD
was damaged. And screw that.
Square needs to learn
how to make a PC game for fuck's sake.
Alright. I do think the game
is going to be pretty neat on Playstation 3.
Yeah. I think I might
jump to that when it comes out.
Do you think the game can save itself?
Like do you think a game can actually
relaunch and
be credible? I think
I think it can.
But probably not to the extent
that they're hoping for.
Like I think it'll bring in a few more
people. It'll probably keep
the current players. But it's not
going to be a huge
relaunch. Despite what they
want. You're not going to get thousands
and thousands of more people playing.
I think honestly the smart thing for them to do is
to go to the Guild Wars model where you're not totally
free to play. But once you buy the game
you get to play online for free. And they
should look at doing expansions for money.
Or just you know more regular content
updates like what they're doing with Final Fantasy 11
that cost money. And that
that's how they should do it. They did that. I'd buy it.
For sure. The monthly fee is not
going to work for this game anymore. Except for Final Fantasy 11
does those little
baby expansions and still charges you
a monthly fee. But Final Fantasy 11 is also
a better game. Ooh
that's true.
It's not as pretty.
Alright on that note I'm going to let you go alright?
Alright. Alright take care. Bye.
Alright I guess that's
all I'm going to do over the Skype line tonight.
Sorry to those of you that didn't get through.
But why don't you think about writing us an email.
Mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com
is the place to send us an email if you'd like.
Mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com or of course
Twitter. We had a very empty Twitter tonight. I'm very
sad. Twitter.com slash
O-L-R. Alright.
Well that's going to wrap up another show. I've got to
ask though Dark Soccer and Loki if they have any last minute
stories they want to throw out here. I've
started a political social blog.
Oh dear.
Wait a minute. Women think independently now?
I'm teasing.
Girl.
She's trying very hard not
to laugh. Like she wants to give me that stern
I hate you look but she can't do it. Rob's going to take
me to Pinkberry to appease me.
Whatever. Alright.
Vote no on that.
That's my political blog.
Alright. You know I'm just giving you a hard
time. Yeah I know. Good luck with that. That's what
you're. I was going to
do another joke but I can't.
No it's my second blog. Alright.
Cause my other blog's like about
girly shit. Okay. Alright.
Alright. Loki
any last minute news you want to get into?
They're supposed to be doing a
Layton Brothers game for iPhone
sometime soon. I'm assuming this is
only going to be on the Japanese IS so.
It's neat though if you
want to play you know Layton.
Yeah Layton's a good series. It'll be fun on the iPhone.
Let me go to the chat room cause we
haven't read enough of chat tonight and I apologize.
I'm watching you guys but we just haven't had a whole lot
of stuff I've been able to work into the show.
Plus live listeners are really behind tonight.
Not of any fault of your guyses. Like I just
noticed the delay is like several minutes tonight
so I don't know what's up. But anyway.
I want to read this cause this guy said
after five years listening he's finally listening to
a live show. It's Swongtong
his name in chat and Swongtong asks
how come MMOs on Playstation
3 don't use the mouse and keyboard?
Actually some
do and I believe Final Fantasy 14
is still they're going to plan on using a keyboard
even when it rolls out to the Playstation 3.
And everything on
Playstation 3 is all Bluetooth
and USB anyway right? Like I know
on Xbox 360 you can hook in a keyboard
you can play Final Fantasy 11 on 360
with a keyboard. I used to do that
when it first came out. So
as far as Playstation 3 goes you can
put in a keyboard. You can
type messages and so forth.
As far as MMOs embracing it
well maybe the keyboard adoption policy isn't
maybe high enough to do that but I think for a game like
Final Fantasy 14 like if I were to play that on
the Playstation 3 I definitely would have to have
a keyboard. Luckily I already
have one that's specifically for
the gaming consoles. It lights up blue it's really
pretty. Alright.
Loki any other stories for
us tonight?
No
the only other story I have is not really gaming
related but my wife is trying to
download the version
of Firefox that is British
English so that all of her
stuff will be spell checked into
the Queen's English because she's
obsessed with Game
of Thrones and I don't know why.
Tell her
she better start learning to use more vowels.
I would have put that on Dark Soccer to do
something like that before Nelly.
I've done it before. Okay
never mind I stand clear. Well no I've actually
got a British
grammar checker. Okay.
Because well every so
okay here's a true story. Use less z's
and more u's there you go.
In college I actually had this whole thing
where I was doing nothing but writing everything in British English
and my teacher let me do it he just said pick one
and write in it.
So every so often
less z's. Excuse me.
Fewer z's.
Alright.
Don't use that.
What? The z word.
I guess that's it.
So we're going around and getting everybody's final thought
and wrapping up another week here at Orange Laundry.
Before we do that I really want to thank you guys again
for tuning in and spending another week with us.
Thank you so much. You know all we ask we do this
for free. You'll notice there's no advertising or
anything like that except for our own other side
projects. Which by the way include
the best little Horde house in Azeroth at Hordehouse.com
if you like your Warcraft. We had a fun show
tonight. In fact we taped earlier today. This is my second
podcast of the day. But other than
ads for our own side projects. And you know
someone has not been putting album art
on Facebook. Because I like to see
which ones get put up. Because they're
funny. I've been putting them on Facebook.
Oh I haven't upgraded the gallery. You're right.
But if you go in and look at the posts they're there.
But they're teeny.
Then go to Hordehouse.com. Alright.
Because they're teeny. Alright I'll get the big ones
on Facebook. But anyway.
What I really want to say is thank you guys very
much for tuning in. Thank you for supporting our show.
The OL Army which is what we call
our fans make this all worth it. And
keep us motivated to do this for years and years.
If you like the show all
we ask. Tell a friend. Tell
somebody about the show. Word of mouth is all we
got. We're not funded by a million dollar magazine.
So please. Please help us spread the
word. And again I'll just say the podcast
awards. Great way to help spread the word. So
please consider throwing us your vote over
in that contest at podcastawards.com.
And one more
shout out to our buddies at The Geek Spin who are
also nominated. And we hope that even
if we can't win we hope they do.
They're in best pod safe music.
In a perfect world we both win. But you know
we don't always get what we want.
We don't always get what we want. Alright.
Anyhow. Let's go
around and get everybody's final thought.
Loki. What's your final thought tonight?
I am
now telling my wife how to
add a British
English spell check
to it. And I unfortunately had to add it
to mine in order to figure out how to do it. So now I
can talk in the Queen's English if I really wanted
to. But
I don't want to.
Congratulations. You'll have to start
tweeting in the Queen's English.
Speaking of the Queen. Dark Soccer. Your final thought
tonight.
I am disillusioned with this country.
My final
thought tonight is Pretty Rainbow.
Pretty Rainbow.
Where? Your dresser's
little drawers there. Oh yeah.
Actually that is why I bought it. Alright.
That's it. Thank you guys for tuning
in and listening to us. We'll do it again
next week. Dark Soccer is next week your week
off or is that two weeks? No it's not the week after.
Alright so we'll all be back here then
next week. So until then
have a wonderful night. Be safe.
And please when you're gaming online
don't be a dick. Good night.
See you next week.