[SPEAKER_05]: More lies, more lies, more lies.
[SPEAKER_03]: This will be edited out later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, welcome to episode 430 of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are awesome!
[SPEAKER_03]: And Rob's not here.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, actually, we are the show that tells gamers what they really want to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I am your host for tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am DarkSakura, and with us is Loki.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: And our special guest tonight is some dude that I picked up on the internet, Dan.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm a hobo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so again, it's Sunday night, 6 o'clock Pacific time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you can join us on allgames.com and listen to us live and hang out in our chat room at allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why am I not allgames.com?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's Bobby's chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: At Orange Lounge, in Pound Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you can also follow the chat at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, it's another derpisode because Rob's not here and I'm kind of ill-prepared So why don't we just go ahead and skip the formalities and go to how was our gaming week And mine, I played WoW for 20 minutes a day every day, that's it Loki?
[SPEAKER_00]: Just 20 minutes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty much, except for the other night when I was doing the pet hunt How do you even play WoW for 20 minutes?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just go on to do dailies Wow
[SPEAKER_00]: I played quite a few things actually this week besides the usual stuff more Grand Theft Auto, more Earth Defense Force Insect Armageddon I did play a few things including some stuff I should be playing
[SPEAKER_00]: Tiny Tower, I played a little bit of that just because I realized that there is an update to it and I did the update and bought the two extra shops of each kind and a few extra residential floors and added those all in there and my tower is super huge.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: I did.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then also on iOS, I checked out Katamari Amore, which is the new Katamari game for the iPod, iPad, iPhone.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: Once again, I don't really care too much for touchscreen controls for a lot of stuff, especially when it comes to virtual thumbsticks, but
[SPEAKER_00]: It's alright, it works pretty good.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you can check out the free version, which is basically just a time trial level that's only two minutes long.
[SPEAKER_00]: And if you want the rest of it, you can buy the download pack, which is $3.99.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's alright, but definitely if you're thinking about picking it up, try the demo first.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then if you like it, then go ahead and pay for the full thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then finally, the other thing I really shouldn't have been playing is a leaked game that came out.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a leaked Xbox Live arcade game called Saints Row Money Shot.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now I'm not sure if this is actually a game that got...
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: Unlocks for Saints Row the Third in the game itself.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can unlock the hover bike and this sniper outfit and one of the sniper rifles.
[SPEAKER_00]: But basically the whole game's premise is very similar to the movie Wanted or at least a section of it where you're firing the sniper rifle and actually controlling the trajectory of the bullet as you're flying to your intended target.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can hit different things that interact with the environment.
[SPEAKER_00]: You'll have different goals like kill three pigeons, get a bunch of close calls, and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: You unlock different bullets to have more speed, more turning ability, that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: Seriously, when they're moving faster, it's a lot harder to actually play the game, but
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, some of the cool stuff you can do, you know, there's one part where you hit a wine bottle of this couple that's, you know, sitting there having a nice dinner in their, you know, condo or apartment and that unfortunately causes the bottle to shatter and hit the candle that's on the table and they both catch on fire.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or another one where it knocks out the cane of an old woman and there's implied, you know, oral sex there and funny stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, uh,
[SPEAKER_00]: Rated E for Everyone
[SPEAKER_00]: It's definitely not the Saints Row drive-by game that was supposed to become an Xbox Live Arcade and PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was going to be kind of like its own thing, and that was the one that was supposed to become the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: But this game may very well come to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would imagine this month, if it's going to come at all.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know, it was alright it was a little bit boring because there's only really three story levels the rest are kind of practice training levels but then again this isn't really a finished build of the game it's something that came out back in June but I don't know it'll be cool, I definitely would want to check out the full version if it did come out just at the very least for the unlocks and that's pretty much it, that's all I've been playing
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, sweetie?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_03]: What have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_07]: I played some Tetris DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_03]: You've been watching a lot of videos.
[SPEAKER_07]: I spent a little time in the vault last week and played some Genesis stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Besides that, nothing really current.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but you have been watching a lot of videos.
[SPEAKER_07]: I watched a couple.
[SPEAKER_07]: I watched a playthrough of Sapphire today.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was kind of a cool game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: You didn't even know what it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, no, I just walked in and it looked like a tank game for a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was like, wait, that's not a tank game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It didn't look like a tank game at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a big skull and I forgot that level, so shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, you're fired.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everyone, Dan's kicked off the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, you're rehired.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you go get me something to drink.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, you're fired again.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyway, a little bit of housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, Rob's at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we're all super jealous.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, at least I am.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dan, are you super jealous?
[SPEAKER_07]: I really want to see Space Mountain Ghost Galaxy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, if all plans out, we're going.
[SPEAKER_03]: But not now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyway, let's go ahead and move on from, let's move past Rob's absence and I'm over it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm over it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was a little upset for a while, but now I'm over it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So how about we launch into the first story?
[SPEAKER_00]: XBOX 360 DASHBOARD
[SPEAKER_00]: Which is going to be part of the new dashboard, they're going to be adding PayPal payments It's listed the release of this as November 15th And of course the dashboard update kind of refreshes the whole look of it Kind of gives it the Windows Phone, Windows 8 kind of look to the whole thing Which I kind of hate, but whatever Um
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: So we have that.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then, of course, some more information regarding the supposed Xbox TV service they're going to be having.
[SPEAKER_00]: Some of the content providers that they're going to be featuring on this, according to Bloomberg.
[SPEAKER_00]: Comcast, Verizon, they're also expecting to get HBO, Crackle, Bravo, SyFy, Love Film, and a lot more.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess also some stuff from Amazon as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it looks like they're going to be trying to source content from, I think not only just cable providers, but actual cable content providers.
[SPEAKER_00]: on top of just actual the cable companies so maybe for example if you don't have cable you may not be just locked out of all this which would be nice because I would prefer not to have cable but getting a somewhat okay deal right now but in the years time that may change and it'd be nice to have some extra sources of content other than the internet.
[SPEAKER_00]: and of course I'll probably get a nice little peek of this pretty soon considering that the dev kit dashboard update that's the preview for this fall thing also leaked to the internet and been taken down pretty quickly but
[SPEAKER_00]: Happened to snag a copy for my dev kit before it did get taken down, so I will get a chance to check that out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Although, based on the YouTube videos I've seen, it's still rather boring because it's basically what you see in the screenshots.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's an Xbox menu.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's like, I don't understand, with each update, they kind of make it worse.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bring back the blades, damn it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, that's what I use pretty much now anyways.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just the blades.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just hit the guide button, the blades come up.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm hoping that's still the case with this because I just really don't care for the new update.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I understand why they're doing it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's because they can say, hey, look at all this ad space we've got.
[SPEAKER_00]: We can advertise games.
[SPEAKER_00]: We can advertise services.
[SPEAKER_00]: We can have third-party ads.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's really what it's come down to.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's kind of scary if you think about it because they're going to do the same thing with Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thankfully, Windows 8, you can turn that off, kind of like you can turn off Media Center.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I wish it was optional like Media Center.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would think by now we have the technology to where we can customize the way that the dashboard looks.
[SPEAKER_00]: If I want the Windows 8 look, cool, I can do that.
[SPEAKER_00]: If I want the old one, cool, I should be able to do that as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: you know what I like about the updates to the dashboard and it's not really even specific to the dashboard but just part of the whole update package I like the fact that they stopped making the avatars look retarded
[SPEAKER_07]: They're like reproportioned a little bit so their heads aren't all stupidly huge and they look a little bit more like people but they still look like avatars.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Miis still look like bobbleheads.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're supposed to look like bobbleheads.
[SPEAKER_07]: Miis always sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Xbox ones I thought weren't supposed to have that bobbleheaded look so I like it too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right.
[SPEAKER_07]: The avatars are like kind of neat but the Miis, yeah, were always just sort of creepy looking.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll just... It's only, what, a month away?
[SPEAKER_00]: So, I mean... Whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm just glad I'm not participating in the fall preview because I fucking hated that.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just like, oh, hey, look, we're pushing another dashboard update to you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Every day.
[SPEAKER_00]: Twice a day.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like, oh, I have to sit here for another ten minutes while this shit downloads.
[SPEAKER_00]: It wasn't worth it And I didn't even get anything free out of it Like the people that tested Was it the last dashboard thing with the XGT 3 stuff Where you got a free copy of Reach That didn't even work Well at least when they updated it Well you still get a games on demand version Sweet Yeah it's not too bad If you don't like hard drive space It's great
[SPEAKER_07]: My turn?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Microsoft's coming out with a new Windows phone that nobody's going to buy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's surprised?
[SPEAKER_07]: It has swappable controller pads so you can have a keyboard, a touchscreen, an extended battery, or a game controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: The problem is it's a Windows phone and everybody hates Windows phones.
[SPEAKER_03]: Totally hate Windows phones.
[SPEAKER_00]: Microsoft doesn't hate Windows phones.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, after all, they're redesigning Windows to look like they're Windows phones.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're just redesigning Windows to work on tablets.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the future for Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_07]: They want to get into the tablet business.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you can turn it off.
[SPEAKER_07]: What, the phone?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, with the PC version.
[SPEAKER_00]: Turn what off?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can turn off that tablet interface and go back to a classic interface on Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I understand that, but the damages are even done as far as... You mean you can make Windows look like Windows?
[SPEAKER_07]: Score!
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm really sad that they took out the support to make Windows look like Windows 3.1.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can make Windows look like old Windows?
[SPEAKER_07]: Score!
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, I am so ready for Windows to be radically different.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Windows is Windows, and you're used to Windows being what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it is sort of like, man, I sure would like to see Windows do something different.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I don't really think Windows now, I mean, there's not anything I've done and said, you know, I really wish Windows 7 did this.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm fine with Windows 7.
[SPEAKER_00]: Windows 7 does everything I need it to do.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't need to interact with social networks any more than I already am.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't need them to post an update.
[SPEAKER_00]: Matt just opened Calculator.
[SPEAKER_07]: no one fucking cares you know what's gonna happen is they're gonna get this whole thing with perfect social network integration and right then the whole world's gonna be like we're done with social networks let's move on to something else that's lame you know what when I looked at your article that top attachment I swear looked like a Wiimote that's right it's the new Wii Microsoft phone Mike I got nothing
[SPEAKER_03]: Microwee.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That kind of goes with what our friend used to call Microsoft Microflacid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, how about some news that makes everybody happy because it has to do with Portal.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is new download content for Portal 2 which is called Peer Review and it is a free download for PC, PS3, and Xbox 360 available on October 4th.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has more of the co-op modes for Atlas and Peabody who are the cutie little robots that like to hug so much and hey, this article has my desktop wallpaper on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gladass will be there, so that's going to be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's also a challenge mode for co-op and single player that has leaderboard support.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you want some more free stuff, the third and fourth group of tracks from the Portal 2 soundtrack, Music to Test By, is on Valve's site right now, which I need to download them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably some more ringtones and message sounds, I bet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually have the Turret Symphony as one of my ringtones.
[SPEAKER_03]: The little one that you hear the four little turrets practicing in the little level.
[SPEAKER_07]: You must be so proud.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am, shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not proud of your face.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well that's it for that one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, this is a little bit interesting and a little bit disappointing because I kind of, I read this and you know, I was craving Subway anyways because I had a coupon for it and although it wasn't for the store I went to.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, why do you need a coupon for Subway?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all $5 anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: Uncharted 3 Uncharted 3
[SPEAKER_00]: Dude, I saw that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I should have got a drink.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it's a 30 ounce drink.
[SPEAKER_00]: And basically, not only do you get a PlayStation Network code for that to play the multiplayer portion of the game, but you also get an exclusive item which earns you the ability to do the subway footlong taunt.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, the $5 footlong thing that they do in the commercials?
[SPEAKER_00]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you have that taunt as well that you can earn from getting a drink.
[SPEAKER_00]: And here I was all ready to get a drink.
[SPEAKER_00]: In fact... You even got a drink.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, well, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: To go back to what I was talking about earlier before the show started, how the person at Subway was really stupid, I asked for a large drink, and she rang me up for a small drink.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because she is stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you reach across the counter and pimp-slop her?
[SPEAKER_00]: I should have, but once again, though, I looked at their cups, and their cups did not have the new stuff on them.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sure that participation will vary by location based on whether they're phasing out their old inventory or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Often those promotions are even no purchase required.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can probably just ask for a code and they have to give it to you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe, but I'm sure this woman would have not known what the hell I was talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Should have been like, footlongs are $5!
[SPEAKER_07]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_00]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, footlongs $5, yay.
$5.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm probably trying to get you really psyched up about the online portion of Uncharted.
[SPEAKER_00]: Uncharted 3
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_00]: And of course, this is to combat piracy, but really it's just, you know, make a little money on the back end from used copies.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's what you call a shameless cash grab.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a way to put the screws to GameStop.
[SPEAKER_07]: And which I'm kind of down with, because fuck GameStop!
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I don't have any problem with GameStop, really.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a problem with GameStop.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, you like movies?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: You like zombies?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: You like movies about zombies?
[SPEAKER_07]: You like movies based on video games?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: I like Wild Zero.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Great.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you like zombie movies, there's more coming.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you like Dead Island, watch the big screen.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, I mean, they're trying to make it an emotional zombie movie.
[SPEAKER_00]: So they're basing it off a trailer, which is great because the trailer had nothing to do with the actual game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aren't zombie movies always pretty emotional?
[SPEAKER_07]: Zombies are into the pursuit of brains.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's heartfelt right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're like, brain.
[SPEAKER_07]: I feel for their play.
[SPEAKER_03]: And people run in fear with great passion.
[SPEAKER_07]: People?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's people in these movies?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the people that end up being food.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought people were just food.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you know what's kind of annoying, though, is all these zombie movies nowadays, especially starting after, what was it, 28 Days?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, they all have the smart killer zombies.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like the ones that run.
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't have the shuffling undead because the shuffling undead aren't interesting anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the funny thing about zombie movies was it was always just about the fact that they were slow but unstoppable.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now they're all fast and unstoppable.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're fast and unstoppable when they think.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which, you know what that really makes them?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not fucking zombies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want them to do a zombie movie where the people aren't zombies but all the animals are.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what would be great?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like zombie cows.
[SPEAKER_07]: They did a movie about Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, well, kind of like Pet Sematary, yeah, but they're all like church and the people don't come back.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they're attacking all the people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Zombie animals.
[SPEAKER_00]: But would they turn the people into zombies?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they'd just eat them.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'd watch that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be a good movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Copyright, Dark Sakura, 2011, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_07]: That movie sounds really stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: So do you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, next story.
[SPEAKER_07]: You got me there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love you, mean it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They are being distributed.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's distributed in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: by the same people that do PlayStation, the official magazine, official Xbox magazine, and of course there's Nintendo Power.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do Best Buys at Gamer and PC Gamer.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're actually saying that since people are, you know, first of all, poor, broke, you can't see the magazine very well at the newsstand.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's really not getting a big order anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the digital revenues are where the money is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, they're thinking about changing how they do Nintendo Power in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: They are thinking about doing it digital only instead of doing it in print.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then again, as someone pointed out earlier in chat, EGM went away and they came back.
[SPEAKER_07]: In my world, when Nintendo quit publishing Nintendo Power, it quit being Nintendo Power.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just did.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was the end of an era then.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now if it goes away, it's just another magazine going away.
[SPEAKER_07]: But when Nintendo published it, it was the official Nintendo propaganda magazine.
[SPEAKER_00]: That would be like Napster going away now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, when you said Napster, I'm like, is Napster still around?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a legit music service now.
[SPEAKER_00]: No one cared.
[SPEAKER_00]: When they're like, we're going legit, everyone's like, we're going elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, wait a minute, I can't steal music for free?
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, according to Gamasutra, Future is going to be doing their update for their plan starting on, I believe, they're going to show what the plan is for November 24th and later through 2012.
[SPEAKER_03]: If anyone cares.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some people care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I care.
[SPEAKER_03]: A little.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's talk a little bit about what's coming out soon, starting with October in the US.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't this hard music?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, we don't have music for this section.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I did it anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so what's coming out?
[SPEAKER_00]: I refuse to have music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyways, today actually Tetris Axis came out on Nintendo 3DS and it was great.
[SPEAKER_00]: Earlier this week Kotaku had actually run a little bit of they do this stupid video blogging crap for some of the games that they get to test and stuff like, oh look, we got the test!
[SPEAKER_00]: And they were showing off the augmented reality portions of Tetris Axis and man, that looks retarded.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm so glad that I'm not a big Tetris fan because it's just like, hey look, I put
[SPEAKER_00]: Dark Souls on PS3 and Xbox 360 Sometimes you're clever
[SPEAKER_00]: Gunslingers coming out on the Wii and this is kind of an on-rails western shooter game NBA 2K12 coming out on PlayStation 2, PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii and PSP
[SPEAKER_00]: Rage coming out on PS3, Xbox 360, and PC Age of Enigma, The Secret of the Sixth Ghost on PC No idea what that is Spider-Man Edge of Time on PS3, Xbox 360, Wii, 3DS, and NDS Hopefully it's not as terrible as X-Men Destiny because that game has gotten some pretty terrible reviews That game got murdered in the reviews
[SPEAKER_00]: It's really nice that you put this unfinished game out.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what's sad about that game too?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's made by Silicon Knights who at one time was a really decent publisher and now they're just bootsy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Girls Only coming out on Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: It is for girls only.
[SPEAKER_00]: They will shoot you on sight if you try to buy that and you're not a girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was hoping it would be like Boobalicious or something.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it's not that good.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just some crappy girl-targeted game.
[SPEAKER_03]: How to knit and shop.
[SPEAKER_00]: Face Raiders Photo Finish 3DS It's an awesome kart racing game where you can take a picture and put your face on the kart or the person driving the kart because everybody really wants to do that in a stupid kart racing game You know you can do that on the arcade version of Mario Kart?
[SPEAKER_00]: Completely unaware of that I'm so unaware of that I'm glad I have no memory of doing that at my bachelor party
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_00]: That wasn't your face.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sid Meier's Civilization V Game of the Year Edition on PC.
[SPEAKER_00]: And they made me drive as Luigi.
[SPEAKER_00]: That is just a crime right there.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it was Luigi.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was so messed up.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have no memory of it until I saw the video.
[SPEAKER_00]: Gabrielle's Ghostly Groove on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a rhythm music game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um...
[SPEAKER_00]: and then finally one week from today Just Dance 3 coming out on Xbox 360 and Wii, Playstation 3 who the hell knows when that's coming out because it's been delayed that is it
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so for everyone in, I guess this is the UK, is this all of Europe?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is UK Hey, for everyone in the UK, here's some releases this week Really the only one that matters, Chrono Trigger hits PSN on the 4th Crisis for the Xbox 360 and the PlayStation 3 NBA Jam on Fire Edition, which is a download Orcs Must Die That sounds fun I gotta believe that's a download, I'm not really sure I think all those are downloads so far
[SPEAKER_07]: Payday the High, Sega Bass Fishing Space Channel 5 Part 2 all that crap comes out on the 5th it's like really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dark Souls for the 360 and PS3 on the 7th NBA 2K12, Power Up Heroes and Rage as well as the Cursed Crusade all land on the 7th as well
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm actually really interested to check out Crysis on 360 when that comes out.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's actually next week, I believe.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because I played it on PC and it was pretty fun up until the end where the game decided, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_00]: Work?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't want to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm interested to see it from a technological standpoint.
[SPEAKER_07]: Crysis, you know, was a real system killer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it was a really unoptimized piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't wait to see if they've managed to make it run well on the 360 and PS3, or if it's going to run like Crysis.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, they did with Warhead.
[SPEAKER_00]: Remember, they totally revamped the whole engine.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like, oh, hey, yeah, by the way, remember that game that killed all your PCs?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, we finally got around to optimizing that, and now I can run in pretty much everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just want to see if it will run on the 360 and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_07]: My understanding is that happens a lot, and I'll ask you about this later, but I was talking to someone about GTA for the PC.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a terrible, very unoptimized.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, oh, it takes such a PC to run it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you see the link that I posted to the Vice City mod that somebody did?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I think I've seen those mods before.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got to play that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's gonna be so good.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyways, so there's the releases for the UK.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder what's coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about Child of Eden?
[SPEAKER_03]: Coming out on the 6th.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, this is the Xbox 360 list.
[SPEAKER_03]: F1 2011, Ogumosukoku X, no, sorry, Kyoku X, my bad, Rage, and the Gun Stringer.
[SPEAKER_03]: And moving forward to PlayStation 3, we have Major League Baseball 2K11, Child of Eden as well, and F1 2011.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: What did you say?
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: God of War, Chains of Olympus, Ghost of Sparta, HD, Rage, World Soccer, Winning 11, 2012, Ace Combat, that's getting a little bit further past.
[SPEAKER_03]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: on the Vita we have nothing because it's on the list for some stupid reason on the PSP .hack link for PSP the best it's a re-released AKB 148 that's idle to Guam to Koshitara and that's going to be a bunch of limited editions too
[SPEAKER_03]: Okashina Shima no Peter Pan Sweet Neverland is also going to be out in a regular and limited edition and Phantom Kingdom Portable will be out on the 6th with a limited edition as well Tsugi no Giseisha o Oshirase Shimasu Kimitoko no Hateru Kotonai Kurayami o is going to be out on the 6th by BoostOn
[SPEAKER_03]: and let's see what else we have on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just Dance Wii but that's not until next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the 3DS we have Super Black Bass 3D Fight which makes fishing sound cool, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the PS2, nothing because no one care.
[SPEAKER_03]: And on the DS, nothing although Super Scribblenuts will be coming out next week which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for Japanese PC gamers, Batman Arkham City, Battlefield 3
[SPEAKER_03]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some other stuff, but they're not giving us dates.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm surprised they're getting that so early.
[SPEAKER_00]: No one cares.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dude, Arkham City is going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just says October and it's at the top of the list, so I said it.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's probably just sometime in October.
[SPEAKER_00]: I doubt that they're getting it that early.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but it gives our friends overseas something to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_00]: Something you can look forward to, but when you go to the store this week, you're not going to find it there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't say it was this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I said it was this month.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is kind of strange.
[SPEAKER_00]: They've got this game coming out for iOS called Life of George.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, you might be thinking, is this like some sort of documentary game based on George Washington?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a Lego game, actually, where you're challenged to build...
[SPEAKER_00]: Different things that you see in this photo album using actual bricks.
[SPEAKER_00]: You buy a $30 kit from the Lego store.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've already kind of lost me there because it's a $30 kit.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm assuming it comes with like 10 pieces.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you apparently...
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: Really a $30 iOS game, and I mean, and I have not actually seen what this LEGO kit is, but I'm going to be willing to bet that it's probably, considering the price of LEGOs, which is really ridiculous, it's probably like 20 pieces, so it wouldn't be that difficult to recreate everything.
[SPEAKER_00]: But just out of curiosity, let's see.
[SPEAKER_00]: Life of George.
[SPEAKER_07]: That actually does sound kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because you're a Lego addict.
[SPEAKER_07]: And at the same time, devastatingly stupid.
[SPEAKER_00]: Whoa, I am surprised.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's actually 146 pieces.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's actually not bad for Legos.
[SPEAKER_07]: But from that picture, they're like really basic pieces.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, yeah, I'd imagine.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I would probably just play with the Legos separately anyway and not care.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I just go buy Legos.
[SPEAKER_00]: That game better be free once you buy that stupid kit.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's all I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's $44.99.
[SPEAKER_00]: That sounds to me like, was it TomTom or whatever like that?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, hey, you gotta buy this GPS thing, $70.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, did we mention the software's in there, $40.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, we hate you.
[SPEAKER_03]: We want your money and you are gullible, so give it to us.
[SPEAKER_03]: How's that, like that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's apparently super popular, but it's not getting a fall update, but it's not going away.
[SPEAKER_03]: They just said that they plan to refresh the Texas heat season in the future.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what does that mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: That means that, oh, we're not going to change anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're just going to say, oh, new tournament start.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: This, I can see, you know, being able to play a lot more without actual structure in a season versus 1 vs. 100, which is more of like a trivia game that's kind of, you know, host-driven and it'd be a little difficult.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, I can see how they're able to carry it on beyond, you know, like a season.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even the 1 vs. 100 extended play, though, just the practice rounds were fun just to pop on there and play.
[SPEAKER_00]: I never played them, and I'm disappointed.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm actually very disappointed that Bob Saget was not the host on the online version.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Bob Saget's a gangster.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's so cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you know, actually there's been one poker game that's come out that I like, and that's Poker Night at the Inventory.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still have got to download that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like I watched Jamie play.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, I don't want to pay $4 for it, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: You paid $4 for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can play it on my computer.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't like your computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cheapo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then put a copy of my account on your computer.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, that's what I'm talking about.
$4.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're so Dutch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do I look like I'm made of money?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're so Dutch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever, Jew.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dutch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about you talk about something that actually matters to people instead of just throwing out religious and ancestry-related comments?
[SPEAKER_07]: What in the crap are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_03]: Classic Game, duh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Classic Game.
[SPEAKER_03]: This isn't music for Classic Game.
[SPEAKER_07]: This music is entirely too happy for Classic Game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Start talking about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is this really the music for classic games?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the intro music, dumbass.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need something cool like the black hole music from one of the Advance Wars games.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pause that for a second.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got to play it in the background.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, before we get into this whole classic game of the week thing, I want to just throw this out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: The whole reason Jamie's been doing this thing for years is because it was stolen from me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know everything about classic games.
[SPEAKER_07]: La, la, la, la, la, la.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, you're not.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know everything about classic games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am the boss.
[SPEAKER_07]: And everybody knows this, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm the master of the vault.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm the one who keeps and maintains the collection.
[SPEAKER_07]: When Jamie comes to give you guys classic games, you know who she asks for them?
[SPEAKER_07]: Me.
[SPEAKER_07]: So anyways, if you like Classic Game of the Week, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I appreciate your work.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I appreciate Jamie's work in bringing you so many classic games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dan's not getting laid tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to get laid anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can flip me the bird for like an hour if you really, really want to.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyways, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can I play the music again?
[SPEAKER_07]: Start the music.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell them about the damn game.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: The basic idea is that this giant computer, get this, you'll never have seen this coming, has taken over the galaxy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the irony is that humanity created the giant computer.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you haven't beaten the game, sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a big spoiler.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so they dispatch you to go in there with your ship, one ship, and annihilate like jillions of enemies and wipe them all out.
[SPEAKER_07]: The levels scroll every which way, the backgrounds move, you face ships that make the giant ship in R-Type look like a tinker toy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Giant flowers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yeah, you shoot some giant flowers too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Robot fish.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really hard to describe how great this game is.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you can throw down an emulator or if you have a Sega Genesis, like I'm sure some of you do, you really need to play this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else should I say about it?
[SPEAKER_03]: What else should I say about it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember you trying to play this on the Nomad and yelling at it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: And when you die, you lose the weapon that you collected.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's not as big a disaster as it is in, like, Gradius when you die.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, you don't start from zero.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you really like the hunter or wave weapons and you get hit and lose them, then you have to, you know, soldier through without them until you get another wave weapon.
[SPEAKER_03]: This level pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys should be able to see this because this level is totally sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, how about if someone reminds me, I will repost it to our Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll put it on our Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll tumble it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll tumble.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like they're flying through the first level of Castlevania X. Yeah, except for like this game came out like four years before Castlevania Dracula XX, the Rondo of Blood.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty cool though, but yeah, I completely suck at this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll admit it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've tried.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really not that hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's way, way more difficult cheaters.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can definitely one-credit it, if not one-life it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I think our type is harder.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, our type is blisteringly difficult compared to Thunder Force.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, the first time you play Thunder Force 3, you think, oh, it's fast and difficult, but the weapons are awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: When you get a powered-up ship, if you're not really lame, you know, it's hard to die.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our type, it's just really easy to die.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: The difference is our type is like a thinking man shooter.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's slow, and it's all about positioning the ship and, you know, handling the obstacles correctly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thunder Force is much more of a twitch shooter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I see that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, how about some boss music before we go to break?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Play whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shoot, shoot, bang, bang.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pew, pew, pew, pew.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lasers.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that is our classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: My classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thunder Force 3 on Genesis slash Mega Drive slash Genesis it was on the Genesis and the SNES and the Arcade and you could also play it on the Saturn yeah all that too alright well guess what that's the end of part A and I'm going to do the ritual saving of part A now so stay tuned I will keep you occupied with Mega Man music this is the part where we sacrifice a goat
[SPEAKER_03]: No!
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, as long as we get to make some curry out of it later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take that, goat!
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, everyone, stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we are back from our break.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for sticking with us.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is, of course, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: And as I said before at the beginning of Part A, Rob is gone.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_03]: We locked him in the firehouse in Walt's bedroom.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we've taken over.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it is me tonight, DarkSakura, Loki, and that dude that I picked up on the internet, Dan.
[SPEAKER_07]: The notorious D-A-N.
[SPEAKER_07]: What what?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hearts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's Dan.
[SPEAKER_03]: I married him.
[SPEAKER_03]: I get to live with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: So how about we just go ahead and get into Rapid Fire News?
[SPEAKER_00]: Dazzling Darling by HHH
[SPEAKER_00]: Also the Dazzlin' Darlin' AKBK Mix Remix by DJ Command Whoever the hell that is Drop by DJ Taka featuring Kanako Hoshino Firefire by Stripe That's an awesome name, Firefire
[SPEAKER_00]: Firefire, Gold Rush by DJ Yoshitaka-G featuring Michael Alamode, May by Amuro vs. Killer, Second Heaven by Ryu Star, She is My Wife by Superstar Mitsuru, Smooch by Kors K, Vanessa by Suzaku,
[SPEAKER_00]: and Yellow Candy by Risk Junk and Zeta the I love the name of this one Zeta the world of prime numbers and transcendental being by Zetbok and I'm very surprised to see actually a lot of Japanese tracks in Dance Dance Revolution 2 I mean it
[SPEAKER_00]: I might actually have to check that out, I mean, with all the songs that they're putting in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's amazing, considering it's from Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they don't always get licenses.
[SPEAKER_00]: These games, they're coming out, they usually tend to put a lot of licensed stuff and weird old shit.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it's very surprising.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also... Does it have Boom Boom Dollar?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, I haven't looked at the other ones.
[SPEAKER_07]: If it doesn't, then fuck it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then, of course, also, Dance Dance Revolution X2 Max.
[SPEAKER_00]: They've got the unlocked code, which is unintentionally released, apparently.
[SPEAKER_00]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_00]: Dazzlin' Darlin', the AKBK mix, remixed by DJ Command, also from Dance Dance Revolution 2 there If You Were Here, the LEDG style remix by Jennifer Kimono Princess by Jun Looks like Roppongi Evolved by Tag Underground Antimatter by Orbit1 and Milo
[SPEAKER_00]: New Decay by Soda F, Possession by Tag Underground, Valkyrie Dimension by Spriggan, May by Omoro vs. the Killer, Pluto the First by Whitewall, and also the weirdly titled Zeta, The World of Prime Numbers and Transcendental Beings by Zetbok, and Vanessa by Suzaku.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something called Valkyrie Dimension by Spriggan actually just sounds kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to say, what, no dropout?
[SPEAKER_07]: But now I'm just wanting to see what Valkyrie Dimension by Spriggan is.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, lots of cool songs.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, of course, based on the last list we just read there, a lot of these are going to be featured in Dance Dance Revolution, too.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it might be worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, I mean, let's just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you don't check it out right away, I can guarantee that the game will probably price drop pretty quick anyways.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's actually not that expensive going into it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So...
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, it might not hurt to check it out.
[SPEAKER_00]: After all these bundles nowadays on the Wii, like the same price as a PlayStation 2 DDR game back in the day.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, you know, 50 bucks will get you a dance pad for the Wii and the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Zether pointed out that Soda Fujimori also did an awesome Gradius Trance mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Step Up Evolution's Kyle Ward and Chris Foy
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, it is now heading to the arcades.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, uh, in fact, the original design, and you can actually see this in the YouTube video that they first put up, um, actually did call for some sort of, like, dance mat control type thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, not sure if that's actually gonna be included with it, but it's gonna include a 42-inch multiplayer touchscreen, um, with a global interactive, uh, ranking network, according to the press release.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, um,
[SPEAKER_00]: It'd be interesting to see if that actually is going to include the dance pad or whatever stage.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it is coming to arcades rather soon.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, Song Pack 15 is out on iOS, including Pegasus by When Machines Dream and also Rock Robotic by When Dreams Machine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or When Machines Dream.
[SPEAKER_00]: When Dreams Machine.
[SPEAKER_00]: But those are coming out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, you can get those right now on the iOS.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow, 15 song packs.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's a lot more than Konami ever did on any of their Dance Dance Revolution mixes recently.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alas.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, how about something that has nothing to do with DDR?
[SPEAKER_07]: So, remember back in 2008, Ubisoft announced that they were going to make a game called I Am Alive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that game isn't dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're actually just about to release it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to come out this winter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Really.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, you don't say.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was amazed when I saw the story.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't this like three or four years old?
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought that it was, for some reason I remember that being like a PS1 game.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not even that old.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it was probably a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was 2008.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really?
[SPEAKER_00]: I thought.
[SPEAKER_00]: I thought it was 09 because I thought that originally it was supposed to be coming out in March and then it got pushed back again.
[SPEAKER_00]: But maybe that's March of last year.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just remember that every time they started talking about that game, there was some sort of catastrophe in the world and they were like, oh...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: and just, it's been backburnered this whole time.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, if you really want to play like a three and a half year old survival horror game, because you know how great that's going to be, watch for it to be hitting shelves before Christmas.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, not shelves at all.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, is it a download?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to be a downloadable game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Download it off the internet before Christmas.
[SPEAKER_00]: But see, that's great though, because it's not going to be like, you know, 50 bucks or 30 bucks.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to be 15.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can deal with 15.
[SPEAKER_00]: I...
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: They should just give it away at this point.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, I agree.
[SPEAKER_00]: Free would be perfect.
[SPEAKER_07]: They'd probably sell a few copies.
[SPEAKER_07]: It might be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I'll reserve judgment on this awesomeness.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what they need to do because it's Ubisoft?
[SPEAKER_00]: The cause of the disaster was the Rabbids.
[SPEAKER_07]: Release Beyond Good and Evil 2?
[SPEAKER_00]: I thought that was actually supposed to be a series that was like a primetime like comedy series with the Rabbids but they haven't done it yet they're kind of you know a one joke character who cares there's a lot of one joke characters that still have like movie after movie after movie
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, you know, if you're talking about, like, well, let's see, any of the dog movies that they have, like, was it Beethoven that they made?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's true, because they keep making fucking penguin movies.
[SPEAKER_00]: Penguins, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, oh, dear God.
[SPEAKER_07]: Disclaimer, this was supposed to be rapid-fire news, everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, you shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm the boss tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, you're not.
[SPEAKER_07]: To rapid fire on to the next news story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: You like rock band?
[SPEAKER_07]: You like Limp Bizkit?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, nobody likes Limp Bizkit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if you want to spend $10, you can get, I guess $7 if you want to do it as a package, you can get four Limp Bizkit songs in your rock band.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gold Cobra, Nookie, My Way, and Rearranged.
[SPEAKER_07]: Plus, they're going to get you for an extra buck if you want pro guitar or bass.
[SPEAKER_07]: Goody, goody gumdrops.
[SPEAKER_07]: In some actually valuable news, the PS3 plays Blu-rays, plays games.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, it's going to validate its existence because now you can get Chrono Trigger on PSN.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's nothing wrong with another version of Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't think of one bad thing about being able to get Chrono Trigger on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: They could charge $50 for it and it would still be worth the money.
[SPEAKER_07]: I ain't saying you should spend 50 bucks on Chrono Trigger, but if you did, I wouldn't be like, you're high.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd be like, high five.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chrono Trigger kicks ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: We should actually play our SNES one again.
Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's some news.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is kind of no one curve, but Harvest Moon is going to have a partner with a farm.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually the Surrey Docks Farm.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they're basically going to actually link the virtual environment to the real Surrey Docs farm.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's official and that's coming from Gary Jones who is the farm manager there.
[SPEAKER_03]: he said we got along really well with the team and were very impressed with the Harvest Moon games since then we stayed in touch and will be looking to work together on future titles so they are merging real farming with virtual farming so when you go to milk your cute little cow somebody is going to be milking a not so cute little but cute cow I guess so yeah farm twinning and when they run into that tainted beef you will also get that tainted beef
[SPEAKER_03]: and Frozen Synapse is a, has a new, you know, I would like to be able to speak English without going bleh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: You are not the count.
[SPEAKER_03]: One, one mistake.
[SPEAKER_03]: Frozen Synapse is going to star in a new Humble Indie Bundle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_03]: We know what the Humble Indie Bundle is, don't we, Dan?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have no idea what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_03]: That where you pay what you want and the money gets donated.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember reading about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't like the first time they did that like 70% of the people just stole the game anyway?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they can pay a lot of money off of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's all gone to good causes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyway, Frozen Synapse is going to be included in the bundle.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you pay more than the average price, which is more than $4.27...
[SPEAKER_03]: You also can get Humble Frozen Byte Bundle, which actually includes Trine, Shadowground, Shadowground Survivor, and the cancelled Jackclaw prototype.
[SPEAKER_03]: And pre-order the coming Splat.
[SPEAKER_03]: The money will go to Child's Play and the Electronic Frontier Foundation as you choose.
[SPEAKER_03]: So pretty cool, huh?
[SPEAKER_00]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: and also Frozen Synapse is included on Linux.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And last but never least, Persona 4!
[SPEAKER_03]: For all you people who like that weird game, there's going to be an anime version that's coming out in the US.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it is going to be released in North America and have digital distribution.
[SPEAKER_03]: The DVD and Blu-ray version are going to be out next year and it premieres in Japan on October 6th.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I was completely unaware until I was actually doing a search for, I was looking up an item for the new Professor Layton game coming out.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the Professor Layton anime movie is actually coming out over here in November.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, something that fans of the series should be interested in too is it's actually got the same art director and the composer, Shigenori Soejima and Shouji Meguro.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you seen that Konami has like a really blatant ripoff of Professor Layton?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Dr. Loric and the something or other, I don't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to try to find it.
[SPEAKER_07]: When I first saw it, I was really excited because I thought it was a sequel to that Dr. Lortrek, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought it was a sequel to that...
[SPEAKER_07]: What was it called?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was like Henry Hatsworth.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was like a side-scrolling game that, you know, I played it in the store.
[SPEAKER_07]: The guys, everyone was playing it in the store and they were just like, you gotta try this game when I try this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your copy is sitting over there on my desk.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, this game is fucking amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I saw that and I saw this Professor of Lautrec and I was like, oh my god, is it a sequel to that?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, it's a Professor Layton rip-off.
[SPEAKER_07]: A really obvious one, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, the guy looks like if he walked up to Professor Layton they would just be like, what up?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_07]: And the guy would like twirl his mustache because he's evil.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuckin' Konami.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember when they made, like, cool original games?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: Didn't they make Frogger one time?
[SPEAKER_07]: They made Frogger.
[SPEAKER_07]: They made Gradius.
[SPEAKER_03]: They made Castle Freakin'vania.
[SPEAKER_00]: Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_00]: What the hell, okay?
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's do another Frogger game for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whoa, hold on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why are you doing Frogger for the 3DS first?
[SPEAKER_00]: Gradius for the 3DS would be perfect.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, they should do Solar Assault for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Solar Assault was a 3D Gradius.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about YY Konami World?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why, why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Konami's YY Racing.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Was that supposed to be the next story anyway?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that was actually Loki's turn.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm ready.
[SPEAKER_00]: So let's talk a little bit about Nielsen ratings.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't agree with them.
[SPEAKER_00]: In fact, they have tapped what they call the top 10 anticipated games for 2011, for the fourth quarter.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sorry, but there's a few things missing and a few things I don't agree on.
[SPEAKER_00]: So let's go down the list real quick and I can point that stuff out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, not very obvious, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3 is number one.
[SPEAKER_00]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to be probably the biggest title this year.
[SPEAKER_00]: Number two, and actually this is the top 20 to watch for the holiday 2011.
[SPEAKER_00]: Gears of War 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: Madden NFL 12 Assassin's Creed Revelations
[SPEAKER_00]: Also kind of a no-brainer, you know, kind of expect that to do pretty well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Batman Arkham City, I could see that.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword, yeah, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_00]: Battlefield 3, of course, it's going to be a pretty big title.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just Dance 3, yeah, on the Wii perhaps, I could see that.
[SPEAKER_00]: NBA 2K12
[SPEAKER_00]: Need for Speed, The Run, Uncharted 3, Mario & Sonic at the London 2012 Olympic Games, Lego Harry Potter Years 5-7, FIFA Soccer 12, The Elder Scrolls Skyrim,
[SPEAKER_00]: That I would see doing a lot better than what they're saying.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dead Island did really well.
[SPEAKER_00]: I could see that maybe being a little higher up the list.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kinect Sports Season 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now this is where I've got to stop them.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, the first one did well, but I don't think the second one is going to sell that well at all.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, they have Dance Central 2 on the list.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, I would hope that the second game will do just as well as the first game, but...
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think that it's going to Resistance 3, that's a pretty good first party title for Sony and finally, Deus Ex Human Revolution Where the fuck is Saints Row the 3rd on this list?
[SPEAKER_00]: That game is going to do immensely well but it's just sadly missing or there's a bunch of other games that could be on this list that they're completely overlooking No one cares about the Nielsen's anyway
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I mean, they're just guessing what's going to be in the top five.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nilsons don't even want to acknowledge that Saints Row the Third is going to exist.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's be honest, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stick to TV, Nilsons.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where the fuck is Grand Theft Auto V?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not coming out for a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I want to play Saints Row the Third because I want to play Grand Theft Auto V. I just...
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, Grand Theft Auto V will probably be out by about a year's time.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, because they've already got their first half of 2012 already kind of spoken for.
[SPEAKER_00]: With Max Payne 3 and XCOM, I believe, are going to be the two games that... Well, no, actually XCOM is 2K, but not Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_00]: But Max Payne 3, I know, is their spring title.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've seen the trailer for Max Payne 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: It started off and I was really stoked because he had hair.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then he shaved his head and I was like, God damn it, Max Payne looks stupid bald.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just really bothers me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it just because he didn't want to render hair or something like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like when Snake was old in Metal Gear Solid 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: That just pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then they made it so I could make him look young and I liked playing with him again.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate it when they make my game heroes look stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: He did have the Burt Reynolds stache.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, the Burt Reynolds stache was cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: but yeah I mean they've got Max Payne 3 I know is coming and Agent is supposed to be the other thing they're working on right now but Agent got cancelled like a long time ago like I am alive ago yeah but L.A.
[SPEAKER_00]: Noire that was also thought to be cancelled for a long time and it eventually came out Grand Theft Auto 5 I could see probably fourth quarter next year Agent could make me wait for Grand Theft Auto 5 if it's good
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm really excited about the possibility of Agent being good.
[SPEAKER_00]: LA Noire was awesome Red Dead Redemption was awesome you know if they keep bringing me other games to keep me busy I could like wait for GTA 5 but it's like seriously I've been dying just to go back and replay The Lost and Damned they don't understand how easy it is for them to in the meantime do something look at this trend that's going on right now with all these HD remakes of older games just take Grand Theft Auto 3 San Andreas San Andreas especially San Andreas
[SPEAKER_00]: Give it some HD graphics, add multiplayer, boom!
[SPEAKER_00]: Who gives a shit about Grand Theft Auto V for a while?
[SPEAKER_07]: I would pay for those two games just to be imported into the Grand Theft Auto IV engine.
[SPEAKER_00]: and they've done that and that's all they would have to do but I mean commercially not as a mod but commercially if they did those games in Grand Theft Auto 4 style I would like I would pay full price for the remakes I would you have a mod team of like maybe 5 people that did it in a couple months what's gonna happen when you have Rockstar that has the fucking tools to make these games they have all the assets to make these games
[SPEAKER_00]: How long is it going to take a team of 30 people?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like printing fucking money.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like making your own money for God's sakes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just release them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give them to me and I will give you my money.
[SPEAKER_00]: It wouldn't take that much.
[SPEAKER_00]: And seriously, they could just piggyback it on the Rage Engine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't even have to really tweak anything.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just piggyback it on what it is now, and people would eat that shit.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're talking like Game of the Year shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Getting to the point where these games, I mean, not that it's ever going to be irrelevant in the video game world, but GTA is kind of losing its relevance because Call of Duty has taken over so big.
[SPEAKER_07]: and and people are playing other things and you haven't heard from Grand Theft Auto which was at one time the dominator of the game world and it's just like where is it at god damn it
[SPEAKER_00]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_00]: Me either.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's starting to piss me off.
[SPEAKER_00]: I could absolutely see them do an HD San Andreas.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it would make sense.
[SPEAKER_00]: It would be amazing just to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's great, but it's really hard for me to go backwards.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I had a hard time going back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I played through San Andreas after I played through GTA 4 while I was waiting for the episodes from Liberty City Pack.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I was like, well, screw this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll go back now and I'll play Vice City.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I couldn't do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just too funky.
[SPEAKER_07]: The old Grand Theft Auto games were great games for their moment, but now they don't look very good.
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't control very good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other than using cheat codes and running around and just doing messed up stuff, they're not really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you can still go back and play GTA 4 because GTA 4's got a really good physics engine.
[SPEAKER_07]: The driving controls are... It's more fun to run around in.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there's just not as much shit to do as there was in San Andreas.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: GTA V. It's like printing money.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I believe you, sort of.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is there more?
[SPEAKER_00]: Battlefield 3, that's almost like printing money.
[SPEAKER_00]: Huh, Dan?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh yeah, is that my story?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, Battlefield 3!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, speaking of printing money, man, everyone is losing their minds for Battlefield 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, I'm not even following games that close and I keep hearing about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, apparently EA, in addition to just paying an assload of money to once again take a shot at knocking off Call of Duty, has decided that it's going to have a Battlefield 3 worldwide conquest tournament in early 2012 with $1.6 million in prizes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: I always want to check out the battlefields, but they never hook me, honestly.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I hate to admit this, but I've played through the first two Modern Warfares, and I want to play through the third Modern Warfare.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just don't want to pay for it, because I think Activision needs to be beat to death with a bag of rocks for how hard they fucked Infinity Ward.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm caught between a rock and a hard place.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd rather give Microsoft my money.
[SPEAKER_07]: So buy that Halo remake.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure I'll get my hands on it somehow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, if you kick ass at Battlefield 3, enter this tournament, win some money, and hook me up for money, you know about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, how about some frivolous lawsuits, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: And how?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ultimate Pointer has filed patent lawsuits against Nintendo and a damn near bunch of everybody else for its, and I quote, easy deployable interactive direct-to-pointing system and presentation control system and calibration method, therefore.
[SPEAKER_00]: I call it my finger.
[SPEAKER_03]: but they filed their patent in May of 2005 although it didn't receive an official status until June 2010 which is four years after the Wii came out in the US anyway and they're also suing basically everyone that works with the Wii like anyone who's done games for the Wii in fact it's included retailers who are also involved too in making, using, importing and or selling of Wii systems, games and related accessories
[SPEAKER_03]: Also called the Accused Products.
[SPEAKER_03]: This will get thrown out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, this is going to get completely pissed on by...
[SPEAKER_00]: Amazon would just squash them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like Nintendo won't Oh, QVC, I mean, even But they're asking that Nintendo of America pay a reasonable royalty due to the alleged infringement Isn't QVC the home shopping channel?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it is You ever see the video where the guy was washing the windows and he fell off the ladder?
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw the one where the guy broke a TV with the Wiimote
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a good one too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Watch the QVC video where the guy, he's like up in the background demonstrating like this ladder and he just falls right off it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: People hurting themselves on QVC is cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm glad you think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, how about some FUs of the week, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I think that we're angsty people.
[SPEAKER_03]: My FU of the week goes towards hotels near Disneyland for not being cheaper.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_00]: FU goes to the stupid woman at Subway who doesn't understand how to put together a payment properly.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or take instructions.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or turkey.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or give you a cup with Uncharted 3 demo on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to F you to Ultimate Pointer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck those guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck them right in the ear.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, we really got our angst up quickly, didn't we?
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess we're all not all that pissed because we don't have Rob's soothing voice here to keep us happy, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck Rob for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck that guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: You like Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: and fuck the people who keep making Penguin movies too.
[SPEAKER_07]: God damn.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was at the movie theater the other day and I mean I was there to see the Lion King 3D so you'd expect that I'm going to see this but I saw the commercial for Happy Feet 2 fucking twice and once was enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dear God.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did it really need a sequel?
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck Penguin movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: So do we have any more news Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's this new...
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, of course, you know, they've got a few people in there that, you know, they're claiming, oh, I love games and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: But then they've got actually some hardcore people that have, you know, Zelda tattoos and button tattoos and all crazy shit like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which is a little bit more believable, but like, you know, rather than the, I remember one time my boyfriend played a game and it was just fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyways, um...
[SPEAKER_00]: So yeah, if you're interested, it is coming out quite soon from New Sensations.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's Geek Girls the Gamers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, if that's not ridiculous enough like the Playboy spreads that they do.
[SPEAKER_00]: But this at least has actual people in it instead of, you know, Photoshop, CG, fake characters that are topless.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kids like boobs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially nursing children.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember BMX XXX?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes That game was awesomely bad It was awesomely bad It was like Dave Mirab Freestyle BMX 2 but you could be naked
[SPEAKER_00]: but no it was an awesome game because not necessarily because of that because of all the missions that they would give you like you would have to it's like ridiculous shit like okay you're gonna have to pull off some tricks to get this dog horny so they'll go fuck another dog that's literally one of the missions in the first level of the game that is like one of like the first missions
[SPEAKER_00]: And then another one where you have to deliver hose to their clients using your bike.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the back of your bike.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the back of your BMX bike.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what was great about that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just go to the cheat code, enter Champagne Room, and then you can watch all the titty videos.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's that simple.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then you can go play Matt Hoffman because Matt Hoffman was just a better game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like that game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I thought it was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was ironic though that the PlayStation 2 and GameCube versions were uncensored.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or it was like the Xbox and GameCube versions were uncensored.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know about the GameCube version.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know that they gave me an Xbox version.
[SPEAKER_00]: The GameCube one was uncensored because that's what I had it on.
[SPEAKER_03]: and like didn't some like girl family sue after the fact cause she was under no that was Dave Mira sued no that was the um that was the Girls Gone Wild the guy game oh that was it yeah I don't even remember being sued it was just that some underage girl managed to sneak into it and then they were like you can't sell that game anymore I'm like that's fine we weren't selling it to start with so one more story and then we're gonna open up the skyplane sounds good oh sure
[SPEAKER_07]: So apparently, Microsoft is looking into auto-mature filtering options.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really understand what I'm reading here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess they did it a while ago where you can go ahead and set the games up so they won't be quite as mature.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which I think, honestly, is a pretty decent idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, you know, you really want to make Gears of War a little warmer and more cuddly so your 8-year-old can play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: They ought to make that game two ways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Violent and ultra-violent.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, this is not part of a show role, but did you notice there was a story this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: Someone had actually built a full-size Lancer out of Legos.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, really?
[SPEAKER_07]: That dude is my hero.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it works.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were a two-Lancer family at one time.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, not Mitsubishi Lancer, you dork.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the gun from Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, I was being silly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm opening the skyline now because I'm tired of listening to Dan.
[SPEAKER_07]: You live with me.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to listen to me all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could just go back to Rob's house.
[SPEAKER_00]: Go to Rob's house.
[SPEAKER_00]: They were talking about Road Rash real quick.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was one of those games that, remember, it was the Burnout Team.
[SPEAKER_00]: Criterion, I think, was actually going to put out a new version.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_00]: That would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_00]: The video was fucking amazing.
[SPEAKER_00]: You say they were going to or they are going to?
[SPEAKER_00]: They were going to.
[SPEAKER_00]: It got canceled.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why would they not do that?
[SPEAKER_07]: They work for EA.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: This needs to happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does anybody know someone at EA?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: For the record.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, don't have a make more need for speeds.
[SPEAKER_07]: For God's sakes, have Criterion make a road rush.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, fuck that noise.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why isn't Criterion making a new Burnout?
[SPEAKER_03]: So the skyline is open.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, I need to get that.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or see us on Skype at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we're awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can see us on Skype.
[SPEAKER_03]: Until then, I'm going to read some of our very, very few tinky Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't want to use whatever song that... Oh, we actually have a caller.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I will answer this first.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, it's CD Thunder.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played the first Contra a little bit, but I just wanted to actually get your guys' opinions on Contra.
[SPEAKER_03]: Contra is if you really hate yourself and want to be defeated at every turn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I mean, it was really hard because I couldn't even get past the first level without dying like five or six times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Practice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Contra's not very difficult.
[SPEAKER_06]: Contra is the kind of game that when you know where everything is going to come from, you'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not hard if you know how to play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really don't know how.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what was your other topic?
[SPEAKER_07]: Play the Contra on the Super NES.
[SPEAKER_06]: Say what?
[SPEAKER_03]: What was your second topic?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's about Metal Slug.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love Metal Slug.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Camel Slug.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw the Orange Slug Radio YouTube video that showed the inside of your vault.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I noticed they had a copy of Metal Slug Anthology.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And a bunch of other different Metal Slugs somewhere on various things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ironically enough, I own no Metal Slug for the actual Neo Geo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Metal Slug, I really like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really basic.
[SPEAKER_06]: All you do is you have a character and you go around killing people.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, how can it get any more basic?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have a copy of Metal Slug Anthology?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should get one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really epic.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's worth owning if you're a fan of run-and-gun games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically all the Contras, all the Metal Slugs are just the best run and gun games you can get.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you go out and buy them and play them, you will be happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And happiness is what you want, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Happiness in game form.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kill all who oppose you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Words to live by.
[SPEAKER_03]: Got anything else for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, a couple last minute things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd like to talk about two of my favorite games to play in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about one of your favorite games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we've got to let other callers come in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of my favorite arcade games to play was, I'm not sure if you've heard of this one, it's called CarnEvil.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I know CarnEvil.
[SPEAKER_03]: That game was awful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't you like it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it was awful.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a gun game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It wasn't very challenging either.
[SPEAKER_07]: It wasn't a good gun game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I hate clowns.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm glad that you like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very popular.
[SPEAKER_06]: You see those machines everywhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that I hate clowns so much that I didn't even enjoy shooting them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I can understand that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well thanks for giving us a call today, CD Thunder.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: We all float down here at Georgie.
[SPEAKER_00]: I sent Jamie, real quick, because I know this is going to make amazing radio, that trailer for the new Road Rash game.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a pre-visual thing that this guy is working on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dude.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we have a bike, and the life bar is a chain going to a deformed skull.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, that dude kicked a van.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now kick him.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kick him!
[SPEAKER_07]: In the face!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, oh, dude, he's grappling him.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you should have pushed him into that car.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would buy, like, five copies of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_03]: Got told.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you can see that some of the cars are untextured, so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, yeah, it's all pre-biz, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well hey, we got another caller coming in, so we're going to put this up on our Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_03]: How does that sound?
[SPEAKER_03]: I detect so much hotness.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, this is Orange Jones Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, it's the one and only Ranma.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranchan, hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kind of wishing Rob was here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, before I continue, I have to tell everyone in the chat room, take two drinks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, there is a drinking game where everyone has to do like one or two shots when I call in, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we've got apple wine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does that count?
[SPEAKER_01]: Good enough.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, no, I think I've got like some vodka left over from three years ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had a bottle of root beer flavored vodka in my cabinet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Went looking for it the other day and it was empty and I realized my other friend who was the local Jack Daniels guy drank it.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the record, we do have that vanilla vodka on top of the fridge that I got for the party and no one ever opened.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like my birthday three years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still there?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, what's up?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I drank that when you weren't looking.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't drink.
[SPEAKER_07]: I drank the shit out of that vodka.
[SPEAKER_03]: You cannot hold your liquor.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, clang!
[SPEAKER_03]: He has, if he did one shot, he would be red in the face and sitting on the couch falling asleep.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not true.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is, okay, two shots.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, it probably wouldn't even take one.
[SPEAKER_03]: See?
[SPEAKER_01]: So, Dan's a lush?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Dan's not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie's a lush.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan's not a very good alcoholic.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, Jamie, you and Patty would have fun together.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd like to come out to your neck of the woods and go drinking with you and Patty.
[SPEAKER_01]: That means y'all would be raiding my liquor cabinet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not that I would be complaining.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'd be contributing to your liquor cabinet and getting you good beer.
[SPEAKER_01]: See, that's why I have parties to get rid of the alcohol.
[SPEAKER_01]: At the end of the night, I open up the cabinet and I'm like, where did all of this come from?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's why for my birthday I have the beer potluck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, how about the show so far, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: So far, so good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I give it three out of four train wrecks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so we're not a derp-isode fully?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're a minor derp?
[SPEAKER_01]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's my podcast.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're the derpy ones.
[SPEAKER_01]: We derail under five minutes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any show that I appear on for the whole show is immediately awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've just been letting them get out their testosterone-ing, so it's been cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_01]: So what else is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I think it was last weekend, I believe.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was me, Patty, and Zeeba.
[SPEAKER_01]: We went down to the Jersey Shore, and Zeeba pointed us to a classic arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, so cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what else did they have at the classic arcade?
[SPEAKER_03]: Were there tons of pins?
[SPEAKER_01]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_01]: and Ninja Turtles
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, those are both really good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ninja Turtles, though, got harder when you had more people.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gauntlet actually got easier.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could last longer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, you got me thinking of Gauntlet 2 for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought I'd beat that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: After 150 levels, I set the hell with it and walked away.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I never got Gauntlet 2 on the NES.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I really wish that I had because it's actually kind of a cool little version I do have Gauntlet 4 for the Genesis which is basically Gauntlet 1 for the Genesis and it's got a quest mode and it's actually four players if you have a multi-tap but I've never managed to get four people on it at once it's one of the failures of my life well I can get you a copy of Gauntlet 2 that's not too hard
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really need one at this point.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never picked it up back in the day.
[SPEAKER_07]: And watching videos and stuff of it later on, I kind of wish that I had.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it looks like it was pretty choice.
[SPEAKER_01]: Indeed it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wish I had picked up the strategy guide for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there were pinball tables there though, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of my friends, Ari, he was playing pinball while I was chucking quarters into a theater of magic machines.
[SPEAKER_03]: Theater Magic is awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then I left that and I went to play this large old school Atari pinball machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Was it Hercules?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone in chat mentioned Hercules.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've never played a Hercules machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen the back glass for once.
[SPEAKER_01]: It took me five minutes, like five tries to figure out how to play this stupid thing because I'm pulling it back thinking all I gotta do is send it forward.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I gotta push back and shove it forth like a plunger and send the ball rolling.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that sounds like, you know, something just makes me think that I have seen one before, though, at one of the pinball.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't they have one at one of the pinball things we went to, Dan?
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought that they did.
[SPEAKER_07]: They didn't have a Hercules, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they just had that giant size old one.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was just a giant mock-up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that used a pool cue, a cue ball for the pin, for the pinball.
[SPEAKER_01]: That sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was pretty cool, but it got boring after five minutes because I could not reach from one side to the other very easily because of my short arms.
[SPEAKER_03]: How classic was classic?
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it just like that 80s era or did it get into the later 90s or was it just like early 80s to mid 90s?
[SPEAKER_01]: The only machine in this one section that was current was a DDR Max 2 machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fragile
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'll think about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me wait until the semester's over and then I'll see if I can be shipped.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think Patty would love that because she's about to spaz at her job, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been hearing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, she's now an assistant manager.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel very sorry for her.
[SPEAKER_01]: That makes two of us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you got anything else for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, no, that's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ranma, before you go, I want you to do something for me.
[SPEAKER_01]: That being?
[SPEAKER_07]: Stay black.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't stay black anymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's not my style.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the fuck did I say?
[SPEAKER_07]: Stay black.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I stay nerdy, man.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stay nerdy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stay that too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keep it nerdy, motherfucker.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keep it nerdy.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for calling in.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye, Ronton.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stay black.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, we will take a couple more calls.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the interim, I will go ahead and see what is on our Twitter.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a mention from Nico Nico-chan.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is tweet heart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tiger Claw sends us a story about...
[SPEAKER_03]: Dota 2 wants you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you ready?
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's a big fan wanting a beta key that they put up a sign.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: You paid $3,000 for an electronic billboard.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_00]: He didn't actually pay $3,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just photoshopped?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: What ended up happening is it would have cost him $3,000 to normally rent one of those signs for a month.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: The links people will go to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guys, we're taking one more call, so that's 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: We also have another one from Tigerclaw about Gotham City Impostors beta beginning on October 5th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's a PC game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Steam codes have already been mailed out to those who are accepted, and the client can be downloaded now, but the beta will not begin until next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any more calls?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're afraid of you.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're intimidated by your awesomeness.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone call Dan so I don't have to... Now you should extra call him.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well I'm closing the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're intimidated by you, I swear.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not intimidated by you.
[SPEAKER_07]: When I roll into the OLR, like, what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I guess since that's it, that's pretty much the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, how about... And I'm not going to do a fortune cookie tonight either, so... No fortune cookie?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's a derp-isode and I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should just play the quartet song again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I'll play the quartet song again.
[SPEAKER_03]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_03]: But because you have all asked for it, I will be doing about 30 minutes to an hour of pump up the volume.
[SPEAKER_03]: So stay tuned after the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nobody asked for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, they did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's like torture on the radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it is not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everyone thinks it's completely awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't help it if you are torture on the damn radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: You are punishment.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Rob's back next week, just reminding everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know you guys are excited that Rob will be back.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I love having you on the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wouldn't you guys rather have me here than Jamie?
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob does not suck on the air.
[SPEAKER_03]: He doesn't even really talk.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have been fucking... I could totally be on the show and you guys would almost not even notice that Jamie was gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to manage... She looks so mad she can barely talk.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wish I would have had a picture of the look on her face a minute ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone has to watch the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's usually me, because I'm the only one that can keep all of these rowdy people under some semblance of not kicking each other all over the place with trouts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, all the people are, like, cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: They ain't having no problem in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're just playing Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do not play Warcraft during the show, Dan.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why the band is going to suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I can stream video while you guys do the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it was really hard to play Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: End of the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stay black.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Thanks for watching!