[SPEAKER_05]: Classic DDR players quickly learned how prolific Naoki was with his many pseudonyms, but there was a strong list of others that made or were part of certified classics too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Session musicians and vocalists, licensed producers, and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't aware until looking up credits just how diverse Mauro Farina was.
[SPEAKER_05]: From the Eurocheese of Boom Boom Dollar, to the utter bop that was MaxUS's exclusive You Leave Me Alone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rest in peace, you legend.
[SPEAKER_05]: May a true artist's art live forever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now it's time for your hosts, Rob Roberts, Jamie Summers, and Loki to tell you about the last few weeks in gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Starting right now on the show, where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, my friends out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is Orange Lounge Radio Live once again tonight in November the 2nd of 2025 with episode number 1067 of our show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Off after a quick break last week and we're back again for our final month of episodes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, Loki, how are you?
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't until I watched you or your video tonight, because we do tape live Sunday nights at the Voice Geeks Network, twitch.tv slash VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's VOG Network, 9 o'clock Eastern, 6 o'clock Pacific, right after the Bobby Blackwell show.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you do watch us live, sometimes there's little things going on on the video, such as Loki with games in the background.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you have the brand new Katamari game going behind you tonight, which I forgot came out because I was a little bit...
[SPEAKER_08]: I was at a work thing this week and then I went to Disneyland and so like my mind kind of wasn't on video game news quite honestly for most of the week so I like forgot there was a new Katamari that came out um so I'm very curious did you get to play it?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, my feet.
[SPEAKER_02]: My feet still hate me.
[SPEAKER_02]: The panel was great, and it's actually one of the better ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though this is like the first year, even though I wanted to go to panels, I actually didn't go to any of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was too busy with people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to meet up with a ton of DBD people, a lot of people I know in person.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trixie Mattel was out of drag at PEX on Thursday night.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um, but I got to, it was, it was packed like sardine in there, like just so, so many people, but I got to run into a lot of my friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went to the drag show on Friday and, um, I actually was glad that I got in a day early.
[SPEAKER_02]: I, I, I had it in my head.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was gonna drive down Thursday and went Wednesday instead because I got, did my hotel room stupidly, but I'm glad I did because that extra day I could go pre-reg and then just chill and do whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um,
[SPEAKER_02]: um and then um and I tried not to really obligate myself to doing more than I wanted to like I was gonna do um the uh the other drag show the one that um Drag Trashly does oh and I'm not going um I actually skipped on a couple of things just because I wanted to chill um yeah we all need a people break now and then
[SPEAKER_02]: But the big day was Saturday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, it's so funny because now some of the people, especially at Stream Elements, there's a couple people there who recognize me now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So shout out to my Stream Elements friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I also went to the Horror Games Meetup, which was predominantly Dead by Daylight people and a bunch of people cosplaying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Allura Bliss, Tanis the Disco, Mikayla
[SPEAKER_02]: and just all kinds of people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I found a Fong and an Ace cosplayer.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a picture of me sneaking up on them as Pig.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just so many awesome people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I met so many fun streamers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I connected with a few industry folks for...
[SPEAKER_02]: doing some promos and actually a gaming idea I might have for a fully blind accessible game that I have an idea for.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to say much more about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to learn a lot more about haptics to implement my idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: So moving through that though, Sunday was just the chill day.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the day I went around and just like
[SPEAKER_02]: I was Swag Day, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just called it Swag Day because that's the day I just did everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I won some stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I just got a couple of some dice and a Jeff the Landshark U2s.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a Phasmophobia mug that I...
[SPEAKER_02]: may or may not be doing something with as a giveaway perhaps we'll see um
[SPEAKER_02]: I, um, and then, uh, I went to a party Sunday night and, um, it was the, the, the big dead by daylight streamer meetup.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was packed.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was horrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just, not horrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it was great, but I didn't really go in and drink or do anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just hung outside with a couple of, uh, new, uh, new friends.
[SPEAKER_09]: Horribly claustrophobic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it was way too busy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did go to this arcade that was across the street.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like you pay at the door and then it's free play for everything, although the crane games are pretty expensive.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I did win a chocolate cream Kirby.
[SPEAKER_08]: Random?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll try to find out where the crap I put themselves into a picture.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just played a lot of classic games, which I mean, I guess I could transition a bit into my gaming two weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they had a bunch of the Beimani stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a full official Guitarrera set up, but it was down to the count.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd have to look at my phone because you know me, whenever I go somewhere and play things, I take pictures of everything that I play.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did not have the para para this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was really disappointed at TwitchCon, but they had a bunch of other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, I think everyone fell in love with my cat because I show everybody pictures of Midna.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so I had to, though, head back to be able to check into my hotel before midnight in Anaheim because I did go to Disneyland and
[SPEAKER_02]: and I did walk over 20,000 steps at Disneyland and murdered my feet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually had to go by Nick's place on the way back home to drop off something for him to give to a friend.
[SPEAKER_02]: And my direction started to take me to Barstow, so I had to turn back around a different way and went past some ghost towns.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then went up 99 Circus Top at my favorite Bravo Farms.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does he still live in the North?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, obviously, I don't want to dox him, but does he still live in the North LA area?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's general enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: He moved.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't know he moved, but I didn't think he moved far.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, still basic area.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll tell you a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, also, one of the booths at TwitchCon had like the big, you know, like the thing with all the pins and you push your hand through it, it makes a picture of your hand.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did one that says OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: How Radio Shack of the 90s did.
[SPEAKER_08]: to have those pins.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was that where those would always be?
[SPEAKER_08]: Those little pin boards?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's fun though.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I would always think the large ones like the Exploratorium.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, the Exploratorium.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the big ones.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I think that's where I first saw them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Spencer's, you're right, had those knockoffs for a long time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like the neon ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Classic, not real nails.
[SPEAKER_02]: Arcade Monsters Arcade Monsters Arcade Monsters
[SPEAKER_02]: The D&D Pinball, Walking Dead Pinball, the Guitar Dora was down, I played Twinkle Star Sprites on an arcade cabinet and I was happy They're a pretty small chain too, they have some across the United States, I remember last year I kept eyeing them up because I wanted to go there but I just never got around to it
[SPEAKER_02]: Street Fighter X Mega Man Poppin' Music Puyo Puyo Esports Pokken Tournament
[SPEAKER_02]: Dance Evolution, Chase Chase Jokers, Marvel vs. Capcom 2, X-Men vs. Street Fighter 2, Vampire Hunter 2, Super Dodgeball, Bust-a-Move, X-Men Pinball, Sunset Riders,
[SPEAKER_02]: Dungeons and Dragons, Tower of Doom Tetris Plus I didn't really play that though They had the Sailor Moon Adventure game, I played that They had Zoltar, they had Contra Evolution I played Tank Tank Tank because I am always happy whenever I play Tank Tank Tank I haven't seen that game in years They had the Where's Waldo cabinet except it was Japanese one so it was Where's Wally They have a Where's Waldo game?
[SPEAKER_08]: I know the Nintendo game but oh wow I never knew that, that's crazy
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I mean, it's lots of stuff, but I really just, I had fun meeting up with friends and hanging out and walking around and just doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I have to address the elephant in the room that SSJ100 Matt brought up about the security issue.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there is a streamer who was attacked at her meet and greet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to remember her name because she's no one I follow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Emeru.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's Emeru.
[SPEAKER_02]: and uh she was um there for her meet and greet and then some person just rushes up on her and grabs her tries to kiss her the TwitchCon staff really didn't do much it was her own staff that pushed them off and got her away and she um she posted um
[SPEAKER_02]: that this person crossed multiple barriers at TwitchCon and got in front of other creators to meet her and basically negated what the Twitch official response was.
[SPEAKER_02]: She said it was a blatant lie and that her assailant was not immediately caught or detained.
[SPEAKER_02]: She says, this is a quote, he was allowed to walk away from my meet and greet and I didn't hear he was caught until hours after he attacked me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It feels like this only happened because of my manager pressing for it and not because TwitchCon staff present thought it was a big deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then her manager contacted the police and she's pressing charges.
[SPEAKER_02]: Twitch was going to suspend the guy for 30 days and then went to an indefinite ban after she pushed back.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they were
[SPEAKER_02]: They were saying that, this is what they said, in line with existing TwitchCon security protocols, law enforcement and event security were on site and responded to the incident.
[SPEAKER_02]: We immediately bought this individual from returning to the TwitchCon premises and they are banned indefinitely from Twitch, both online and in-person events.
[SPEAKER_02]: Clearly, that is not how it happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: um the video of the incident is really scary it was yeah around social media and it's one of those like you know that could have been a lot worse I mean not not that it was good don't get me wrong I'm not but it was like that could have been a lot worse like just I'm shocked at how he was really able to just walk right up to her essentially yeah it was wild to me
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and also I am trying to see if there was... Okay, so five days ago there is a post put out that Clancy, Dan Clancy, the CEO guy, he finally put out an official apology.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although like
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do they put stuff on their freaking Twitter?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because why not do something that actually means something?
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'll read what he said.
[SPEAKER_02]: It shouldn't have happened, and we take that very seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: We failed both in allowing it to occur and in our response following.
[SPEAKER_02]: We mismanaged our communications about the incident, and that includes the comments I made.
[SPEAKER_02]: I apologize to Emeru for all that took place.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because he went on and said some things himself.
[SPEAKER_02]: um the last thing on here you put a lot of trust in us by attending TwitchCon we take our responsibility to keep you safe seriously um I'm gonna say this now I am not you know a big streamer I have my groups you know I have my people um I did not feel at all unsafe for myself I also am uh you know
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty vocal if someone steps to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am going to very loudly say something about it and probably punch them, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: But all that aside, I do think that if you are a high-profile person in that situation...
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to have the security detail, whether or not you are teeny tiny like Amaru, I'm saying physically, or a behemoth giant of a human being.
[SPEAKER_02]: You always need to have security detail.
[SPEAKER_02]: It needs to be stepped up.
[SPEAKER_02]: They started removing the ability to bring a friend in line with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the whole plus one thing is gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if they're going to reinstate it next year, but even so, they need to step up their game.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was absolute mismanagement.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, I heard about it because I got a text from Sterlok, who, thank you for being concerned for...
[SPEAKER_02]: My well-being, but it wasn't like this was a big full-out someone ran into TwitchCon and tried to set it on fire or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was an isolated thing for that day.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was nowhere near where it happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to say, respectfully, I know you would be nowhere near that VIP area because that's just not how you roll on Twitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just fucking people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll put it this way even if I was ever a biggest streamer is that I wouldn't want to fucking meet all those people I'll have a panel maybe and I'll just you know say some shit at a panel panels are fun oh yeah there's a thing about Emerus couldn't bring her chosen person because he got kicked out for touching somebody when he was trying to get them away from her
[SPEAKER_07]: He got banned last year, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that says he was holding someone back.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, he didn't hold someone back.
[SPEAKER_07]: He detained somebody, essentially.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was someone who was trying to attack his client.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was doing his job.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they're going to have to figure all that out because Emer is not the only one who's saying, I'm out for next year's TwitchCon.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is a ripple effect happening here.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there were already people out this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so I'd be very curious to see what the ripple effect is for next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know there's still a lot of small to medium streamers that want to go meet their people, kind of like your story here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm wondering if some of this VIP culture element changes, but at the same time, one could argue the VIPs, even if we don't follow them personally...
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, they, they draw a lot of people in to the con.
[SPEAKER_08]: There are a lot of people that go to meet the VIP people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, so it's going to be interesting to see how Twitch sort of finds that balance for next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's got to be secret.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: Other than that one thing that I did not in person witness or hear anything about until after it had happened, I was fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a great time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I enjoyed meeting all my people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did get orange juice from an orange all over my shoe by poor Doc Martens.
[SPEAKER_02]: It really needed to be cleaned.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was in costume.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought like an Orange Lounge radio fan gave you orange juice.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought that's where this was going.
[SPEAKER_08]: That makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were free oranges that were at the meet and greet rooms.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, thanks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did go to the guild's meet and greets, so that was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I ran into Funko Beard.
[SPEAKER_02]: I told Funko Beard he's officially my gunkle.
[SPEAKER_08]: What crappy affiliate giveaway did they give this year?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I remember the last year I went was like keys for a mechanical keyboard that I'll never use in my life.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't fucking remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: Would they give you a bookmark?
What?
[SPEAKER_02]: They have those little plastic bags again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those little plastic things from last year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I, however, did get three Leon Kennedy blood splattered shirts.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a copy of Just Dance 25 that I need to redeem.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually kind of jealous of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Savalos in chat says, I heard Orange Julius.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yo, if an OLR fan wants to win my heart real fast, bring me a fucking Orange Julius.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'd be amazing.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, not that that's going to happen anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be leaving a lot of widows after this month.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll come back to you in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I did buy a bookmark.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you buy a bookmark?
[SPEAKER_02]: I did buy a couple of bookmarks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, they're useful, but I just, you know, they're not particularly expensive.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to see my favorite dice vendor, too, so that was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I bought a candle.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember the candle, but it's Lemony.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to say, what scent?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's from the same, it's the guy and his wife.
[SPEAKER_02]: She makes candles and he does the dice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was there still like the whole like artist alley in the back sort of thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, that's cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I actually bought the cutest hat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a bucket hat, but it's black velour with a cat face on it and cat ears.
[SPEAKER_08]: I missed TwitchCon this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I feel like I've just been a little bit out of the loop on Twitch culture.
[SPEAKER_08]: I lurk in people's channels, but I've been very not active in people's channels.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just feel like October, personally, I had a lot of stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had a very, very big show that weekend.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was not going to be able to get to TwitchCon.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if the cards align next year, I would love to go back just because I like a lot of the community.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like a lot of the people that I see there.
[SPEAKER_08]: and plus if it's in San Diego it's not that far like I like that it's on the west coast I'm gonna lean into the west coast privilege thing a little bit because it was a lot easier to go than if it was like in New York I had the best drive I had the best drive really though my drive down was really smooth my drive back
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: This was a completely different aspect of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: These mountains did not look like the mountains that I remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: So when I got past, I found myself a place to go pee.
[SPEAKER_08]: You must have been in Lancaster or some shit, way out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I found my place to go pee, and then I rerouted my map, and it took me back.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was only another hour-ish out of my way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, Dan loaned me his car refrigerator thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like an electric ice chest is kind of more what it's like.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I had, you know, I had, you know, nice cold snacks with me and my drinks were cold.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so when I stopped at Bravo Farms to buy copious amounts of cheese, which I got cheese for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember you texting me about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everyone.
[SPEAKER_02]: And by the way, Savalas, I think I've beaten you now because I found pumpkin spice cheese and I bought it for Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do they have any Trader Joe's?
[SPEAKER_08]: To be fair, I have scaled way back on the pumpkin spice thing in recent years.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds like you had a good time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope the timing works out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd love to go back next year, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did also have I came back with fudge and Dan and I consumed it all.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had carrot cake flavor and I
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, me and Carrot Cake.
[SPEAKER_08]: I also find it funny that you and I were both at Disneyland separately, but like a week and a half apart.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like not that far apart, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and we sent each other the same selfie, everyone.
[SPEAKER_08]: We did, we did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I sent Rob a picture of me on the teacups, and then Rob sent him on the teacups.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I knew you'd appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are a video game podcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: We talk about gaming news here once in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since we were gone last week, again, I had a work thing that was mandatory for a few days.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mandatory fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it was actually...
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm not just saying this because I know my boss listens to this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I actually did legit have a good time because we all work online and we work, you know, hybrid and at home and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it was really lovely to see a bunch of people in person and just kind of like get to do stuff for a few days.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then it was really lovely to just take an extra day and go to Disneyland, which I originally thought would be like a trip with coworkers.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then it kind of slowly became, oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not going to stay a day.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I called Victoria and
[SPEAKER_08]: And when I kind of started to sense that, like, all right, I don't think many of my coworkers are going to go, I called Victoria and she was, of course, in like a flash.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then thanks to a very, very generous person out there, you know who you are, I was able to get into the parks for free, which I really, really appreciated and just able to, you know, just have a great day at the parks.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, but yeah, kept me busy last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we didn't have a show on Sunday, but we missed a lot of gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Loki, I would love for you to talk about one of the big headlines we missed last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just some small stuff happening in the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, we knew this was eventually going to happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: We probably thought it was going to happen a lot sooner than now because with all the multi-platform stuff coming out from Xbox, it's like...
[SPEAKER_07]: One of these days we're going to have Halo on PlayStation, and sure enough, now we do.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have Halo Campaign Evolved, which is a remake of the original Halo game in Unreal 5, and now it's going to be multi-platform.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be on the Xbox, PC, and PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: But not Switch, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not Switch 2 because I don't think it has Switch 2 will be getting Halo Combat Evolved, the original Xbox game, and it will barely be able to run.
[SPEAKER_02]: No great loss, it's just Halo.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do find it funny that more people are talking... Like, the fact that this is also on Xbox is being completely overlooked.
[SPEAKER_08]: I feel like... Well, I shouldn't say completely, but majorly overlooked.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, everybody's talking about, oh, this PS5 version is coming.
[SPEAKER_08]: The PS5 version of Halo is coming.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's like, you know it is going to be on the...
[SPEAKER_08]: Xbox Platform 2 but I just feel people are pivoting so fast to a world where maybe Xbox isn't a player anymore and maybe we'll talk more about that later but now it's talking about the PlayStation 5 I am not usually as big on the original Halo as I am like Halo 2 and maybe 3
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and what's interesting about it, it is the campaign.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't have the multiplayer version.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I missed that part.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're not even bothering to put in multiplayer?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, there's no multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the campaign.
[SPEAKER_07]: Co-op for two players in split screen or up to four players online.
[SPEAKER_07]: Crossplay is supported, but it's not like the multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's my thought on this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that they're doing the campaign as it's... They're going the Call of Duty route.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're doing the campaign as this, and then they're going to do a free-to-play...
[SPEAKER_08]: Why get $60 from you once when they can get it from you twice?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you think there'll be a free-to-play multiplayer?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it'll be free-to-play, but it'll have microtransactions, passes out the wazoo, like Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or perks if you have Game Pass type of thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could see where maybe they don't want to cannibalize a multiplayer Halo thing they have coming next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think...
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, still, what do we think?
[SPEAKER_08]: Cats and dogs living together in mass hysteria?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, you know, Halo... It's not as shocking anymore now that we've had so many games coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And honestly, like, you know, we've... I think we've long moved past this whole console war nonsense.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm super with you actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've all just grown up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like Forza and Sea of Thieves and the other things already coming to PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_08]: This was an inevitability.
[SPEAKER_08]: This was going to happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just imagine for a second.
[SPEAKER_07]: Imagine for a second.
[SPEAKER_07]: We take consoles out of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's update the whole dynamic to something that's more current.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I think the thing about this is that the optics is a little weird to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think the timing of this is not great.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I realize they didn't decide the week before when to announce this.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot of thought that goes into the rollout campaign and the when and all that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I completely understand that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to get that out of the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that being said, there's a lot of...
[SPEAKER_08]: Xbox gut punch stories that have been happening over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I realized another one that came up the week we were gone.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, I didn't put this on the show world, but I have to bring this up.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Loki, I know you're going to know what I'm talking about the minute I start talking about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that is the whole word that came out about that the Microsoft division is being forced to hit a 30% target.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that potentially this is what is actually driving some of the Game Pass increases and some of the things we see and that, in fact, it may even be playing into some of the hardware increases and not just the tariffs as originally thought, which is extremely problematic if that's like...
[SPEAKER_08]: There's this arbitrary 30% that they're trying to hit on this front.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they've let us all believe that it's, you know, the tariffs, which, you know, I don't think you can say that's not to blame because you see it hitting PlayStation as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: But there was an odd disconnect about it doesn't seem to be hitting PlayStation in the same volume or Nintendo even in the same volume that it's hitting Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now we might have some insight why.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that is this whole that apparently there is this
[SPEAKER_08]: Arbitrary 30% profit margin, which by the way, is not common for the industry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Usually it's a 10 to 20% margin.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like-
[SPEAKER_08]: I do not see Microsoft being a player in the hardware business in another year or two it is that dire with what's going on right now and I'm not saying that to be like an angry gamer I'm just saying real facts name a win for Microsoft in the last six months I'll wait
[SPEAKER_08]: Now I'm sure there's going to be an Xbox fan out there that's like, this game or that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, name a win that offsets the losses.
[SPEAKER_08]: Name a W that offsets the L's that Microsoft has been taking.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this whole 30% thing is just really not a good look.
[SPEAKER_08]: The optics of this is really shitty.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now to hear that Halo's going to PlayStation 5, I think there are so many people now that are just like, I never have to buy an Xbox again.
[SPEAKER_08]: and perhaps there's a part I think Microsoft sort of has to figure out what do you want to be and I think we're hearing most of the business say they are ready to pivot to games like every screen is an Xbox and not so much have a focus on hardware but then you get these things out of nowhere that are like oh but we're working on the next generation of Xbox we're committed to the next generation of Xbox that's going to happen or you know we're going to release this really expensive game
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, handheld with a partner that, you know, probably doesn't even run as well as a Steam Deck.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you just, you find these weird ways that they're committing to hardware that are in conflict with that vision that is supposedly there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I think a lot of decision makers at Microsoft need to sit down and answer two key questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: Number one, are we all aligned?
[SPEAKER_08]: And number two, if we're not, who needs to get packing so we are?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I don't see how Microsoft gets out of this mess without making some serious changes at the top.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I've kind of been hinting at this for a while, that Phil Spencer's time, I think, is about up.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I...
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe two years ago I would have said, I hate to say, now I say, it's a logical conclusion.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not just, it really isn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh no, there's a whole, and you know, I don't think, the Phil Spencer was not the one that mandated that 30% margin either.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember who the, I can't remember the woman's name who's ahead of, I don't remember what she's ahead of.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sarah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: None of them have had good takes on anything lately.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because she's in charge of software, I actually think she has the least amount to worry about right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because the wins are all in software right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's where she's at.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even then, it's not really that much of a win.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't really been thinking too much about...
[SPEAKER_07]: The games that Microsoft's necessarily releasing, but there hasn't been a whole ton that have been like, oh my god, like, I need to run out and go get this right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's some that have been looking really good, but there's also games that, like, where's Fable?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been waiting for that for years now, like, where's Fable?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, we were talking about brand new Fable back in the Kinect days, like, that's how long ago it's been.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, I don't know, it's...
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby and Chat, Bobby Blackwolf, who tapes live before us on Sunday nights at VOG, is saying some things about this in our chat over at twitch.tv slash VOG Network, saying the Microsoft CFO mandated it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not Sarah Bond.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's somebody else.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the CFO of Big Daddy Microsoft mandated the 30% profit margin, and the Xbox division, Phil and Sarah, have to do whatever they can to meet it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's because they're going all in on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going...
[SPEAKER_07]: All in on AI over the main Microsoft area, which they're going to dump a ton of money into that, and that's going to flop.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I can't wait to see that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I understand a lot of companies are navigating this whole AI thing, but I think those that are going as all in as they are, as fast as they are, are going to quickly find that you get what you pay for.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Microsoft may be one of the first to learn that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually, and I'm kind of rooting for this to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate to say it, but that's just where my head is at.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really want Facebook to have disastrous financial outcomes because of everything they're doing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Facebook as a company has been
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been a shithole for years and a blight on the internet.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so I would love to see this type of investment sort of backfire on them, to be quite honest.
[SPEAKER_08]: So anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Meta hasn't done anything exciting for a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, the only thing that you can say is remotely exciting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Boomer memes.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're into misinformation, boomer memes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_08]: Facebook's where it's at.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I was going to say, like, their VR stuff was actually kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: The hardware was.
[SPEAKER_07]: Software, eh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, where's my Grand Theft Auto San Andreas meta?
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought you were tooling that to be, like, first off, why you would even port that to VR in the first place, no idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, like, I thought they were working on that, and that certainly hasn't happened.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, yeah, that was the only thing that was somewhat exciting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everything else is just, eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: So several people in chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: QuestBuster saying Facebook lost roughly 10% from their AI unit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: QuestBuster says Facebook lost roughly 10% in the past few days of their stock price.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby says they laid off 600 from their AI units this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: QuestBuster says Facebook is so behind right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: SGO100Matt says it would be great if the American oligarchs got knocked down a few pegs.
[SPEAKER_08]: That fucking part.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is what it really is.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not going to happen anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, but you... Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I second, third, fourth, and fifth, and sixth that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Facebook could have leveraged AI to combat the massive amount of misinformation on the platform.
[SPEAKER_07]: They could have leveraged... But they want the misinformation because more engagement, which means more ads.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, they don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all about profit over ethics.
[SPEAKER_08]: You are 100% correct.
[SPEAKER_08]: At some point...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: and honestly at this point all I do is I cross post promotion yeah and anytime I find myself opening it at a muscle memory I have this add-on on my PC called FB Purity which forces the chronological meme without any of the fluff I used to use that
[SPEAKER_08]: And the thing is, you really quickly realize, like, if I were to scroll my feed, meme, meme, politics, meme, meme, politics, meme, misinformation, quote, it's just, there's literally, like, what the fuck ever happened to cat pics and lunch?
[SPEAKER_02]: The last time that I used Facebook was specifically to post a GoFundMe.
[SPEAKER_08]: That being said, if I were to not use Facebook, a certain group of people that I know would have no idea what shows I'm ever hosting locally.
[SPEAKER_08]: I use it for promotion.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't type any personal insights on it anymore.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm getting the free ads from it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all it's worth at this point to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: So anyway, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got on a tangent from Microsoft to Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, it does feel like a lot of that big tech bubble is going to burst.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm like, how much of that is realistic thinking and how much of that is wishful thinking?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I will admit, both are coming into play.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think a lot of it is the perspective.
[SPEAKER_07]: You look at, for example...
[SPEAKER_07]: Sora, like what is that platform even?
[SPEAKER_07]: It is just a platform that people use AI to generate short videos of essentially trash, garbage stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a misinformation factory.
[SPEAKER_08]: You are literally creating things that aren't real on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right, right, right.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so what's the purpose of it though?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like how does that make that company money?
[SPEAKER_07]: How does that make open AI money?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well, they want to serve ads.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not a viable company.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not doing anything revolutionary.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why should we allow you to steal all of this IP?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just straight up, both them, Meta, everybody, just steal all the things just to generate slop.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no reason for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, anyway, we went down a rabbit hole, but that's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have feelings.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get into our gaming weeks and the types of video games that we have been playing this week, Xbox or otherwise.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, I have a feeling you are team otherwise.
[SPEAKER_08]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, apart from what I had already said for TwitchCon, I started Portal 2 last night as my retro game, which I feel kind of dirty calling it a retro game, but I literally have not played it in like 10 years.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I played that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like up at puzzle 10 in the underground section.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I got GLaDOS again, because she's a potato.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am still playing Dead by Daylight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got all the way through the event, finally.
[SPEAKER_02]: My pig is P92.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though I really want to get through the DLC that I'm on before the new DLC comes out, which I have to see Fire and Ash first and then play the DLC.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm frustrated by it because I do not want to play as Solek.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, he's a cool character, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole reason I play Frontiers of Pandora is to play my character that I have...
[SPEAKER_02]: Benwith from the beginning of the fucking game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks, Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just hoping that if I get through the story part of it, then I can go back to playing my character.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm not super invested in Sleek.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, he's a cool guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool character.
[SPEAKER_02]: Read the comics.
[SPEAKER_02]: I prefer my character.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why I play the damn game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am less invested in playing a male character.
[SPEAKER_02]: Within reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unless it's Richter Belmont.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll play Maria, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, if I'm playing Rondo, the game is freaking easy mode when you play Maria.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus she has that little la la la la la la la.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else for your game of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then we'll go over to Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: How was your game of the week?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mainly was working on Minecraft stuff, trying to get a modded... Still working on a modded series and trying to get the seed and the mods set up for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I think I've gotten that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got a seed I like and...
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been working on trying to figure out how to get that all set up and started and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there was that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Today I played through a Minecraft event that was Clix with InsideMC.
[SPEAKER_07]: They did an event with Clix Games that was kind of like MCC, so it's a bunch of different events.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our team actually ended up...
[SPEAKER_07]: Number one for points, and then we came in second for... Because basically the top two teams go to a final match where you fight each other, and then whoever wins that actually wins the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we didn't win, but we came in first points-wise.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we raised money for the Macmillan Cancer Fund Society.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember what it was.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Support, Cancer Support.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it was, I think, 1,900 pounds they raised.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I played this game that's behind me, which is Once Upon a Katamari.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I love me some Katamari, except I have some issues with this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the reason for that is like, OK, so Katamari, when we first played, it was on a PlayStation two.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was basically, you know, not HD.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: The problem is these games have been getting more and more elaborate as far as like the visuals go.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so playing this game, there's many times where the king of the cosmos will be sitting there talking to you and it blocks the entire center third of the screen.
[SPEAKER_07]: and so it's becoming now a problem with even though my screen resolution is going up these UI inner pieces are staying the same size it is taking up a massive amount of screen real estate and it is irritating because I cannot see what I'm doing in this game because there's too much UI that's unnecessary in there I think a good description I saw in the Steam reviews was the game lacks confidence in itself
[SPEAKER_07]: and the reason they say that is because they're not confident in their soundtrack because they're selling the old soundtracks as DLC they're not confident that the players will be able to learn the controls from the tutorial so there's constant control prompts on the screen at all times they're not confident in
[SPEAKER_07]: just going back to these levels again for replayability to like try to up your score so they hide these crowns in there which is fine that they have them but there's a lot of unnecessary menus there's a lot of unnecessary like hub worlds and stuff a lot of forcing you through like all these menus and customization like I don't care about customizing the Prince of the Cosmos I don't literally on like you can't really see it on the screen behind me right now but literally on that like the Prince is like
[SPEAKER_08]: maybe five pixels tall like you cannot see any sort of customization that you are doing on on your prints okay so in chat Bobby is saying that the king would interrupt on the PlayStation 2 game and it's a lot more to everything you're saying you could always pick from his cousins in the PS2 game too so yeah you can do that maybe not customize but it's you know changing it up you can
[SPEAKER_07]: You can do both.
[SPEAKER_07]: But he's constantly talking to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's doing it right now in this video that's behind me.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's just constantly talking and blocking a good portion of the screen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I saw some crown icons.
[SPEAKER_07]: These icons are coming right up over your... Yeah, there's icons and then there's power-ups that you get now, which also sit above your player as...
[SPEAKER_07]: So UI design is really bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then on top of that, they have these unnecessary hub worlds that you go select your levels from.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just feels really unnecessary.
[SPEAKER_07]: The other games did it so much better.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just want to play a game where I'm rolling a Katamari around...
[SPEAKER_07]: We start off in a room and then, you know, at the very end of the game, we're rolling up the whole universe or whatever the case may be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, that's all I want.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I want it simple.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't need all this, like, fluff and pizzazz and everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it is a little annoying that they have, like, all this stuff in the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yeah, this is another thing where they do, like, a cutscene and it has a bunch of stuff in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, is this really necessary?
[SPEAKER_07]: But...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a minor gripe.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's still an okay game.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a really great soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks super crisp now with the new graphics and everything, so I really do like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it also feels like it's just so sluggish to move around.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, it really is a slog sometimes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't quite feel as sharp or tight as I remember it was on the other consoles, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: That's just my gripes on it, but there are other people that agree with it, at least.
[SPEAKER_07]: How much was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it a $70?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or is it still leaning into budget stuff?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so it's more like a $40, $50?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's not super expensive, but it's... Bobby says $40.
[SPEAKER_07]: $40.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's definitely worth $40 or get it on sale.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a fun game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just there's like, I just think there's a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: All they really need to do to fix it is just like, hey, can you like have some options?
[SPEAKER_08]: A UI percentage scaler.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like take all UI elements and scale them down 50%.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it didn't auto-detect my hardware or anything, and so when I started the game, I was in a super tiny window.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was like 720p, just in the center of my screen.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, what's going on here?
[SPEAKER_07]: I had to go and adjust everything, because a default is a really stupid thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they just have a UI scale or something like that that you can adjust.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be so much better, or just an option like, hey, can I stop getting reminders for how to control it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy XIV has that, and I love it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy XIV has the UI percentage.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: basic UI stuff like just quality of life things that they could have just added into it and it would be so simple and make it so much better but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's still fun to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just minor annoyances that would make what would be like it's a good game to a great game I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well if that's it for your gaming week, I'll talk about my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, considering the fact that I was gone most of the week, I actually had a very active gaming week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, still playing some of the old standbys, Diablo 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: I feel like I'm going to finish all the Battle Pass quests this season, or whatever they call it, the season journey.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not really Battle Pass, it's the season journey.
[SPEAKER_08]: I feel like I'm going to finish it this season with my build, which I haven't done in a long time, so that's kind of exciting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been leaning into that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played Final Fantasy XIV for the first time in a bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got a notice that my
[SPEAKER_08]: House was going to get destroyed if I don't log in.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like, all right, I should log in and play and like check out some of the things they've done in the recent patches.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so I checked out their new deep dungeon.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played a little bit of that, that they just added the most recent patch that supports up to level 100.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I was playing a little bit of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I was playing some new stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I actually checked out Dragon Quest 1 and 2 HD 2D remake.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was really excited to check that out because admittedly,
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Reminds me nothing of the original Dragon Warrior.
[SPEAKER_08]: Quest or Dragon Warrior 1 has aged significantly and so of course they've got to do a lot graphically to it they're going to do some quality of life things like you don't need torches and dungeons anymore it's just an automatic thing because it goes with the art style but they really changed the story like a lot I'm talking like Final Fantasy 7 remake a lot
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just like, oh, OK, I didn't realize this is what it's going to be.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I feel like there's a lot I still can't really evaluate until I beat it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I will just say this is just like a new Dragon Quest game that in theory has some threads that are in common with the original game.
[SPEAKER_08]: But now I understand.
[SPEAKER_08]: I understand their big picture now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe it was obvious to some of you that are bigger and longer Dragon Quest fans than I. But it's very obvious that they released three first because chronologically it's first.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now they're releasing one and two to basically kind of, I guess, retcon the original trilogy as a chronological trilogy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because a lot of the changes they've made in one are to support three first.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Dragon Quest 1, Dragon Quest 2, Dragon Quest 3
[SPEAKER_08]: Like fairies and characters that have threads to three, but they weren't in the original Nintendo version of the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I would say it's very akin to the Final Fantasy VII Remake.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's got some elements.
[SPEAKER_08]: of the original story.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I would say the Final Fantasy VII remake actually had more threads than this does from where I'm sitting.
[SPEAKER_08]: But again, not bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm enjoying my time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do intend to beat it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do think it's a lot of fun to go through.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've put in a lot of collectible stuff like mini medals and the shiny spots on the map and the hidden layers and things like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've given you a lot to do and explore to sort of beef up what
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a new Dragon Quest game that has some threads to the original trilogy.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, then I also bought the Mortal Kombat Legacy Collection.
[SPEAKER_08]: I bought both of those in the same day because they both came out when I was gone.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have not played as much of the Legacy Collection.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this is the Digital Eclipse, who does the Gold Master Series, like the Karateka, you know, and the, um...
[SPEAKER_08]: The Tetris ones they did recently.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is their Mortal Kombat, but it's not technically a gold master because per Blue Sky replies, a gold master game is documentary first and the games are there as a nice to have.
[SPEAKER_08]: The collection is a games first, documentary second, even though I don't know from where I'm sitting, I get more excited about the documentary.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: or somebody that I know is about as good at Mortal Kombat as I am, I would do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I don't want to play against all the elite people online.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be a waste of my time.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I've been playing the single player.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was playing Mortal Kombat 2 Arcade and I kind of liked that if I missed a fatality, I could just rewind and you can put the moves up on the screen and so I can practice and do it that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I feel like that'll help me next time I actually play the game in an arcade again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I will...
[SPEAKER_08]: The muscle memory I have for Katana's fatality, block, block, block, block, block, block, high kick.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just have that memorized.
[SPEAKER_08]: I go to a hard game.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I get the finishing screen, block, block, block, high kick, chop off the head with a fan.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I don't know any of the other moves.
[SPEAKER_08]: I couldn't even remember all of Katana's moves.
[SPEAKER_08]: So having them on the screen has actually been very nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, so yeah, there's, there's parts of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like, I like that they have some of the more obscure Mortal Kombat titles like the Game Boy one and the PlayStation spinoff games, even if none of them are particularly good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think sometimes a collection is not necessarily about having all of the good games, but having a complete retrospective.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this seems to do a pretty good job from one to four.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm enjoying it so far, but more to come once I finished the documentary, because I am noticing something pretty big missing from the documentary.
[SPEAKER_08]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Today, October 31st, is The Wall.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am resting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not doing anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because the next day, yes, last night, I knew I had tickets to go see, I keep wanting to say Dear Friends, but that's not what they call it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't called it that in years.
[SPEAKER_08]: Distant Worlds, the Final Fantasy Symphony, happened to be here in Sacramento for the very first time.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I went, because every other time I've seen it, I've driven to San Francisco, LA, when I went to the very, very first one, or even, I think there might have been one in San Jose that I saw.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I went to San Francisco, LA,
[SPEAKER_08]: So this is the very first time it was in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I went to Distant Worlds.
[SPEAKER_08]: I went with Alan and we took our friend Dan.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like a late birthday present.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it was a good show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would say the first half was really like some of the best.
[SPEAKER_08]: The mix of music they played was like some of the best.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's because now they have intentionally added a ton of 14 and 16 into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I will say if you're going to see the show this year and you've seen it before, you can count on the fact
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to play Zanarkand.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to play One Wing Angel.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to play something from Nine.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they're going to play Liberty Fatale.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're always open with eights opening movie thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there's some standards they are simply going to play every time.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this time they played four songs from Final Fantasy XIV and they played four songs from Final Fantasy XVI in the second half, which ate up a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: When you consider it's a night at the symphony and they're playing... There's maybe...
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to say maybe 15 songs tops they play all night so that was a big chunk of the program and the 14 part was really obviously I love 14 it was really cool to hear that they had the original vocalist that sang Flow and I can't remember the name of the Crystarium song in the moment but it's the really good ballad that goes with and she was the highlight of any time I have been to see Distant Worlds which is probably like four or five now
[SPEAKER_08]: Having her there actually singing live, she was fucking incredible.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amanda Aiken's her name.
[SPEAKER_08]: She is incredible.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so to hear her sing the 14 songs live was great.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that was really a highlight and really worth the price of admission.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to be honest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not everyone is going to like what I'm about to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is my opinion.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can take it or you can leave it.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Final Fantasy XVI stuff...
[SPEAKER_08]: It just reminded me how really woefully mediocre 16's soundtrack is in the grand scheme of things.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it does pay me to say, I love Soken.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love what he's done for 14.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just think 16's soundtrack was not, it doesn't have as many standouts as even like 15, to be quite honest, or some of the ones that came before it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It does have some bangers.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love the prelude.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Titan theme is great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Neither of those were played.
[SPEAKER_08]: but they did have Amanda come back out because I didn't even realize Amanda does sing the ballad at the end of 16 but that's also the
[SPEAKER_08]: The most infuriating part of that game to me is the love theme, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is the most infuriating part of 16 to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was completely out of place in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've gone into this before and we're way past the spoiler limit at this point, but I cannot stand the love story with Clive and Jill in that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it feels extremely shoehorned into me.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so that by nature, that song that goes with that whole thing
[SPEAKER_08]: is just like she I can recognize and say she did a very lovely job performing it was a great performance and I can sit here and go I just don't like this the soundtrack does not the same now on the other hand I will tell me when they get Angela Aki I will be fair and say this I feel like they might have had her at more friends years ago years ago like 2006 or whenever I saw it at E3 um
[SPEAKER_08]: but I will say Alan and Dan don't know 16 as well so that whole segment was like we don't know these songs but Alan was like that first song was really good and I was like I couldn't even tell you what the name of it was
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the song when Ifrit and Phoenix are fighting.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby Blackwell says Ben Starr is now sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: They actually used his voiceover.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the only dialogue from those games I've heard in that performance.
[SPEAKER_08]: They do have Ben Starr's big accept the truth moment.
[SPEAKER_08]: Come to me, Ifrit!
[SPEAKER_08]: Except they cut that part out.
[SPEAKER_08]: But everything leading up to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they started playing that song with Ifrit.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was one of the songs they played.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: Plus, the one song they did play from 14 twice, so I heard it last year and heard it again, is the Beef Soft Tacos song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which, if you don't know what song that is, it's the end singer.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the very last boss fight of Heavensward.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you got to do the whole choir, and they're singing lyrics that sound like...
[SPEAKER_08]: Beef Soft Tacos, the Beef Soft Tacos, the Beef Soft Tacos Supreme.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what the lyrics sound like.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so to like, like, I'm sitting there in my seat and I know they're saying whatever it is in Latin or other languages.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just sitting there.
[SPEAKER_08]: All I hear in my head is Beef Soft Tacos, the Beef Soft Tacos.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like, and I was telling Alan, I'm like, they played the Beef Soft Tacos song.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's looking at me like, you're a fucking freak.
[SPEAKER_08]: And he's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, that was my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Busy, busy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get into some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we can go back and talk about some more Xbox stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So their revenue, as we mentioned, is not doing well.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is where that whole 30% requirement is coming from.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically saying, you know, that they have...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: them wanting to charge $80 for all of the games that come out all that type of stuff because yeah right now they are working on increasing AI capacity by 80% this year that's where all the money at Microsoft is going is into that type of stuff and co-pilot and putting AI into Microsoft Teams and Calculator or whatever
[SPEAKER_07]: Notepad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Notepad has AI now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, is this why Copilot, the equivalent of the 2025 equivalent, or Bobby says in chat, this mandate's actually from 2023 and we're just finding out about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: The 2023 equivalent of Clippy is now showing up in Copilot.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's worse because they have like
[SPEAKER_07]: Other thing, it's not even Clippy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like something else.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, I don't want to talk to that or do anything with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, it's a lot of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's also why you're seeing more employee cuts.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're seeing games be canceled, like Perfect Dark.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, that type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all because of these mandates to...
[SPEAKER_07]: Make Lang go up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Praise the shareholders.
[SPEAKER_07]: That type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's kind of annoying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, if AI can't feed people this month, I think there's going to be a lot of people who don't give a flying fuck about what Copilot can do for them.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's the topic for another show.
[SPEAKER_08]: But interesting that Microsoft, it's not...
[SPEAKER_07]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: you know maybe not making up what they could there but definitely going multi-platform will help with that but once again that also makes it more of a gamble when it comes to the next piece of hardware because it's like well
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't need to buy a Microsoft console because I can just play your games when they come to PC or I can play Halo on my Playstation now exactly so it's like so that's really gonna eat into the next Microsoft console unless this console's like really doing something different I think if it's just like yeah the graphics are slightly better no it's gonna be AI stuff is gonna be what they push in the next console 100% 100%
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, cool, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of which, well, you know, and I think, I think too, and this next story is really going to underscore this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, AI has always been around in video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: You would expect video games to have AI.
[SPEAKER_08]: This might shock you that I'm going to say this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Video games ought to have AI.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're going to have player versus environment or player, you know, your game has to have AI.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've had AI since the era of the Atari 2600.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's this generative and what it really is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've given this a lot of thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's my red line?
[SPEAKER_08]: What is it about AI that I don't like?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure, I'll use AI as an idea generator.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll use AI for things here.
[SPEAKER_08]: But where I don't like it is when it starts to replace art.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's not even necessarily, it's just the terminology gets changed.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not artificial intelligence.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, artificial intelligence in the sense that I've coded some rules that this thing follows, that something follows, given environmental circumstances or a random...
[SPEAKER_07]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, yeah, sometimes it may summarize stuff, but we're not to a point where we can trust that that is correct.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is most of the time going to be wrong, and sometimes it can't even do the simplest of things.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's just, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, leading into this story about a brand new release that came out this week that apparently a lot of people are playing on Steam.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is a looter shooter, so it's not really... I mean, once in a while I get into these games, but this one hasn't really been on my radar.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I am seeing some friends online that are enjoying Ark Raiders.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's a lot of discourse, trademark patent pending, around the use of AI in Ark Raiders.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: It does have an AI generated content disclosure on the Steam page.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the disclosure says that during the development process, we may use procedural and AI based tools to assist with content creation.
[SPEAKER_08]: In all such cases, the final product reflects the creativity and expression of our own development team.
[SPEAKER_08]: and the design director, Virgil Watkins, when being interviewed by PC Games N said, Arc Raiders in no way uses generative AI whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_08]: And in an interview with Eurogamer, Stefan Strandberg, CCO said, the experience of the game doesn't use any generative AI.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it turns out the details are a little like, so, okay, it's not using like language generation, but what is happening is that some of it is voice actors.
[SPEAKER_08]: So apparently the text to speech is not all voice actor, meaning it is in the voice actor contract that we use AI for this purpose, and that allows us to do things like the ping system, where it says every single item name, every single location name, and compass directions.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's how we get that without needing to have someone come in every time we create a new item for the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: and that's the interesting sort of muddy waters now we're in because they're claiming we don't want a voice actor to have to come in and name the, you know, thousand things that are in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, again, some of us that sort of really appreciate... Why does it need to do that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why does it need to do that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Then make it a very obviously robotic type of voice or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't love this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I feel like this is trying to be like...
[SPEAKER_08]: We're not really screwing over the voice actors, but we're mandating that they allow us to use their voice to generate stuff in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's just so many lines we'd have to pay them for, and we don't want to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that not against the part of the agreement with SAG-AFTRA?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not when your game is made in Sweden.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's and that's the loophole.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, so just something to consider with the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you know, if the voice actor is getting compensated for it, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just it's it's a slippery slope.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, apparently AI tools were used to create a 3D model of the game from a YouTube video.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was more of a research project, but not something that they're using in the game now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think AI as a play field is whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fine, but it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to be seeing more about this and a lot of companies trying to figure out the ethical use of AI over the coming years.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because some of them are completely signed in onto... This is a wasteland.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to use it for whatever we want.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think there's other companies that are really trying to figure out how do we ethically use this?
[SPEAKER_08]: And it'll be interesting to see how that works.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some other comments and chat on this.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby is pointing out the SAG-AFTRA thing only applies in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's why a lot of movies are moving production to the U.K.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, we need to get some worldwide lockdown on this.
[SPEAKER_08]: QuestBuster says, as a note, they used AI tools in the finals for some of the announcer voice lines.
[SPEAKER_08]: They recorded with real actors and then used AI to generate contextual audio, which they appear to have continued with ARC.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bobby says, I think in this case, they're specifically scripting what the AI voice is saying, unlike Fortnite.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see what continues to develop.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, pleasant little announcement from earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did I not say that it would take something along the lines of a new Animal Crossing to make me get a Switch 2?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's not a new Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me finish.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I said something like, and I said that very specifically, because Animal Crossing New Horizons 3.0 update is coming out and there is a Switch 2 edition on the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is free for any New Horizons players, whichever version that you have, with a lot of new content, although some is very specifically Switch 2 related.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this will be out on January 15th, 2026.
[SPEAKER_02]: Both versions available the same day.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you are going to be getting things like Resetti's Reset Service, the Katten's Resort Hotel, so they're bringing the entire Kappa family.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you get to decorate hotel rooms kind of like it was Happy Home Designer.
[SPEAKER_02]: which I think is awesome and you can invite people via amiibo cards to come and stay in your hotel I think indefinitely
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to be getting to the rest of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Switch 2 upgrade pack is not free.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is the one that's about $5.
[SPEAKER_02]: The one I was referring to that's free is the Switch version which is the one I'm focusing on first.
[SPEAKER_02]: but you also are getting upgraded storage your storage goes up to I believe 9,000 items you have the dream world and the slumber islands which you can just basically build infinite extra islands so there you go you get three it's not infinite three how about let me do the thing myself thank you um
[SPEAKER_02]: There are Lego items.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are new Zelda items, new Amiibo.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's Splatoon items.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's NES and Game Boy games, different consoles, retro toys.
[SPEAKER_02]: And with the Dream Island, as I was getting to, they're not permanent.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can start over.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can do as many different ones as you want to, up to three.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty excited about the Katten Hotel.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then though for Switch 2, there of course is going to be an immediate graphic improvement.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's going to be 12-player multiplayer, the megaphone item, mouse controls with the Joy-Con, and again, like I said, improved resolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm also kind of excited that we're getting the systems in the words section.
[SPEAKER_02]: The video game system is available in the store Like with the NES you get Clu Clu and Ice Climbers And Dr. Mario for Game Boy It even is specifying that you have a Famicom Disk System An NES, a Super Famicom There's the Ultra Hand, the Ultra Machine, the Love Tester All of those are back So that's pretty cool
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm with Artisuya in chat who says some of the in-game Nintendo merch is definitely tempting me to come back.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like I realize that the NES stuff and all the stuff they're putting in are bridges to the online console service.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like I understand that that is like an element.
[SPEAKER_08]: I still love  like I'm fine with them leveraging that because I feel like to me that's Animal Crossing kind of going back
[SPEAKER_08]: To its roots, in a way.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what drew me into Animal Crossing in the first place.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's really exciting to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I think all the Lego and the Zelda stuff is just a bonus.
[SPEAKER_08]: And to be quite honest, I didn't really bother with Animal Crossing when the 2.0 version came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I never bothered with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm excited to have a reason to revisit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although...
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm a little sad it's not a new game and I feel like this is a time buyer for an inevitable new game but then again Mario Kart we got a shit ton of tracks from Mario Kart 8 and we didn't get Mario Kart World until a little while later it wasn't that long of a wait for Mario Kart World so I shouldn't jump to that conclusion it's tempting to do but I guess maybe with Mario Kart there could
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, be that kind of precedent that they can turn around and do a new Animal Crossing real fast But it sounds like there's enough meat in this Especially because, to be honest, I didn't see the full trailer So a lot of this stuff Jamie's saying, I'm like, oh, I didn't know there was all this other stuff that's going in it too I just heard about that I watched the whole trailer I'm just like, oh, this sounds like there's going to be enough meat here That it's going to make the game worth revisiting Because I have not played it since 1.0
[SPEAKER_02]: and there's also if you don't have some of the amiibos you will get special visitors showing up like Minero and Tulen they can be random visitors that show up at the campsite so you do have that and I don't know what anyone's saying about this ripping off of
[SPEAKER_02]: The Hello Kitty thing, because this has been kind of a thing with Animal Crossing, the ability to decorate the rooms and have people visit.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is just an expansion of the campsite.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or it's also a little bit more like Tortimer's Island, come to think of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually think the 12 people multiplayer is really fascinating too, because I think about my friends that did like, and I thought it, I honest to God thought it was limited to four.
[SPEAKER_08]: They must have upped it to eight in 2.0 and I just missed it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't on my radar.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, but I had friends that did like an online survivor thing in Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now I'm just thinking about, oh my God, they actually can have a decent sized tribe now if 12 people can.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, that's going to be so fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and with the little cameras and the people.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's going to be actually super fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yeah, it's...
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's... I'm glad the game gets a little bit of a renaissance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo has these very interesting ways of just bringing these old-ass games... It's not even old, but just... Maybe because so many games in this day and age feel like they come and go in six months.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's very few games that stay.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I said it was from the before time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, yeah, with the whole COVID thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I definitely, Bobby talked about a very interesting sort of, I don't know if you'd call it like a Pavlov association or something, but basically that like Animal Crossing kind of takes him back to a similar mental state from COVID.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's kind of one of those, I can see that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can see where like Animal Crossing could be kind of like triggering in a way of that sort of time and era.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just kind of depends what you associate with it.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still wish there's like some stuff though that like it's like once again going back to quality of life discussions with some of these games like one of the things that's bugged me the most about this most recent Animal Crossing is the the first user on your Switch console that started the game is now in charge of the island and in this case my youngest son who doesn't play the game anymore is
[SPEAKER_07]: It is annoying to have to log into his account to do certain things.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should have an option in the game to change which user is in primary control of your island.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is stupid that it is locked down permanently forever to one user.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why can't they just add that to the game to fix that?
[SPEAKER_07]: It would just be so much easier.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome for me because I don't want Dan to do crap to my island.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's your option, but it should be the option to be able to correct that as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's weird quality of life stuff that they have, and also a lot of the stuff that they're adding, it's nice that there is some new things, but it feels like it's a retread of the whole paid DLC.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just decorating rooms, a little bit lesser to an extent because you're not doing the exterior as well, but it kind of feels like the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's only if you bother getting it for Switch, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're just playing the Switch version, no charge at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: The DLC, though, I thought the DLC was paid.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is all free.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Happy Home Designer, no, no, that's part of the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: According to what the trailer said and according to what I'm reading here, that's all part of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right, I'm saying that it was paid DLC.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was similar to the old DLC.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a Happy Home Paradise DLC.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's different.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right, that's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very similar to that, which is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not to further complicate it, but wasn't that actually bundled in for free, even though it was paid DLC, if you were like a Nintendo Plus thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly, exactly so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I would have been paying for the plus anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need a fucking map.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think a lot of Switch 2 people are assuming they have to pay $5 to play it on Switch 2 but technically you can play the Switch 1 version on your Switch 2 and you'll get the 3.0 that's the bridge that's kind of missing I wish they would address though with it because there's the whole animation when people come to your island and leave your island now imagine and multiply that by 12
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's going to get very... Oh, the loading area.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's why you can do the disconnect thing instead, even though the leaving through the gate is supposed to be safer.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is just all the same if the player disconnects.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because then you don't get the animation.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just says so and so is disconnected.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should just have an option.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I guess it has to load stuff, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, right now, I think, actually all it was is you just had the little, I mean, you have the thing of them walking off and on, but you don't have to watch the plane arrive and leave every time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only the person traveling sees the full thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking forward to having a reason to revisit the game again because I want a Nintendo collection in my basement.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure, even if I'm paying for Switch Online, I can play those games anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's just something about the collecting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look, I like to collect games and have them in my house.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think a lot of us do.
[SPEAKER_07]: They should have the PlayChoice10 stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what they should have.
[SPEAKER_07]: They should have the full arcade cabinets so you can play the PlayChoice10 stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would be cool if they had new games, but I just don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's asking for a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm glad we're getting this.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you mean not getting new games?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're getting Game Boy titles.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're getting Famicom Disk System.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're getting games that have not been available before.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but they're all things that are on the Switch Online.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just a bridge to the Switch Online catalog.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is very clever, and it's giving people what they asked for.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I agree.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's clever.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm happy for this bridge.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I was just like, oh, it might be kind of fun if there's a game you can only unlock through Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I understand that Nintendo doesn't want to cannibalize Switch Online.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's just one of those, it's a pipe dream thing that when I sit down and think, is this logistically the smartest thing to do?
[SPEAKER_08]: I go, no, it's probably not.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's what it ends up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just think it would be great to actually now have those items for the Super Famicom or the disc system or have the actual console models in the game Yeah, I do like that it's more than just the NES models, that's kind of neat
[SPEAKER_02]: It's funny, there's a channel I've been following that goes into some of the programming things that they did to make your game glitch out and modify for earlier versions and how much of that original code carries over into the modern Animal Crossings.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some stuff in there including part of its inventory system that is the same by necessity.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot... I've kind of gotten this...
[SPEAKER_02]: Approach lately, the yeah, so and such may be annoying, but I have a feeling it is programmed that way for a very specific reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or maybe it's just that Dead by Daylight has lowered my standards.
[SPEAKER_08]: A little calm A, a little calm B. All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where are we at?
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, let's talk about our favorite topic as of right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the Olympic esport games were dumb.
[SPEAKER_07]: I get the chess stuff, that makes sense, but archery on a mobile phone?
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, some of the games mentioned there.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I mean, it also makes sense...
[SPEAKER_08]: as to why Saudi Arabia is trying to buy up so much of video games because if they are turning it into a global sport and all of this... It could be bigger than the Olympics.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, well, think of all the money that something like MLB or NBA or those big sports leagues rake in.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's something that...
[SPEAKER_08]: The Saudi government wants to invest in, which is kind of kind of honestly, that's already kind of been a known thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're very originally we're going to be in a 12 year partnership that they agreed on a 12 year partnership back last year, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: And now they're just like, Nope.
[SPEAKER_08]: but it sounds like Saudi Arabia now just wants to maybe make their own damn thing like we don't need the Olympics we'll create a must we'll pay oodles and oodles of money to get some of the big names to come to Saudi Arabia and play their big games and you know create our own pretend work crimes and how they kill people is not happening yes
[SPEAKER_08]: That is what the ultimate hope is, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: That we will all just forget that all of that is going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Talk about something else I'd like to forget is going on, and that is that there's layoffs going on everywhere, everywhere, everywhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Amazon, as some of you have talked about in chat earlier tonight, Amazon is one of those companies that did get hit with job cuts.
[SPEAKER_08]: And a lot of their job cuts this week ended up affecting New World, which I don't mean to sound bitchy.
[SPEAKER_08]: because it is really sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do not enjoy hearing stories of job loss.
[SPEAKER_08]: But at the same time, I'm also surprised that New World was still going because I sort of thought that game was already sort of cooked some time ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: It seemed like it made a big splash when it launched and then it kind of disappeared.
[SPEAKER_08]: And unfortunately, Amazon has not had a great track record in the gaming realm, which is wild, wild when they own this site.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here I am on my soapbox again.
[SPEAKER_08]: How does Amazon not get this right to leverage what they have here on Twitch television into generating more hype for their games?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't understand the disconnect, but here we are.
[SPEAKER_08]: and it's not just New World because New World at least it felt like it had a somewhat successful launch it just kind of sank after that it didn't it didn't hold people it was that whole you know remember I said the hot shit for six months and then then you're gone vary that with New World except it was more like two three months
[SPEAKER_08]: Amazon wrote in a blog post at newworld.com,
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: You can still buy New World.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they are saying that PlayStation Plus subscribers for extra and premium can still get that until further notice.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Nighthaven is apparently free for everybody right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the company has committed to running the servers through 2026.
[SPEAKER_08]: But...
[SPEAKER_08]: They said they will provide a minimum of six months notice before making any changes that impact your ability to play New World Aeternum.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't wait for New New World to come out at some point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it may not because apparently Amazon, Bloomberg did a whole thing on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that usually means somebody internal sent something to Jason.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Amazon told staff in a memo that...
[SPEAKER_08]: That as part of widespread layoffs, it's going to dial back big budget games, especially MMOs.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Thrown in Liberty, Lost Ark.
[SPEAKER_08]: These are MMOs that Amazon has published, even though somebody else developed them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those will continue.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amazon not commenting on the Lord of the Rings MMO that apparently they've been making for a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: I feel like Lord of the Rings, even worse, sorry, not Lord of the Rings.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amazon, even worse than Niantic, a company I've been following for a long time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, New World, just so you know, there are 914,000 people still playing it on Steam over the weekend.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's interesting, but it just sounds like maybe Amazon sort of bit off more than they can chew with the gaming thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or again, I feel like Amazon may not know how to run itself as such a mega company.
[SPEAKER_08]: Coming back to the Microsoft thing, there needs to be some type of meeting in the minds.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is our company and what do we do?
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's a lot to ask, apparently.
[SPEAKER_08]: These mega companies just keep growing and growing and growing with no aim in mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby Blackwolf says Twitch was affected, but not super affected.
[SPEAKER_08]: They did lose some people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I did hear that some Twitch people were unfortunately impacted with this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's left running Twitch right now?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of what I want to know, but interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby says Microsoft should have sold off the Xbox division or made it its own company instead of buying Activision.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Quest Buster in chat says about New World.
[SPEAKER_08]: It had a rough launch, but it managed to retain enough players to keep going.
[SPEAKER_08]: The latest expansion was really good and brought a lot of players back right before they announced the party was over.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, if the latest expansion was good, unfortunately, the word isn't out there everywhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: So maybe Amazon just doesn't know how to market their games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, if only there was a major website.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although I'm sure there's plenty of ads for New World on this website, but I wouldn't know because I bought the thing that hides all the ads.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had a website that they maybe had lots of eyes in front of it and then a streaming platform.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but they don't have that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie needed to step away for a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: She is up next, but I think what we'll do, we'll just skip over to Loki's story and then come back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well, two of the directors from the Multiverses game have formed a brand new studio, Airlock Games.
[SPEAKER_07]: And instead of making giant fighting games featuring Warner Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: characters, they are now making a more smaller indie title that looks a little bit like a space...
[SPEAKER_07]: Sim type game, a little pixel art space sim game called What the Stars Forgot.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's their brand new first game for their brand new company, Airlock Games.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are putting it on Kickstarter and it's like, man, we're like 20 years back again and we're kickstarting games and everything is hunky dory and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, apparently...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, it looks interesting They're planning on launching the game in early access in December But yeah, it's a sci-fi sim management horror game
[SPEAKER_08]: It's nice to see the phoenix from the ashes sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I realize it's not the whole, you know, it's just a couple of the directors involved and so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's nice to sort of see that wish of, I hope these people that are affected by the layoff can go and launch their own studio.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's nice to see.
[SPEAKER_08]: I realize that takes money, that takes investment.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's nice to see that actually happen once in a while, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's nice to see that that's happening.
[SPEAKER_08]: And by golly, I hope the game is good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and I mean, also like with all these big game studios that seem like they can't fail or are too big to fail and that releasing, you know, products that are underwhelming or stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And all these massive layoffs that we're having, I think you're going to see a lot of these indie studios kind of come out and a lot of them be successful.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like we've seen that in the last few years, there's been a lot of these like game of the year projects.
[SPEAKER_07]: titles that are from smaller independent studios where these bigger studios are like, you can't make a game like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you can't make a game like that because it won't be as profitable as our shareholders want, but you can make a game like that that will be profitable for the studio and make them enough money to continue to make the next big game or the next project they want to work on if it's not a super huge game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I think...
[SPEAKER_07]: hopefully we'll see a lot of these people land on their feet and maybe spin up some of these studios and see what happens but then again then they eventually get bought and it's like continues again
[SPEAKER_08]: On that note, on a similar note, it is wild to me that Claire Obscure did not come out three years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, the Game Awards are next month, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: We're about a month away from the Game Awards, which is a whole other thing, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: To which I expect Claire Obscure is going to win a lot of stuff, although I guess some people are saying there's some other... What's the other big one that just came out recently?
[SPEAKER_02]: Claire Obscure, though, is gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is, and I think there's so much, you know, I think that's the one to be...
[SPEAKER_08]: but like it's honestly honest to god it feels like that game came out three years ago like it's it's wild to me that that was a game from this year
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, DarkSakura, we'll go to you in just a moment, but I do want to read some of these other comments that came in from chat on the New World thing because there is quite a bit here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby Blackwolf talking about Amazon and maybe where they misfired says, Amazon thought they could take down Steam because they were Amazon and Valve was not.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of companies have felt that they could take down Steam and have had mixed success.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe Epic being the only one that has had a reasonable amount of success and Epic has Fortnite.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Valve had a mandatory Steam install with everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Plus they were kind of first out the gate in that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if I want to say first, but they were early out the gate with the must-have game.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had the right formula at the right time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby says they were surprised that they couldn't just snap their fingers and make a game store and have everyone use it instead of Steam.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's the same EA with Origin, Ubisoft with Air Launcher, Stadia.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of people are learning this.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Gwen points out that New World is through Steam.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, yeah, it is, it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Looney Barred also mentioning that they were in the game when the news hit.
[SPEAKER_08]: People had just bought the paid track of the season and new cosmetics, and as soon as the main page told us what was happening, the game population went down by two-thirds in a few minutes.
[SPEAKER_08]: that's wild people wanted to just abandon ship that quickly that's I don't know I feel like if a game I really loved like I don't know Final Fantasy 14 let's say they say tomorrow oh we're shutting down the Final Fantasy 14 servers I wouldn't want to like just stop playing the game all of a sudden like I don't know uh it might be in that moment you might just need to step away from it yeah yeah
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a moment to process how much money I've spent over the years and all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least with Stadia, I got all my money back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I had to fly to Alabama, so it came in really handy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mishin Chat says, it makes me sad because I really like that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, just because I hadn't played a lot of New World, I recognize it had its fans, but it seemed like it had a real problem getting a lot of new ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is exciting news to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, and I immediately told Dan that I have to attend.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, one of my favorite ever sound designers and composers, Akira Yamaoka, or properly Yamaoka Akira, has been a mainstay in a lot of whatever playlists I have going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: He has done a number of sound direction, including Silent Hill, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Medium, Lollipop Chainsaw, all of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he is doing a US tour starting in February 20, 2026.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he's bringing some of his soundtracks to play on stage.
[SPEAKER_02]: and working with Raj Ramaya, who is known for his work on Cowboy Bebop and Resident Evil, who is opening for Yamaoka.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've also collaborated on a single called Encrypted Code Reality, which will be actually available yesterday on Halloween.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have to go get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the tour dates are starting in Los Angeles on the 19th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I probably would be trying to go to that one, but I bet it's going to be crazy expensive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then show dates in Phoenix, Arizona, San Diego, Orlando, Florida, New York, Dallas, Austin.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the tickets go on sale on Friday, November 24th.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Someone needs to make this happen for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: This news is actually really upsetting to me because his tour is the same week.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all like the dates are like it's only like 10 days and it's when I'm on the Star Trek cruise.
[SPEAKER_08]: I fly out on the 19th and I get back on the 27th yeah it's just bad bad luck on my part I mean if I really wanted to go I would pick one or the other um but I'm not gonna say actually technically that Orlando date is the day after we get back and the cruise is out of Orlando so you bet your ass the thought has crossed my mind could I extend my stay for a day so I can go to that concert but there comes a point where I start to go
[SPEAKER_08]: I think we're crossing the line into that's irresponsible at this point.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to get back to my real life and everything after all that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But don't cry for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going on an adventure that I love to do every year.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was bummed when I saw the dates.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Of all the weeks in the year, he had to pick that one?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I hope it does really well.
[SPEAKER_02]: He just knew that you weren't going to be able to go during those times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all about me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, this crazy American's gonna go on a boat instead of listening to me?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, he is on my Facebook, but if he's smart, he's not reading it either, so... I don't look at it anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: As 200 Matt says, maybe he'll add more dates if it sells well.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's kind of where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, I still wish, as much as I'm salty, I wish this thing nothing but huge success, because if he makes lots of money for his family...
[SPEAKER_08]: He'll probably do it again and maybe I can go the next time.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be lovely.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I wish this nothing but success.
[SPEAKER_08]: And for those that can go, please take pictures of the merch and let me know what I can send you money for.
All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, that concert last night, the Final Fantasy thing, the merch line, unreal.
[SPEAKER_08]: Half the venue was in line for merch.
[SPEAKER_08]: I shit you not.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were selling, I think, a bunch of vinyls that I saw a ton of people.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if maybe it was the first time some of them were on sale, but I swear I saw a ton of people walking out of that merch line with vinyls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, speaking of which, did I tell you what arrived a month ago?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: my N7 four disc four record collection for Mass Effect oh that's fun the box set I never got into the vinyl thing but I kind of feel like I want to I have a bunch and I haven't hooked up my record player yet I want to get one of those like my parents used to have the shelf that had the record player built into it I'd love to get one of those like old school like a console yeah yeah like from the 70s type of thing I'd love that thrift stores maybe maybe
[SPEAKER_08]: I honestly would like one that uses glass transistors that'd be fun alright we got another story here before we get to the classic game and it has to do with another let's shit on Xbox story and I'm not intending to do this but it's just again there's a lot of yeah exactly this is what people are talking about this week the new spiritual successor to Pixel Poops it's X Shit
[SPEAKER_08]: One of the designers from the Doom series, Sandy Peterson, coming out on Twitter to talk about, I should call it X because Twitter is dead.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sandy Peterson came out on X and said that Ensemble Studios, where he worked into 2000s, apparently Ensemble and the Halo MMO were scrapped by Don Matrick, who was the head of the Xbox at the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we all know he was a terrible boss for Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_08]: and he said in 2008 Ensemble Studios started planning a gigantic MMO set in the Halo universe.
[SPEAKER_08]: We codenamed it Titan.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was to take place tens of thousands a year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why does everybody call their MMO Titan?
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say why Blizzard did the same fucking thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop calling your cancelled MMOs Titan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, we codenamed it Titan.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was to take place tens of thousands of years ago before the Halos were set off and destroyed all sentient life in the galaxy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, it goes on and on and said the lowest estimate we and Microsoft had for the game's total income was $1.1 billion.
[SPEAKER_08]: But apparently, Dom Matric came in and canceled it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was all brought to naught when Dom Matric realized that his stock bonus was based on the income Microsoft had from games in three years.
[SPEAKER_08]: You see, we estimated three and a half years to finish Titan if we did it right.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's beyond Matric's drop-dead date.
[SPEAKER_08]: So by firing all of Ensemble, he didn't have to pay for our expensive studio for three years, and he didn't care about Titan.
[SPEAKER_08]: All he lost was a game studio who never sold less than 3 million copies of everything we made.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't believe he did justice to Microsoft stockholders, but hey, Don started as an EA hatchet man, so what would you expect?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yikes!
[SPEAKER_08]: But if we were to bring out the wield of plausibility, do we believe that Don Matrick would make a dumbass decision like this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's one of those things that just goes to, you know, and maybe other people would look at it and go, well, he got the stock bonus.
[SPEAKER_08]: So was it a bad decision or was it a smart one?
[SPEAKER_08]: To which I say, shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, let's go back to a simpler time with our next segment.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go back to an era well before stock bonuses, at least I think they were.
[SPEAKER_01]: And now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where I'll dive into the vault and pull out a classic and tell you about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's time for the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And apologies, a little bit of the loud noise from said game making its way out over the stream there.
[SPEAKER_08]: But what did you pick tonight, DarkSakura, for the classic game?
[SPEAKER_02]: I picked a game that is more colloquially known outside of Japan as Gourmet Warriors.
[SPEAKER_02]: Its actual name is Bishoku Sentai Barayaro, which is Rose Rascal's Gourmet Squadron.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a side-scrolling beat-em-up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was developed by WINS and published by Virgin Interactive Entertainment for the Super Famicom in 1995.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, Japanese-only release.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll get into the re-release about it a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_02]: but it's basically it's just like a total lampoon on Sentai the Sentai genre so you have five stages with a time limit and you lose you basically have to go through and pick up ingredients and each of these stages you lose all of your ingredients when the timer reaches zero but you have multiple lives so you can just
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like if the character dies, it's an automatic game over.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you have to focus on the time limit if you want to recuperate your strength after fighting the final boss.
[SPEAKER_02]: You also have a button in the game that makes the character do sentai poses when held down and used with a directional pad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just there for flex.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically in the year 20XDX, you have a city known as Zeus Heaven Magic City, recovered after World War III, and the inhabitants have to ingest protein in whatever food they can find.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there is an organization called Bath that basically is just constantly expanding corporate, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that their names are just like we have.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Ma'am.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we have Very Good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those are their names.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bonjour, Mademoiselle, and Trs Bien.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Retro Gamer gave it a 79% saying that one should at least play it once.
[SPEAKER_02]: Their quote is, if you can stomach Chowai Nikki or enjoy it, then this might be right up your alley.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's a silly one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it got re-released on January 30th, 2018, Blaze Pro Pico Interactive.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they also, Pico, created and published a US SNES cartridge with a full English translation called Gourmet Warriors.
[SPEAKER_08]: so there you go that's the game there's not much else to it I have to admit not not a game I think I ever have seen somehow but um very very much of that you know Final Fight clone era uh but kind of yeah I'd check this out there's always beat-em-ups where are you getting new beat-em-ups now based on old things yeah that's true that's true so
[SPEAKER_02]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also just think that the cover is absolute fan service because Mademoiselle there is very busty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Boobalicious?
[SPEAKER_02]: Busty.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's busting out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's armor.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's highly armored.
[SPEAKER_02]: Her boobs are not armored.
[SPEAKER_02]: The most protected part of her boobs are the nips.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's cover a couple other quick topics here in a segment we call Rapid Fire News.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so Limited Run Games is having their 10th anniversary.
[SPEAKER_07]: Has it really been that long?
[SPEAKER_07]: and they've done a lot of announcements of Switch games coming out so starting off we have Onimusha 2 Samurai's Destiny coming out next year Little Goody Two Shoes Turbo Overkill Jay and Silent Bob's Chronic Blunt Punch Xenotilt Hostile Pinball Action that's a cool name TMNT Tactical Takedown Bad Cheese
[SPEAKER_07]: I love these names, Fuga Melodies of Steel 1 and 2 and 3 coming next year, Fear Effect 2, Retro Helix, Choa Aineke Collection, Valiant Hearts, Coming Home, Double Shake, Slam City with Scottie Pippen, Respect Edition, Broken Reality,
[SPEAKER_07]: Renane, Lil Samson, Arrow the Acrobat Collection, Ernest Evans Collection, Sigma Star Saga DX, Shantae, it's a brand new game, Keyman and the Masters of the Universe, Dragon Pearl of Destruction, I think that's a beat-em-up game too, which sounds awesome, Capcom, Arcade Stadium is also coming out, 2026.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots of physical releases.
[SPEAKER_07]: that unfortunately I probably won't buy.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was something really interesting I was seeing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Dark Tetsuya posted it to Blue Sky, but apparently something about how the Little Samson, like the way that they're releasing it has to do with like trademark abandonment in Japan is like how they were able to actually make that happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to actually pull up his feed to see if I can find that originally skeet on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: but of course now I can't find it I hate that term so much sorry about that um
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Note to the legals.
[SPEAKER_08]: LRG using Japan's arbitration system.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, this is a post from All City Slop Shop.
[SPEAKER_08]: Note to the legals.
[SPEAKER_08]: LRG is using Japan's arbitration system for orphaned games to reissue Little Samson.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you can demonstrate that you've made a genuine effort to contact or identify a potential rights owner to no avail, you can legally commercialize an old game by paying royalties to the Japanese government.
[SPEAKER_08]: and apparently that is how Little Samson is happening.
[SPEAKER_08]: To which I say, Guardian Legend wins.
[SPEAKER_08]: How many royalties do you have to pay for Guardian Legends?
[SPEAKER_08]: Right, exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then Dark Tootsie posted President Cat.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think there was a tie into a TV thing with that particular game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that one's going to be a lot harder.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have President Cat on my portable emulation device.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, what else do you have in the news front, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: And then along with that, we have a Call of Duty movie coming.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're being written by the writers from Yellowstone and Friday Night Lights.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, I can see the demo now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I can't wait to not see that movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's a code for the Dracula X Nocturne in the Moonlight for Saturn, also known, it was the Castlevania Cynthia Knight version, the one that I just finished playing through.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has kind of an Easter egg now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's escaped notice for years, but if you enter your name in as staff, you get right to the credit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe any percent speed run, shenanigans?
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: And as mentioned in the intro to tonight's show by Jason, a little tribute there to Mauro Farina.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope I said that right.
[SPEAKER_08]: A really large name in Italian Eurobeat and Eurodance scene who was a producer there.
[SPEAKER_08]: He did pass away this week at the age of 68.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you actually look up his book,
[SPEAKER_08]: Bio, or just search like RemiWiki for some of the things he's contributed to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boom Boom Dollar, The Red Monster Mix, Upside Down, which was... So he released a lot of things under pseudonyms, just like a lot of people that worked on the old DDR did back in the day.
[SPEAKER_08]: You Leave Me Alone, he had a credit on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So he had a lot to do with the old DDR series.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you were a fan of...
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, some of the legendary songs in that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You probably heard his work at some point.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, RIP.
[SPEAKER_08]: 68, pretty young in the grand scheme of things.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, very unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's travel around the world and check out some release dates.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's start in the US.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well we've got A Thousand Times Resist on PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series Age of Empires 4 Anniversary Edition on PlayStation 5 Cling to Darkness on PC Europa Universal Alice on 5 on PC Football Manager 26 on PC, Mac, PlayStation 5 Xbox One, Xbox Series, iOS and Android
[SPEAKER_07]: Satisfactory on PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series Bypad 2 on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series The Fable, oh my god, it's coming out!
[SPEAKER_07]: Except it's not Manga Build Roguelike on PC and Nintendo Switch Yeah, that's a different thing
[SPEAKER_07]: Second Son on PC, Sonic Rumble on PC, iOS, and Android.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got Amanda the Adventurer 3 on PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chicken Police Into the Hive on Nintendo Switch.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's on the Switch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Point and click adventure game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dinkum on Nintendo Switch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dinkum?
[SPEAKER_06]: I hardly know him.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's supposed to be like Animal Crossing, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a survival game that's on Switch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello Kitty and Friends Freeze Tag Party.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's also Switch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honeycomb The World Beyond on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hyrule Warriors Age of Imprisonment on Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: of Ash and Steel on PC, Siberia Remastered on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series, and Unbeatable on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series, and finally, Anima, Gate of Memories 1 and 2 Remastered.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said Anima, not Enema.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry to disappoint.
[SPEAKER_07]: On PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_08]: that is it is that the subtitle for Power Wash Simulator 3 uh anyway moving on to uh Japan and the release is coming out there so we have uh in Japan this week on the Nintendo Switch 2 probably the biggest thing you know for Nintendo probably this month Hyrule Warriors Age of Imprisonment so the Hyrule Warriors games are pretty fun so I don't know if I'm
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot that's come out this last month where I don't know if I want to drop 70 on another Hyrule Warriors game, but I'm super curious to see how it's received because I might.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not off the table either.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on, also Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had no idea
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's Sing, 2026
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, in Japan for the PlayStation 5, you can get a variety of controllers for Street Fighter 6 characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's like 10 different controllers coming out for 10 different characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you really want a Chun-Li arcade stick or you want a Cammy or a Rashid, some of the newer characters, Marissa, you can get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Otherwise, as far as the game goes, Absalom is coming out this week on the PlayStation 5 in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess everybody else got out of the way for Hyrule Warriors this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's go over to the UK, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: That ain't stopping anything there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tavern Keeper for early access on Steam is November 3rd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also on November 3rd, Devil Jam PC, PS5, Xbox, and Switch.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 4th, Age of Vampires 4 Anniversary Edition PS5.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1000x Resist, PS5, Xboxes, Age of Empires IV, Dynasties of the East for the consoles except for Switch and PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, it's on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the fourth, Beyond the Grove for PC, Windstorm, The Legend of Killamori, Early Access for PC, Europa Univalis 5 for PC, Football Manager 26.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, this is real football and not American football.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also for PC, Football Manager, 26 console, Xbox, PS5, and the Netflix version as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Master Lemon, The Quest for Iceland, PC, PS5, Xbox, Switch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's Sing, 2026, as you said before, for PS5, Xbox, Switch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Satisfactory, PlayStation, Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shard Squad for PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: I almost said Shard Squad and that would have been funnier.
[SPEAKER_02]: Windstorm, Legend of Killamore for PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 5th, my mama's birthday.
[SPEAKER_02]: And our old friend Rob Kipman.
[SPEAKER_02]: Happy birthday, friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dogwitch for PC, StrangeSeed for PC, VividWorld for PC, Nature for PC and MacOS, ByPed2 for PlayStation Xbox's PC, Kang for PS5 PC, TheFableMangaBuildRoguelike for PC, OnThe6, Unbeatable for PS5 Xbox's PC, Siberia Remastered for PS5 Xbox's PC, Hyrule Warriors, Age of Imprisonment for Switch 2,
[SPEAKER_02]: Honeycomb, The World Beyond, PS5, Xbox's PC, Dinkum for Switch, the Post Humus Investigation PC, Whiskerwood PC, The Last Caretaker PC, Dino Cop PC, Jitter PC, Avash and Steel, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rebel Engine, the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: A Pizza Delivery for PS5, Xbox's PC on the 7th, Anima, Gates of Memories 1 and 2 Remastered,
[SPEAKER_02]: for PS5, Xbox's PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate this place.
[SPEAKER_02]: PS5, Switch, Xbox's PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that is it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, I just loved it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did I not say?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I just loved that there's a game called I Hate This Place.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is the place?
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it just America in 2025?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a UK release, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: It could still be somebody's on a trip over here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate this place.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, just one other quick story for you before we get to the listener roundtable tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki definitely thought of you when I saw this headline.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can't imagine why.
[SPEAKER_07]: hmm uh yeah so apparently the the thing that we could have had a Kojima Matrix game uh the Wachowskis did approach uh Hideo Kojima on the possibility of making a Matrix game back in the late 90s um unfortunately Konami being Konami at the time said nope
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's annoying.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so they were shut down by the higher ups at Konami, the vice president of licensing at Konami Digital.
[SPEAKER_07]: Talk about screwing up.
[SPEAKER_08]: This would have been right in the beginning of that era where Konami really didn't know what the fuck they were doing.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's too bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to put it all on Patchy Slot.
[SPEAKER_08]: At the same time, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just saying it's not too late.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really not too late to do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It isn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: If that's the game he wants to make, I actually would be super curious about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would like to see it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not too late.
[SPEAKER_08]: Listener Roundtable, we're going to take your calls over at our Discord server, vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you all want to stay in touch after the 23rd as well, Discord is going to be a great place to do it and any of our future projects will certainly be promoted over there.
[SPEAKER_08]: VOG Network is continuing as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby Blackwolf is still going to be there and whatever else is cooked up by us in the future.
[SPEAKER_08]: And one email.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, we'll get to that too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ranmari sent us a tweet saying that they got the Street Fighter burgers and actually sent a picture.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and I was like, oh, those do look kind of good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why is McDonald's better than it is?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkDeadSea, talking about our last episode, sent us a message saying, I was catching up on last week's show on this Tuesday evening.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exorbitant thank you to Rob for mentioning my situation.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a pretty rough October for us then to have that fall into my lap.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was not fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep up on the medical stuff if you are able, which I think is a very good life lesson for everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: If something doesn't feel right, it's probably not right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So at least talk to a teledoctor.
[SPEAKER_08]: If not, go into the office and be seen by one once in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Mish followed that up saying, you haven't got a clue about, I think this was a few days later, but I'll read it anyway because it's adorable.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mish said, you haven't got a clue about how much I love him, do you?
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'll be forever grateful to at Orange Launch Radio for helping us find each other.
[SPEAKER_08]: We may never officially get married, but as my mother says, legalities aside, we are already married and it's till death do us part from here on out.
[SPEAKER_08]: As far as I'm concerned, Mish,
[SPEAKER_08]: If you say you're married and he says he's married, if the two parties say they're married, they're married.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is coming from somebody whose marriage is back up for debate in this country and could possibly in the next few years no longer be legally married at the national level.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so, you know, I might be in a similar... I realize our situations are very different, but it's one of those things where it's like...
[SPEAKER_08]: The government is not going to tell me how to feel about the guy I've been with for over 15 years.
[SPEAKER_08]: And y'all know how I feel about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't need to say nothing else.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Mish, you're as good as married to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck what the government says.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're not getting a lot of things correct lately, so we don't care what they think.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby in chat did some research on I Hate This Place.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently it is a survival horror game.
[SPEAKER_08]: The place is a creepy ranch at night that you're trying to survive.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Bobby says they greenlit a new Matrix movie without the Wachowski sisters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that true?
[SPEAKER_07]: I would be surprised.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I think there was a new Matrix movie coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to be something.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have a call in the green room.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do want to get to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's bring them on into our broadcast room.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, this is AJ Twist.
[SPEAKER_08]: AJ, it's been a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you doing, my friend?
[SPEAKER_00]: Doing pretty well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm calling in to kind of make a confession.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess I'll start off by saying, since you guys will be ending the show soon, I started listening to you guys way back in the To Go edition.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a while ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was that like 06, 07?
[SPEAKER_00]: What's it called?
[SPEAKER_00]: Unfocused Podcasts How long have you been doing it?
[SPEAKER_00]: That sounds like my life
[SPEAKER_00]: It's our life too.
[SPEAKER_02]: How long have you been doing it?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's so unfocused that we're currently on hiatus right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not sure if we'll come back.
[SPEAKER_00]: We've been on a hiatus for like about three years now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe two or three years now.
[SPEAKER_00]: We've done that before once too.
[SPEAKER_00]: We took like a one or two year break at one point as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, just life stuff happens.
[SPEAKER_00]: My co-host started a family.
[SPEAKER_00]: He has like two kids right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: So we're kind of taking a break because of that.
[SPEAKER_00]: But we've gone like, I think we started in 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's when we started ours.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I think we went like 300 episodes deep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that really is, thank you for saying that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That really is one of the absolute nicest compliments we can get over the years is that somebody says, I was inspired to do my own thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, it's a weird way of looking at it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't take this the wrong way, AJ.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a weird way of looking at it, admittedly.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think about all these children that we have.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so many children we don't even know about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, Mamoru.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's exactly the joke I wanted to make, too.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was going to say, you know how people, you know, sleep around, come around 18 years later.
[SPEAKER_08]: All I had to do was whisper some things in your ear.
[SPEAKER_08]: Omelette du Fromage It is quite the compliment.
[SPEAKER_08]: It really truly is.
[SPEAKER_08]: So thank you for saying that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know there's other shows I know Anime Jam Session has said openly they were inspired by part by what we were doing here.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're still going.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, DarkSakura has been talking about a successor project.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so that's, you know, there's plenty of kids out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so hopefully that sense of like, don't be an asshole to people on the internet and get all the voices in the room and hear some different perspectives and listen to some things in different ways.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully a lot of that kind of carries on from this.
[SPEAKER_08]: And yeah, it's just, it's...
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot of awesome people that listen to this show, and I'm really happy to hear that many of them are taking it forward in their own ways.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that really truly is the nicest compliment, so thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, and then hopefully, I mean, yeah, I would like to get back and do some more shows again once my co-host can find some time again.
[SPEAKER_00]: Especially now since you guys are leaving, it's like, okay, where am I going to get my news from?
[SPEAKER_00]: I've got to start doing my own news again.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm doing something, huh?
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, yeah, we'll see what comes out then.
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll check that out for sure, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: I want to ask, too, a couple things.
[SPEAKER_00]: Number one, because I remember when we first started our podcast, it was so jank.
[SPEAKER_00]: We were literally using Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_08]: This one still is.
[SPEAKER_08]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was using a headset I stole from my old job.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, what kind of equipment did you guys have in the first few episodes?
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a Plantronics call center headset.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had a cheap-ass Radio Shack mic, which was like a $10 mic, which probably was just an exposed wire, like literally in a plastic case.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you actually go back and listen to that first episode, so something about OLR's history that not everybody knows, Loki made himself a co-host on this show by showing up every episode.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm so thankful.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wouldn't have had it any other way.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you go back to that first episode and listen to Loki's comments, he literally sounds like he's talking into a tin can, and it's because he is.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a real shit microphone that he was using.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to say I was also using one of the headsets, because I believe that's how we were running it.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura and I used headsets, and then all the guests that were in the room would use this little... We had a microphone that I would say you could walk up to, but literally it was sitting on the edge of the unused fireplace.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: but I think also brings me back to kind of like my main point which is so many people out there that want to get into podcasting get so focused on having the right equipment and yes it helps it's necessary you want to be able to sound good you know it will turn people off if you're hard to hear you have volume issues and things like that but I will say this do not let it stop you from creating because it is far harder
[SPEAKER_08]: to have the discipline to keep it going week after week.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've got to make it a habit for yourself.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's the only way you're going to be able to stick with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the only way we've been able to do this for as long as we have is to be able to say like every Sunday night is OLR time and have that for 23 years and have that set into our routine.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, we had rock band microphones and we plugged in two of them into our computer that was barely running at the time.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I remember listening back to it and there was desync issues between the mics and I had to go do a lot of editing in there to just fix it, make it sound good because...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, in my technical mind, I was like, it's rough.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I was like, actually, this is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, we were actually kind of on it, like, in the very beginning.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was fun to go back and listen.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: My other question, too, for you guys was about DDR, because you guys came from the DDR days.
[SPEAKER_00]: I kind of missed that boat.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think I got on the boat, like, right when it was shipping out.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I got in late.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I never saw any tournaments before.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I don't know if you guys remember what I've come through and talked about, but I go to like tournaments.
[SPEAKER_00]: I go to like fighting games tournaments, like GC, EVO, all that.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I've seen bracket style tournaments.
[SPEAKER_00]: What were DDR tournaments like?
[SPEAKER_00]: How was that run?
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, was there brackets?
[SPEAKER_00]: Was there, was it just judges?
[SPEAKER_00]: I know there's freestyles, so you need judges for that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like what were, what were those like?
[SPEAKER_08]: Most of them were separated into two categories.
[SPEAKER_08]: You would tip the standard, quote unquote, the boilerplate DDR tournament would have perfect attack that ran during the day and then freestyle competition that started at night.
[SPEAKER_08]: So perfect attack could kind of be done one of two ways.
[SPEAKER_08]: You could be competing for a high score.
[SPEAKER_08]: Usually I found that tournaments with less entries were going that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like you play a qualifier song.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would say maybe you're...
[SPEAKER_08]: Average setup would be that a qualifier song or sometimes I've even seen ones where you could pick from one of three.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that qualifier song would place you into the bracket of eight or the bracket of 16, depending on how many participants were doing this thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then you would go head to head on different songs that were pre selected by people not participating, you know, in envelopes or what have you to compete head to head for a higher score.
[SPEAKER_08]: The best I ever did in Perfect Attack was I got fourth place in some tournament.
[SPEAKER_08]: I beat somebody big to get there, so it was like, oh, who did that?
[SPEAKER_08]: But then it was like, I never did that good again.
[SPEAKER_00]: What were the songs?
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Paranoia Evolution It wasn't always the hardest songs because sometimes the pop songs with the strange step charts were actually more challenging because you didn't... I think that's how I got...
[SPEAKER_08]: And now Pink Dinosaur
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I was playing when I started?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Xanadu.
[SPEAKER_02]: Paranoia.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I started with the first mix at home.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, then you would have the freestyle at night, and yes, it was judges.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you'd enter, and they'd call people up in a random order or whatever, and that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I remember, because there was a tournament Jamie and I did at Milpitas.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember if Loki was there, but Jamie...
[SPEAKER_02]: I was there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was there.
[SPEAKER_08]: and so we entered freestyle and we did it so Jamie and I entered freestyle obviously we were screen starers which is a terrible thing to do but I feel like I actually feel like we did decent like considering that like we didn't know the note chart and we hadn't practiced beforehand I feel like we got enough baps in on each other with the bat that it was kind of funny for a minute plastic trumpets
[SPEAKER_08]: for a minute it was funny I'm sure the crowd was annoyed because we weren't a rehearsed routine but I don't care
[SPEAKER_00]: and then an orange badge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that how Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we're talking about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is pre-OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, this is pre-OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, funny enough, that is not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Bat Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is funny that that came into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, the name was because, again, sort of the boilerplate and where we started Under Sedation Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: Under Sedation is a line from the Time Warp and the Rocky Horror Picture Show, Riff Raff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it was a great decision for the time, but it definitely hurt our discoverability factor in the later iTunes era because we were not the show that we may be the oldest show, but we were not the show that decided to call ourselves video game news radio or gaming lounge radio or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: No disrespect to any show.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's I'm just you.
[SPEAKER_08]: You beat us to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it is what it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: I feel the same way with the Unfocused podcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think that really helped.
[SPEAKER_00]: But we were unfocused though.
[SPEAKER_00]: We were not only gaming, but we talked about comics, anime, and just nerd stuff really.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will say this.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's part of the reason, I don't think I've ever said this, it's part of the reason I rushed a podcast that went for about 10 episodes, not even that, maybe 7, called Pokestop Podcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: I used to do that show with Shane for a hot minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: I rushed that podcast to a reality fast to get the name Pokestop Podcast as soon as Pokemon Go came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know if you remember, but I think I contacted you over Twitter and I wanted to be a co-host for a day, but my schedule didn't work out that day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bummer, because I probably would have done it.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had some fun episodes, but I was not into the mainline games at that time.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the allure of Pokemon Go kind of wore off for Shane real fast, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: So unfortunately it did get, but I was, man, we had the name.
[SPEAKER_08]: so but it is what it is yeah I remember writing a whole like script of what I wanted to talk about too I remember I probably have it in my notes my phone somewhere actually that's awesome well we could still do that episode you know if you have you have two minutes right now I can all right well maybe maybe another time because we got to wrap up tonight's show but anything else on your mind tonight AJ
[SPEAKER_00]: No, that was about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just wanted to just admit that and just say thank you for all the shows you guys put on over the years, all the great, just the news.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's hard to find good news shows that you just would like to hear.
[SPEAKER_00]: Other news shows, they're just so plain.
[SPEAKER_00]: They just maybe don't give enough, I don't know, like...
[SPEAKER_00]: connections to other stuff like a fun way of just explaining news again like you guys started off as just friends talking together just you know BSing and just having that vibe as well as the info at the same time which is you know I really vibe with that I used to like just sneak you guys into work too speaking of Platronics headsets I wired my headset that I used to work in my office job way back to my iPod just to listen to you guys too at night when there was no calls coming in oh my gosh
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, so, yeah, just thanks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hear that, and I hear the PSP thing a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, Loki building OLR PSP was, like, the best marketing thing that... Well, second to iTunes was the best thing... Well, I'm thinking about it in my mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somewhere, iTunes, All Games, and that were all the big moments that this show got more exposure.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the PSP thing, I hear an awful lot about when this show got discovered.
[SPEAKER_08]: So kudos to you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're the marketing genius on that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even know how I did it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't either in retrospect, but good job.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, AJ, thank you so much for calling in.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if we don't get a chance to hear from you again before it's all over, I really want to appreciate your words here and what you said.
[SPEAKER_08]: And thanks for being... I know we don't hear from you all the time, but I appreciate your perspective on what goes on at EVO and the fighting game community and all of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just really appreciate you being part of the fam.
[SPEAKER_08]: And again, none of us are dying and we hope to see you in our future projects.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you so much, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care, AJ.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have a great night.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, let's do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, OLR crew.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Rin.
[SPEAKER_02]: As I write this email, I'm on a Shinkansen train from Nagoya to Tokyo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hope you're doing well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I started listening in 2006 after seeing the OLR domain on a tapestry at Fanime.
[SPEAKER_02]: I distinctly remembered listening during the university orientation downtime as at the time I had just graduated high school.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I'm 36 and I'm a working-ass adult trademark.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: The most surprising was finding an AXE on Senichimai near Dotonbori.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looked like your usual metal games and crane game arcades at first, but I was shocked when I went to the third floor and found an entire row of shmups in great condition and with auto-fire buttons to save players from suffering repetitive stress injury.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm disappointed I only discovered this right before I left for Nagoya.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've also been playing Sega's rhythm games, MaiMai, Chunidham, Ongeki.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're miles better than Benmani in my honest opinion, both in terms of gameplay style and ease of getting into them.
[SPEAKER_02]: MaiMai cabinets just started rolling out across the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Round 1 branches, and I hope Chunidham follows suit soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, the risk of being canceled by American gamers and branded as a traitor to gamers in the West.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played some metal games, similar to coin pusher games in the West, particularly Marble Fever, known in the US as Marble Carnival, which is a marble pusher game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yeah, they're about as deep as you can expect gambling games to be, but ball mazes and contraptions activate my autistic stems, and so does getting big-ass jackpots.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of the same, I'll admit.
[SPEAKER_02]: it should be noted that metal games technically aren't gambling since the medals you win and use to play can be redeemed for cash or prizes hence why they're called amusement games literally just for a dopamine rush or gambling minus the actual stakes while I can make do without playing them I just look
[SPEAKER_02]: Just like looking at them for their noticeably high quality artwork.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, I'm going to enjoy Tokyo for the next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I look forward to keeping in touch with you folks even after OLR has ended.
[SPEAKER_02]: Much love and take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: System Clarity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rin Clarity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mari Clarity.
[SPEAKER_08]: And thank you for the commitment to stay in touch when it ends.
[SPEAKER_02]: We always hang out at California Extreme every year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm thankful you're having a great time in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm thankful you came back after all these years too.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's funny because I think every podcaster who's been doing this a long time, I know Bobby, I think I'm stealing this line from Bobby, but says, I have a lot of former listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: and sometimes that's kind of how it feels here too and that's that's okay that's not a read that's not like it just you know I can think of shows I used to I think of TV shows I used to watch every single week without fail that I don't watch as much of anymore RuPaul's Drag Race great example because I even had a podcast on that with some buddies for a hot minute I don't watch Drag Race anymore it's hard to avoid on social media I kind of see the highlights and stuff but I don't I don't really watch that stuff anymore so um
[SPEAKER_08]: and it's not that I hate it or anything in fact I love a lot of the talent that comes from that stuff but Survivor I don't watch every week religiously like I used to or like maybe The Simpsons probably for a lot of people like we all used to watch The Simpsons you know for those first couple years not all but you know a lot of us did and now a lot less do or South Park would be another good example of that that used to be like must see TV in the college dorms and then you know I only see what I see on social media so anyway
[SPEAKER_08]: is a lot of former listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, and that's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope, I noticed OG Happy Dude just came into chat going, wait, wait, OLR sending.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm sorry, the news is only just now reaching some people.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually sitting here thinking,
[SPEAKER_08]: I probably need to do something I don't want to do and log into Twitter just to get the message out to people that maybe have left some time ago and haven't followed us over to Blue Sky or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: As much as it's paining me to say it, I feel like I might need to send a note just so people know they only have a few more chances to catch us in this form until whatever the future may hold.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: What else?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to send us an email, participate at orangelawntrader.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would highly encourage you to get those emails in in the next two weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because on the last episode, I don't think we're going to really have the time to read 17 emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not that I think we would get that many.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would like to make sure that everybody who wants to call in on the last episode has a chance.
[SPEAKER_08]: We may have to put in the two-minute timer, but I would like everybody... I was kind of stewing on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like, do we want to open the following?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do we not?
[SPEAKER_08]: This really is...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: so long for now goodbye baby tell me why beep beep oh maybe that'll be the thing if there's too many people then we're going to require that you sing your favorite DDR song to get on I'm just kidding but anyway so that's where you know where we're kind of leaning right now so Jamie says she'll read 17 emails if you send them but I would really encourage you to get those I didn't say that well yes you did you said try me you said watch me I said try me I didn't say I would get through all of them
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, she'll abbreviate them all.
[SPEAKER_08]: She'll say, I'm going to read the first word of each of these emails.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one says, Jamie's the best.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one says, I like Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: This one says, grow your YouTube.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, spam.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one says, hey, I checked out OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you didn't, you fucking liar.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's trying to sell us something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate those.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you checked out this show, you know you're probably... Yes, and dear.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're contacting you, dear.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm your dear.
[SPEAKER_08]: OG Happy Dude says, nothing is preventing a 24-hour call-in episode or party.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think we all are accepting that that night will probably go late, and that's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's already taken the week off afterwards, so it's all good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't you say you took the next day off, Jamie, that Monday?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember if you said it or not.
[SPEAKER_08]: I probably won't, but again, I'm fortunate in that my boss listens to this program.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if I'm on my Zoom calls wearing sunglasses on Monday, I feel like I'll get a little bit of understanding.
[SPEAKER_08]: 24 hours is a lot, but six maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: We could just drink.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100Matt says, I gotta ask, are we doing one last listless, maybe best gaming moments of the last 23 and a half years?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember the last 23 and a half years.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since you asked so nicely, maybe we will.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe we will bring one of the old games back for one last swing.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can't do a cage match because we all know it's going to be Sandstorm.
[SPEAKER_08]: we can't do a cage match because of copyright streaming things on Twitch so unfortunately you're going to have to get that dream I need to stomp out real quick but a listless or a match game we were doing OLR match game before Drag Race was on TV I just want to put that out there it's Holic the ultimate cage match song forever is Holic how about the FUs of the week you don't want me to do an FU
[SPEAKER_02]: because I'm going to admit I have a little bit of feeling I don't voice and yeah alright so last minute stories do we have any last minute stories tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna just completely go off on the entire industry so you don't want me to say anything
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I actually have a few things real quick I was going to mention.
[SPEAKER_07]: So here's a fun one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you know that GameStop has their own official game that they're actually selling at GameStop?
[SPEAKER_02]: How to suck?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's called Buck in the Curse Partridge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did they label this box correctly?
Pfft.
[SPEAKER_07]: uh yeah you have the final unwrapped box display boxes that you're gonna sell is new no it's buck remember that stupid rabbit that they have that's like their mascot i guess but they're selling it it's now a game boy color game that someone made for them or they commissioned to have made for them and they sell it at their store so yay um
[SPEAKER_07]: This is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is a mod that was developed for Bully, the old Rockstar game called Bully Online.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is exactly what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is a multiplayer mod for Bully that allows you to play... As if you need a mod to bully people online.
[SPEAKER_08]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, now you can.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yeah, so you can do all sorts of roleplay stuff in the bully game, which until it gets shut down by Rockstar, which I believe will happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, they they like to be litigious and also they like to bust unions because apparently that's the other thing that they're doing right now in the UK.
[SPEAKER_07]: They fired.
[SPEAKER_07]: 30 employees across offices in the UK and Canada that they say they're claiming people were terminated for gross misconduct however also those people happen to be part of the Independent Workers Union of Great Britain and this is a basically a way to bust some union so fun fun that's it alrighty
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, with that, we're going to wrap it up, get some final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were a little long tonight, but I expect these last episodes will be.
[SPEAKER_08]: Usually at the end, I talk about spread the word and all that stuff, but ever since we made the announcement, I think I just want to say here, a reminder, our last episode is November 23rd, and we want to thank all of you for being along with us on this journey.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got into it a little bit on that call tonight, but you guys have been what has made this show a success for as long as it has been.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we're just hashing out a couple of things, that's all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw someone working on something, so I know things are happening.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I was also asked a lighting question, so I know that there's things occurring, and that's exciting to see.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I look forward to the children that will be birthed next.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just don't ask to pay child support.
[SPEAKER_02]: Children.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is like the drunk aunt.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's do them.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, you're streaming tonight, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, tonight's Pali and I because, you know, I like to do something chill after the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, man, I have some feelings about Debra Delightful here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they're starting 2v8 again and they're taking out Legion for shame.
[SPEAKER_08]: How dare they take out my legion Growl Hiss So Pallia happens tonight Have fun with Pallia Yeah Bye kids Bye, see you next time Alright, we'll go over to Loki Your final thought tonight, Loki My final thought is I need to work more on content Because I've been busy with everything else You'll have some extra time in a few weeks
[SPEAKER_07]: I need to figure out what to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, if I do it all cinematic and it's all scripted, that's kind of a lot of effort.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I also want to play it, you know, so I'm like, I don't know how I'm going to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I may just not do it fully scripted.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only reason I wanted to do it scripted and cinematic is because I thought that that would get more views.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, based off of what my channel's doing right now, I don't know what gets more views.
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously, that is not working at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nothing to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll figure it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep at it, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: You do good stuff and one of these days you'll be rewarded for that success.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Someday.
[SPEAKER_08]: I choose to believe that that is true in my heart.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then my final thought is I see a news article about Civilization 7 scrolling along the bottom of the screen and then I realize I still never played Civilization 7.
[SPEAKER_08]: I should probably get on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I need to finish Dragon Quest.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm playing games like a lot lately.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's that time of year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exciting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a great week, everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see you on our next episode, episode 1068.
[SPEAKER_08]: Until then, good night.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you next week.