Orange Lounge Radio With your hosts, DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice. It's Orange Lounge Radio. Live tonight, episode number 756 for this December the 19th of 2018. I am Rob Roberts. He is Techmaster Loki.
It's a big move over from Shoutcast where we've been for, and some people don't realize this, we've been on Shoutcast for 16 and a half years.
That's a long time.
A varying degrees of Shoutcast and now we are on Twitch, which is a big move. Well, it's not, I mean, as Jason kind of referenced in the intro there, it's not really like the first time that we're on Twitch because we did the Justin TV, the precursor thing.
Right.
We did like the simulcast, but it was really like, I don't even know if any clips are still out there on our old.
I don't remember. I just remember playing games on like the TV while we were doing the show. So we had something to actually display, but I don't remember. We didn't film anything, did we?
I sort of vaguely remember it.
It was on, it was on Justin TV. I mean, we were doing like a simulcast, but it was really like, it was like you would just have the static camera there and you weren't really getting like the actual mixing board audio that you're getting through this new setup that we have here.
It would just be like our hollow voices in the garage and you couldn't even hear the Skype callers or anything like that. But this whole transition has been a process.
But I really do think it's it's the right move for Orange L'Ange Radio, probably one, admittedly, we probably should have made about two years ago, maybe, maybe sooner back.
But I'm happy we're here and hopefully going to get some new faces here checking out the show and yeah, talking, talking about the news and everything.
So where do we begin? Well, shout out, of course, to Dark Soccer or Jamie Summers. Usually this is a three host show.
But a little while back, Dark Soccer had a conflict with her day job. So she actually works on Sunday nights right now. So unfortunately she can't be here. She should be back here full time in February.
Not that she's going to be on camera or anything.
Yeah, it is the show.
She'll be behind the camera.
It is the show where every gamer has a voice, not necessarily a face.
But, you know, we respect that. Like there's a lot of people that can be I think our community has always been very welcoming.
And every experience I've had on Twitch has been really cool. Like, you know, I have a personal channel over at Rob Roberts.
Cheap plug. But, you know, every experience I've had has been really cool. And I haven't had a lot of like, you know, weirdo people.
But I totally respect like she don't want to be on camera or any guests that we have here, because I was actually asked that question randomly.
Like, are you gonna make your guests be on camera?
No, I'm not going to make anyone do anything. If you want, we'll have Pikachu dance and to you as you talk.
And that will be that will be what it is. And yeah, we'll work with that.
So. All right. And of course, we are in chat as we usually are over at our Twitch TV channel.
You still can access everything over at live.voggenetwork.com.
Of course, we want you to still check out VOG Network and all the other great shows that make up the Voice Geese Network.
The live ones like Bobby, Anime Jam Session and the non live ones as well. Hooked on Bond, Electricista Hood, Gamers Gone.
Wow. The list goes on and on. Check it all out.
And and some folks giving some feedback on some of the voices right now over.
I guess I'm sounding a little low, but you're something a little high, but I'm looking at the recording and everything seems OK.
I think the positioning of the mic and now now I can show this to you.
You could see I've been tired about must be up on your face.
The mic has to be up in your face because when it's not like look, if I put it just a little bit away.
My audio like really drops. So it's really.
Yeah, the distance is very important, but we're working on that.
I know you can do things with gain and other stuff. It's a brand new mixing board, a brand new computer that's dedicated to the video end of things.
Whereas we were going to have an upgraded computer that works with some of the things so I can do stories and all that.
But yeah, lots, lots and lots of changes here at Orange Dawn Studio, but a lot staying the same, you know, for folks that aren't able to participate live on Sunday nights
and aren't able to come now see what fat, middle aged men we actually are doing this show.
I'm not as fat. That's true. I'm still very middle aged, but I'm not as fat as I was.
And I've been working on it. I've been closing all my ring. I've lost a few pounds.
Although I must say the last month has been a little bit on the eased side of things.
I haven't been as strict and I've been. The holidays, things are going to happen. What can you do?
They have the 12 days of snacking at work. So, you know, I have to have the 12 days of snacking.
So I have to have the 12 days of snacking. You know what I'm going to ask after last week's show, are you snacking on broccoli?
Are you mixing in the broccoli? No, it's a popcorn. It's all been popcorn this week.
Going to chat over at live.vognetwork.com in our Twitch room.
It's going to take me a little while to get over some of these things I've been saying for years.
But VG realness says this is such an exciting moment. And I agree, it is an exciting moment.
And I want to give a shout out quickly to Bobby Black Wolf. You know, you guys all know who he is at this point.
But everything that you see on Twitch, I know on the podcast, you know, let me kind of describe what's going on.
But you actually can see now what we're going to be talking about and what we're talking about right now.
Kind of like I think some shows only ESPN do this. I mean, I don't really do the whole sports thing very often.
Drag Race doesn't do this. I couldn't tell you. But like, you know, the nightly the 24 hour news ticker.
And that's what we have at the bottom. We have that whole, like, you know, glorious headline down at the bottom.
But not only is it pulling in top headlines from a variety of different websites, but it'll actually say, like, here's my Twitter.
Here's my personal channel. And so that way we're not disturbing the podcast listeners every few seconds with,
thanks for the follow. Thanks. We do want to acknowledge new followers. That's all acknowledged down here.
So you still get and we'll give you a shout out at the end after we're done with the recording.
And, you know, because we we really appreciate the follows. We're trying to work our way to Twitch affiliate status.
You guys have been we we were 50 followers in before we even went live tonight.
So like that the hardest thing you have to do already done. So thank you guys very much for all your support of the show.
Like it means so much and has made this very, very exciting.
Quest Buster over in the Twitch chat room says we'll also see the awesome food brought in from time to time.
I already ate it. Sorry, it was subway. It was it was it was not great.
I was just it's because I had Pete. Well, I didn't really have pizza.
They had like a piece of pizza and like a breakfast sandwich, both both parts of meals that my kids didn't need.
So I have that. And so I was like, well, you know, I should probably just get like a subway sandwich so that it's somewhat low calorie.
So I did that and I hated it. But it's what I eat every day.
It's just it's not the same subway. It's like I have a particular subway that I go to like my work routine.
So there's one that it's on the way of the show here and they don't get it right.
It's just the people near my work. They know what I order every day. It's the same thing.
And it's just like they. Oh, yeah, you haven't usually. Yeah, sure. OK. And then these make it and it's great.
I love some of these cars. We get a few more of these chat comments and then I want to quickly reintroduce the show a little bit.
But I hope I see your name right. I'm sorry. Oh, Tejero asks, is it sunny there?
I'm sorry if I butchered your name. No, it's actually raining.
And now now my fear is, is the power going to go out during our first show?
Because that would know that would be a hoot. It's not windy. It's just raining.
OK, well, that's good. That makes me feel a little bit better. And K Arts one over in Twitch wants to know.
So now that we have video SimCity action news reenactment, when? Careful what you ask for over on.
Did you notice we did a little something something over on Twitch, a little little just a little something and a little little something that wasn't in the podcast, but just like a little extra little bumper.
I hope to do more things like that. Silly little pre-shows. And that part of that is inspired, inspired by a variety of things.
But probably primarily when I do Rocky or a picture show over at The Colonial, they do pre-shows to get the audience hyped up.
And they'll show things like they show the the rock band Snack Bar that's like we have all your fucking money and like it's really funny.
I think it's from Adult Swim or something. I don't know. They show it. It's hilarious. They'll show like a Tim Curry music video, gets everybody hyped up.
There's an infamous one of John Waters and he's saying, don't smoke inside the theater.
And he takes a big puff on a cigarette like, don't you wish you could be enjoying this right now, but don't be an asshole.
It's great. It's an infamous clip out there. But anyway. All right. Let's talk about video games. We're going to get into it.
I'm going to ask Loki to kick it off with this story about Discord.
But first, I do want to reintroduce the show since it is kind of like the first show over on Twitch.
And there might be some new people checking out for the first time either here or in the archives.
Hello, we are Orange Town Radio. Our first broadcast was June 23rd, 2002, and we decided to put this show together.
Myself, Dark Sakura and Loki joined us from day one because we all met playing a little video game called Dance Dance Revolution.
So music games are still near and dear to our hearts. We met playing Dance Dance Revolution and other music games.
Like I was always into Bust a Move or Groove, depending on which side of the ocean you're on.
Or Parappa the Rappa was a huge thing for me, too. You know, we got into all types of music games.
And, you know, then we kind of shifted into covering more general games because music games were kind of fading a little bit.
And then right when we make the move to covering all the games, Guitar Hero comes out.
And music games are all the rage again. But that's alright because we love all games.
We always have a fondness in our heart for music games.
It's okay because Activision killed it really quickly, too.
That's right. Actually, the thing went offline not that long ago. It's very sad.
But also, you know, the whole thing we envisioned is that when we used to play DDR, we used to go to the diner right across from the arcade.
And we used to just sit around, you know, eating unhealthy things like mozzarella sticks and so forth.
And we'd sit at the table and we would just talk about, like, did you hear what they're doing with that game?
Or what's going on with, you know, your Soulcalibur character?
And I fought your character in that one mode that everybody used to play as Soulcalibur at the arcade.
Was that, like, Conquest or something like that?
Yeah, something like that. And so, you know, we always just sit around and talk about that.
And we wanted to kind of, like, bring that to a virtual space where everybody, no matter where they are, can kind of join in at the diner table with us.
So, you might want to eat a little healthier, though, so get your broccoli sticks and join us.
And, yeah, while we talk along what's going on in gaming news.
But we are going to get into, for our long-time listeners, they're waiting for, let's do it, let's get into this week's news.
So what are we going to start off with tonight?
We'll talk about, since last week we talked a little bit about the Steam store and how they kind of decided to tweak their revenue split with publishers.
Especially publishers that sell over, like, 10 million copies of a game.
So they're going to give you a little bit more money, like 25%, if you happen to even get close to that.
Then, of course, to rebut that, Epic Games Society said that they're going to put out their own game store.
And they're going to give you 88% of the revenue, because that's better than the 30% that they're taking on the Steam store.
And then Discord's like, but we'll give you 90%, and 90% is better than 88%.
And so, of course, that's what they're doing now, because with yet another game launcher.
Because you remember, you know, Discord is now offering some games through their storefront, or they have a storefront, I think.
I've never actually explored it, but...
I have a little bit.
Discord, you know, and I've talked about this on a previous show, like, Discord is doing a lot of things right right now.
And I'm not on a payroll or anything, but it was incredibly smart that they gave this thing that, you know, people were paying for with TeamSpeak and Slack.
They were giving it away for free, and then they just kind of, you know, started to subtly slip in there.
Hey, we noticed what games you play, and we're just going to start showing you headlines for all these games you play.
Oh, and here's all your friends they're playing.
And for streamers, it's great, because if I'm streaming, people see that, right, in their Discord.
And I love that, as a streamer, right?
Except, sadly, since this is tied to the VoG network, nobody may know.
Well, I'll just have to...
I'll have to promote OLR other ways, such as through the VoG network Discord, available at vognetwork.com slash Discord.
Bing.
Anyway, but, you know, promote that way.
But then it was like, oh, hey, wouldn't you like us to scan your computer, find all your games, and have a game launcher all in one place?
It's like, oh, sure, why not, you know?
And now it's, oh, by the way, now we have a store, so you can add to that.
It's, like, very interesting how they built that.
But, yeah, and now if you subscribe to their thing, you get some free games, which is another, like, huge...
You know, obviously we know, like, Humble has the monthly bundle.
We have Discord is in on that.
Twitch gives away games.
Twitch, Epic Games Store is giving out games.
Yeah, PlayStation and Xbox have been doing it forever, so...
Subnautica is free on Epic Games Store.
Yeah, so, love it.
Anyway, yeah, so, is this gonna be a good thing?
I mean, how low can you go as far as how much of the revenue is gonna be taken out of this?
I think that's about as low as you can go without actually just saying, hey, you can put them on there for free.
We don't wanna make any money from it.
Are they still gonna be curating some of the content in there, though?
Because that would be my concern, is that are we just gonna get, like, you know, all sorts of questionable things like we've seen on Steam?
Well, yes.
Garbage games.
They are gonna be curating it, so they kind of described it as basically a boutique bookstore of game stores.
So they're not gonna necessarily open the floodgates to everything like Steam did.
But it's gonna be a little bit more curated, I guess.
PixelPaka is in chat over at live.vognetwork.com, says, people can sell on itch.io without giving away revenue, any revenue to Twitch itch.io.
However, it means the developer has to deal with the PayPal, et cetera, transaction fees.
Which, again, I just gave the old address.
But luckily, live.vognetwork.com forwards to the new Twitch.
Right.
Because I'm gonna say the old one a lot tonight, sorry.
And itch.io, it's a decent way to do that as well, but it's more, it's not so much, I don't know how they promote stuff on itch.io.
If it's actually, like, they don't really, I think, have a storefront where it shows you a bunch of stuff.
It's more of just, it's a place that you can put up your storefront.
Kind of think of it like a mall, a shopping mall that you can put your own kiosk up to sell your game.
It's not necessarily gonna be like, you know, Steam where they're, well, maybe Steam's a bad comparison because they're not necessarily doing anything to promote your game either.
Except burying it under crap.
I don't know. Sure, why not?
You know, competition is good because competition's how you get down from, you know, taking 70% of your revenue home to 90%.
So, why not?
I wanted to go to the email, our mailbag. I don't usually do it this early in the show, but we got a really good email from somebody whose viewpoint I really respect on this, so I want to get to it.
If you want to email our show, you can. Participate at orangelaungeradio.com.
I know in the last episode I threatened to take it away, but we got some good emails this week, and as long as you guys continue to use it, we'll still use it too.
We won't have to punish you this time.
What?
So we won't have to punish you this time.
Yeah, no punishment this week, which is a bummer because All Stars 4 Star...oh, another time.
For those that don't know, if you're new on Twitch, I always threaten if we do not get emails, I use that time that we dedicate to emails to give you a RuPaul's Drag Race recap of what's going on.
Which is great because I don't watch any of it, so...
My favorite television show.
I totally need to be recapped on all of it.
Three words. Brown cow stunning.
Alright, anyway, let's get to the emails.
Hello LR, I figured I'd pop a message over to the old outdated mailbag for old outdated people because why not?
And you can tell this is coming from YYR from that tone.
Regarding the Persona 5 character that was added to Smash, maybe Persona 5 isn't on Switch yet, but let's face it, it's 99% guaranteed to happen.
Persona 1 through 4 all got releases on dedicated portable gaming consoles.
Persona 3 portable on PSP and Persona 4 Golden on Vita both sold well.
Are they really not going to release 5 on Switch?
I don't gamble much, but even I'd bet on this happening.
I think it's probably going to happen to, it's just a matter of when, but we'll see.
Alright, obviously I didn't skip to the email to read that part, but I want to acknowledge all of YR's perspectives, but let's get to this next part.
Regarding the Epic Games Store, and now the Discord Store, offering bigger shares to their developers.
Actually, I'm not upset about this at all.
It only goes to show that you get what you pay for.
Would I like to get more than 70% of the revenue?
Sure, but for that 18% or 20% difference, 1.
My games support integrated leaderboards, a critical feature in score attack games like mine, and I don't have to run any servers.
2. My games support Xbox One, 360, DualShock 4, Switch Pro, and Steam controllers, and all I had to do was implement one of those.
3. My games have achievements for those who enjoy chasing them.
4. My games support cloud saving, even for Windows to Mac and Mac.
5. My games can't be copied or pirated willy-nilly, because they can detect whether they're running through the Steam client, and can quit if they're not.
6. Steam support has gotten back to me very quickly when I've encountered any issues, and they've been very thorough when reviewing my builds.
If I released my games anywhere else, they'd have none of this or close.
The price difference is justified in my opinion. My customers get more and I get more.
Now, if Epic and Discord can offer comparable service in the future, that'd be awesome. I hope they do.
But if not, then dollars aren't everything. You know what is? The experience that I can deliver to my players.
And right now, on Steam, it's better.
What do you think about that perspective from YYR? Because I'll admit, when I first heard this story, I was like, oh, more money for indie developers. They're going to love that.
But as YYR is kind of outlining these things like leaderboards, online, controllers, a lot of things that make it easier, it kind of did make me go, oh, that's interesting.
Well, I know Epic's doing stuff for online. They have, I think, some APIs that they're putting out to help with cross-platform play and stuff.
I'm sure because these storefronts are a lot newer than Steam, that maybe some of that stuff is forthcoming, but we'll have to wait and see.
It's more of just at least there's options out there. And if anything, maybe it puts a little bit of pressure on Steam to consider maybe increasing the revenue share that developers get.
So that can be bad. But ultimately, it's going to be just up to you where you decide you're releasing your game with what's more important to you.
Do you want a few additional percentage points in your revenue or do you want all these other features?
VG Realness comments, I guess Steam has the right to essentially charge you for this service as they are providing you more than competitors.
Good point. But do you think that Steam will still kind of cave in to some of this pressure?
I mean, remember, we heard about some of the changes they were doing to their store, but this was before Epic made their move and now Discord's making their move.
Do you think Steam is going to feel some social pressures of sorts to drop that percentage down, which honestly could have a big impact on a company that isn't exactly releasing a lot of games?
No.
Their bread and butter is Steam right now.
I don't think they're actually going to have...
Mostly. HTC Vive, I know somebody will say it, but VR. But, you know, there are other things they get into, but let's be real, the bulk of it right now is Steam for them.
No. I don't think so. Because I think a lot of, right now, there isn't a lot of games leaving the storefront to go strictly to the Epic Game Store.
There's a couple indie games that are exclusive on the Epic Game Store right now, but it's not going to make or break them.
I think they're making so much money from it right now.
They haven't done crap for that platform at all, as far as fixing a lot of these problems with all these games just being on there.
Fake games or Bitcoin miners disguised as games and all of that.
And, of course, now with loot boxes and the gambling and stuff, now they've made Counter-Strike into a free-to-play game.
They're just making money from all sorts of avenues. I don't think they really care right now until it makes a significant impact, and then they'll make a change. But, no.
I'm so curious to see if there is going to be any type of counter-response, but, I mean, you lay something out, good stuff out there.
Not to spoil something that's coming up later, but it happens inevitably, but we know that, you know, because the Epic Store is affiliated with Unreal Engine and all of that,
I know YYR gives a lot of props to some of those things built in with Steam, but it seems like the relationship between Epic and Unreal is going to provide some of that as well.
Like, there's going to be perks to releasing on the Epic Store because of things in the Unreal Engine.
I mean, I guess you could take anything in the Unreal Engine and put it on Steam or what have you, right?
Yeah, you can.
Do you think Epic might wall some of that for things that are just their store, or are they going to try to sail through that on cost?
I don't think that they're going to do that right now. I mean, they're not walling off anything, because I think that, you know, they're trying to get people on that storefront.
I don't think they would just all of a sudden start breaking the engine or, like, walling things off to that one storefront.
But, I don't know what they necessarily offer there, but I gotta imagine that they've got somewhat comparable stuff.
I just don't know all the details, because I haven't published anything, as you may be aware.
Because you haven't finished anything!
Haven't finished, started anything.
Bobby Blackwolf reminds us in chat, Epic gets 5% of all revenue from an Unreal Engine game on Steam, because that's what you pay to use the Unreal Engine.
So they don't want to wall things off from Steam. Good call out.
Bobby also wants to point out, now I know I just said I wasn't going to name all the followers and all that, but it is worth noting, we're on night one here at Twitch.
Even though we created the channel a long time ago to save the name, this is our first official night of broadcasting on Twitch.
And, Loki, we just got our 69th follower.
Nice.
Nice. Thank you for that. Oh, even Smush. Smush isn't, I don't know if the mics are sensitive enough to pick him up. Probably not.
He's across, he's all the way.
I actually, I had to actually mess with the game so that when he starts screaming for food around 7 o'clock, it wouldn't pick him up on the stream.
I know you all really want to see and hear Mr. Smush, but, and that's my cat for those who don't know.
But, A, Mr. Smush is going to do whatever the hell he wants to do.
B, if I'm trying to make a point, I don't really want the cat screaming in the background, because you all are going to think we neglect him or something.
And that's totally not the case. I love him more than anything.
He's a cat. He'll whine whenever he wants.
Exactly. He's a cat. Every cat owner knows what I'm talking about.
Just like my cat. Like, every, like, I will literally drop treats down for her. She'll eat them. I'll walk across the room to refill her water. I'll put the water down.
I look at her and she's like, more treats? More treats? Like, I just gave you some goddamn treats.
In chat, I'm being asked, Pod Culture asked, what's in the box next to Rob? I don't know which box he's referring to.
This is a stand. So, I have a stand next to me. What might be the thing that Pod Culture's noticing, this is actually a stream deck.
So, this is a thing that I actually spent money on, but, you know, Elgato's not paying me to advertise it.
But I will say, I kind of like it a lot. It's very convenient and it actually controls the sidebar news stuff.
I can see exactly how many people are watching on Twitch right now as it updates. I can kill the mics with a button press, which I won't actually do.
It's been pretty neat. So, that's one of the things that is, you might see me poking out a little bit there is that thing there.
And that's the other scary thing about video is that now, like, now you're gonna see all the times when, like, Loki is doing a story and I just get up to go to the kitchen.
Or, I get up to do something else, it's like, oh, maybe I should-
So, anyways, this week, we have lots of stuff going on.
Alright, anyway. Let's move on. Oh, wait, no, didn't we have a little more on, like, what stores are doing? I thought there was one more little thing to this.
Then we'll move on to our gaming weeks.
Oh, what they're doing? I don't give a crap.
They're doing things and it's significant.
Alright, look. Oh, I thought we had another, oh well. I guess maybe we're, oh no, that's the story we're coming up with later.
Alright, so I'm just, I'm all mixed up, what can I do? Let's get to our gaming weeks.
Loki, how was your gaming week? What types of video games have you been playing this week?
Sadly, uneventful. I have not been playing DDR this week.
Only because I've been getting ready to put in the step mania component of my cabinet.
So I got all the parts for that, finally, so I'm going to be running a Ryzen 3 computer that's an APU.
And just some, you know, keeping it really compact.
It's literally going to be screwed to the inside of the monitor housing of where the monitor would be.
I have an HDTV in there right now.
So, getting all that, I got all the hardware, I got a lighting board, because originally they had lighting boards that you can buy.
They're like, I don't remember what they're called now, but they were based off of a pack drive, which is a device that's from Ultimark that's used to drive lights on an arcade cabinet.
And they use it for, like, you might be familiar with the iPack and stuff for like a main machine or something like that.
So this is their light controller thing.
It's more of like, I think on those cabinets, like lit up buttons and stuff, you can control this.
So I got that, but it's called a lit, it's lit or lit something, lit board, I don't remember who it is.
But some guys making, it's using Arduino and like a breakout board for the lights.
So it's very comparable to what the $200 board is, but only $50.
So I'm beta testing that, so we'll see how that works.
And then, of course, I already had a JPEG, actually I have two JPEGs, so hopefully one of those will work.
And then it's been just fighting with StepMania to try to get a theme that I can use.
It's like, I've been spending a lot of time making like, you know, logo and stuff for a fake mix that I'd put on there.
But I need, since I'm not, I haven't really dabbled in theming on StepMania,
aside from one time when I just kind of changed the color of a max theme or extreme theme to like make a max 3 or something.
And I did that for Roseville Golf Land at one time, but that was more of just like image editing,
and I didn't really change any of the Lua scripts or anything.
So now I'm trying to find something I can base off, but every theme that I've messed around with is broken in a different way.
Like some will be too laggy, some will just not support the features that I want.
It's just been trying to find one to build off of, and it's been frustrating.
So I've been just messing with that.
We need to get some b-roll for next week, because they're actually asking in the Twitch chat,
does Loki have photos of his hardware adventures?
But you do, you have your own stream, but you're playing DDR on your stream.
Our Twitch channels will crawl across the bottom at some point.
Yeah, yeah. So you can, in fact, this week I'll probably be playing again, because I do need to go back and do that again.
And I haven't actually put the hardware together, but I mean, that's going to take like a day to do that.
And then I just have to install Windows 10 on there, because I don't think Windows 7 recognizes a Ryzen 3 chip.
So yeah, I'll be doing that. This week I'll probably be playing Fifth Mix, because I'm going to get rid of Euro Mix 2, because it's driving me nuts.
And then, Pokemon Go. I've been playing a little bit of that. I've been meaning to play Pokemon Let's Go.
I've had like a Wartortle in my Pokeball Plus for like a week now.
Oh yeah, I think some poor thing's been imprisoned in my Pokeball for like three weeks.
Like the kids, they're like, I usually have them play with the Pokeball Plus in the car while we're taking them to school.
And then they're like, do you have something different in there now?
No, it's the same when they're like, oh, I don't even want to play with that anymore.
All that changes.
I want Pikachu back in there, because Pikachu makes noises. I'm like, but Pikachu's level 70, he doesn't need to go any higher.
Do they understand the different chirps and everything? I'm always like, what garbage bit noise chirp is that Pokemon?
Well, the Pikachu will make all sorts of noises, and they think that's great, but they don't like Wartortle.
And I don't necessarily either, but I'm trying to get a Blastress.
Life is hard.
Exactly, well, you know.
So, yeah, it's been that. I bought Katamari Damacy reroll.
I still need to.
But I have inflated, I have it on PC.
That's okay, they have your money. That's all they want.
I have it on PC. It's joined my backlog of everything.
And then, yeah, that's pretty much it. The only thing I played on PlayStation this week was the Harry Potter movies, because the kids wanted to watch it again.
I need to watch them, too. I'm going to come over and watch it with the kids.
Cheap plug, though. Spider-Man into the Spider-Verse. Fucking amazing. Go see it. Amazing movie.
It is literally the best Spider-Man movie to date. I mean, it's so good.
I believe you. Let's see. Before I get to my gaming week, somebody had asked in chat, Codeman had asked in chat, are we going to talk about the Kingdom Hearts 3 leak?
It wasn't on our show roll for tonight. Yeah, I saw it on Discord, actually. Again, over at vognetwork.com slash Discord.
Somebody actually posted on the Orange Lounge Radio channel that there was a leak, I guess probably overnight or yesterday, where the retail version, there's a box print of an Xbox One is out there somewhere.
But what's interesting about it is that there is a follow-up from the director of the game or something on Twitter that basically says, and guys, feel free to correct me in chat if I'm wrong.
It's part of the beauty about having a live chat room, live fact-checking. But I believe in the statement, they basically said the epilogue and the bonus scene aren't on the disc.
They purposely left that out for a day one patch just so this wouldn't leak, which I actually think is really smart, in a way. So, they left the movies out for a day one patch, which, you know, big games always get day one patches.
They should put a terrible ending on it, like a really stupid ending, so that's what people ruin, is this fake ending. That'd be hilarious. A dog ending. UFO ending.
Why can't we get a UFO ending for Kingdom Hearts 3?
Well, maybe it'll happen. You never know.
It just comes down to the end and it's like Sora standing there with Mickey and stuff. He's like, hey guys, I got something to admit to you. I don't know what the fuck is going on in this entire story right now.
Like, I gotta be honest, we've been killing these things and I have no fucking clue why I'm here.
And Shane in chat, or Shad Leland, excuse me, brings up a point that was something I had thought about too, asking, is it smart? What if someone buys the game and they live in the boonies and have terrible or no internet? Then you don't get the full game.
I mean, that's certainly a perspective worth talking about, but, you know, high speed internet is getting to more and more places, but okay, if you live in remote Alaska or somewhere that maybe doesn't have the most reliable high speed internet or it's satellite or something that's very expensive,
and maybe you're a Kingdom Hearts fan, you know, you may not get to see the epilogue because it's not on the disc.
Unless maybe they offered it for download and you could go, I mean, I don't know, that seemed really silly, but I know like some companies have done that.
You can like download a patch that you install via like a USB driver. At least that was something we could do on 360. I don't think we really do those anymore though.
It's just kind of one of those, if you're not online, too bad. Maybe new game consoles aren't for you.
You know, you're going to miss out if you're not on the internet. It's just the way it is.
I guess, so you'll just have to read about it or something. It'll be unfortunate.
You'll have to watch it on YouTube. Oh wait, you don't have internet. Can't watch YouTube, I guess.
Don't be mean. Don't be mean. Also, breaking news from our Discord that missed our show roll for tonight because this broke after the show was finished,
but SSJ100Matt actually posted over in our Discord that Colin Kroll passed away.
And even though you might wonder what that name has to do with gaming, he was the co-founder of Vine, which, I mean, Vine has brought us so many great six-second clips of things.
Love Vine. And also the popular game show app HQ Trivia. And I think most people have tried that app.
I don't know. I played that app once or twice a long time ago, and then I was like, I'm too stupid for this, and it's a waste of time.
And it was like a lot of bugs and things like that, so I just kind of stopped. But I think some people still play it. I don't know.
So, did you ever play HQ? No. Anyway, I'm not saying the app is going away, but it is very shocking that this individual has died because he's only 34 years old,
and the headline says that apparently it's a drug overdose. So, yikes. Don't do drugs, kids. That's really sad.
You never hear about drug underdoses.
Stop it. Alright, anyway. Yeah, it's really kind of, yeah, yeah, Kaijuto in chat is a fan of HQ Trivia.
So, yeah, I mean, whatever you feel about Vine or HQ Trivia, those have still been, like, big things.
And I will give HQ Trivia this. You guys know I've stanned this for the longest time is on the Xbox 360.
They used to have one versus 100, and that was so much fun to play, like the live game show thing, right?
So, HQ was, like, kind of that? Like, it was different. But, you know, it was a little bit of that same feeling.
So, I'll give it that, even though it was kind of so buggy I stopped playing. But you guys know I miss that like crazy.
Maybe now that we have the Twitch outreach, maybe I can make a personal plea to the folks over at Microsoft to get interactive game shows back because I really miss those.
You better listen to me, Rob. You want your one versus 100? You know what you can do? You can play fucking Fortnite like everybody else.
There's your one versus 100. No.
You can play Fortnite and your PUBG.
I've already told you about my Fortnite experiences and how I'm just like, what do I do in this game? I'm gonna go hide in this house, open the door.
Oh, I just got a shot in the face, but somehow I got 65th place. I mean...
My son loves playing that game. He just will not stop talking about... Well, he plays as a creative mode.
So, there's Fortnite creative mode, which is like, hey, it's like Minecraft, except you build crap in Fortnite and stuff happens.
I don't know. I don't really know what you do in that game.
It's so...
I don't want to play it.
No, I mean, it's not that hard of a concept, Loki. I mean, you want to outlive everybody else and the little bubble gets smaller and smaller.
So, you're forced to interact with other people.
That's all of the games.
Well, yeah, that's the battle royale mechanic and Fortnite just kind of did it early on.
I would only say first, but they did it early on. They did it very well. So, it's worked out for them.
The cartoony thing has made it very appealing to kids for some reason.
It should be like battle rail, battle rail.
Yeah. Anyway.
Like you should be randomly thrown out there with a random weapon.
All right. Anyway, my gaming week. Before we got on all those breaking news tangents, which we tend to do tangents here at Orange Launch Radio.
But I was going to talk a little bit about my gaming week.
And honestly, since I've been so busy trying to get this, what you're looking at, set up, I haven't had a lot of time to play games.
But I did play some Super Smash Brothers online, as I'm sure a lot of people have been doing if you're a Switch owner right now.
I was streaming some of that, did some stuff with my buddy Delvin at VG Realness on stream.
And just having fun with that, playing with some viewers.
And I still need to work on unlocking some of those characters. I've been playing very slowly.
But I really do enjoy the like the quest mode, the spirit mode.
I kind of like it. I know some people think it's a pain in the ass just because it goes on and on and on.
But it does kind of give me like something to do.
It's something for me to do. Just if I'm not wanting to go to bed yet, I'm just kind of chilling.
And just like, oh, I'll play a couple of these matches and knock it out.
Have you unlocked all the characters yet?
No, no, I'm not quite there yet. But maybe about half.
So, still working on it. I don't know, it hasn't been a huge race for me to unlock them.
Save if there's going to be a party or a get together or something and people want to play whatever character they want.
But I've got a good chunk of them so far at this point. So, we'll see.
And then I've also been playing more World of Warcraft because they just dropped a patch in that game this week.
And I've been working on my little warlock in that.
And I'm up to item level 350, which probably doesn't mean something to a lot of people.
But to those of you that do play WoW, you know, I've been grinding to get better loot and all that stuff on my Warcraft.
So, there's that.
Little bit of the incidental stuff like Pokemon Go.
I've barely touched Ingress. I've just been so busy with everything else.
So, yeah, just, you know, trucking along a lot of the same games I've been playing.
I do really need to get to Katamari Damacy reroll, though. I might do a stream of that once this all settles down.
And we are comfortable that our video transition to Twitch has been successful.
I heard that, well, the port of that game has been kind of, well, rushed, I guess.
They, like, cut out the English language, like, in the cutscenes or something like that.
There's no English language in there.
You can patch it back in on PC. They have a way that, of course, people have made to fix that.
Of course. That's part of the reason why I'm sure people are buying it.
That's why I got it on PC for all the...
It's made in Unity, too, from what I hear.
So, I'm looking forward to the mods on that.
Yeah, so that'd be awesome.
All right.
Well, we're going to get right back into the news, but I do want to just remind you guys.
We are here live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Black Wolf show over at Twitch TV slash VOG Network.
And if you miss a show for whatever reason, you can always download the podcast, which is available just about everywhere where podcasts are sold, including iTunes and Google Play.
All that good stuff. So, check out Orange On Radio.
Please consider leaving us a nice review while you're there. That stuff goes an awfully long way.
So, we will be back next week, and then I think in two weeks you said you might not be here.
Maybe.
So, we'll still...
We may or may not be here kind of in that break between Christmas and New Year's.
But then come 2019, we're really going to try to, you know, obviously we got enough set up on Twitch to bring you this tonight.
But we're really going to try to like keep, you know, I want to get a better shot that's going to include more and, you know, more of the studio and make it a little more studio-y in here and try to get all that going for next year.
That's a lot more studio-y in here than it was, right?
Yeah. So, it's the lighting, isn't it?
It's the lighting.
It's not like a dank cave anymore.
You know what's funny? The lights actually came with the green screen that I use, but I only really use the green screen because the lighting in the office, the office is so small it actually kind of works.
Like it's good enough for the green screen to work and for what I need on my personal Twitch.
But it came with these guys and now these guys are paying off.
Trust me, it was a really dark cavern man cave.
Although, you know, a gender discriminatory free cave and all that stuff.
It was just very dimly lit, like yellow lighting and probably candles too at some point.
So anyway, let's get into some more gaming news though.
I think we're ready to move on into this week's news.
So, Loki, why don't you start us off?
Yeah, so one of the big things that happened this week was that Blizzard had scaled back on Heroes of the Storm.
So they were actually, you know, taking some developers off of Heroes of the Storm and putting them onto other properties and projects right now.
So along with that though, they did announce that they're going to be canceling the esports stuff related to Heroes of the Storm for 2019 as well.
Unfortunately, they forgot to tell anybody that's involved in the esports with Heroes of the Storm.
They just kind of like, oh, hey, you guys are learning about it now as well.
So, you know, of course that didn't go over well.
If they had told them early, it probably would have leaked.
I mean, not that I'm defending that choice, but I can sort of maybe understand why they felt that was a risk they didn't want to take.
I don't know, but basically, you know, for example, one of the team's, I guess, Method, their general manager stated that,
we are troubled by the way the announcement was made, namely the impolite choice to use social media and to share such a message that effectively ended the careers of hundreds of players,
content creators, casters, production crews overnight and broke the hearts of countless fans.
As someone who is, and this is Wolf Schroeder, who is one of the casters basically,
as someone who has commented Heroes of the Storm since 2015, I mostly really feel for the 200 plus pro players who have lost jobs via a blog post today.
I always loved casting heroes, so it's tragic to see it suddenly, or go suddenly.
Thanks for all the kind messages today, friends.
So that sucks, especially for a lot of people that make this basically, you know, their livelihood.
Right, and I'm not defending this choice and how Blizzard did it, but I mean, what's to stop another league from still forming outside of Blizzard being,
I mean, is they just worry, the money's not going to be, you know, everything good takes money, is it just a concern that the money's not going to be there?
I mean, there's so much that's homegrown, especially in this day and age where any idiot can build a Twitch channel, you know, like,
I mean, and I say that, that they can go and, you know, maybe form something, I mean, but it wouldn't, the dollars wouldn't be there, I get it.
Yeah, I think it's that, but put all your eggs in one basket, though.
Well, that's a very interesting, like, reality of esports, I think, in a way.
And again, I don't want to sound like I'm being disrespectful, it's just one of those, because actually I really do enjoy Heroes of the Storm,
and other than Overwatch League, HGC is probably the one thing I have watched before, because I don't get into it enough where I really follow the teams closely,
I couldn't tell you who's on what team or whatever, but I just like to watch because I learn about the characters and how to play them better,
and so I kind of learn a lot of that watching that. Like, watching football is not going to make me better at football, you know what I mean?
Watching baseball is not going to make me better at it, but when I watch Heroes of the Storm being played live, sure, there's a lot that's not going to make me better at it,
but I learn things about team composition and skills that you take and why players do certain things that maybe I don't get from other sports.
So, I will say, two Heroes of the Storm's complement, and the HGC and all these people that have been working with it,
I don't consider myself hardcore with Heroes of the Storm, I casually play once in a while, but I enjoyed what I got out of watching these professional matches.
So I, too, am sad to see it kind of just end like that, that was Thanos snapping, actually, and that's what happened here.
Only half of it's gone.
Well, I mean, but the soul still burns, but you know what I mean, there's still going to be-
I think that's Soulcalibur.
I know. There's still going to be fans streaming it on their personal Twitch channels, like Heroes as a spectator sport is not necessarily dead,
but my whole point with this, bringing it back to esports, is that it's something kind of unique that we don't deal with with football and baseball and basketball on ESPN,
like those sports have been around forever and they're not really changing majorly.
Yeah, but it's not necessarily, though, so much the participation in that, but even, for example, there was one of the casters, Tetcher,
basically said that he's been making $4,000 a month since during the season, and he received a day rate from Blizzard that he relied upon to pay his rent and bills,
and it was his only source of income outside of his stream, and so unfortunately it's like almost losing your job,
so it's not necessarily that, yeah, they're not going to get the income from the actual event, the prize pool or whatever,
but they're also not getting the other income for keeping this whole tournament scene going, including all the commentating and running, filming, all that stuff.
But it's also like a scary reality for people that are involved in esports playing, is that one day this can happen,
you know, one day there's going to be a new game and people move on from the old game they were playing,
and so, I mean, I hope, it's kind of like, I've kind of joked about this and I don't want to say joke, because it's, you know what I mean, though,
like I'm serious about this, even though it sounds like I'm being an asshole, but I'm being serious is that what happens if you're a Twitch streamer
and that's how you make your living, or you're a YouTube, you're a YouTube person and that's how you make your living, right, because there's people that do that now,
and then YouTube makes a rule that like fucks you and your income gets cut by like two thirds in like a month or whatever,
like are you saving money for when the bubble breaks on any of that stuff, like that's the scary stuff.
Us, and I know you're probably looking at this going, the irony of you doing this while you're doing a podcast live on Twitch,
but the reality is we haven't made shit from this show in 16 years.
Nothing to lose.
No, I've lost a lot actually doing this show, but exactly, you know, it's fine, you know, I'm not going to miss it when it's gone,
that sounds terrible from a financial perspective, I'm not going to miss it when it's gone, but obviously I'll miss it terribly,
but you know what I mean, like, and again, people, if they want to make a living off YouTube and they have that talent,
they want to make a living off esports, that's their prerogative, but it is this weird reality of one day it could end.
Well right, and I have to also wonder too, like with this, that Blizzard's going to have new games that will be esports, I guess, compatible,
what's going to happen then when they're trying to get, you know, these people to come on, hey, come participate in our new esports game.
Yeah, completely forget that we fucked over all those people before, but hey, come join the new stuff, come on over, we won't fuck you over again, right away, promise.
I mean, I guess, you know, now that I'm thinking about it here, because we do that a lot, we just kind of brainstorm a lot,
now that I'm thinking about it, I guess there are a lot of like basketball and baseball players who might get an injury,
and then they can't play anymore. That does happen, you know, and it's like, well, I think there's insurance and stuff that happens in those scenarios,
but I don't know all the specifics.
Well then they're going to have to turn to esports, which some of them will.
Some of them have, I think, some of them do commentating and stuff, I don't know if there's a lot of players, but some of them do like commentating and all that stuff, so, anyway.
Bionic limbs, I say.
So anyway, YYR in chat says they doomed their future esports prospects outside of Overwatch, and I think that might be referring to the way this was all announced,
but even Overwatch is going to fade one day. I mean, there are very few, and I love Overwatch, but there are very few games that are very, very old that still are played competitively.
Smash Brothers Melee on the GameCube.
Counter-Strike.
I'll give you that Counter-Strike. There's a handful, but not a ton, you know?
It's, you know, and I'm sure Overwatch is probably worthy of being in that, you know, that grouping, but that is for the public to decide at the end of the day, right?
Right. I don't know.
Well, we'll see. I just, Activision hasn't had, or I should say Blizzard hasn't had really good luck with messaging this year, especially recently.
Doing a few more chat comments over at Twitch, SH2100Matt does verify there is insurance, he watches a little more of the sports ball stuff than I do,
but says there is no insurance if the league shuts down, which is kind of what happened in this scenario.
KArts1 says, as much as I love Heroes of the Storm, in the back of my mind, I always had a feeling that this would eventually happen, LOL.
Oh, I'm sorry. LOL. League of Legends. Sorry. League of Legends.
LOL. LOL.
Sorry, I was like, wow, that was really harsh to laugh at it. Sorry.
League of Legends and Dota have such a market share on the genre, and Heroes of the Storm never really took a large chunk of that.
It's interesting because I've played all those games, and personally, just as a player, I've always preferred Heroes of the Storm because it's a little bit more easy to learn, easy to get into,
but that's also why I think some people prefer Dota.
Easy to shuffle our developers off of so that we can make other games appropriate for Chinese markets instead of them being banned there?
Yes. Alright, anyway.
S2100matt says, all it takes is someone to put the money towards the League if Blizzard or Activision were allowed. Well, we'll see, but now they've also announced that the developers are kind of being shifted to other projects,
that they'll still have a crew working on Heroes of the Storm, but that Blizzard is working on a bunch of other stuff right now, and they need some of the key developers other places.
So you sort of get that sense that Heroes of the Storm, while it's still going to exist, it's still going to be happy to take your money, like it's not going to necessarily get gigantic content upgrades in the future.
Kind of like where Diablo 3 is at.
Aside from canceling, obviously they have to make the announcement for canceling the esports stuff, but why do they even have to announce that they're going to shuffle people around in their company?
Why is that something that needs to be like...
Because Blizzard wants to remind you there is more coming than just Diablo Immortal.
It didn't help! They didn't make it better. They made it worse. It didn't help. People are still thinking that, you know, well, they're fucking things over, and then they fuck things over even more.
Bad dog. Bad. Didn't do it right.
YY Orange Chat says, I did see a thread on Reset Era this week that basically was like, Blizzard was told to ship more games and spend less time on them.
And of course, you know, you have to take all that kind of anonymous forum post with a grain of salt, but I mean, this is where a lot of people have wondered, is Activision's influence.
Some of these changes too, Mike Morhaime kind of officially left not long ago either.
Like, are some of these changes starting to show their not-so-fantastic sides? I don't know.
We'll see.
All the mighty fall at some point.
It's depressing though. It really is.
Well, you know what? The Mortal Kombat franchise looks to still be going, and it's still going to be doing pretty well.
Mortal Kombat 11, I think a lot of people are looking forward to. There is going to be customizable variants in the game.
Esports-focused multiplayer mode, so there's something you can take up if you want.
We're all esports now.
We're all esports now. Well, but fighting games have always, they have EVO, you know, there's always kind of been like a place for them, and you know.
Yeah, fine.
I'm pretty sure, you know, I don't think Street Fighter V has been going so well, so I'm sure people are waiting for, I shouldn't say that.
Because then I'll get the Street Fighter V fan that's like, fuck you, you don't know what you're talking about.
But, you know, just, it's been a bumpy ride. I think we all agree with that.
But Mortal Kombat 11, you know, people are gearing up and getting excited about this.
They want to remind you that if you pre-order the game, Shao Kahn is going to be a bonus character that's playable.
Mortal Kombat 11 will have a new game engine, a new personalization system, which I'm assuming is create your own character.
So I'm sure that's going to go well, based on what we see in Soul Calibur and all that stuff, right?
I see no problems with Soul Calibur. What are you talking about?
Especially when you consider the personalization system is now in a game where people die horrifically.
Like, nothing's going to happen with this. Maybe personalization doesn't mean you actually create the old characters.
Just that, like, clothes, accessories, and stuff, you can kind of build on the existing ones.
Maybe that's what they're going for. That would make a lot more sense.
Yeah, okay.
New fatalities and a new gore-tech system. Oh, joy.
They should have a creative fatality.
What the fuck is gore-tech?
It's a made-up word.
They are saying the multiplayer is oriented towards esports and personalization systems daily news, updated rewards, and so forth.
The limited edition will have a steel case and six extra characters in the combat pack pass.
Excuse me. One of those characters, potentially Spawn?
Yeah.
Mortal Kombat has been getting some, you know, bigger name characters, licensed characters.
Well, we had Predator, we had Freddy and Jason, right? We've seen, you know, a few of them.
Spawn, although ironically, has been in Soul Calibur, right? The Xbox version of Soul Calibur 2.
Probably the one people didn't play as much because everyone wanted the GameCube one with Link, right?
But the Xbox one had Spawn.
However, a recent Reddit Ask Me Anything with Todd McFarlane, who of course is the man behind Spawn, asked,
would Spawn be available to be in the upcoming Mortal Kombat game?
McFarlane said, I believe he's on his way, dot dot dot.
So, did he let the cat out of the bag a little early? Is he just fucking with people? Who knows?
What do you think about Spawn as a potential character in 11?
I love Spawn. I'm fine with that.
You know, there's supposed to be a new Spawn movie, I thought.
Yes, I know.
That's the thing we were working on.
I know that they're doing that. I watched the original Spawn movie because at the time I was really into Spawn.
In fact, what's kind of funny, my dad was delivering to the...
At the time, he was delivering for FedEx to the same video distributor that I ended up working for at some point.
So at one point, he was just delivering to them and they would get screeners and whatnot.
But he got me the Spawn standee that went along with the movie.
I had a giant Spawn standee in my room.
Not to mention, I mean, just to give you an example of how much I love Spawn,
I had on my wall a mural of Spawn and the Violator.
Like, a giant fucking mural of that shit.
Which was great when we were selling the house, because they're like, wow, there's a giant fucking demon on that wall.
I don't get a creepy feeling from this house.
It was the cover of issue 16, if I remember correctly, which had the Spawn from there.
And then, I think it was issue 7 or something like that. It was a Violator from one of those.
But they basically drew it on the wall and they painted me a nice mural, because that's what I wanted.
And it was awesome.
Everybody else was creeped out by it, but it was so awesome.
It was cool.
So, if I really liked Mortal Kombat, yeah, I'd still be down for it, but I don't really care for Mortal Kombat.
But Spawn's awesome. I'll totally go see the movie.
You know who really likes Mortal Kombat? My husband, Alan.
Even though I'm like, eh, it's so gross now. I love the old ones. The cartoony ones are great.
I heard a rumor they're going to do the trilogy again, Remastered.
I thought I picked that up. I don't know if it was on Discord or where I picked that up.
Remastered again?
Well, I think fans did it already, so I don't know if that's crossing wires with the fan project.
I thought they did that already, like an Xbox 360.
Well, they did, but it was just the games ported.
Oh, you mean like actually recaptured everything?
Yes, yes.
Fine.
I was going to say, there was actually, someone was saying, I don't know if they wanted the petition or something,
but they wanted Doomguy in Mortal Kombat, which I could totally see that.
Sure, I'm for that. I'm for that.
Well, that goes right into what we're going to talk about next, doesn't it?
Yes, it does. So Doom just had an anniversary, a 25th anniversary actually.
The game was released December 10, 1993.
And to commemorate the anniversary as well, John Romero had a livestream that he did,
and during that livestream he announced a sigil, which is a Doom megawad.
And for those who may not remember, a wad of course was the container files that they used to store all the levels and data for the game.
So this giant megawad file that you can get, and it contains nine new single player and multiplayer levels.
And it's basically a giant mod from the original creator of the game.
So that's pretty awesome.
And then he basically said, I wanted the levels to feel like they belonged in the original game as if they were the true fifth episode.
There's more detail in the levels than episodes one through four, but not overly so.
I believe that the people playing sigil will recognize my design style,
but see new things I'm doing because this episode does not take place on a military base.
It takes place in hell, which is new to me within the Doom design space.
There's massive room in episode five, mission six, that contains the coolest room I've ever created in any map.
So sigil's going to be coming out in February, and it will be free to download.
And then he's also going to be doing some limited edition fan boxes as well, full of goodies like floppy disks, a soundtrack,
and apparently if you buy the deluxe edition, a pewter statue of his own head on a spike.
Because that's, that's awesome.
Would you, you know, Doom has had so many like fan wads over the years, it seems so weird that like,
it's just like you're kind of getting what fans have been doing for forever, but it's kind of cool.
But it's the original creator, that's awesome.
It is cool, it's nice to see him kind of like jump back in the waters and so forth,
but is this going to be like something we've just never seen before, or is it just, I want to check this out because...
It's cool, it's just like, I mean, I haven't played it yet, because I'm surprised I haven't played it yet.
I think I actually have it, but the Duke Nukem 3D that they did, the world domination or whatever one they had,
the last Duke Nukem 3D remaster or whatever they put out, they had the additional episode in there as well.
That's kind of the same type of thing, except I don't think that was the original creators that made that episode.
It was more of just, hey, we're throwing a new episode in there, yay.
So, yeah, it's cool. It's free. I'm not going to complain, you know.
I like free stuff.
And plus, you know, the fact that Doom has been supported for this long, I mean, it's ridiculous. 25 years.
And that, the new Doom was pretty good too.
Yeah, new Doom was awesome, but even the original Doom, they've got so many tweaks and stuff to it now,
and they even have a Battle Royale Doom thing as well.
And I believe it's one of the Xbox One compatible, because I had it on Xbox 360, and it's Xbox One backwards compatible.
Sadly, I don't think you can do any of this stuff. I wish you could.
I don't know. Not without modding, maybe, but a lot of those games still use the same WAD files.
It's just, you know, they rebuild the launcher.
All right. Well, let's move on to another game kind of crossover thing that's coming up.
Capcom and CD Projekt Red are teaming up for a Monster Hunter event.
So, in Monster Hunter World, in a free event that's supposed to launch in early 2019,
you are going to get to have Geralt in the game. Of course, Geralt from The Witcher,
which is, again, one of those games that, like, I really, really need to, like, sit down with the 70 hours and play that game,
because the little bits I have played were great, and it's just, you know, so many games, so little time, right?
It's the gamer's crisis that we've been dealing with forever.
But anyway, with this, the expansion is actually called Iceborne, and so there's gonna be freezing ice biomes
that'll be a little bit new to the game, and this is all part of more Monster Hunter World content.
More information in the spring, so I don't think it's gonna be, like, you're not gonna get this in the next few weeks or anything.
It's still a few months out, but that's pretty cool. There's also gonna be a new event quest,
which allows 16 people in groups of four each to team up towards a common goal.
That comes back on December 20th. Also, ooh, and I might have to check this out.
Oh, darn it. It's going on now, and I missed it. A free trial from December 11th through December 17th.
Just buy the game. It's, like, 20 bucks.
Oh, wait, I'm sorry. I'm thinking Witcher.
Oh, yeah, no, Monster Hunter World.
I have some friends that play it and seem to enjoy it, so...
I was gonna say The Witcher. Yeah, I've been...
Every time I see it go on sale, I'm like, ooh, maybe I should get it.
And I'm like, you know, when you buy that, you're never gonna play it because
you have all these other games you haven't played yet.
But, yeah.
Cia Tiberian Chat says, I'd rather have Geralt throw up in Monster Rancher.
Well, he had a cameo this year already in Soulcalibur VI, so they're putting him out.
The CD Projekt Red's kinda...
I'd just rather have Monster Rancher come back,
but then again, we don't use CDs anymore, so what the hell would that be?
He could be a character in Mortal Kombat 11, maybe?
I don't know.
Anyway, now, Monster Hunter has previously collaborated with Final Fantasy XIV,
and they are saying that that was a pretty well-received collaboration.
I can tell you from the Final Fantasy XIV perspective, it was a cool fight.
Like, they did, like, a boss fight, basically, but...
And then the way it ended, you had to, like, loot the boss similar to how you would in Monster Hunter.
Like, it was a little different.
Ooh, they should make Monster Rancher, but instead of using CDs to unlock the monsters, it would be, like, image files.
Okay.
So it's like, you know, hey, that picture of that giant dick I found on the internet,
that just unlocked some, like, really strong, like, monster. That's awesome.
No. No, no, no.
No?
All right. Well, maybe.
All right, let's move on. Just a couple more stories for you guys before we get to the classic game of the week. Loki.
Yes. So, because we were talking about fighting games, let's talk about Street Fighter V
and all the great choices that they're making. All those great damn choices.
So, somebody at Capcom had the fantastic idea, hey, you know where we haven't advertised yet?
On the players and everywhere else. So, that's what they're gonna be doing.
They have...
I remember this coming up a little bit last week.
Yes, but now that we get to see what it looks like.
Got it.
And it looks, like, fucking terrible. Like, it's everywhere. Like, it's ridiculously everywhere.
And apparently...
By the way, we're selling space on our studio wall. If you want to sponsor us, we'll put, you know, we'll put stickers and things over there.
A lot of this stuff is... Look at this. This is a poster for Final Fantasy XI. You know how old that is?
It's gonna come back. I mean it.
Kingdom Hearts.
Kingdom Hearts. The first Kingdom Hearts. Like, a bootleg scroll from the first Kingdom Hearts.
And look, all the way... I know it's washed out by the light a little bit because I can't get the lighting perfect in here.
Pop'n Music XI for the PlayStation 2.
Didn't we have, like, an Indigroove or something? Like, Indigroove 2 poster that was signed by Kyle Ward or something like that?
We might have that around here somewhere. We have a lot of stuff we didn't... We kind of ran out of wall space for.
Unfortunately, it's not on cam. Maybe I'll move things around.
Yeah, we have an actual Dance Dance Revolution machine marquee over here.
And our picture. Our happy 300th episode picture that was drawn.
Remember? We were 300 episodes in. Remember that?
Yeah.
But this Borderlands 2. Actually, Codeban saw that in chat. He's like, is that the poster I sent you?
Yes! It was signed by Randy Pitchford.
And it's actually signed?
It is. It's signed by many people from the team.
I still have, in my garage, framed up a true crime... Well, at the time it was true crime.
I don't know what city it's gonna be because this is E3. We're not announcing what city it is yet.
Spoiler. It was New York.
So, I have that poster signed by the entire cast as well, which...
It's got Tracy Lords that signed it. That's neat.
Anyways, since I was distracted by everything else that's in here...
So yeah, they have this whole advertisement mode that literally plasters this logo.
For example, they're doing the Capcom Pro Tour right now, which...
It's just plastered everywhere. Like, on the arms of these players, on this giant belt that they have...
It's fucking ugly. It's just stupid. You can opt out of it.
They want you, of course, to opt in on it because if you opt in on it, you get some additional fighter bucks, whatever the fuck they call it, to unlock shit in the game.
It's not worth it, but it's optional.
But, you know, I can't wait until the next thing that comes out, you know, like...
Old Spice or whatever the fuck they're gonna, you know, match up with this.
I can't think of what other terrible possible, like, sponsors they could have.
Totino's Pizza Rolls.
That's an awesome sponsor. I'm sorry.
Okay, fine.
I love food.
But I guess this isn't as bad as maybe Cup Noodle in Final Fantasy XV.
I mean, that was ridiculous, but that was over the top. This is just obnoxious.
It was. It was. The little, like, armor and stuff that uses that was always a little bit crazy.
It's just obnoxious. But you can turn it off. But it's terrible. So don't...
Just... It's better if you just turn it off because, I'm gonna tell you right now, if they find that this is effective, they're just gonna make it fucking worse.
So it's... Just... Just turn it off.
Alright. Let's move on for one more story here before our Classic Game of the Week.
And we're gonna talk a little bit about the Mega Man Legacy Collection, which is a classic game collection of sorts, right?
Yeah.
The Mega Man Legacy Collection has Mega Mans 1 through 6.
Now, what you may remember, this was already released a while ago on the PC, PlayStation 4, Xbox One.
And then they came out with the version on Switch.
Well, for the most part, they were the same, except the Switch introduced a rewind feature.
So you could actually, you know, if you screw up in the game, which I do a lot, you could hit a rewind button and, like, instantly replay it, basically.
Kind of like, I do this a lot in Forza Horizon as well. Also has a rewind button and I use it a lot there.
So anyway, they ended up actually patching this feature in to the PC, the PlayStation 4, and Xbox One versions three years after the release.
At least they're still working on it.
Yeah, I know. That's kind of cool. So now you can rewind in those versions as well. So that's pretty cool. Sorry, 3DS owners. You're screwed.
But I guess they figure most of you may be upgraded to Switch by now. I don't know. But what can you do?
So there it is. The Mega Man Legacy Collection updated, which is a game that I've played maybe a little bit of on Switch.
I probably need to play some more of. But those classic Mega Mans.
Yeah.
Which one's your favorite?
Two, maybe?
I would say two is probably my favorite as well, even though I know there's so much love for three and that the bosses from two are in three.
It's just I just choose the one I'm always going to remember.
Yeah, I remember three as well. I don't know. It's been a long time since I played all this.
I did at one time, like, beat, I think, all of them. But I don't remember. It's been so long.
All right. Well, I think it's about time we get to the classic game of the week and figure out what's been picked out.
It's not Mega Man, unfortunately, but I think it's another good one. So what do you say we get to the classic game of the week?
Sounds good.
All right. And tonight we're playing with a new kind of magic. So this is all it's new, uncharted territory.
Well, as Arthur C. Clarke says, any technology suitably advanced enough is indistinguishable from magic.
But one thing is, of course, going to be consistent. That know it all, Dark Saga or Jamie Summers is still here with us.
Hi.
Hi, how are you?
I'm OK.
Good. Good to see you here.
A peddler enjoyed us all week.
Yeah, except unfortunately, just the magic isn't quite there yet for us to see you here.
Not if I can help it.
Twitch thing going on. I've got to get those wigs ready.
I know. I know you're doing this, but we're here talking about the classic game of the week.
Yeah, as we always do. That is still going to be consistent. Always.
Never.
Yup. Except when it's not, because once a month you do something different.
But we'll talk about it.
I already did the different. I know. But I did that live.
Different is fun. Anyway, let's get to it. It's the classic game of the week.
Dark Sakura, what did you pick for the classic game of the week tonight?
Nineteen X X.
The war against destiny.
I know. Sounds pretty dramatic for, you know, a fucking shooter game.
It is a vertical scrolling shooter by Capcom released in 1996.
It takes place before a fictional war in 19XX as a lone pilot.
Tries to defeat an entire army by himself trying to prevent another world war.
Which would escalate to a nuclear apocalypse.
Apocalypse.
Sounds like a prolapse.
Alpaca lips.
More like alpacas.
I don't know. Given the way the world is, it's more of a prolapse.
Anyway.
Anus or something. I don't know.
Wow.
Anyway, it is the fourth game in a series of World War II vertical shooters by Capcom.
The other games in the series were 1942, 1943, the Battle of Midway, 1941, Counterattack.
They were all on Capcom CPS1.
Released through 1984 through 1990.
This one is a CPS2 game so it had a different style from the previous games.
It also was followed by 1944 The Loopmaster in 2000.
Which may end up being a classic game in the future.
Womp womp in the future.
So you select one of three planes.
Each one has different ratings and speed, power, and their homing attack strength.
And so they fly through the levels.
The three primary weapons can be used by either picking up their respective items.
You have a fire that does Vulcan bullets, a straight firing laser, or multi-directional missiles.
By holding the button one, you can charge them up to shoot a special missile.
Sorry, my brain instantly went to gachamon.
I want to fire the bird missile!
Anyway.
Or that was more like G-Force.
I don't know. He always wanted to fire the bird missile.
I don't watch the animes.
So I don't know.
Girl, don't even lie.
Maybe once in a while.
You've watched some things.
Maybe a little Pokemon.
Yeah.
I listen to- I watch what-
I know a certain somebody in this room went to go see the Pokemon movie with the very first one.
So.
That is true.
Twice.
I was just saying, I saw it with Amanda.
Remember Amanda?
I remember.
She's adorable.
When you told the person with the small penis to shut up.
No.
That was not a Pokemon.
I would not say that at Pokemon.
That was a grudge.
Oh that's right.
That movie was great too.
Anyway.
Oh hi.
19XX.
Yeah.
XDX.
You also-
Not 20XDX.
Which is a great Mega Man club.
19XDX.
Well at any rate there you also get smart bombs that can clear out the whole page.
Whole page.
The whole screen with all the projectiles on the screen too.
You can also charge them up so each level of charge gets a different effect.
If you are shot- I was going to say shart.
If you are shot down while charging a bomb.
The bomb does not go off.
Which is sad.
It should just go off and clean everything while you reload.
So at the end of every level you get additional points for the number of bombs you still have
in a rank of 1-5 depending on the percentage of enemies destroyed.
And for the time it took you to take down a boss.
And a bonus for every medal collected which is multiplied by rank.
After beating the last level you also get a large bonus for the number of lives you
have remaining.
It has been ported to GameTap which I wasn't aware of.
But it was not released in the Capcom Classics collection as it is considered a modern game
according to Capcom.
It was commended for having some of the cleanest looking animation, multi-level backgrounds,
digitized explosions and various streams of patterned enemies place.
19xx among the cream of the crop.
That was from Next Generation magazine.
He also did find that the various methods of attack set it from different shooters and
gave it a 3 out of 5 stars.
That's kind of middling though.
But the words are nice.
So yeah, again to go through the whole series starting at the beginning we have 1942, 1943
The Battle of Midway.
Also called 1943 Kai which I'm sure you've heard of before.
I think you did at least one of these games before.
I'm sure I have.
I think I did 1942.
There was also 1941 Counterattack, 19xx The War Against Destiny.
1944 The Loopmaster and 1942 Joint Strike.
And there you go.
Alright.
The classic game of the week.
19xx.
19xtx.
There it is.
And 20xtx is not the sequel.
No.
This was the first of the series on CBS2.
Alright.
Well that's going to do it for our classic game of the week.
But Dark Sakura, any final words as we go back to our debut on Twitch?
Actually I was double checking one thing just to see what the other one is released on.
Actually 1942 Joint Strike was actually an Xbox Live Arcade and PSN copy so it never
had an arcade release.
Well there you go.
But The Loopmaster did.
And The Loopmaster was also CPS2.
Alright.
Enough about playing shooty pew pew games.
Although they are a good series.
Is there a great series?
Well some of them were kind of meh.
But they were all Capcom's foray into it and certainly maybe they were a little bit bitter
about World War II.
I don't know.
Any parting words as we go back to our debut on Twitch?
We have done a lot of tweaking behind the scenes getting this shit working.
We've been working real hard.
Ever since we saw that preview footage from Bobby Blackwell I was like,
Oh crap.
We are not ready.
You are not prepared.
But I think we're prepared now.
We're good.
Alright.
And my voice has finally decided to go off.
Fuck it.
So last words.
Words.
Alright.
We're back here live with our episode number 756 in progress tonight.
You know the date was wrong on the top this whole time until like somebody told me like
just maybe like 20 minutes ago before we went to the last game of the week.
So yeah.
Boy.
It's certainly.
You know it's the first night.
Things are going to go wrong on Twitch.
What can you do?
It's a huge change.
Again we did things one way.
16 and a half years.
So this is definitely a little bit different for us.
But we are going to get back into the show.
Thank you guys so much for you guys joining us along in our chat over at Twitch TV slash
vog network.
Of course is the channel where you can you know subscribe and follow along and watch
ourselves and Bobby Blackwell on Sunday nights in 2019 the kids over anime jam session are
also going to make their move.
Yeah.
It's exciting.
And who knows.
We're looking for more shows especially those with video.
You know the talk shows type of things would definitely be interested in working with some
more individuals in that capacity.
I do want to stress that the current vog network and all the shows we work with there.
We're not like getting rid of given those show shout outs and things like that.
Unfortunately we've lost a few shows over the last year you know just the shows of pod
faded for various reasons you know pod culture just finished up.
Critical Myth I know was taped in their last episode and they were on their way out.
I think Power Ranger Pride is said they're they're pretty much done but there's still
a lot of great shows there that are moving on and we hope to still work with them and
find ways to promote each other and keep promoting independent podcasting because that's what's
all about.
We got to support independent podcasters.
So and thanks you guys.
I love that it's flea and chat says you guys are doing great.
Yes.
Thank you.
We appreciate that.
We're trying we're trying our best.
All right.
But I'm I'm trying almost my best.
Yes.
I so since we haven't hit affiliate status yet you can you know view all the previous
stuff.
I do want to point out and there's a whole article over VOG Network that explains this.
If you want to watch the archives in the future once we really get things kind of locked down
here the way the way we envision them long term we are going to have that that you have
to be a subscriber for the twitch channel to be able to see all the old videos.
But the podcast none of that is going away.
So you know the free audio podcast we would never take that away or make you pay for that
all the sudden but only the video is going to be something where it's a subscription.
But so many of you I think have the prime accounts anyway and you get a free one every
month.
So I mean just toss that over to VOG Network and you'll be able to access the archives
again.
We are not an affiliate of twitch yet.
We just kind of think that's that's the design is we're hoping to get there pretty soon and
then we'll be able to open that up to you guys.
But if you guys want to make clips and things like that I don't remember if non affiliate
they can do the clips and the hot.
But if you feel like making clips of something of this show is funny or whatever we have
another broccoli farm moment this week or what have you.
Feel free to clip away.
You do that stuff all you want.
That's not that old already.
You haven't.
The joke isn't as funny as it was last.
No it isn't.
It's really it's kind of kind of come and gone.
It's sunset.
We'll see the broccoli farm.
Well I still want to hear how that goes over when you finally tell the kids where you're
really going.
Oh I'm sure they'll be really excited and then ask us every single day where we're going.
Yeah because my one son doesn't understand the concept of time very well.
All right.
Well let's get back into some news.
We have some rapid fire news some quick stories we want to get into here before we get to
like the mailbag and stuff.
So apparently the SNK 40th anniversary collection has gotten an update with additional 11 complete
games for free.
So they have split this up against three downloads but you get Beast Busters, Bermuda Triangle,
Chopper One, Fantasy, Much Mobile, Osmo Wars, Paddlemanium, SAR Search and Rescue, Suzuki
versus Commander, Time Soldiers and World Wars.
I need to pick up that collection.
Crystallis alone.
I love that game on NES.
I used to play a ton of Bermuda Triangle on the NES.
Yes.
Yeah.
So it's available for free.
So check it out.
Love that game.
And then of course Nintendo has stated that they're going to be discontinuing the SNES
and NES classics after this holiday.
So basically this is the last chance to get them.
And finally it's not hard to get these things.
No.
But you need to get them now.
You gotta get them now because if not you're gonna be stuck at the PlayStation Classic.
Which is being marked down by the way.
Already.
It's $75.
Where?
Target.
Right now.
Already.
Target.
In fact earlier you could get it for $75 on Amazon plus a $25 gift card to Amazon.
It's $50 bucks.
Uh oh.
Alright.
And they're modded already completely.
You can put whatever game you want.
I hope Sony has learned a couple things.
And maybe we'll get something a little different next time.
We'll see what happens.
So.
They tried to half-ass it.
And unfortunately.
Yeah.
That's not gonna work out well for them.
Well.
But the NES and the Super Nintendo Classics.
They're pretty good.
You know.
Unfortunately.
You can't really.
Well.
If you mod them you can add new games to them.
But officially you can't add new games to them or anything.
You're kind of locked into those games.
But that's.
That's.
They're still.
They're good picks.
Unofficially though.
You can put whatever the fuck you want on there.
I know.
So anyway.
A lot of that classic library for NES stuff is moved on to the Switch online.
That's kind of where they want you to go now because they ink pay that every year basically.
They did recently update the Switch online.
Nintendo Switch online library.
With some new games.
Including the Adventures of Lolo, Wario's Woods, and Ninja Gaiden.
Which I had talked about this week.
I actually had played Adventures of Lolo a little bit.
I forgot to mention that in my gaming week.
So there's those.
But they also added.
They've been kind of doing this every month.
They add bonus SP modes from other releases.
So there were some bonus SP modes.
There was Dr. Mario SP and Metroid SP.
So in Dr. Mario SP you basically start right near the end.
So you can see like a rare animation thing that you don't normally see unless you beat level 20.
So Dr. Mario SP kind of lets you go right to that.
Basically.
Or right before that.
You still have to do a little bit.
Metroid SP.
This one's interesting.
All they are, they're save states.
That are just basically preloaded.
So the Metroid one starts you off at Ridley.
So you have all the items and everything you need.
You start at Ridley and you can go in and just kick Ridley's ass.
Which is really not difficult.
I remember it being a lot harder as a kid.
But hint.
Just freeze all those fireballs then blast away with missiles.
That's really all you have to do.
And it's very very easy with the ice beam.
So you can fight Ridley there.
And I think they're probably doing that because of Ridley's appearance in Super Smash Brothers.
So they want to remind people.
Because a lot of people probably aren't going to be able to play their own way there.
So you can kind of check that out as a classic or whatever.
No word yet though what's coming out next year.
You know we've kind of known for the rest of this year.
What is going to be coming out.
But we don't know what's coming out in January.
So Nintendo still has to kind of announce that.
So we'll see what comes out next.
Alright anyway.
Moving on to a new Final Fantasy character coming to Final Fantasy Brave Exvius.
Which I know some people are really addicted to on their cellular phones.
That was the game that Ariana Grande was actually in.
You remember that?
My favorite Final Fantasy character Ariana Grande.
Well you might have a new one.
Because Katy Perry is coming to Final Fantasy Brave Exvius.
That's right.
Katy Perry will be in a commercial.
Which features one of her songs that I guess she's out there promoting.
And she'll also be a character in the game.
So the promo started earlier this week.
And good luck trying to get her as an unlocked character in the game there.
So you can check out the little commercial out there featuring her song.
Immortal Flame is out there on the YouTubes and all that stuff.
I'm sure she knows what Final Fantasy is.
To which they say in chat.
Oh my god. Wig. I feel that.
Let's see.
Now you're talking.
I can get on board with that.
That one I can get on board with as well.
Pixel Pacas reminds us this isn't the first time that Katy Perry's teamed up with video games.
Katy Perry was also in The Sims 3.
Remember when she sang all those songs in Simlish?
I remember that.
No.
I don't.
Cause you don't want to.
Cause I don't care.
Alright.
Let's move on and check out what's in stores this week.
Loki.
What's in stores is a bunch of cookie in my mouth.
Sorry bad timing.
We're gonna do it anyways.
Do you need help?
No I'm good.
Alright.
So is the cookie.
Yes.
So we have London Detective Mysteria on the Vita.
What's that?
A Vita?
Warhammer Vermintide 2 on Playstation 4.
Dragon Quest Builders 2 on Nintendo Switch and Playstation 4.
And would you believe it?
That's it for this year.
That's all folks.
No more games.
Well I mean you know it is the big busy time of year so it makes sense.
Well over in Japan there's still a few releases cause the holidays are a little different.
So the cycle of gaming releases changes a little bit.
But on the Playstation 4 Dragon Quest Builders 2 is out this week.
So I think I like the first Builders game so that might be interesting the sequel.
And I know the Switch is supposed to be getting that as well.
That's out on the Playstation 4 this week December 20th.
Kunio-kun a world classic collection is out this week.
Brave Neptunia.
Sakai Uchiyokatsumoko Seiyuu comes out in a regular and limited edition this week.
Onimusha Warlords on the Playstation 4 this week in a regular and a limited box.
Battle Princess Madeline is coming out this week as well.
And Ys VIII Lacrimosa of Dana in a Christmas gift package.
So I'm assuming that's another price reduction and just a repackaging of the game.
Do they have cookies in that package?
I don't think so.
I haven't heard about a Christmas cake being included with that or anything like that.
On the Switch this week I want to see that Dragon Quest Builders 2 is out on the Switch as well.
Also Kunio-kun which I mentioned is there as well as Onimusha Worlds.
Katamari Damacy Encore as they're calling it in Japan that is out this week.
So we actually got that one a little bit earlier than they did in Japan so that's kind of cool.
So that's what you have to look forward to in Japan this week.
Also a lot of price reductions kind of around the board.
Just things moving into the best collection and so forth in Japan.
Loki are you able to do the UK dates while we get the mailbag ready to go?
Yes sadly not much going on in the UK as well.
We've only got one game coming out over there.
Bridge Constructor Portal.
They're finally getting that on PC, Mac, Playstation 4 and Xbox One.
Oh and of course Android and iOS.
Alright.
So it's coming out over there now.
Alright well it'll pick up again in the new year though.
Because we have some like Kingdom Hearts is a huge release here.
Next year is going to be pretty busy so lots of stuff coming out.
Hold on brace yourselves.
Alright well let's move on we're going to get to the mailbag.
So if you want to email our show you can.
Participate at orangelaundrydo.com is the place to send your emails.
Earlier in the show I started an email from YYR because I wanted to get his perspective on the whole stores thing.
Yes.
I didn't finish it.
Oh my god.
I should probably do that shouldn't I?
So anyway YYR saying anyway I'll finish this email giving you my opinion on the possible cutting of the mailbag segment.
OLR is advertised on the show where every gamer has a voice.
Well some people use Twitter.
Some people use Facebook.
Some people use Instagram.
Some people use Discord.
Some people use Twitch.
No one uses Google Plus.
Some people well they can't after a certain.
I think after April you can't even if you wanted to.
Some of my Ingress pals still use Google Plus because Ingress was a Google thing.
So there's a community there but you're right.
Ain't nobody using Google Plus in a few more months.
Anyway some people use Skype and depending on where in the world you are the popularities of all these can vary widely.
But every gamer has email.
Every gamer.
And I'll leave it at that.
So like I said if you guys keep using it we'll keep it.
But they can only take so much of RuPaul's Drag Race talk when we have no emails.
I'm hoping again introducing this show to a new audience on Twitch and all that stuff.
I'm hoping that'll help grow things but we'll see.
Rock on OLR and best of luck on Twitch.
I hope we get a million listeners by next week.
Well I heard we were up to 74 followers on the network so that's pretty cool.
I'm going to have a lot of names to read at the end of the show.
So alright awesome.
Thank you very much otherwise for that email YYR.
Let's go to some other emails that we got.
Including let's see I think this one.
It's from Rhetortainment.
I'm looking at our chat too over at Twitch TV at VOG Network.
Yeah PixelPakas is talking about they closed Google Plus early because there was another data issue.
They bumped it up to April and I think he's found a story that says that.
Yeah it was supposed to be like over the summer and they bumped it up to April because yes there was yet another data issue.
But then they closed Facebook because of all their data issues.
Not yet.
Anyway Rhetortainment emails us saying dear Mr. Smoosh and the other broccoli heads.
Recently a business has opened in my area that has been discussed on OLR before.
Round one.
Yes we have a round one in the Salt Lake area and it's just as glorious as I've heard you people gas on about.
I haven't heard that. I haven't heard gas be used as an expression of a good time in a very long time.
This makes me wonder the following.
Are there any other businesses that you people adore that you perceive to be local treasures.
Or at the very least don't have much of a presence outside of California.
Know this up front.
There are in and out burger locations outside of California.
We have many of them in Utah and they're OK.
A bit overhyped but not that bad.
That was from Broccoli Entertainment as he's renamed himself this week.
So thank you for the email.
What do you think places here locally or in California that people are missing out on not having other places.
I got a couple answers.
So I think this is in a lot of big cities.
But Fry's Electronics.
Yeah I've had to go there three times this week because of all this shit.
So there's that because they don't have Radio Shack anymore.
Most know most of the stuff I was buying.
I get a radio once you go to Fry's or you're like I don't need Radio Shack anymore because they have way more so.
I know that Fry's is on the other side of town. That's the only my only complaint about it.
It's true. Yeah. Yeah. For me it's like kind of a trip over there for you.
It's a little shorter to get to the one. But yeah for me it's like I got to go.
I got to get on the freeway. So yeah there's all that. So that's one.
But I would say locally here in Sacramento where our show is based if you didn't know that.
There's a food chain that's here kind of locally and I think they're starting to spread to like some of the Bay Area.
But like it's so good that my friends in the Bay Area come here to eat there. It's Jack's Urban Eats.
It's like salads is that you know they usually made a face.
You don't like them. All right. They're good. Not that great.
My pals from San Jose will like come up to eat at Jack's because it's like this big deal.
But you know I think you know what I think is is hyped the squeeze squeeze burger.
I think that's over. Yeah that's over hyped. People love it. It's with that.
They put a gigantic piece of cheese on it so that it's not a gigantic piece of cheese.
I'll have you know. So what they do use me. Well hello. We got to get it correct. OK. Sorry.
So what they do is they put it's a cheese skirt. So they basically create a burger.
They put the burger down. It's on the grill and everything.
And then they take shredded cheddar cheese and they just literally dump way too much fucking cheese on it.
And then they put a lid on it and squeeze some water under so that steam melts the cheese and you get this giant fucking thing of cheese that's on there.
And then you eat your burger and the burgers is kind of it's all right. But the cheese is really good except the cheese is super greasy because cheddar cheese.
I ate there a couple of times when I was working in Sacramento for my company's innovation shop and I got over it after about two times.
I was just like yeah I'm not eating here ever again. It was all right.
Why why are says I don't understand how you can walk into an in and out and get super yummy feeling burger for under five bucks when nowhere else can do the same thing.
I like in and out but like people go crazy about it. I'm like I like them but they're always they're always so crowded.
You know what I mean. Like it's just like it's like this event thing and I'm like it's OK. It's it's good. It is a good burger and fries for a good price.
I don't like Burger King burgers are fine. Like I don't know I just I would go there like in and out is OK but it's not like here's the thing I need to go there.
My like friends from like Chicago and the East Coast because I guess they don't really have this out there but they think some of them think that the bigger deal out here is Jack in the box and they're everywhere.
So it's like it's like giant balls like McDonald's out here. They're everywhere right. But like because of like let's be real that company really caters to stoners.
So they have like they have all these munchy things on the menu right. Right. Like look they have a late night snack box that's like two jalapeno poppers some mozzarella sticks a small fries like you know what audience that's catered towards because they only sell it.
Well they did that in the commercials. It's like you know. Yeah. Like what was it tacos or whatever. Ninety nine cent tacos or something like that. Like how many should we get. Ninety nine. Yeah.
So yeah. So I think I like Jack in the Box just because I think I like the sourdough sandwiches they do there is not really a thing you see everywhere else. And yeah I just like OK.
Can't eat there anymore but you know you know what else. Somebody in chat earlier had said let's see because I want to get proper proper credit. W 0 4 says Pinkberry there.
They were everywhere now but I don't go there as much as I used to know. I like now is cheese is the one. Yes. I was just supposed to go there. Yeah. Yes. Men cheese with their dole whip yogurt land which had the Nintendo promotion it closed here.
So we can't go there anymore. Remember when they had the Nintendo promotion all the flavors were Nintendo and the spoons were Nintendo. Oh my kids love it but no. Yeah no it was a couple of years ago. So it was that.
So let's see a couple more comments in our chat. Bobby Blackwell says we actually had a local place called Stoner Burger here. They tie dye everything on the wall. The town basically ran them out of town because the imagery. Great food though.
I like round table. That's local. Oh yeah. Best pizza. But I'm biased because I work there. No it's it is. It's more expensive though. Like you can't get two pizzas for 10 bucks or whatever. It's a little pricier but it really is like half off delivery days or something.
I never go there. All those companies better be paying us for those free shout outs. But that was an email. Let's move on to which you know it pisses me off is my local round table they used to have.
See they have these like I guess royalty programs. So there's this one that's I remember it's called now but a lot of different places share it's done with your phone like a phone app or something like that.
So then I had all these points you know built up on it. They got rid of it and then they brought it back. I'm like you fucking assholes. I had like free twists on there so they can't go to that place anymore because they fuck up my order every time.
But that's just the employees that necessarily I'm not going to hold that against round table themselves because their pizza is fucking good but it's just the employees not always the sharpest.
You are a former employees. Yeah but fuck up orders like that. Do they have mountain mics everywhere because that's kind of like like that one day we're sick around table we'll have mountain mics.
Yeah mountain mics is pretty good too. I don't know if that's all over the place. I don't know. I don't know what's local what's not. I don't see mountain mics in Atlanta though so maybe they are like pizza.
That's good. But that's everywhere. That's on. But we don't have a lot of them here. No. And I'll tell you what the other thing we don't have. And then I swear to God we're moving on.
The other thing we don't really have in California which surprises people like here's the one that's going to really surprise you that like is a delicacy for me when I travel.
Dunkin Donuts. Now recently in SAC we got like two of them. Yeah there's one right by my house there. OK. Which couldn't be any further for me. Yeah. So like to me I still like it's it's I almost eat Dunkin more often when I travel the one I'm here.
I've had their doughnuts and I was just kind of like it's the coffee it's not about the doughnut. Oh OK. OK. Coffee because I didn't have the coffee but I had the doughnuts and I was like the doughnuts are OK.
I would rather that you were like something else because your doughnuts are kind of crap.
Yeah I know Raginator in chat says Dunkin Donuts are a dime a dozen here in Buffalo. Yeah. Most of the places I visit on the East Coast they're like everywhere. They're like Starbucks here.
You know every big doughnut place that's around here. Starbucks is also not Starbucks. Yeah Starbucks is fucking everywhere. What was the other one. Krispy Kreme I rather they would have been a Krispy Kreme one more and I swear to God we talk a lot about food for a gaming show but this one this is huge because if we're going to talk coffee I don't have a coffee drinker but here's the one you're missing out on in my opinion.
Dutch brothers the best those little there are those little stands and parking lots you have to drive. Oh yeah. They're starting to get more of them. Yeah. Yeah.
It is the best. Super sugary. Probably not good for you coffee but it is amazing. Like if you're a Starbucks fiend go try that when you're in California.
We're missing out on these fucking like I don't know what they call them but you know it's those like topless coffee places. It's like like the ones and I don't check bikini baristas.
Yeah. Bikini baristas we're going to see now on that shit. You put that in fucking laws against it here. Oh it's whatever.
It's whatever. I mean we need that because it's like fucking I I not I don't really care for it. You know the Dutch brothers shit that they have it's just it's just it's overrated and they fucking block. Try going into a parking lot that has the Dutch brothers it's fucking impossible to get around in there because it's just like lines.
I know the fucking as it's good and we went there. I've been there before. All right. But yeah no more free commercials. No more free commercials. You're all paying up with free stuff. All right. Moving on. Let's get to an email from pixel pockets who used to go by MXC in the chat but now on Twitch pixel progress.
Well it says hello. The new video format is fantastic. Sure it's changed but it's changed for the better. I wanted to send an email to say thank you folks for continuing to do all our year after year and for inspiring me in many ways.
Yours was the first podcast I ever listened to back in 2004 2005. Just remember just remember we were a lot younger than we looked a lot younger. I didn't have a beard. I was you know more of a skinny legend back then.
But it's a different time anyway and has remained in my weekly rotation years later way back when I first started listening in. I wanted to start my own podcast. It never happened until this year. My friend was looking to start a new podcast called the pixel X pixel that might be pixel cross pixel pixel cross pixel primarily about Japanese media games anime etc.
And we decided to do one together. It's only six episodes in so far but we're having fun. Good job working in your free promo but I support that. That's awesome. And keep having fun. Yeah because when it's not the most important it's no longer fun.
It's it's done for one of our anniversaries. I emailed to share being thankful for Rob as being an openly gay gamer which I did not have gay people in my life to look up to.
It's a bit funny to look back on this point with tons of LGBTQ folks in my life now but I'll always be thankful for or during a tough time of my life. Thank you. That means more than you can know it really does.
Or is my favorite part of Sunday evening. I'll keep listening and now watching as long as you folks keep going. Well we'll see how long it takes for them to kick us off twitch. But I think we're in a good spot.
Thank you so much pixel podcast is very sweet email. And people are being very nice tonight because Bobby Black was asking first tears on twitch. Not yet. Not yet. Getting close though Frodo swaggin sends us this email and I think this is another very nice one.
Hey well our Frodo swagins here. Just wanted to write in and say congrats on the move to twitch. I'm really excited to see your show get bigger. There are way too many people missing out on this wonderful show.
You mentioned possibly taking emails away in last week's episode. Just make sure to have another way for us to write in and say hi if you do. That's one of the great things about this show is being able to write in and participate.
I've I've taken my claws back a little bit from where I was last week. You guys keep using it. We'll keep reading them. Also I've heard a lot of episodes on here where people talk about what games help them get through hard times.
Rocket League is mine. That's for sure. But I realized that Orange Andrea was something I'm going to look back on and say that it played a big part of my life. I love knowing that once a week your show is always going to be there not forever obviously.
But you have been at this for years and it means a lot to me. It means a lot to many of us. I'm certain that's ironic that. Yeah I swear I didn't like order these emails or only reading the good ones I swear.
I really look forward to hearing the podcast every week. So thank all of you for all that you do to keep this show going. I've said it before but I'll say it again. I've heard lots of podcasts but OLR is my home. You three are awesome people heart.
Can't wait to see the first twitch stream. Thank you so much Frodo that these nice comments that is that is the fuel that keeps it burning for a long time. So thank you guys so much.
So there you go. No questions in those emails though just some very nice compliments a podcast plug that I'll have to check that out too. Yeah maybe I'll learn a thing or two about my pronunciation because I need to work on that for Japanese release dates.
Are you guys good at pronouncing things special pockets because I'm excited to learn. So any anyhow.
Justin is in our chat room that says can we stop acknowledging that OLR may someday end. It's making me think about my own mortality and I don't like it.
I had the honest honest to God. There was a point where I think we made a joke in an early episode. There's a song in the game pop and music which I know some of you know which I think I know across from the car freeze.
But there's a song called 7 7 7. And it was said in an earlier episode. Oh well if OLR only keeps going until like 2019 you'll get to play 7 7 7 on episode 7 7 7.
And I was like give me a break. We're not going to be here in 2019. But now I'm look I'm reevaluating only if you know I'm a part of your way. Some of my earlier words are coming back to haunt me a little bit.
And now you know maybe this whole twitch move and hopefully discovering some new people out there in twitch land. Maybe that's going to be the push we need to really move towards episode 1000 which again I always thought was like no fucking weekly show gets to a thousand.
Maybe if you do like three a week or something or multiples a week you might get to a thousand. No weekly show gets to a thousand. But I'm sitting here going you know we might get to a thousand Loki.
Or we ended at nine ninety nine and you never get that satisfaction of watching the odometer in nine ninety nine point one ninety nine point two. That's a good idea too. I like that.
All right. Anyhow there you go. That's it for the mailbag tonight. I think it's time for us to get into some more news. But remember you can always email us participate at orange lounge radio dot com.
I should I should put that on the see ideas for next week. I should put the email address up there that maybe more people will use it off to do that. The right email address and we'll put the right email address with the right date. Yes I will do that. Meanwhile how about new games.
All right. So there's this game called high tail which is being developed by a studio called high pixel and high pixel it will high pixel studio just to say high pixel is actually a team that runs this large Minecraft map.
One of the world's biggest Minecraft servers and they've teamed up with right games to build this game called high tail and high tail as you may imagine since you know a lot of this is based around Minecraft is a Minecraft like game.
So they had an announcement trailer looks very similar to Minecraft. Same kind of art style. It's going to be a voxel based game but there is also you know like kind of you know it's a little bit more geometrically pleasing.
Just all blocky. What's kind of unique about it though they did have an adventure mode that's going to have a full narrative with dungeons and boss fights and the single player campaign as well.
And of course they're also going to have the creative mode as well. And you'll be able to design your own levels and whatnot with some like really elaborate set of tools they were shown like you can even like stream videos and stuff into the game which is kind of cool.
So it's supposed to be set to release in 2019 on PC. So I guess we'll have to see what happens there. But it looks interesting. I'm interested in it because I dig Minecraft but I thought you know with Minecraft there's not a lot of structure as far as the story goes.
So like kind of doing the survival mode stuff can kind of get boring if you're playing by yourself. And even with like mods sometimes it's just kind of I don't know it's hard to stay interested in it I guess. But this is pretty cool. So I'm willing to check it out when it comes out.
Yeah. You know as far as this Hypixel goes you know I've kind of been itching for something kind of like new in the Minecraft universe for a little bit like I really want that super 4K texture pack to come out.
I know haha 4K graphics in Minecraft but I mean like the water effects and everything else look really really good with all that. So I would like that to kind of you know give the game a kick in the pants and it just kind of feels like I don't know Minecraft's been around several years now.
You know like it's ready to let's look at where's Minecraft 2 or what's next for Minecraft.
Well this almost seems like it could be like a Minecraft 2.
Exactly. That's what this kind of feels like is that all right if Microsoft isn't kind of jumping on it maybe we got another company. And I know Minecraft clones are a dime a dozen but you know you got some pretty big names behind this including huge Minecraft fans.
And you know obviously Riot Games which really I don't think they're known for anything really besides League of Legends. I mean they're not they may have other stuff they're not really known for anything outside of League of Legends. I'm sure they're itching to get outside of that box. So yeah this could be very interesting to see where it goes.
Yeah I'm curious to see as well so stay tuned. Keep an eye on it.
It's Flee says in chat have they said anything about the 4k lately. No they announced it like two weeks ago and they never really dated it like you kept thinking it was getting close but then it like never actually happened.
Yyr in chat says 4k is the shiz. Yeah I can't wait too much. I mean I don't even need the 4k graphics. I mean my computer monitor I guess will handle it but certainly not on my Xbox One which I still have a crappy TV for but whatever right.
So yeah I I'm trying to see real quick if they've mentioned anything better not in a while like if you look for the news and stuff like it's been quite some times they've really talked about when it's coming out like I see the last mention of it was kind of talking about a delay and that was like months ago.
Yeah my favorite comment though on this. What happened to the Minecraft SuperDuper graphics pack. It got super duper delayed.
It sure did. Yeah. So here's the comments official comment. They said Minecraft developer here. The graphics team is still hard to work on this. It ended up being a ton more work than initially anticipated.
The graphics part of our engine is quite honestly simply not built for this. And when we tried to put all the new features piece by piece things went bad performance even on the Xbox One X was between bad and inconsistent during all of the internal play sessions we had.
It will come but we don't have a release date yet. The gameplay team has been hard at work on update aquatic and the rest of the engine team has been working on the switch release just to give you an idea how fucking old this is.
Now the switchboard is out and going. I don't know. So they're still working on it. But makes me wonder though because like they have like high res texture packs since like you know Sonic ether is unbelievable shaders and shit like that.
It's on the Java version and it looks just like that. Why can't they do another console version. I don't know. Interesting. Seems like it'd be easier but maybe not.
Well some people are playing in four K. Some people are playing in VR VR is something that's growing of course as well. I know I'm still playing a little bit Tetris effect here and there.
Although I keep forgetting to check the weekend challenges. I just realized shoot yesterday came and went and I never went in and looked at the weekend challenge for Tetris effect. So bummer.
Well I keep forgetting to play the game altogether. You should get on that because it's seriously probably one of my favorite games that released this year. Totally.
So anyway but as far as VR goes there's an ongoing dispute that was going on between ZeniMax and Facebook. Facebook of course owns Oculus and ZeniMax and Facebook finally settled this whole thing.
Which is interesting that there's a settlement because I thought there was a judgment already of five hundred million dollars. There was a judge that found that ZeniMax claims held merit and awarded a five hundred million judgment.
It was halved on appeal. So I don't know if there's like an appeal to the appeal or what happens next. But yeah like for whatever reason they sat down in a room and they worked it out.
Of course we don't know. We don't know how much money they ended up getting out of the whole thing because of course terms of the settlement were not disclosed which is pretty customary.
So CEO and chairman of ZeniMax Robert Altman said we are pleased that a settlement has been reached and are fully satisfied by the outcome.
While we dislike litigation we will always vigorously defend against any infringement or misappropriation of our intellectual property by third parties.
And Facebook said we're pleased to put this behind us and continue building the future of VR. So I guess at least they don't have to worry about litigation holding things back.
But of course we'll never know the good stuff so to speak. So all right. Well let's move on and we will get to the Skype line soon and I'll tell you a little bit more about that when we get there.
We have a few more stories before we get there. So Loki what's up next.
So as I alluded to earlier when we're talking about you know what these different platforms offer as far as developmental tools Epic has announced that they are offering services to help cross platform gaming.
So what they did is they are allowing launching their suite of cross platform services which is going to be available for PC Mac iOS Android PlayStation Xbox and Switch.
And it's basically going to allow developers to use the same tools that they had for you know Fortnite that's going to be free for developers and will be open to all engines all platforms and all stores.
They can be mixed the match says developers see fit and it allow them to basically aid in the cross platform play.
So services including like cross platform log in IDing friends voice chat parties matchmaking data storage achievements etc.
And that's pretty awesome that they offer that and they are not you know it's not something that's necessarily going to be locked down to their store.
It's just like hey use this you know maker games better. So cool. I'm glad that's out there a little bit goodwill that they're putting out there.
Yeah. And this was kind of the thing I was alluding to at the top of the show we talked about what could their marketplace kind of give on others.
Although I think we kind of arrived at well since unreal is still making money off of steam games. It's not something they're going to really lock away but it definitely pushes this narrative that we saw you know Sony kind of resisting for a little bit.
It's definitely kind of wondering so cross play is the future get on maybe the whole cross play thing though with you know being able to like log in and something that maybe you need an unreal account or an epic account to do that.
Wouldn't that be interesting. But I mean that's free. So it's not horrible but it's you know signing up for that newsletter so we can tell you about those sales.
You can uncheck that. I guess it's interesting why we are in chat says sounds like it sounds like at least a sprinkling of the steam features that I mentioned earlier.
But see the thing though is that is something that you can also still use on steam because they're not locking it down to their stores. They're basically saying it's going to be available for you know all engines so you can use in unity any platform any storefront.
So it's going to be kind of its own separate API type stuff. Neat. All right. Well let's move on and talk about Carmen San Diego coming to Netflix. Now you know if twitch muting wasn't a thing I would play that Rockefeller song right now but maybe Loki can give us a rendition.
No. No I do. I tried everybody. I tried. All right. Anyway but I don't know who's looking forward to this. It looks like could be interesting. The Carmen San Diego series on Netflix is coming out January 19th 2019.
So now there's some new images that are out there. Entertainment Weekly has a whole preview of the 20 episode series. So it's like an animated kids thing like half hour little bits and pieces.
It will be divided into two parts. Carmen's enigmatic past that led to the criminal career and the present day heists that take place around the world. Gina Rodriguez will be voicing Carmen San Diego and also will star in a live action film in 2019.
So that's kind of that's pretty cool. I like to get the Carmen San Diego Cinematic Universe. Can we get like you know maybe all the other PBS edutainment like Cinematic Universe. You know we'll get like Mr. Rogers and Sesame Street reading Rainbow Square one television math net.
It's all together. Yeah just one giant like a fighter game. Absolutely. Yeah absolutely. So yeah they released some screenshots and so forth. It kind of looks like this particular Web site is talking about it looks like an old flash animation which makes me think of like strong bad and things like that.
I don't know. I think it looks a little better than that. But yeah it could be it could be interesting to see those old games wrong Brad needs his own Netflix show. Yeah.
See it to bury in chat says it's a shame that Rita Moreno isn't going to continue being The Voice. She's still on another Netflix show. She's in that once upon a time reboot which I think has another season still coming and it's it's great.
I mean it has nothing to do with games but it's great. And if you're like oh but it's the 70s show reboot it's it's it's completely different. Like yes same character ideas they totally made it different.
So that's where you can see Rita Moreno if you if you want to at least there's that. So Bobby Black Wolf and Chad says Carmen San Diego math net square one. They're all here.
Hey there's some really crazy ass rumors about DLC characters upcoming that they might all be from other series and stuff. So who knows. Who knows math. Yeah.
Oh sorry. See debris correct me it's one day at a time. Not once upon a time. I guess I'm thinking of the and the ABC series with all the Disney characters one day at a time.
Dar Tetsuya over in the twitch chat suggesting Oregon Trail the movie. I'm kind of surprised. I mean I'm sure they've done like westerns and more historically tilted pieces but I'm surprised they haven't done like the game the movie.
You know what I mean. The Oregon Trail. Just make it a game show. How would that work. I don't know. The Oregon Trail game show. Yeah but you have to do like physical challenges to like not die.
And then you make do we for the river do it. Well I'm seeing debris points out Carmen San Diego and Oregon Trail both have card games now so you can you can make those life altering decisions in the card game.
So there's that is that not not good enough for you. We should just mix the two decks together then we have where in the Oregon Trail is Carmen San Diego. Yeah I like that. That is good.
We'll leave it at that with the catch up to her but we're going to die of dysentery. We don't let you move on and do a couple more stories and we're going to try to open up the Skype line. I say try because this part we haven't been able to test so well.
So I'm a little worried it might not work. So we're going to try our best. If we aren't able to get Skype calls though I think we have some unused stories we get into a few more things we probably just talk about to buy us a little more time here tonight.
But for now Loki with a few more stories for us. So apparently Charles Martin a voice of many things including one iconic character Super Mario.
He has made a world record for the most times voicing a single character. So and when we reached for comment Charles Martin a said woohoo.
So basically he's voiced Mario 100 times in 100 different performances. So a hundred times. Are there that many Mario games or like things that feature Mario. I guess maybe. Yeah. Did he do commercials for the cereal and that stuff. Maybe I guess it seems like a lot.
Kids won't eat that cereal. It's still sitting there. I'll eat it. Bring it over. Is it expired. I don't think I would eat it if it's stale. It's they eat some of the marshmallows and like these aren't as good as Lucky Charms. We're not eating this crap anymore.
I'm like but you had me buy that for you. What the hell. We want more fruit loops. Why we are in chat suggests I was going to say how is it only a hundred times. I don't know.
Well unfortunately there Mario shown up in more than 100 games but he's only been voice acted since what the end 64 era. Yeah. Yeah. And that was kind of barely at that. So although Mario never really talks in full sentences. It's always like you know.
Well yeah. Well it's just what that's what it is. Don't give me that look.
All right.
Fine. Lastly he did. He did voices for Skyrim 2 which I'm on a meant Charles Martin who didn't do a voice for Skyrim.
I didn't hear Mario and Scott. Well maybe I haven't played the switch version so maybe he was in Skyrim.
He's been in other games though. He was in a bit trip runner 3 Mario. I'm sorry. No Mario. Sorry runner 2. Yeah. And he's like even in the intro he's like this is Charles Martin and you're playing runner 2 or something like that.
So he's he's shown up in other stuff. He doesn't just do Mario. OK. Yeah. All right. But I'm. Hey I think. Was he like an official representative of Nintendo or something. I thought he was. He should be by now. I think he was the early day.
That's how he was found. Anyway let's move on and talk about lastly tonight our last official story tonight anyway that you'll see over on the lovely sidebar over there.
The ZX Spectrum or ZX Spectrum if you're on this side of the pond. Many people notice that ZX Spectrum is getting a new game 30 years after it's been finished. That's right.
It's a new game called Quadron a new developer a developer Andy Beal who goes by Cosmium online finished the game Quadron back in 1998.
But the publisher that he was working with Palace Software kind of just left it behind. So there was no label and no future. So he ended up doing other stuff like he did theme park on the Sega Mega Drive the conversion there Sega Saturn racer called high octane.
But I'm assuming some type of copyright or hold must have expired now that it's been 30 years. So this game Quadron which is kind of like robot on 2084 is now being released UK publication retro gamer reached out Andy Beal dug out the title and did a little tweaking little engineering.
And now you can check it out. You can buy it if you want on itch.io for five bucks which apparently I didn't realize this itch.io has like a pretty big library of ZX Spectrum games.
So that's kind of neat. So yeah classic computing you know I'm going to end the first twitch show officially anyway with a with a ZX Spectrum or a retro story that's for sure.
So anyway I'm going to chat over at live.lognetwork.com which is now linked to our twitch chat. See it Tabiri says Mega Man ZX Spectrum Quadrant.
Why not. Why not do it that way. Let's do it. All right. I think it's time that we open up the Skype line. We're going to try this and it may or may not actually work.
It may be a little bit flaw filled but we're going to try it and we're going to take your calls on our Skype line so you can go ahead.
And those of you that are actually watching on twitch. Yes I am kind of rigging this up as we go. And that's how it's going to have to work this week.
So they're coming up on the desktop not on my iPad. I don't know iPad or I want them on my iPad not the desktop. So let me quit on the desktop and see if that makes them roll over to the iPad.
That's what I need. So yeah we're figuring this out live. So while I attempt to take a phone call Loki maybe you have a last minute story or a few that you want to get into.
Yeah we could talk about there was an Infinity Blade that was added to Fortnite because you know Epic made a game called Infinity Blade and apparently the Infinity Blade was too overpowered and ended up coming up in some tournaments and stuff like that and screwed with the balance of the game.
So they have vaulted the Infinity Blade because it was too epic for the game and they're going to reevaluate and re balance it.
I actually saw some gameplay of people playing with it and basically allowed you to destroy any sort of structure with like one hit. It was kind of ridiculous but basically the way it ended up is anybody that was able to get the Infinity Blade pretty much ended up winning the game.
So that definitely needed to go. So that's the thing. I mentioned Spider-Man into the Spider-Verse so because that of course just came out in theaters.
But Sony wants you to preorder that digital copy when that's going to be coming out on the PlayStation storefront as well. So you can preorder that and if you do preorder that you also get a nice into the Spider-Verse skin the Miles Morales Spider-Man skin for your character in the Spider-Man game.
So definitely check that out. Which by the way I'd like to mention if you haven't seen the movie yet there is a post credits scene that apparently is really awesome.
I did not stay for it because my kids would not want to stay that long past the credits but apparently is really awesome and involves Spider-Man 2099.
But I wanted to see that but I didn't get to. I'll just have to wait for the digital version of the movie to come out before I actually get to see that unfortunately.
Questbuster over in the Twitch chat agrees the post credits scene was really good.
Oh man. I guess I'll just have to see the movie again. Which I do want to see it again. Just it's going to be a while. Can't see the kids again.
Still want popcorn in me.
Alright the Skype is still open. I see missed calls but I don't see current calls coming in. Like they're not ringing through.
But you can see that people have tried to call but unfortunately it's not ringing through over to ye olde iPads.
Apparently Skype sucks.
I don't know if it's just the fact that my iPad is old which is certainly possible but for whatever reason it's not coming through with the calls.
So that may be unfortunate. What can we do?
Going to chat. Tigerclaw says you gotta teach your kids to stay during the credits because they will miss out on the goodies.
I know but the problem was that they had to use the bathroom and so I'm glad that they at least survived through the movie.
But you can't tell a four year old that sorry you can't go pee right now.
We gotta wait to watch this funny bit of movie.
And Bobby says kids wouldn't understand the goodies actually.
Let's do that. I'll just go see it by myself then. Again.
Any other last minute stories for us tonight?
Sadly Skype does not appear to be ringing through. This may be a bust tonight. It's one of those things I'm going to have to work on this week.
It's alright. It can't be 100%.
Oh I wonder if I can use my phone. I'm going to try using my phone.
There you go. The powers of your phone.
There's apparently been a discovered game that's available through MAME now.
Sega Sonic Brothers. It's a puzzle game that kind of looks like columns or maybe even Puzzle Fighter a little bit.
But it's like this. Yeah I can't really tell how it looks like.
Oh it looks like a little bit like maybe Puyo Puyo.
But apparently it's some unreleased game that you can go check out if you want to play the other game.
I don't know where exactly they have this but I'm sure it's out there on the internet somewhere you can find it.
They're doing a board game for Metal Gear Solid. That's pretty cool.
The Metal Gear Solid by Emerson Matsuchi.
And it's coming I guess from IDW Games.
They're going to be demoing it at E3 2019.
So hey you got something that's going to be at E3 since everybody else is skipping out on it.
So check that out. I'm not sure that's going to be in the Konami booth.
I would assume that's in some IDW Games booth but it looks neat.
I'm curious to see how you play it.
But I guess we'll just have to wait and see.
I'll say this probably in GameStop someday.
That's kind of a weird thing.
They have since they carry a lot of this geek stuff now.
There's a ton of fucking board games in that place.
So I think I actually got the Skype thing to work.
So if you don't mind I'm going to try to take a call.
Hi you're on Orange Launch Radio. Who's this?
Hey it's Brad from Pod Culture.
Hey it's working.
Hey I think it's working. I just have to make sure it's broadcasting to Twitch and they can hear him over there too.
But I think it should be. What's on your mind Brad?
Oh just figured I'd call in on your first Twitch livestream there.
Well and yeah and the folks are confirming they hear it and I see the bars going up and down.
Well I can think of no better person to be one of our first callers here than one of our long time podcasting peers.
I know you guys sunsetted Pod Culture a little bit ago but I'm sure you'll come up with something new soon.
Oh there's already something in the works and stuff recorded for.
That's how it works sometimes.
Well what's on your mind tonight? Anything in gaming that you want to talk about tonight?
Oh just figured I'd call and test the lines that you're having problems there.
Well I appreciate that.
Well we hear you. We hear you loud and clear. We're all good.
So thank you for being the first kitty pig here on Twitch.
Which I can kind of show there. Brad is there live with us.
He's captured in the phone.
He's a man in a box. That's right. It's just like the Superman movies.
It's like the Superman movies.
Oh my God. We totally need like a screen or something where we can have like the people just like right there on the desk.
It's so much better than having to actually in the actual stream.
I just want them like on the desk talking you know.
Yeah like on old game shows or something.
It's like Conan O'Brien and stuff with like the heads.
If I'd been more prepared I'd have the lights set up better so you could see the studio.
That's okay. You can you can barely see shit on my tiny little iPhone but there you go.
It's fantastic.
That's right. All right. There you go. All right. Brad take care. We're gonna try to get some other calls. Okay.
All right. I'm glad it's working.
All right. Take care buddy.
Peace.
All right. That was our pal Brad who used to be with the show Pod Culture and I think we have another call coming right in.
So what the hey we're going to get to this call too and see what is on this person's mind.
And of course they hung up right as I answered it. So I have to keep plugging on plate.
You know I have to keep doing this because of the ringtone.
I don't want the ringtone coming through while you're trying to talk about a story or something like that.
So I have to do this.
Well it will work for now. It'll work for now.
And I think the call is coming back in. We're going to try to take it this time.
God damn it. Stop hanging up after you get through.
All right.
I do like all the comments and chat about Brad being trapped in the box there.
Call Superman and all that stuff.
Tiger class says you can mute the ringtone. You can on desktop. Can you do it on mobile.
If you can. That's news to me.
I thought that was a thing they that like you can't mute.
We're learning about live right now.
All right. Well the call's coming in one more time. I'm going to try to take this.
So hopefully the person doesn't. They keep hanging up.
Maybe it's not connecting on the iPhone or something.
Well obviously it worked a second ago. It's true. It worked a second ago.
I don't know. All right. We'll see if anybody else gets through. I don't know.
But it's Orange Laundry all one word on Skype and we'll try to take one or two more calls.
And then we'll we'll close up shop.
Well there is a new rhythm game called Rhythm Land that's coming to the Famicom and Mega Drive in Japan in 2019.
And it's like Rhythm Heaven. It has four mini games.
Where you have to press a button in sync with music.
And they have 20 songs and other surprises.
I like that it's on the Mega Drive.
Yeah. It's old school.
It says apparently you can you can preorder that now on Amazon Japan for six thousand four hundred fifty eight yen.
And it's going to be out February 15th.
And they're also going to have a preorder up on Play Asia at some point.
I haven't been to in a while.
Probably going to regret going there.
Let's play Asia.
Oh yeah. Because they're like oh I want that and that and that.
Oh and then you start buying the whole house down that.
Yeah. It's a struggle.
But it looks cool.
Like even on the cards are pretty awesome since they're going to be printing those and everything.
They're running girl music baseball.
Melodian Shield Earth Crisis.
It's like well game.
Let me answer this quick question from Jirama and chat kind of a technical question about our setup here.
Jirama wants to know is Skype on the computer you're at and connected to the mixer.
So yes it's connected to the mixer.
But here's the crazy part.
So we can do the mixer into the computer here that is doing audio dedicated stuff.
That works fine.
That's how we were able to do the call with Bobby because we just did it on this computer here because we didn't need it to go out on Twitch for y'all.
The problem is the audio from this computer when we try to hook it back in the mixing board it's coming through on crap quality.
And I think it's because I either have some type of short.
I don't think so though unless the short is in that little adapter.
So I have to try getting a new one of those but I'm trying to get to try to get a RCA because I remember on the old mixing board you had like an RCA that went in.
And that's like how we used to do it back in the day.
So all right.
So I guess we're going to close up Skype for now.
We'll try we'll try harder to work on that next week and we won't imprison you in a box.
I promise no promises.
OK maybe no promises.
Maybe a small box.
Actually I would love to be able to take that on the iPad and then have you there.
So all right.
Anyway I guess I guess that's it.
Are we are we.
Let's see.
I guess that's yeah that's unfortunately there's not a whole lot other news this week.
Worth mentioning I want to say.
But I'm sure there'll be stuff next week that we get to check out.
I don't know.
Oh I was going to mention there is one thing I did read.
Apparently there do I think they opened up that beta for the Google streaming platform to play Assassin's Creed Odyssey.
And if you do that between now and sometime in January that you can actually get Assassin's Creed Odyssey for free.
They'll give you a copy of it.
So that's something you're interested in checking out.
I mean you should probably check it out anyways because it sounds like a neat idea.
But hey free game.
Assassin's Creed Odyssey.
That's not bad.
Yeah for you.
Check that out.
I've been wanting to check that out too.
I've heard a lot of good things about it.
So yeah.
And some folks are asking about the hardware.
So I haven't really gotten into it yet because it's not final.
But basically we're using we're using a Mac and a PC.
It's a little bit of a buy a computer world here.
So the Mac is dedicated to the video portion and everything you guys are seeing on Twitch.
That's all handled over there.
And it's going to be the more portable part.
It's actually a Mac Mini.
It's one of the new ones.
So it's going to be the very portable part of our show.
So when we're able to come to a convention near you which I hope will be a thing we can do.
Or cover more like local gigs.
That'll kind of be our piece that moves around with it.
Now for when we're doing shows in house.
We have kind of like a hybrid old computer with new stuff.
And Rama has been very helpful in that whole process there.
So that is going to be the part that for now is capturing audio.
But I think that will move to the Mac long term.
Jamie and I have a plan on that.
And then for this old computer it's going to be kind of the one thing that drops in the incidentals.
So I can bring in more background music.
More things like that.
And I continue to send the signal out to the mixing board that way.
Plus I need a place to do my stories and to look at chat and all that stuff.
So I've always kind of needed my own thing as well.
Just like how Loki has his laptop.
Because my laptop is probably older than this thing so it wouldn't work for something like that.
So there you go.
I guess I can talk about one more story here.
Yeah.
This was the whole.
I have a chat comment and then we'll close up.
So there's this new Minecraft thing that's going on right now.
This Paws and Claws pack.
So they're doing like a charitable thing.
So they can't do 4K but they can do the charity.
Yeah they can do the charity.
So it's going towards the World Wildlife Fund.
And basically it's going to...
Any proceeds on the pack sold between now and December 11, 2021.
So it's going to be going for quite a while.
They're going to donate money towards that.
Or all the proceeds are going to be donated to that.
And on top of that as an added incentive.
Microsoft's going to donate $100,000 once 10 million bamboo blocks have been placed in the game.
So you get those blocks and you place them.
And then once it ticks up to 10 million they're going to donate another $100,000.
But I guess we have a long time for that.
Yeah.
So alright.
One other chat comment.
Tigerclaw wants to know our reaction to the Sonic the Hedgehog movie poster.
Which I forgot that was like all around the Twitters and all that this week was the reaction to the Sonic poster.
It's in the theaters too.
Yeah there's the one in the dark that somebody lightened up and it was kind of like.
It was probably like when you saw us on Twitch for the first time and what we really looked like.
It was like you know it was kind of a very gross reaction.
No I'm kidding.
But Sonic the Hedgehog lightened up and that poster was kind of scary looking.
And then there's that other weird poster with like his legs up in the air.
That's the one that's in theaters.
Oh is it?
Yeah it's interesting.
They had it in the main lobby in the theater they went to this weekend.
And I mean I don't know.
It's supposed to be a kids movie right?
Yeah but.
It's for kids but adults will get it.
Like is that kind of where they're going with it?
I don't know.
I'd be curious to see what it looks like but.
I I'm interested to see how it goes.
I'll leave it.
That's probably the nicest way I could put it.
I'm interested to see.
I like Jim Carrey.
I'll go see it because Jim Carrey is in it.
I mean.
But.
Yeah.
But I'll tell you this much.
You know going back to Spider-Man again.
So Spider-Man's actually into the Spider-Verse was done by the same guys that did the Lego movie.
And.
Oh God was the other movie that they did was also really good.
I don't remember the other movie that they worked on as well but.
All the movies that they've done have been fantastic.
Too bad they aren't making the Sonic movie because then that would be pretty awesome but.
No.
I'm down for the Lego movie too.
It comes out in February 14th.
All right.
Well I think it's about time to get final thoughts and close up our very first Twitch episode.
Which was a little shorter.
Sometimes this show runs 3 hours.
Tonight it was probably what maybe like 2 hours 50 minutes.
Yeah well I mean it's you know.
All the winner breaks are going to start next week.
And we just had all the big game releases.
So it is starting to slow down a little bit.
But I feel like we still have some substantial stuff to talk about.
And obviously we're thrilled that those of you guys came out to join us on Twitch tonight.
And this is the new norm.
So this is going to be.
Well I mean things will get the Skype stuff working and there will be other upgrades here and there.
But the good news is it can only go uphill from here.
So that's going to be what we're working on.
So be prepared for some more streams throughout the week.
Just some random stuff.
If you're not already following us here at VOG Network.
Please consider doing that.
Because we're going to be doing more like streams throughout the week.
Because we want to try to hit that affiliate status.
So that you know we can get all the perks that come with that.
Partner might be a little harder.
But because you have to stream a lot for that.
But you know we'll see.
Who knows.
We get enough shows that want to be a part of this.
Who knows what is possible.
We'll see.
So but thank you guys again for showing up.
I hope you enjoyed it.
I hope everything you wanted and more to watch the show being done.
And for the podcast listeners I hope you guys really kind of felt that not a lot really changed.
You're still getting the same audio that you're used to.
Except you don't get to see my reaction and my playing up to the camera.
That's the one thing that you're missing.
So which I guess I'm already seeing clips come through with some of that.
So that'll be that'll be pretty cool to look at that later.
So all right.
It's time to get final thoughts.
Thank you guys as always for listening to the show.
If you enjoyed what you heard leave us a five star review on iTunes Google Play on Twitch.
You can't really review things on Twitch.
But tell your friends.
That's all we ever ask.
We're not begging for your money.
All we ask is that you tell a friend or two about the show.
Help us spread the word because we are the show where every gamer has a voice.
But we can only you know spread spread those get more voices here if they're being brought to us.
So we really appreciate all of that.
So I guess I'll let you start with an actual final thought tonight Loki.
So I'm going to hopefully be streaming some more this week.
I'm maybe doing fifth mix.
I'm hoping they'd be doing set mania very soon since I have the whole set up.
Most the hardware portion of that I think is out of the way and hopefully I'm not going to have any hitches with that.
So I'm hoping to get that set up sooner than later.
Really just the theme right now is holding me up.
But then once I I picked out some songs I need to put steps to and stuff that I want to do.
The problem is like I saw there's this skin that they have for pump it up called rave it out.
That's really elaborate and I like it.
I can adapt that unfortunately to work for what I need to do but I'd like to do something similar to that just because they have it like where when you're selecting your song and actually plays like a video preview with the background video looks like and that's just really fucking cool.
I just don't know how feasible that's going to be.
And then also I need to make sure it's running smoothly because all of the ones I've seen like even the DDR ace the 2014 stuff that just it's it's not smooth enough for what I want.
I want it to be like buttery smooth and it should be on the hardware that I'm running.
So we'll see.
So yeah I'm hopefully going to do that and hopefully play some more games this week.
All right.
My final thought for tonight is I'm excited to exhale that we got through the first video show and it worked.
And I'm just very psyched about all that.
And I'm really I taught myself how to use stuff like light works and movie editing software that I never thought I'd use.
I taught myself how to use all that this week and that was it was awesome.
And again I guess here at the end did you make the fancy vogue thing or is that by.
No I think code man did that a while ago we actually lifted that.
But the whole.
See it's not on the podcast but the whole.
You can't do that on television inspired thing which yes I do play.
I sat down.
We were at a restaurant with Alan and Jamie and I were all at a restaurant with that whole idea like to do that came up because it's the thing that Dragon Con TV has done as well.
So we just started spitting out all these ideas.
Obviously I can't repeat them now because we're going to use them in the future.
But I'm like oh I got so many ideas but I use light works to make that as well and some of the other little things that you see here.
So I need to do stuff like that.
And we'll also like I need to go into like cinema 40 and stuff because I need to make.
I need to make videos stuff for my semi skin.
Yeah.
At least I'd like to do that.
Let's be honest I mean I don't want to overcomplicate things like I do with everything I do.
But the nice thing is I mean I can't do with a three hour show I can't do the level of B roll that like Bobby is doing on his show.
I think I mean we can do some but we can look into you know this nice little thing makes it really easy to just drop in video.
Like as long as I kind of have it on here ready to go like it's really easy to drop in video and keep talking over it and all that stuff.
Yeah.
So you know that's something we can look at doing in the future is not necessarily just going to be our ugly mugs on stream the entire time.
But do we get other stuff.
Yeah we can do that.
Oh you don't take it offline.
You know what else I did.
Yeah.
In light works the classic game of the week thing.
For the first time when you were watching on Twitch you got to see the game that she was talking about.
I did that online works.
So of course learning credit to also I think then Jason used to put stuff like that and he did.
You know this isn't necessarily our first foray into video.
We were on Justin TV a long long time ago with the simulcast which talked about the top of the show VX Jason X to be or simply Jason if you will who is our continuing voiceover guy.
He's done more for the show than you guys could possibly imagine especially when it comes to being able to download the podcast in the first place.
But yeah Jason also for a short time was putting these shows on YouTube.
I mean it was just kind of like the picture with the audio but then like he'd go in and spice it up.
He'd be put in some of the classic of the week over it.
He when we did a list list he did a whole little thing where he actually showed it on there.
So he tried to make it a little more exciting.
But you know now that video is getting easier and easier and cheaper more importantly to self produce.
I think you know this is something that we can kind of keep doing on Twitch and you know have the audio here and all that.
So pretty cool.
Anyway I guess that's it.
I think we're done right here.
So we'll see you next time.
Thanks again for coming out tonight.
You know and we did our very first show ever on my 365.
We had 12 people show up and we had we had a few more tonight.
So that was great.
It wasn't hundreds and hundreds.
But it feels really good especially we see a lot of old faces from the past and some new faces too.
Hope you enjoyed the show.
Thanks for being here.
Thanks for checking out Orange Lounge Radio.
We will see you next week.
Have a wonderful night everybody.
Good night.
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
To join us for a live show, tune into VOG Network dot com Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific, 9 p.m. Eastern.
The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network.
But you know they were all still true.
See you next week.
Music.