[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, December 17th, 2006, Sony fesses up to a fake website, a popular role-playing series jumps to a new system, and are the Wiimotes really being Wiicalled?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are that podcast dedicated to video games, gamer culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts and I'm here with you for the next three hours as well as my partners in crime.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say hello to the one and only, happy, happy bunny, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're doing it differently, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm doing the opening differently?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're doing it differently, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Am I not allowed to change things once in a while?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nobody likes anything different.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember, people only like happy trance.
[SPEAKER_02]: We fear change.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a corncob up their ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say hello as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: You will be like us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here comes another podcast review.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Sakura is too angsty.
[SPEAKER_02]: She is so angsty on the show all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we love her.
[SPEAKER_02]: We love her.
[SPEAKER_02]: Angst and all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Far Cry Vengeance for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't know what they're talking about.
[SPEAKER_03]: But everybody's been giving this thing like a 4 out of 10, 3 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, and then Elebits just recently was reviewed in Electronic Gaming Monthly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was reading on Destructoid something about it, and they were pissed because some people over there gave it 4s.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, and... Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I know just from reading what the... You know, just different specifics about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No level editing in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, there was an arcade version of F-Zero, which came out on the GameCube not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was kind of like that, where you got in and it would tilt around.
[SPEAKER_02]: I loved that game, except for the fact there were only six tracks, so it got old really quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: My dad was playing that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played the Japanese one at Arcade Infinity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but it still kind of sucked, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought it was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, no, the game was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're simple-minded.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, the game was great, don't get me wrong, but it sucked because it was over before it started.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, there was that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and Dancing in the Rain lots of rain and I was watching Chris fall headfirst into the lagoon you know what, that was not my fucking fault we were on this little kiddie boat ride anyone who's been to Disneyland it's the storybook ride where you just pretty much sit in a boat and look at these little miniatures that are from the stories and it was raining and neither the people who were helping me into the boat were really paying attention so I slipped and almost went headfirst into the water
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Cookie Ma!
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots of Cookie Mama, because Mama will make it better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you been poking Mama's steak?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I have, and Mama liked it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: For those who don't catch the reference, there's obviously a part of the game where you have to poke the steak.
[SPEAKER_02]: Describe what Cookie Mama is all about for those who haven't heard of it, because we get new listeners every week.
[SPEAKER_07]: You use the stylus and you cook, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: You shake the pan.
[SPEAKER_07]: You blow on the pot to cool it off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of those levels make me think of DDR with food.
[SPEAKER_07]: Beatmania with food is like cooking mania.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, I don't know, it's a pretty fun little addicting game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because mama will make it better.
[SPEAKER_02]: To quote Chris.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just cooking mama?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just cooking mama and Creature from the Black Lagoon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pinball.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, is that a new one, or is that one you guys had?
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't keep track anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: We got it a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're still working, though, on the Rocky and Bullwinkle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wasn't there something about your Guns N' Roses table damn near went backstage to a Guns N' Roses concert?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and then all that fell through, and then they canceled the Sacramento show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate you, Axl Rose, you bastard.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate you for the Metallica thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, ho, ho, ho to you, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, by the way, happy holidays to all of our listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: Happy Christmas, Kwanzaa, or whatever it is you celebrate, because I think Hanukkah started.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we're in the middle of Hanukkah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yule is the 21st.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh, we got Yule on the 21st.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Kwanzaa is after Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think, what, it starts the 27th?
[SPEAKER_02]: God, I hope I'm right.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's too many holidays to remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Christmas is on the 25th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So whatever it is you celebrate, I hope you're having a good one.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we should probably give an advance happy birthday to another person who has been on the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Happy Birthday to Megzi Happy Birthday to Megzi
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Elebits.
[SPEAKER_03]: Elebits is fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm actually kind of far in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not too far, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm on level 9 now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried playing around with the level editor a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was kind of surprised.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still haven't seen any edit data from anybody else yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know a bunch of my friends have to have this game, and yet I see no level data.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't played enough
[SPEAKER_03]: Cars for the Wii that I bought for Nelly because she wanted another racing game and she insisted on Cars and a game sucks balls.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I knew when I bought it that it was going to be awful and I just had no idea how bad it sucked, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And the car, like, steers like a tank.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it can't, like, turn for shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's a bunch of, like, useless-ass moves that you can do in the game, and it's just, it's really bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's meant for little kids, that's really what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, um, you know, Nellie wanted an easy game to play, so there's cars, and I guess she'll have to play that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, she's been ignoring cars and playing more Excite Truck instead.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's trying to get all the S rankings in mirror mode like Christopher has.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, my roommate is obsessed with Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_02]: I doubt there's anybody in the world that has played this game as much as Extover.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's beaten Excite, Super Excite, Mirror Mode, and now he got all the trophies or something, so he got some super car thing that flashes when he drives and he can just go right through trees and right through other cars.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not
[SPEAKER_03]: Chris, can you describe this look on your face to the listeners?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Death Stare, Grand Theft Auto, WarioWare
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But seriously, if you've seen that YouTube clip of the dancing stage in WarioWare, you know that this game is all you need for January.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, but that's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Just other things that you want to play and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even for the 360, there's really nothing I want to pick up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, January's always a dead month, really, for games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I did play Assault Heroes, and that was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although people are comparing it to Quarry Warriors or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not exactly like that, but I guess you could... It's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, it kind of reminds me of if they did an update to Breakthrough.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excite Truck got old quite quickly
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, for me, it kind of did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I was like, okay, I'm kind of done with Exciter.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I pop it in once in a while for fun, but I think it's more extroverts, Excitements wears off on me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know, maybe it's something about the casual gamer, because you notice the people that are really into this that we know are two people who don't usually play a lot of games.
[SPEAKER_03]: But she's not playing it casually anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's playing it for hours.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, but there's, you know, the casual gamer that plays Bejeweled for hours.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what it is about that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's the gross simplicity of the controls and everything, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game really could have benefited from more tracks and maybe more diverse cars or something else, like different types of cars.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I really think, because it comes down to you play basically like five different continents and
[SPEAKER_03]: Each track kind of has portions of other tracks in it, so you'll drive on the same stretch of track.
[SPEAKER_02]: Airtost in our chatroom says, I didn't like Excite Truck until I put my own MP3s in.
[SPEAKER_02]: It makes it so much better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I only need to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't really done that with a sight track because I don't have my own SD card, but I know Xfer does, and he does that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's what I do with Burnout, which is the racing game I've been playing a lot lately.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like all the emo EA tracks that are in it, so I put my own music, and I'm like, Sinpop in 80s, and Madonna, yeah!
[SPEAKER_02]: So, as I'm, you can just imagine what my Burnout games look like.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I'm flying through the air, and you know, I'm hung up, I'm hung up on you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crash!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what it's like to play Burnout with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've also been playing Elebits a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I think the comparisons to Katamari Damacy are fair.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it has a lot of that same cuteness factor.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the only kind of weak point is the music does not have the same infectiousness as Katamari Damacy does.
[SPEAKER_02]: And to be honest, I think that's really what sets the two games apart.
[SPEAKER_02]: But so far, so good gameplay-wise, which is, you know, what's really important about a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm liking the whole discovering aspect and the levels take a long time to beat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was going to be like quicky little three-minute levels.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of these levels take like 15 minutes to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as the game is, where I have played enough of it, I think, to give a fair review, I did check out Final Fantasy III on the DS, which Loki was kind enough to give me a copy of.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: The one aspect of this game I have not been able to review is the Wi-Fi, because no one's given me their stinking code.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm going to have to go on the OL Army forums over at OrangeLaunchRadio.com and see if anyone has the Final Fantasy III on the DS, because I'm really curious.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you can send letters through the Moogles and towns, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it kind of seems like the Wi-Fi thing is like,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy V Final Fantasy VII Final Fantasy V
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chris, how about you?
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki's computer just made a weird noise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I don't even know what that was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did your computer fart?
[SPEAKER_02]: What did it do?
[SPEAKER_02]: It went, ah!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, strange.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: My gaming week, aside from making Mama really mad, I actually, and I played Sims 2, obviously.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all I play.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you do any of the fanfic stuff in Sims 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Jamie was just showing us a picture of the Doctor and Rose in bed together in Sims 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you do that kind of stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you know, I used to play just the Sims.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I used to put anything I found on the internet, I'd put it in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't do that with this game because it really messes it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they have it so that if you want to customize it, you can.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it still messes it up to no end.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I just don't do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I just make random characters that do stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like getting the... Like, they have little things that your characters can work up to, so I've been trying to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I actually played a PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_02]: What'd you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What'd you play on it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was in a kiosk, and it was at Target, and it was free!
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: It is the devil!
[SPEAKER_06]: You know.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, and then I finally, you know, actually get to play it, and, you know, it was like, oh, this is not bad, because I like the graphics, but other than that, then it froze on me, and I was pissed off.
[SPEAKER_06]: I also got a little farther in Rule of Rose.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game is weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now when Kingdom Hearts 3 comes out for the PlayStation 3, though, you'll be all over PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ring it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how I'll be when Final Fantasy XIII comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'll finally be the one that wins me over.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, you know, and I don't think it made tonight's show roll, so I'm okay in saying this.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if I took somebody's story, I apologize.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I believe there was a late-breaking story.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if it's a rumor status or what's going on, but that Metal Gear Solid 4, which was one of the PS3's big, big exclusives, some insider information coming from like a friend who knows a guy at Konami or something, you know, take it with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Megzi told me that.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's like, I am so happy that they're going to bring it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because for Christmas, she's getting a bunch of money, so she's going to end up going to get an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she was like, if they're going to start putting stuff on the Xbox, I don't need to get a PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am so happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to join our chat room and participate in the conversations with us, it's chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Head on over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got a nice full chat room tonight, so thanks, you guys, for sticking with us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some quick housekeeping before we get into tonight's news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Earlier in our last week's show, I should say, I promised that there would be some big changes coming to our website.
[SPEAKER_02]: Realistically, that's probably not going to happen now until January.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're trying to plan a big overhaul for the website, so stay tuned for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, we should say, this is our last live show of 2006, if you can believe it, because next Sunday is Christmas Eve, and the Sunday after that is New Year's Eve, and of course we have respective family and friend plans for those days, and we imagine most of you guys do too, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have no lies outside of you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to think that, but no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: We know that you guys probably have your own things going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we will be delivering new content to the podcast feeds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Certainly look for a year-end roundup type show, our top games of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those types of things will be prerecorded and coming to our audio archive, which is available on our website.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just click on podcast over at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: One other quick thing I wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted to give a quick plug for iTunes.
[SPEAKER_02]: and leaving us reviews there like happy things because the more reviews we get in iTunes the more people notice the show and you know we're all about hey we do this show for free and we try not to ask for too much um you know we in the beginning I think when we first started podcasting we got all up on this oh you gotta vote for us on podcast alley and oh give us a good thing on yahoo podcast and now we kind of you know we're just kind of like okay whatever we just want
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, enough begging and pleading.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get into some gaming news, the core of what we're about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Begging and pleading is awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially when I get stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you want to beg for something?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you above begging?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm above everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what she said last night.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: You liked it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not what she said last night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but you didn't argue.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well this...
[SPEAKER_02]: This sounds like something we ought to send over to Howard Stern instead.
[SPEAKER_02]: GameDistributor.com
[SPEAKER_03]: and we do keep in constant update with a lot of them especially through the holidays because we're cutting POs like every day and stuff so
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm going to be the devil's advocate here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just going from your track record in 2006, it's a little bit hit and miss.
[SPEAKER_02]: We found that your ties really tell us the new games that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: You knew about PlayStation 3 Oblivion long before anyone else did and mentioned it on this program.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, one of the big things that had us out there in 2006 was the Konami before E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: You knew there were going to be two DDRs for Xbox, Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: You knew there was a Castlevania game coming on DS, da-da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_02]: Release dates?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's harder because the companies move them around.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's really companies that move that shit around because I wish it were, you know, announce a release date and actually the game comes out, you know, that day.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's usually not the case because they're shifting their priorities around, you know, working on certain games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Certain games are, you know, behind in development or ahead in development or, you know, certain games are done and they're just waiting for, you know, certifications.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: Halo 3 coming out March 15th It has been delayed
[SPEAKER_03]: A little bit, probably because they're not done with it yet, but the new date now from Microsoft is May 15th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: That could change once we get closer to May.
[SPEAKER_03]: But as of right now, it is May 15th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, that date makes a little bit of sense in some ways and not in others.
[SPEAKER_02]: To me, it makes sense because of the beta test that we all know is going to happen in March.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the appropriate time frame, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: So we knew that March date was going out the window when they announced the beta test.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the March date, too, it would make sense, too, that they'd move it because they've got other games coming out in March.
[SPEAKER_03]: And to stack three Microsoft games in one month,
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Trying to have a lot of... Because maybe they think Sony and Nintendo are not going to have a lot of big titles in 2008?
[SPEAKER_02]: And usually... I should say the 07-08 fiscal year?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, usually April-May is pretty slow.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I think what last year... Or I should say this year, during May, the big game release... Well, they had X-Men 3, Hitman Blood Money, and Jaws Unleashed.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I mean, that's not really that big.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, when you think about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, so, it makes sense that they would, you know, kind of push it back, because there's a lot of games coming out, and they also, you know, they're pushing to sell more hardware units, um, right now, and I think a lot of people are buying 360s, because, again, can't get a hold of a PlayStation 3, and kind of listening to what they're doing with the PlayStation 3, and how they're still having trouble getting units out there, despite the fact that they're still seeing 2 million by the end of the year, right, um,
[SPEAKER_03]: It's probably, they're thinking that's going to be when they're starting to catch up a little bit, and then they just need something else to kind of pull the attention away from Sony type thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, that could change.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, also Forza 2 was scheduled for May now, so there's a lot of stuff that's being, you know, delayed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other game that got delayed, though, into February is Wii Play.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that I'm kind of surprised about, because the game's
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever the case may be, Wii Play is delayed to February 20th.
[SPEAKER_03]: It used to be actually one month prior, I think on January 19th is when we had it before.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is great, because I was, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, thank you very much for the, I guess, exclusive news, and we'll see how it plays out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I look for date changes every single day, three times, four times a day, and Halo, as soon as I saw that change, I had to talk about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that also kind of makes me go, okay, well, what's to say it's not going to move again?
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if it's not going to move again, and really, it could just... I've seen games that were scheduled to come out last year, and now they're scheduled to come out in 2007, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: It all depends on how quickly, you know, they're getting the game done.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would trust your date more than the, you know, placeholders that people use on EB Games and GameStop.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they go, oh, the game's coming out 11-1.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, they're saying, oh, it's going to come out for Christmas because they want to sell it during Christmas.
[SPEAKER_03]: That may be, they may want to try to sell it on the anniversary of Halo or something like that, but I don't think that they're really going to hold to that, you know, just because, I don't know, they'll sell it when it's done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well the game will be out when it's out, so we'll see if you were right or not, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there have been some strange goings-on, at least concerning Microsoft and Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, there was a site in Europe that was trying to sell the promotional codes for the Halo 3 beta that were actually supposed to be given out as a promotional item.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they've had a major smackdown on them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, they are not going to receive the beta codes.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're being removed from the Xbox Community Network immediately.
[SPEAKER_07]: Microsoft is not going to have any involvement with their sites.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're completely cutting them off.
[SPEAKER_07]: No goods, no nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've been excommunicated from the Church of Gates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's basically people trying to turn a profit on something that doesn't really belong to them to sell.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, yeah, they shouldn't do that crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: I say they have it coming.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm kind of glad Microsoft's laying the smack down.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's hear it for some values.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Microsoft's going to have to choke a bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is Bill Gates going to have to choke a bitch?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that would more be like probably Peter Moore choking a bitch or Major Nelson.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe we'll see why they call him Major.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why is somebody in the chatroom named Marky Mark?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe that's their name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe the Funky Bunch is not far behind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or maybe they hear that line a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Marky Mark, you are the chatroom hero.
[SPEAKER_02]: But look, Marky Mark's the first to bitch, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why all this old news?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, we do a show weekly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if you heard, but we do a show weekly, so sometimes we have to do stories that might come out on Monday.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: XBOX 360 Backward Compatibility
[SPEAKER_02]: Family Guy, Mortal Kombat Armageddon, Psychonauts, which a lot of folks were waiting for, Scarface, Soul Calibur 2, and a lot of other titles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Many, many, many titles, and the list is now over 300 original Xbox titles.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to see the complete list, you can check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Major Nelson posted a list on his blog, or you can head over to the Xbox official website to check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_06]: For dumb people, what does backwards compatibility mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no, not a problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's okay, because you play, like, casual games.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you do more computer gaming, right, than you do console?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't do a lot of console games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mostly do, yeah, computer games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do not know what backwards compatibility is.
[SPEAKER_07]: A gamer on a Mac.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up, DJ Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm pointing out Mac games.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the biggest things about the PlayStation 2 is that all my old PlayStation games will work on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: When PlayStation 3 came out, it was, oh, all my old PlayStation 2 games will work on it, and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_02]: But when the Xbox 360 came out, it was, well, we have software emulation because we changed our graphics chip, so some of the games will work on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we'll release updates every so often, and we're going to get 99% of our library.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did he say?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was supposed to be every month, and it's been every six months or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So needless to say, Microsoft hasn't been quite as speedy as we would have liked, but they're trying to get more of the old school Xbox titles playable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, speaking of being behind on updates and stuff,
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, speaking... One of the updates that just recently happened to the dashboard is causing a lot of stir, especially with people claiming that it's bricked their console and now they want their share of the profits.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, as we mentioned last week, there was a class action lawsuit filed by some guy for damages basically caused by this update.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now, there's been some actual updates to this and what exactly it was about.
[SPEAKER_03]: The whole...
[SPEAKER_03]: The premise of this class action lawsuit was they claimed that because of this update, they had to have their console fixed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Microsoft wanted $140 to fix their console instead of doing it for free because it was their fault.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so he's basically saying that they're using this to profit from it.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's seeking $5 million in damages, which is basically just to get them into the correct courthouse.
[SPEAKER_03]: They will, of course, adjust the amount depending on how many people are claiming to have the same problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right now, it's about 400 people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they're saying 1% of the 360 owners right now have this problem, and 400 people have come forward saying that they do have this problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, I think, I thought that what I heard before that they were fixing these for free, you know, the ones that were
[SPEAKER_03]: I think so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sounds like what happened to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't think that, I mean... No, I think if Microsoft realized their error, apologized for it, and fixed the machines, there should not be a lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_02]: There shouldn't be a lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_02]: People have a right to be mad at them and question, you know, if they want to trust them in the future, but lawsuits are totally unnecessary.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's what they need to do, and this is basically what they did before with the overheating problem with the consoles.
[SPEAKER_03]: People had sent them in to get fixed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say they sent it in to get fixed for this specific issue.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they paid the money to have it fixed they would be refunded this money
[SPEAKER_03]: If they haven't sent it in yet, they would be fixing them for free.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like they did with the consoles sold at launch that were having heating issues.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if your console bricks because of that, they would fix it for free.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or they will send you a refund for the amount that you paid to fix it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was pissed when my console bricked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go back and listen to a show around.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was around Valentine's Day when this happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was pissed when my console bricked.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I said a lot of nasty things about Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: When we say a console is bricked, Chris is like, bricked?
[SPEAKER_02]: When we say a console is bricked, that means it broke.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can't do anything but hold down paper with it, essentially.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why we call it bricks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm helping people who may not know that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then also the other cool term I like is that they send you a coffin.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the coffin is what you put the brick in because you're sending it back to Microsoft to be buried.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish, though, I understand why they want to do these lawsuits and stuff, but I really wish that people would just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: We have a lot of new people in chat tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks, you guys, for coming in the live experience.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if anyone else ever wants to join us live, we tape Sundays at 6 o'clock Pacific time, although you'll have to wait until 2007 to really pick that up again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess our first live show would be, what, January 6th or whatever that first Sunday is in January.
[SPEAKER_02]: So look for us then.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is there any other chat comments here?
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of folks going back and forth between
[SPEAKER_02]: The Lawsuit, DDR Dollar Bill says, I will sue for stubbing my toe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe that's from playing too much DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mystic, oh, the Weird Al song that Jamie was playing in her car the other day, because I was going to say, this whole thing makes me think of that Weird Al song about all the lawsuits.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, anyway, let's keep it moving with some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I don't want to move.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm comfortable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I will pick you up and throw you.
[SPEAKER_07]: No!
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, speaking of throwing, we had someone throw up some secret information, apparently.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm sure everyone's familiar with the actress Kristen Bell, yes?
[SPEAKER_02]: Veronica Mars?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's one of Extrovert's favorite shows.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need to watch that show because apparently Joss is a big fan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_07]: Joss Whedon is my lord and master.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't watched it, but I want to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now, Heroes is my lord and master.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is the best damn show I've watched in like the past five years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those fuckers are making us wait until January for new episodes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, the Lost fans have to wait until February.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's still Lost fans, but Lost sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do, by the way, have to thank our friends at PodCulture for sending me 11 episodes of Heroes so I can get started.
[SPEAKER_02]: All I have to say, you'll love Peter.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's the bomb.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'll love him.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, back to the story.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a game coming out called Assassin's Creed that's out by Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, she sort of spilled the beans.
[SPEAKER_07]: She said, to quote, it's sort of based on the research that's sort of happening now, but the fact that your genes might be able to hold memory.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you could argue semantics and say it's instinct, but how does a baby bird know how to eat a worm as opposed to a cockroach if its parents don't show it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess he's talking about genetic memory and all that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: And my favorite thing about this, I'm getting this, I actually get this story from Eurogamer, who, they are fantastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just love that they call it Ass Creed in the title.
[SPEAKER_03]: Completely, well, not exactly off topic here, but I'm officially boycotting Ubisoft games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because all of the games... Newbie Soft?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Newbie Soft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Newbie Soft?
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you ever heard of that, Newbie Soft?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Their last few games have really blown, and I think back to everything that I've bought from them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Granted, Ghost Recon and the Tom Clancy games aren't really my cup of tea, but the stuff for the Wii, Red Steel, Blue, GT sucked, Monster 4x4 sucked, the Wii version of Splinter Cell sucked, Far Cry sucks...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not buying any more of your games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rayman's Raven Rapids was okay, but still kind of sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, so... And Shannon Arms wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't they publish that?
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't make it, but they published it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They published it, okay, but still, though, I think that... They just kind of bought something from Ubisoft already.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm done with Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, looking forward to some of the stuff that they have coming out, like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter 2 which by the way looking at screenshots of that in the original one you can't tell them apart I will not be buying that game I am so inviting somebody from Ubisoft to come on this program in the future
[SPEAKER_02]: Jeremy Todd 1 says in our chatroom, Loki, that's a dumb move.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boycotting games will cause the Wii to turn out the same way as the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_02]: No third-party support.
[SPEAKER_02]: If people boycott third-party games, then they will stop making games, and the Wii will die just like the GameCube did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree and I disagree.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think that you should buy a game just to support third-party development, but if Loki thinks the game sucks, he shouldn't have to buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Loki's just kind of harsh on games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, God, you think GameSpot's bad?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean... Hey, listen, listen.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not harsh on games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, seriously, Red Steel.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had high hopes for this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: This game, you know, sold the console for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now, whose fault is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: You got your hopes up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take a deep breath.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's awful.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyways, back on track here, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Keep going.
[SPEAKER_02]: Real quick, real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Tetsuya, Loki, Red Steel 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's gonna suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not buying it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll just be the same damn fucking engine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, they can go back and tweak it and make it a little bit better, but please, you know, take a page from Capcom, listen to the goddamn feedback from the people that play your games.
[SPEAKER_02]: James Patrick, Red Steel is better than Killzone, and Mace Griffin on PS2, Red Steel isn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, Killzone on PlayStation 2, that game was fucking old.
[SPEAKER_03]: And granted, the game itself, I mean, is probably pretty good, it's just the controls that suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's what's really bad about it, is the fact that they really fucked up what could have been a good game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blackboy says, I kind of liked Red Steel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good, to each their own, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's people out there that are actually going to put down money for Splinter Cell Double Agent on the Wii, and I go, why?
[SPEAKER_03]: But, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go ahead, buy GT and Monster 4x4 for the Wii, because those aren't like old GameCube games or something that they just re-released and tacked on controls to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh wait, no they are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I see Jamie twiddling her thumbs over there, she's sick of Loki bitching.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's ready to get to a new story, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Aren't you, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well I have a story about Luminous.
[SPEAKER_02]: You like Luminous, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: I like Luminous!
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you like Luminous on the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll take that as a no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, I don't know how to answer that because I like Luminous and I like the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Luminous on the 360 is great except for the Xbox 360 controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: and the fact that, you know, you have all these microtransactions and the fact that if you own the PSP version, there's really not a lot of reason to get Luminous on 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you don't have a PSP, you really should have Luminous on the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, but anyway, there's a reason why I bring this up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox and Microsoft apparently thinks more people should be playing Luminous and they are going to have an official competition.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the Xbox Live Arcade Challenge and it's going to feature Luminous Live starting...
[SPEAKER_02]: Today, the 17th, and it's going to run through the 23rd of December.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you think you're good at Luminous, specifically the 60-second attack mode, if you can make a ton of bricks in the 60-second attack mode, I mean, it doesn't take long to try, you should enter this contest, and you might win a 42-inch Hitachi Plasma HD TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: Four runners-up will get an HD DVD bundle, a wireless headset, and the 360 wireless racing wheel.
[SPEAKER_02]: 100 ranking players, like the next 100 ranking players,
[SPEAKER_02]: will get 500 Microsoft Points tokens to be redeemed for Xbox Live imagery, which I'm assuming means you can't buy games with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably because it would... I'm assuming the reason why is because it would screw up the reimbursement to the creators of the game, which is why they force you to get imagery with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you really wanted a Halo theme that you have to pay for or something, I guess you could place in the top 100 and get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, they're also doing Small Arms, and that is running from the 24th of this month through the 30th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you only have to be in the top 105.
[SPEAKER_02]: So get to work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to see some OL Army members win some Xbox Live imagery.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wouldn't that be fun?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do I have to buy into this competition for Loomis?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you have to buy the game, but I believe that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everything else you have to purchase.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I don't believe so.
[SPEAKER_03]: They should have had a thing that you have to purchase to turn the game off.
[SPEAKER_02]: The tournament skin or whatever?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Power Button skin?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's keep it moving.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, um... God, I hate Luminous.
[SPEAKER_07]: Luminous is great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love, like... I love Luminous for PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was my absolute favorite game that came out last year, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I love Mizuguchi.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the man's a god.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgive him for 99 Nights.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even I didn't think that game was that bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I found the good in 99 Nights, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Every Xtend Extra I ran out and bought.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, Luminous 2, if you didn't have Luminous 1, Luminous 2 is really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: And even if you're a fan of Luminous, Luminous 2 is really, really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're just hating on puzzle games.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're hating on everything today.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, if you're looking for some better games to be coming out, the XNA is definitely one way that might happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially since now it's allowing a lot of independent developers to create their own Xbox Live Arcade games, or possibly Xbox Live Arcade games.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they're saying that basically the XNA is going to become the YouTube for games.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I have to ask, are these going to be games that are reruns of shows that were on the night before that I can catch in case I missed, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or is it going to be like, you know, knockoffs of everything or, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: Game A with music from Game B
[SPEAKER_03]: To be able to share your own games with the whole community.
[SPEAKER_02]: XNA, XNA, XNA
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I downloaded it and I'm like, I don't know how the fuck to use this, and I deleted it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, I don't have to pay $99 a year for YouTube, so I don't understand how this... You only have to pay $99, I believe, to play the games on your Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can distribute them for free, like using Windows.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can play the games on Windows.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently, I guess, the wired controllers and the wireless ones, once that wireless adapter comes out,
[SPEAKER_03]: All the XNA games will support those controllers.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't necessarily need to buy into this yet, but I would like to see an open place where you can play some games or download some free arcade games.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Funnydale says, XNA will never be YouTube because 90% of people are too stupid to use XNA.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could you imagine if they banned stupid people from YouTube?
[SPEAKER_02]: There'd be no YouTube.
[SPEAKER_02]: So nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: You better patent that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Britney Spears, I really want you to put on panties.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why won't you listen to me, girl?
[SPEAKER_04]: Britney Spears is actually listening to you on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's searching for your blog.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now there's a game I'd like to see in XNA.
[SPEAKER_02]: Help Britney Spears dress herself.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: They made Britney Spears dance beat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Britney's dance beat?
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw the greatest thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought about getting this for you for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had it at some stupid jewelry store or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a DDR-like game, but it was to teach you how to cheerlead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, I saw commercials for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was so fucking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, okay girls, go!
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't that just like Para Para Paradise?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like an exercise video, except you're on a DDR-type mat.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, hey, how about something different?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure, like what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Other than cheerleaders.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about release dates?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, now let's talk about some games we'll actually get to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chris laughed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Coming out... Oh, stop that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's kind of funny because this game's coming out on the winter solstice.
[SPEAKER_07]: The 21st, we have Sam & Max Episode 2, Situation Comedy for the PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: The 22nd, Marvel Ultimate Alliance on Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Open Season, Star Trek Legacy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wii Sports on Christmas Day, which is bizarre.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: and then a few other to be announced ones.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Silent Hill Origins, Point Blank, Limbo of the Lost, which just sounds very interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really not too much else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, what's to be expected right before Christmas?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, actually, if you're in Japan, you have a lot of other options.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox 360 over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, these Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lost Planet coming out on December 21st.
[SPEAKER_02]: Madden NFL 07 if you're a football fan in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Need for Speed Carbon and Sonic the Hedgehog all making their way to the Xbox 360 on December 21st.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 3 is going to see Armored Core 4 on the 21st, also their version of Need for Speed Carbon and their version of Sonic the Hedgehog all making their way to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Over on Nintendo Wii, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Need for Speed Carbon, because that game comes out everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, you're getting Monster 4x4 World Circuit from Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_02]: On the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: School Love, which is our game name of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: School Love comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, a limited edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game is made by Views, and again, it's a PlayStation 2 game, and of course, what Japanese release would be incomplete without the anime-looking cute girls in uniforms on the cover with the name School Love underneath that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dating Sim, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's what it looks like, because I'm looking at the little screenshot pictures here.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a Dating Sim?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it looks like a Dating Sim.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you have ever wanted to date school girls in the comfort of your own home,
[SPEAKER_07]: I have yaoi dating sims, those are always fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Not the porn one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta get to the rest of the releases, because there's some big stuff in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of Evangelion, there's Secret of Evangelion coming out from Jinx, also in Japan on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, uh, Squeenix fanboys, prepare thyselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here comes your fanboy boner.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seiken Detsetsu 4, also known as Dawn of Mana, December 21st, this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need new pants.
[SPEAKER_02]: There goes her boner.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_02]: On the Nintendo DS, you have a cute pouch, DS, oh, these are like just little pouches, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Angel Pocket with DS Diary.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of little things coming out there for the DS, accessory-wise.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the sweet pouch, also coming from Konami.
[SPEAKER_02]: But get this, if you cannot get enough hamster action on your Nintendo DS...
[SPEAKER_02]: Hamster to Kurasawa is coming out on the Nintendo DS in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And look at the cute cover!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh god!
[SPEAKER_02]: This is great radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me post that link in our chatroom there if you folks would like to check out the Love Hamsters there on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: They can't... What... Seriously, can one of our, like, Japanese listeners, because I know we have some, can one of them email me and please tell me what is up with hamsters?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I think I want to buy... Apparently they're good for the ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I... I think... Sadly, that trend was probably started in America.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I'm going to actually buy one of those DS hamster games, because they have the hamsters ones over... Unfortunately, it's by Ubisoft, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: So much for your boycott.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have Hamster's Life or whatever, and you get to create your own little house and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I might buy that just to try it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do have a rebuttal for the chatroom, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't you know Cyberbots is Capcom's number one game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a quote in Puzzle Fighter
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh no, I'm sorry, those dates are in February, never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: You got a ways out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you will get new games on the 22nd of February.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's all I care to share with you at this time.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're looking for games in the United States this week, you're not going to have much to choose from, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Coming out on the PSP, we have Metal Slug Anthology.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, Bubble Bobble Evolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then on Playstation 2 Brave the Search for Spirit Dancer which is delayed since like August and on PC Paws and Claws Pet School where you get to
[SPEAKER_03]: You get to cure animals by petting them and... I swear to God, you... Oh my God, cute!
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all you do!
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you're dying from cancer!
[SPEAKER_05]: My petting will save you!
[SPEAKER_03]: That's basically this game, I swear to God.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then on the Xbox 360, you're getting Rappala trophies, because if you really want a really crappy-ass fishing game, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Mad Catz, the Xbox Live Arcade Retro Stick, which...
[SPEAKER_03]: People say it's awesome for Xbox Live Arcade games, but I think it looks like a giant piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, if you want to buy it, great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shouldn't you try it before you pass judgment on it here on this program?
[SPEAKER_03]: It just looks awful, dude.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not buying an arcade stick for just a couple Xbox Live Arcade games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will build my own stick before I go and buy one.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I have some game news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy Tactics, Shishi Sensou
[SPEAKER_07]: Meaning that they're also saying it's going to be cel-shaded, have new jobs, and is a sequel to the PSX one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay, because I heard it was like a direct port of the PlayStation one, but it sounds like they're enhancing it, like a lot of these, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a sequel.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if it's the same one with more stuff, then that will still be fun, because Final Fantasy Tactics, even though I'm not a fan of tactics games, I think it's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like watching people play them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy Tactics A2, Fuketsu no Gurimore I like Final Fantasy Tactics
[SPEAKER_02]: All I want for Xmas is a PSP.com
[SPEAKER_02]: All I Want For Xmas Is A PSP.com
[SPEAKER_02]: All I want is a PSP!
[SPEAKER_02]: Xmas of PSP.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Zipatoni is one of Sony's marketing firms.
[SPEAKER_02]: So people, once this caught wind on the game blogs, people started spamming the crap out of this site.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, liars, we found you out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, Zipatoni.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just all this nasty, nasty shit written in these comments.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you missed all this action play out, sorry, the site's gone because it's just a big white page now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what happened later in the week, Sony fessed up at something to the effect of,
[SPEAKER_02]: Blah, blah, blah, you caught us, blah, blah, blah, I guess we were too funky fresh for you, blah, blah, blah, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: Continuing to make themselves look stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because the problem I think most people had with All I Want for Xmas is a PSP.com is not necessarily the fact that they were being lied to, because there's been previous viral marketing campaigns that were kind of, you know, fun, like the I Love Bees and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the problem with All I Want for Xmas is a PSP.com is they made your typical gamer look like a dumbass.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, just a complete and utter... Seriously, when I watch these videos, I felt my intelligence be insulted.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, this is supposed to win me over?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is really what marketing people think gamers are?
[SPEAKER_02]: And for Sony to come out and say, I guess we were too funky fresh for you, that's like when grandma says something about... Who says funky fresh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wow, that was really the bee's knees trying to be cool like you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going like, you people really don't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: and the thing too about it is they're all using they had a bunch of fake comments on there too by people saying oh this is the best site ever and then like using number two for every time they said two and just trying to fake that leet speak or whatever on their website and why the fuck do they create a website other than to get buzz and stuff about the PSP but it's just
[SPEAKER_03]: to create a fake website, you know, with a bunch of people saying, oh, the PSP's awesome and stuff like that, it's just, it's really dirty, I don't know, it just seems like...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't see Nintendo making fake websites going, oh, the Wii is awesome and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't need to make up that publicity.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just the PSP and the PlayStation 3 have been having a big problem with their marketing campaigns.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, I got some comments from the chat room I have to read here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crispy says, at least they fessed up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of feel like they had to fess up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, seriously?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony was caught with not only their pants down, but their boxers down too, so the world could see what an incredibly tiny, tiny penis Sony had when it came to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because seriously, that's kind of what it boils down to right now, is that Sony's probably a little pissed that people are all hyped about Wii and DS and da-da-da-da-da, and that there wasn't a legitimate blog out there for PSP rabid fandom.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they created this.
[SPEAKER_02]: And let's see, Funnydale in our chatroom says, I hate to break the news to you guys, but every video game commercial makes gamers look like a bunch of losers.
[SPEAKER_02]: What, Chris, you say that's not true?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not true.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't get that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't get that when I see those.
[SPEAKER_02]: It depends.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, it depends on what commercial I'm looking at.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I kind of like the Wii commercials, but then again, the Wii appeals to those that are not gamers, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think... Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let's look at... I can see where he's getting that comment from, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has taken the society a long time to get gamers, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it really... Like, the PlayStation commercials, like, for both the PSP and the PlayStation 3, I never really got them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, and I always knew that they had a problem with their marketing firms, because look at the way they're advertising.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, the PSP, they have two stick figures, or not stick figures, but, like, you know, sketch drawings of, like, dust bunnies or whatever...
[SPEAKER_03]: Like talking about random shit, you know, and they're all PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, you know, nuts.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like a nut you can play outside or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nor do the PlayStation 3 commercials.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're in the room with the, you know, PlayStation 3, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Flaming Bozo in our chatroom says, No, the commercials for gaming colleges make us look stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, those are awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, thank you for citing a commercial.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're right, that one does make gamers look pretty stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think people need to get the concept of, and this is one of those things I feel like, you know, at least in the Wii marketing, and again, I'm not talking about the systems, I'm talking about the marketing.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the Wii marketing, it's kind of got that gamers are everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who enjoys movies?
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who listens to music?
[SPEAKER_02]: Shouldn't games be accessible to everybody too?
[SPEAKER_02]: Right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: One would hope.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, real quick question, then we'll get to another story here.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I want to go around the room and ask, yes or no, and any other thing you want to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony should fire any company related to their marketing right now and start with new companies around the board.
[SPEAKER_02]: In other words, Sony should just axe everything to do with their marketing right now and start anew in 2007.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes or no?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it would be a good idea to not only get new marketers, I mean, get some people that actually know how to market this stuff, like the people behind Burger King, or even like Geico, just like people that come up with really creative marketing campaigns.
[SPEAKER_03]: Great, that's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get some of those people to help you out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, get your higher-ups to shut the fuck up, because they keep ruining any good marketing that you do for yourselves.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's what they need to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, I think companies have a really...
[SPEAKER_03]: Crazy idea what viral marketing is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, yes or no?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony needs to fire all their marketers.
[SPEAKER_07]: To take this from a business point of view, that would actually be pretty damn illogical to expect them to because they have contracts set up with these.
[SPEAKER_07]: What they need to do is have more express control, you know, better, I'd say better QA with what goes on, with what's marketed, more involvement with this, you know,
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's look at this realistically.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because honestly, anything that their marketing firms come up with, doesn't Sony have to approve?
[SPEAKER_07]: So somebody at Sony approved these.
[SPEAKER_07]: They need to find whoever was in charge of approving it and fire them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or a structural reorganization.
[SPEAKER_07]: Structural reorganization, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Either that or...
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't like to talk about people getting killed or fired or anything, but structural reorganization is a need.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or hire me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Would you save Sony?
[SPEAKER_07]: I am brilliant.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would save Sony's ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love you, Jamie, but damn.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it would be like PlayStation 3 starts fires.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fire, fire, fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be PlayStation 3 presented by Sega.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, here's what they really need to do, and they really need to just focus on
[SPEAKER_03]: What makes the system good?
[SPEAKER_03]: It plays games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's great for gaming and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe show off the 6-axis controller and how it's used in games and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe just focus on what the system offers instead of just these really cryptic fucking commercials.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, the PSP, they need to fucking get some good marketing behind this thing because right now, they're hoping Metal Gear Solid Portable Ops is good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was like a system seller, but
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think anyone really knows what's a good game on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, maybe word needs to get out there that maybe it's Metal Gear.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're trying not to be like a Sony hate fest.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, maybe some of you guys are.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to see this be like a total Sony hate fest because there are, you know, like I said, I love Luminous 2 every cent extra.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are good things I like about the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just that, boy, your marketing sucks right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of their commercials and print materials have been decent.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so if I were to answer this question, I would say whoever was behind this whole thing, definitely structural reorganization.
[SPEAKER_02]: But when it comes to, you know, some of their marketing hasn't been bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: What happened to the really cool marketing that they had at E3, like the Play Beyond stuff?
[SPEAKER_07]: That stuff was cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: They should have stuck with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But see, my marketing scheme for the PlayStation 3 would start off with fire in the commercial.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony needs to hire Jamie to be their Major Nelson.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Sergeant Sakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would start off with fire.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then there would be some more explosions in the background.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then... This Sunday, Sunday, Sunday, your PlayStation 3 will be on fire!
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: There'd be like a fence in the background, like a chain link fence.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there'd be like all these really awesome people walking around with PlayStation 3s.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then the announcer going, buy a PlayStation 3, dammit!
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I gotta let Chris comment on this being the, you know, one who maybe isn't as into consoles as the rest of us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony needs to fire them all, yes or no?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, well, realistically, we all know they're not going to, because like somebody said, I think it was Jamie, they got contracts, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they should get fired but someone definitely needs to go I nominate Jamie for this someone needs to go in there and like bitch slap them because I think what they're doing gladly yeah I know I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm reading chat room and these comments are too good to pass up hold on let Chris finish your thought yeah the chat room upped me it's okay no I'm sorry finish your thought go go go quick okay
[SPEAKER_02]: Fireboma has an idea for a campaign, and that is the PlayStation 3 campaign will go something like this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only faggots buy a Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: And look, look, I am gay, so I can laugh at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you buy a Wii, that means you like it in the ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox, this will be the other commercial.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox 360 owners are fat and retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: You aren't fat and retarded, are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sergeant Firebomba, everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you have the Wii 60, does it mean that you're a big fat dyke?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, honestly, even though... That means you like fried chicken.
[SPEAKER_03]: And even though that is so offensive, I would still think that's a better advertisement.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would laugh at that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would at least laugh at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, if I saw a commercial come on TV, like, you think I should be offended, you know, being gay and all, but I would probably laugh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I'd be all, that's better than the all-I-want breakfast is a PSP thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm laughing so hard, that's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just thinking of the hate mail that's going to come in.
[SPEAKER_07]: New ad scheme, new ad scheme.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys should not be using those words on the air.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what?
[SPEAKER_07]: We have a mature rating.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, whatever, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, the ad scheme would be this.
[SPEAKER_07]: You just have a black screen, yeah?
[SPEAKER_07]: And a PlayStation 3 shows up.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, you want one.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're Sony.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kiss our ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, I got one here.
I got one here, I got one here, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Buy a PlayStation 3 or we will kill you!
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're getting too crazy here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to put a call out to the listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have a voicemail system, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a homework assignment.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we'll even turn this into a giveaway.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We want you to leave a voicemail.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not now.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're listening live to us on Sunday, please don't call now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But call after when the podcast feed hits.
[SPEAKER_02]: Call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Leave your best 30-second Sony commercial.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: The winner, the one that persuades us to buy a Sony product the most, we will send something from our prize pool somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll dig something up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want a paper for Rob's bathroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: So get to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Leave your 30-second voicemails, and we'll play our favorites when we come back live here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Feral Trade Commission on Monday said that companies would be required to
[SPEAKER_03]: to disclose ties of word-of-mouth marketing campaigns.
[SPEAKER_03]: These fake grassroots efforts, dubbed astro-surfing by critics, hire people to endorse products as themselves rather than respective companies.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, actually it's pretty cool that they're doing this, and I do think it's something, because I always see when they're advertising different games and stuff, all these viral marketing campaigns, and
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think people know what viral marketing is.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're not supposed to know that you're being marketed to not by saying, look, I'm a site called I love such and such game or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love Barbie Horse Adventures.
[SPEAKER_03]: And having a bunch of people saying, yeah, that game rocks.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not viral marketing.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is basically lying to people.
[SPEAKER_03]: A viral marketing campaign is saying, Barbie's saying, oh, come try out my new horse game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Getting an email like that or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to get emails from Barbie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why don't I sign up for that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Be a dirty whore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alternate Reality Gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's another good marketing campaign because it gets people involved and it's kind of some mystery to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's a really good way to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isle of Bees, the whole Xbox 360 campaigns that they did, the Hex 168 or whatever it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's good marketing, but I guess when you have retarded marketing companies working for you, that's all they can come up with.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, I forgot to give you the voicemail number.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of a good lapse of judgment, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's toll-free in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Canada.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, U.K.
[SPEAKER_02]: listeners, you'd have to pay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you could do it the free way if you use Skype, our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can just give us a call there, download the program.
[SPEAKER_02]: More information on OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, I thought of another idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ad campaigns.
[SPEAKER_07]: Going back to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: A giant crab comes out clutching a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would laugh at that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the slogan is, buy a PS3, get crabs.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're welcome, chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: So hey, my turn, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, yes, now you can go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, speaking of the PlayStation 3, you know, by our crabs, they put out the 1.31 update, which adds support for Final Fantasy XI for all you weird addicts.
[SPEAKER_07]: The update on the US page does not state what is involved in it, but however, the Japanese site does, and based on a rudimentary translation,
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the installation of the hard disk PlayStation 2, so basically the hard drive attachment is going to be compatible.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that means you get Nobunaga's Ambition Online and Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, they're saying that it's not quite working on the Japanese site for the PlayStation 2 system data.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: My question would be, though, would you really want to play this game on the PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I don't know if you guys have seen this video on Dig this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It hit Dig and it was all over the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: But some guy actually made a side-by-side comparison of playing Final Fantasy X on the PlayStation 2 and on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And honestly, it looks like absolute horseshit on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they show you what the PS3 one looks like.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm playing it in the studio here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can see the PS3 is on one side of the screen, the PS2 is on the other side of the screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me go to a section here that has, like, a face, and you can really tell the difference.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can see how the PS3 one is, like, kind of like... It's faded.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's, like, faded out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks a little washed.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can see, especially when they get into, like, the shots... See, look at the shots of Yuna's face here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can see, like, all these jaggedies there.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can see, like, all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: The one thing in defense of the PlayStation 3 side is the colors seem a bit more normalized, not over-contrasted.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, anyway, what basically is going on here is that, you know, they're saying this could be really fixed with just a simple firmware update.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, that's all they really had to do to get rid of the jaggeds and the artifacts that are there, but nothing yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess it was one of those things that was overlooked to get the system out on time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I do think... I'd have to see other games to compare it, honestly, but I do like... Some of the backgrounds looked more washed out, but I think for skin tones...
[SPEAKER_07]: It was clearer.
[SPEAKER_07]: The skin tones were more realistic and accurate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're being more forgiving than most of the internet was.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, then again, I'm taking it from an artist's point of view.
[SPEAKER_07]: There are more dragonies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let's also, you know, it's YouTube.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not going to be the best quality.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, look, you got a PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should go home and try for yourself and let us know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to borrow my Final Fantasy X?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have Final Fantasy X!
[SPEAKER_07]: I just went checking.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, seriously, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, that would be good because all I have to do is switch my channels.
[SPEAKER_07]: We actually did that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan and I did that a long time ago with our Saturn and the PlayStation for Castlevania Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: It turned out that the Saturn version had better sound and the 2D effects were better, but the PlayStation had better 3D, so that was our comparison.
[SPEAKER_07]: I could do that again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Try it with other games.
[SPEAKER_02]: That might be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'd have to find duplicates of some of the games, but I could do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oops, sorry, I keep playing the video there in the background.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to get the link there for chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they do this little, like, unnecessary intro to the thing on YouTube, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, they're... Oh, damn it!
[SPEAKER_02]: I reposted the hamster thing in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Son of a bitch!
[SPEAKER_07]: Hamsters!
[SPEAKER_02]: Go hamster!
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn YouTube.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me make sure that copied.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is great radio, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_02]: What can we say?
[SPEAKER_02]: We are taping live, and this is what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once upon a time, there was a Final Fantasy game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's try that again.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's the link the chat room's been begging for.
[SPEAKER_02]: God.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, ShadowCharlie has also pointed out that you can play as Maria in the Saturn version, but you can also play as Richter, and he's not an easy kill in that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Dan just unlocked Richter and Maria mode in Portrait of Ruin.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's like TurboGrafxMaria.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I'll just say that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, it's awesome that you get to play Final Fantasy XI on your PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, you can't do that if you're in the UK because it's not out yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the speculation is...
[SPEAKER_03]: It might not be out for quite a while, and there might actually be a delay on the March date, and they're saying that it's possibly delayed to May, if not September, according to Computer and Video Games, that website.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, what did Sony have to say about this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, actually, Sony's Computer Entertainment Europe
[SPEAKER_03]: David Reeves, he said, well, we're still on schedule with the launch for the PlayStation 3 in March throughout the PAL territories, and all speculation otherwise is without foundation.
[SPEAKER_03]: It should be noted, though, this is the same guy that was saying that they're on track for releasing...
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, in 2006, spring, he says that they were on track at that time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm basically also saying that, I don't know, it's pretty funny though, you know, this guy is basically just giving people the assumption that the thing was coming out in spring of 2006, and then when it passed that date, he's all, oh, by the way, it's not coming out at that time.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, who knows if it's coming out in March.
[SPEAKER_03]: And by the, looking at how many units they're producing, supposedly they're done with the bottleneck with the Blu-ray diodes, but if that's not the case, it might not be coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see why the UK won't be getting us on time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, but this guy's word isn't enough for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: My thing would be, is they're going to get it in March, but it's definitely not going to be as major.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be like our launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have fun, our friends over the UK who are going to be waiting for this system.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com EarthCam.com
[SPEAKER_07]: No, seriously, you can look at, you know, London, Moscow, Japan, you know, anywhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically different webcams in different locations across the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to check that out because one thing I've been playing with a lot this week is Google Earth, which is one of my favorite programs ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It lets you look at satellite photography and zoom in and out anywhere in the world, anywhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of the ones I'm looking at right now is in Meppen, Germany.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, that's of an ice skating rink.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's very cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's just basically linked to different international webcams.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's actually a webcam, I hope that they've got it back up, but it was in, uh, New Orleans in the French Quarter.
[SPEAKER_07]: They used to have a cam outside one of the, uh, the bars.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_02]: My friend was on that cam once and sent a picture from it.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was years ago, before, you know, all the disaster.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, isn't that funny?
[SPEAKER_07]: And, um, but some of the other places listed here, there's one, um, in, um,
[SPEAKER_07]: Effort, Germany, and a few in Russia.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to weather for Texas, Peak District, England, Jerusalem, Miami.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's very neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's sort of, you know, I don't think there's any in any bathrooms.
[SPEAKER_02]: No locker room webcams, Chris.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think it's a very good idea, another way to bring us, you know, sort of closer together.
[SPEAKER_02]: GS68 in our chatroom says we need an OLR webcam and I'll tell you guys it actually looks like it probably will happen if you're all good boys and girls for Christmas there will be a cam coming back to the show in 2007 I'll be doing the dance of the seven veils in the background
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie doesn't like to be seen.
[SPEAKER_02]: The problem is the studio we're in now is a lot smaller than any place we were before.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a lot less people and weird stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I say studio, I mean spare bedroom as opposed to the living room at Loki and I's old apartment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now we're in a spare bedroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's kind of tough for us to situate a webcam here where we can actually see everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm thinking I know a good place we could put a cam where you could see most of the action.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you show up, which you need to show up more often, Miss Thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm coming up from the South Bay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I come up as often as I can.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's the website of the week, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Give it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to some more news, kind of in other types of game news, not about games themselves, but an interesting program going on in Oakland.
[SPEAKER_02]: The SFGate newspaper, or I'm sorry, is this a newspaper or just a website?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or...
[SPEAKER_02]: Alternative Press
[SPEAKER_02]: The SFGate is mentioning that you can go to Fruitvale Elementary School in Oakland where the War Against Improper Toys Drive is going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is happening is that they will... What you can do, you can take your replica shotguns, rifles, pistols, whatever, and you can trade them in for books and family-friendly toys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, how this plays out is that you can also take your violent video games...
[SPEAKER_02]: What about my Jeff Stryker action figure?
[SPEAKER_02]: I dare you to take it to the school and find out.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you do, please tape it so we can YouTube it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: That address, by the way, 3200 Boston Avenue in Oakland.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right by 580.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are they going to send all these improper toys to the Island of Misfit Toys by chance?
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that special!
[SPEAKER_07]: They need the Island of Misfit Sex Toys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not said what they're going to do with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to burn it in effigy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, this is actually pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of games and stuff, improper toys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Capcom's revamping their multiplayer once we actually ran a story was it last week where they were fixing the small text issues well now they're kind of going off of some more of their user feedback and fixing the multiplayer including some of the lobbies and matchmaking and stuff like that so I'm glad to see a company actually listening to the complaints and maybe suggestions from their users so that in turn you know they create a better product
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's excellent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cannot wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be probably one of the only good 360 games coming out in January.
[SPEAKER_07]: Has anybody ever heard of the GP32X?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, the GP2X?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, basically this one is... Okay, no, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_07]: What this is, it's a Linux-based handheld console.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's for movies, games, music.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can develop and run your own software, run MAME on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's supposed to be pretty versatile.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's actually getting its first major game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's getting a game called Payback, which is a crime caper game that was originally on the Game Boy Advance in 2004.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a top-down action, 11 cities, 50 missions, updated 3D graphics, sound special effects Custom jukebox mode so you can put your own soundtrack on it And it'll actually, again this is for the UK It's going to be 22.99 Think Grand Theft Auto 1 and 2 That type of game Huh, interesting
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I did not remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this handheld was talked about on an earlier show, but I kind of forgot about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's interesting they have a Linux handheld because it's funny because they try to put Linux on all the other handhelds.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the toaster.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's kind of humorous to me to hear about a Linux handheld.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd actually love to get my hands on one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, I would like to see the presence of this increase.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if anyone wants to see the website on this game, go to gp2x.co.uk.
[SPEAKER_07]: slash payback.html.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's got a movie file up on there, a bit more about the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has some stuff on the system.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, actually, I remember seeing the system at E3 a couple years back.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Linux, their logo is like a penguin, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I saw that on someone's license plate.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was actually part of the license plate.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are some hardcore nerds out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have a neighbor here that has a license plate that says,
[SPEAKER_02]: ZOMG Hack.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I want to know who that is.
[SPEAKER_02]: We live in this huge complex and there's some guy with a license plate there and I'm always like, wow, it's another nerd.
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone had that said noob on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just to give a little bit more about the system, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has two 200 MHz CPU, 64 MB RAMs, custom graphics hardware, decoding chips, takes SD cards, has 64 MB of NAND memory.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, you don't have to re-encode any of your movies that you put on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll play anything directly like on a computer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Price on it is 124.99.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a partridge in a pear tree.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have everything else.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why don't I have one of these?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dear UK friends, send me one for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love you forever.
[SPEAKER_03]: eBay, the gamers shop of choice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, eBay, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so last week we talked a little bit about Interlink's lawsuit with Nintendo over the Wii remote and basically saying that it's infringing on their patents for a Trier-operated electronic device.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's interesting though is we've kind of figured that the whole lawsuit was about the fact that it's like a Wiimote type thing, something motion sensitive, but it's actually just for the stupid trigger on the bottom of the Wiimote, which I don't know about you, but I think there's been remotes with triggers on the bottom of them way before this whole patent thing came to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's going to be interesting to see how that actually plays out in court.
[SPEAKER_02]: Doesn't technically the Xbox 360 controller have a trigger on the bottom of it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It does have a trigger on the bottom of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Two of them?
[SPEAKER_03]: What about the Nintendo 64 controller?
[SPEAKER_03]: Has a trigger on the bottom of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The PlayStation 2 has a trigger on the actual controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think they're going to get very far with this, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to try.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we will see, and we'll follow up in a future episode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got a ton of it coming up next in Orange Lounge Radio Part B, so please stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see you back here for Part B.