[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, December 10th, 2006, Microsoft gets sued over Brick 360s, the old Apple entering the console market rumor resurfaces, and is the PlayStation 3 harming the acceptance of Blu-ray?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are that video game program dedicated to video games, gamer culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_03]: My name is Rob Roberts and unfortunately not joining us this week is DarkSakura, Jamie Summers, but we do have the ferret to speak for her in her place.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's actually in L.A.
[SPEAKER_03]: this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's spinning around on the teacups back at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, again?
[SPEAKER_03]: She's at Disneyland again?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, she's there with Chris and, oh well.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's not here this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: She was going to call in with a special report, but I guess she got too dizzy because I didn't see anything on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_03]: So maybe she'll bug us later.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But in the meantime, the one and only Loki is joining us here tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm doing okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of weird because we haven't been live in a while, like since before Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, we missed that show Thanksgiving week and then we were pre-taped last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now this week, it doesn't feel like a full thing because it's just you and me and there's no DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no special guest yet, although supposedly Miklatov's going to be here.
[SPEAKER_03]: But like an hour before we went live, they were like, Bye, we're going to go play DDR at the bowling alley.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Viva Piñata
[SPEAKER_04]: until which the game decided I don't want to play it anymore, which is ironic because I really didn't want to play it anymore because, well, it froze up on me.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the game itself was just very kind of boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I got really bored with it really quick, so I plan on selling it back since I didn't pay for it in the first place.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know, can't recommend it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I guess if you stick with it long enough, it might be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just found it very, very, very annoying, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Played more Excite Truck, because that's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Played more Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've been doing more of the Wii Sports bowling, and my friend who's used to being in a bowling league was kicking our ass, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, I don't know, just waiting for Elebits this week, and actually I'm going to probably try to pick up Far Cry Vengeance as well, so those will be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And more Grand Theft Auto Vice City stories, and
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, was it on Tuesday, actually, I'm going to be hooking up the Wii in our kind of giant theater at work that we have for a demonstration for all the sales staff, and it's going to be kind of cool because we get to use my wireless sensor bar that I made, so I'm going to be playing the Wii on a giant screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually tried it out on Friday, and it worked out pretty good, so I'm looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But in the meantime, just kind of kicking back and waiting for some better games to come out, and
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the reason that you decided to go to RPM today?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: What made him decide to do RPM of all places?
[SPEAKER_04]: He likes race cars.
[SPEAKER_04]: He likes to drag cars and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we thought it'd be fun to go down there because I've never been down there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: The second car I got really sucked, and the tires were all fucked up on it, so it wouldn't grip it, and I kept spinning out and hitting the wall.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, I don't know, it was fun, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you imagine what Loki must be like at one of these places?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, that's right, the music's starting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's like, oh, it's like initial D!
[SPEAKER_03]: Ready, set, go!
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we should totally get out of here, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everything I need to know here I learned from Initial D!
[SPEAKER_03]: Mega Drift!
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn, I left my little stupid Sega card at home.
[SPEAKER_03]: What am I going to do?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was fun, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, really, we should go do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it would be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's something we should put on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_03]: We could, too, because you could film it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only if we get loaded.
[SPEAKER_03]: Before we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't drink and drive, kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're only kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought I'd mention that, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played a bit of Motorstorm at a kiosk at Best Buy, and I like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's kind of cool, but it's a lot slower, though, than Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be honest, I really wish that EA would do a Burnout off-road series.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what Motorstorm did for me?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, this game sucks!
[SPEAKER_03]: That was Motorstorm.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: When I played it at Target.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi Miklatov!
[SPEAKER_02]: You decided to join us after all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we just got back from the bowling alley.
[SPEAKER_02]: How's my mic?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think you're okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I might have to turn you up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: But how are you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm tired now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you guys want to go play the new DDR without me?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not the new new DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: The newest DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: The newest DDR to us in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_03]: How was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't realize how stupid I am when I make steps sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's right, because you do steps for the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and we had to redo some steps a while ago for the Ultramix One songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I played Gorgeous 2012 on doubles, and I played Heavy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if many people realize, but it has new Heavy steps.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so I was playing, and I was like, oh, yeah, I remember making these.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then it got to utter crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, what was I thinking?
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I just gave up and died.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was there a large crowd there playing DDR?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: If me and Irene are a large crowd, then yeah, there was a very large crowd.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to fix your mic here.
[SPEAKER_03]: How else was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I played more Elite Beat Agents, trying to S everything on Hard Rock.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, I can hear myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're supposed to be able to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I played Elite Beat Agents.
[SPEAKER_02]: I started playing Zelda again, and the fourth dungeon boss is the best boss fight I've ever played in my life.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was so cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um, I don't think I did anything else besides that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's just been Zelda all week long?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, because I don't play video games anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: When have you been playing PSP and DS and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: PSP?
[SPEAKER_02]: When did I say I played PSP?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or DS, I'm fine, DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Elite Beat Agents?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's my favorite game that I have on DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a good game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called Elite Beat Agents.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hello as well to someone else who's here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hello to Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, we haven't seen you in forever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's been a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: What have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you take a guess?
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got to get real close to the mic.
[SPEAKER_03]: These mics are not very sensitive.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you take a guess?
[SPEAKER_03]: I can.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is it, Shane?
[SPEAKER_03]: It rhymes with kawau.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'd be right.
[SPEAKER_03]: It rhymes with World of Boarcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you saying I'm the world of boar crap?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, Rob, you are a world of boar crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, what server are you on?
[SPEAKER_03]: What character class are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you doing in the WoW or the Wob?
[SPEAKER_05]: The Wob?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm on Elder Thalyss and I PvP.
[SPEAKER_05]: All day long?
[SPEAKER_05]: All day long.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, have fun with your Wob.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, My Gaming Week, um, not a whole lot of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I decided to go back and rediscover, um, GameTap, because I haven't been playing it a lot lately.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so I decided to load that up, and they actually have some cool new stuff on there, because they have, like, the Castlevania games and Contra games from the old school, like, 8-bit NES are on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Silent Hill 2 is on GameTap, which it looks very nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was very surprised.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks better than it does on PS2 because, you know, it uses the advanced hardware on the computer to give the smoother textures and things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was very, very pleased with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you can really control the resolution and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that was really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Civilization 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for those who have listened to the show in the past, you guys know I love Civilization.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's my favorite PC game of all time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yet Civilization 2 was such a shock to me that I just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not liking it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to go play it some more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe I'll have to play some OLR listeners because it's multi... Although I don't even know anyone else with GameTap besides our webmaster, VxJasonXV.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm still waiting for Myst Online to come out on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have not played the Sam & Max game yet, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely play that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Otherwise, I decided based on a new forum we have in our...
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Launch Radio Forums, PC Gaming Forum
[SPEAKER_03]: and it's actually pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a lot of fun, so much so that I decided to spend the 20 bucks and get every X10 extra on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'll know more about that game next week when I've actually played it some more.
[SPEAKER_02]: You found it today?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it was actually easy to find.
[SPEAKER_03]: GameStop has it cut down to 20 bucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, too bad GameStop is evil, but wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, I'll get it wherever I can get it because I use their online search the store to shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, I got a present.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki got me a Christmas present.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got Final Fantasy 3 on the DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, you may not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to punch you in the face.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then I will play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only I get to divergenize my cartridge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know that feeling?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like when you buy a new game, you don't want someone else to crap up your game with their save file, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like you want to be the first one to turn it on, see the opening cinema, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't want someone else to skank it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need bread.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll be my Christmas present.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll be my Christmas present.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: You got it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you make a high-pitched squealing noise?
[SPEAKER_02]: I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I thought I heard you from the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully that was me and not something, you know, some bathroom noise.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess that's it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really have anything else to share.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: RedRum6622 RedRum6622
[SPEAKER_03]: Red Rum.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love The Shining.
[SPEAKER_03]: Claims he's filed a class action lawsuit against Microsoft because of some problems he had after their recent fall system update.
[SPEAKER_03]: This was posted on the official Xbox forum.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, you can kind of take this with a grain of salt because it's an official Xbox forum post and those can be a little crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: He basically said, he filed this class action lawsuit, plaintiff versus Microsoft Corporation, a Washington corporation, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there's summary of claims, blah, blah, blah, legal mumbo jumbo.
[SPEAKER_03]: One, this is a class action against Microsoft and its affiliates for breach of contract, violation of the Washington Consumer Protection Act, and alternatively, negligence.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plaintiff brings this action on behalf of himself and all other persons who experienced hardware problems with their Microsoft 360 gaming consoles following installation of Microsoft's Fall 2006 update for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: The parties.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plaintiff, name blocked, is an individual resident of California.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plaintiff is the original purchaser and current owner of an Xbox 360 gaming console.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plaintiff brings this action individually and as a class action under Rule 23 of the Federal Rules of Civil Procedure on behalf of the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Class specified herein, blah, blah, blah, ipso facto, etc., etc.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you think, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: But he's saying that it's in violation of Washington law, yeah, he's a California resident.
[SPEAKER_03]: I... Supposedly, that's what it is, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, and the other fact that the fall update only affected... The glitch in the fall update, I guess, only affected less than 1% of the 360s out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to admit, that's still a lot, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: To which, any of them that were affected by that were immediately fixed and replaced, you know, if you called the 1-800 number.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's not like they're saying, fuck you, you're just out of 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're doing, you know, their part to fix it, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: This is just some dumbass Californian who's trying to get more money from them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boo fucking hoo, your damn 360 broke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send it in like everybody else and just get a new one.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, is it really that big a deal?
[SPEAKER_03]: ShadowNextGen in our chatroom, which by the way, hi chatroom, chat.orangeloungeradio.com if you want to join.
[SPEAKER_03]: ShadowNextGen said, dude just wants attention.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that what's going on?
[SPEAKER_03]: He does want attention.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, now you have his gamer tag, so fucking send him hate mail.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: OL Army Alex says, I can't prove my 360 having died, though my useless posts in the forums and having called MS Support twice count.
[SPEAKER_03]: In other words, how are you going to prove that your 360 was bricked?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess that's an interesting idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was another comment here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Jumpman said, My 360 died.
[SPEAKER_03]: Microsoft gave me a new one and all is right with the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: See?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it that hard?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they're aware of the problem, and they were fixing them.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, what more do you want them to do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fucking give you a blowjob or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just... This guy... You're a little bit feisty tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: He needs to... Go ahead with your class action lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who ruffled your feathers before the show tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead with your class action lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just because you have a lawsuit doesn't mean you're gonna win.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you waste all the money in the world, and I hope your 360 doesn't work afterwards.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Macman in our chat says, It's about time someone sued Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rise, my iMac.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rise from your grave.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Altered Beast reference.
[SPEAKER_03]: Altered Beast.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a good game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Altered Beast.
[SPEAKER_03]: I said I won't buy it on Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not for eight bucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not when it's not the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so more craziness, 360 related, of course, this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: On Monday, during Monday Night Football, the first kind of teaser trailer for Halo 3 was aired on TV, and of course, everybody and their brother basically took this and decided, hey, you know what, it'd be fun, let's change the music on it, just like we did with the Mad World ad for Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I thought it was a pretty cool trailer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like, it has the same impact as the first one, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first teaser during E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really psyched for the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully we'll hear something from the beta, you know, despite the fact that there's probably going to be, you know, you know, tight lip.
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear I could not sign up for the beta.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried like 50 times and I couldn't get in on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stupid site.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was funny because they had the link up for the beta before the beta thing even launched, so I signed up then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so did I. I didn't have to worry about the page.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, la-di-da to you both.
[SPEAKER_03]: But some of us have to actually work at work and can't refresh constantly on the site.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't hit refresh constantly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I read it in a blog and then I went and signed up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I also signed up for Shadowrun, so hopefully I get in on one of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, to be honest, the last one I played was Test Drive Unlimited and, you know, just the PlayStation 2 version is not as good as the 360 one.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, yeah, Halo 3 looks cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: We know it's going to be pretty good, so... Just have to wait!
[SPEAKER_04]: Until they tease us with more shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, many folks in our chatroom are talking about how they signed up for the beta.
[SPEAKER_03]: JeremyTodd1 says, I signed up for the beta, but still, there's like .9% of actually getting into the beta.
[SPEAKER_03]: Too many Halo fanboys.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's going to be more ways to get into the beta as the weeks go along.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is straight from my EA rep, because we were like, once we saw that the beta... The fuck does EA know about Halo, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not EA, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanna play some Pimps at Sea!
[SPEAKER_03]: as that was called when folks were spotting them on Xbox Live this week, testing Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: You really think we're going to have to wait all the way to next Thanksgiving for this game?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, jeez, they're advertising it like it's coming out tomorrow, it seems like, with all this hype.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think we'll have to wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to be honest, I really... They're pretty much, you know, if they're going in the beta, I mean, the game's almost done then.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they wouldn't be going into the beta if it was, you know, being put out in November.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's a perfect example right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: The beta test is in the spring because it's a beta test.
[SPEAKER_04]: It means the game's right about to come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, I think it's definitely going to be hitting the, probably the stores around the end of March, mid-March.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is some interesting stuff, though, because this,
[SPEAKER_04]: Beta sign-up was mainly for the US and North America type stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, if you're in the UK, there's going to be a few ways you can get signed up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's actually quite a list of websites, depending on which country you're in, that you can sign up.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have limited slots for the beta available.
[SPEAKER_04]: Such sites, for example, the UK, Rewired Mind, 360 Monster, BritXbox...
[SPEAKER_04]: MSXboxWorld.com, Totally360.com, and then of course Germany's got a bunch of different sites as well, PlanetXbox, etc.
[SPEAKER_04]: So definitely take a look out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's tons of links.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know IGN ran a story with some of this stuff, so if you're looking to get signed up and you don't live in the United States, then definitely check these out because they haven't finished their beta signups yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I suck at Halo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm really, really bad at Halo, but I think the game is presented just beautifully.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm getting suckered into this marketing campaign stuff a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: My hype meter is going up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm excited for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've played Halo 2 maybe twice in my life.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you going to get Halo 3?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll get Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sucker.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a first person shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure it'll be good.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a good multiplayer game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like Call of Duty 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing Call of Duty 3 and that's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's... There's a few things that... I don't understand why they're making sequels.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why they don't just improve on the original one.
[SPEAKER_04]: They always have to take content out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's really obvious stuff that should be in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I don't know, a radar or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, when the gunfire is going off, you can see where the person is on the map.
[SPEAKER_04]: Flash, where they're at.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was perfect for Call of Duty 2, so you had to be quiet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now, you can just fire away, and no one knows where the hell you are.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't really played that series.
[SPEAKER_03]: Couldn't tell you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, Loki messed up there and was talking about EA, but maybe it was a bit of a slip, because the next story is about EA, and...
[SPEAKER_03]: EA is famous for putting out things on Marketplace that basically just unlocks things you can get in the game anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Need for Speed Carbon has gotten their list on Xbox Live now of some various custom car packages.
[SPEAKER_03]: and aftermarket hoods bundle and spoilers bundle and roof scoops and a 1987 Toyota Corolla that you can now purchase for various amounts of points.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is just all crap that you can basically unlock in the game if you're patient.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least most of this, I believe.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think some of it, some of the cars, I think, are exclusive to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, a couple, I think maybe the 87 Corolla, but most of that other stuff you can get in the game if you're just patient.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly, so, yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, other news about EA, and this was kind of cool, because I like Burnout.
[SPEAKER_04]: Burnout's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're doing a special Burnout game for the PS2 and PlayStation Portable, Burnout Dominator.
[SPEAKER_04]: And from what I've gathered from the press release so far, is it's going to be similar to the Burnout Legends game on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of a culmination of the entire series so far, featuring all the tracks from 1 all the way through 3, and probably also...
[SPEAKER_04]: Burnout 4 or Revenge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looks cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of a good way to end the series on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe there might be another PSP version.
[SPEAKER_04]: Assuming this one does okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Burnout 5 is going to be coming out on PlayStation 3 and the 360s.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that will be kind of fun to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully they have one for the Wii because that would be kind of cool too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Burnout on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have Excite Truck on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would be a little weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually, one game, I don't think I mentioned this during my game of the week, but I have been playing Burnout on the 360 quite a bit this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: For no particular reason, I just wanted to play more Burnout and have custom soundtracks and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I also really suck at Burnout, so I don't just suck at Halo, I suck at Burnout too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will definitely check out the next Burnout on 360 though.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: WEEE60 Magazine
[SPEAKER_03]: it's being called an underground movement birthed by the most noble of players during the E3 2006 conference they're calling it the unadulterated voice of truth in this generation of gaming these men of valor are some of the most important people in the video game industry and their voice must be heard not just from coast to coast but from pole to pole what the who writes this crap what probably the same people that are going to be you know writing this magazine and to be honest it's probably going to suck
[SPEAKER_03]: These people really love themselves.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, anyway, you can check out www.we60.com to get more information on the magazine if you are curious about this and want to check it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, what's interesting is that there is a we60.com, but the link here leads to we60.tv, so I'm not sure what that's all about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe there's two sites.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe you should type it in and look.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking, I'm looking.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it looks like we60.tv looks like the real site.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, get this.
[SPEAKER_03]: The publisher's name is Martin Loki Alessi and his email address is loki at we60.tv Here's another magazine that'll be stealing from you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blaze in our chatroom says, Hi, I write for the magazine We60 and I fucking rule, heart.
[SPEAKER_03]: James Patrick calls this the hate on Sony magazine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those comments from me come from our chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, speaking of the Wii, Sony and Microsoft may have a Wii dilemma.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If, you know, basically this, what Jack Aldrich from Motley Fool, if what he says is correct,
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is kind of what they were targeting towards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Since the Wii is kind of aiming at that casual gamer, non-gamer, people that haven't picked up a video game system yet market, they may be able to actually grow the games market and basically, instead of just trying to target the same people that have, say, a PlayStation 2 or Xbox or GameCube, they can actually get a bunch of new gamers and
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aldrich is basically quoted as saying, Unfortunately, because most of the time and energy for the past year has been focused on providing more horsepower and fancier graphics for existing customers, the hardcore gamers demand the upgrades found in the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony has not busied themselves in developing products that appeal to non-gamers.
[SPEAKER_04]: As a result, it appears that they are now behind the curve in development of simpler to use and less expensive technologies like the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the PlayStation 3 is... That's a lot of money to drop on a system that you might not be sure about.
[SPEAKER_04]: And whereas the Wii, I think, it's pretty much pick up and go type thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially since it comes with its own game already.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, so you kind of agree with what's going on here with this story?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then again, the 360, I think...
[SPEAKER_04]: With Sony, though, I don't rule out that they're not going to try to copy more stuff that the Wii is doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I think there is already some patents registered for more devices like the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't be surprised if they try to copy everything that the Wii is doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even if they did copy it, though, do you think it would work?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think so, because even still, so you have some games that appeal to a casual gamer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, a casual gamer is not going to drop $600 for your system.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, I kind of think about, you know, I don't know, I think about the Wii and I think about all those real big brand names that Nintendo has and big franchises like Metroid and Smash Brothers and Mario and Zelda and, you know, you get my point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sony, Nintendo, Mario, Zelda, Metroid, Halo, Nintendo
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo 4, Final Fantasy XIII
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Final Fantasy XIII for the PlayStation 3, if it ends up that the Xbox 360 has sold tens of millions more systems than, say, the PlayStation 3 at the time the game's coming out, I will bet you anything that they will be putting it out on the Xbox 360 as well as the PlayStation 3, if not only on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: FootyMonster in our chatroom responded to something I said earlier, saying Sky, but on the other hand, Nintendo has no third party so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes and no.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, the third party, they don't have any really huge third party franchises the way that maybe some of the other consoles do, but third parties do seem to be sort of rallying around the Wii a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they want to put out some of their franchises on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it has gotten support, at least at their launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Red Steel was a big title, even though it was a critical hit and miss.
[SPEAKER_03]: Trauma Center was a great game, even though it wasn't
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean, at some point they're going to have to understand, okay, this system, you know, let's say a year from now when Final Fantasy XIII is coming out, say that they're not able to sell as many systems as they would have liked for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're behind by, say, 10 million systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why would I develop for a system that has less units out there, less of a chance for me to make my money back when there's a system that's cheaper to develop for and has a lot more systems out there and is capable of doing comparable graphics?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't understand why that would be pure idiocy to just develop for the one system.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why you have companies like, you know, Koei developing Fatal Inertia and their Bladestorm game for both systems now because...
[SPEAKER_04]: To be honest, they're not going to make their money back if they just put it out on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's a big problem for Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to figure out how to get these systems sold.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, get enough systems out there and give people a reason to buy this system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because right now it's just saying it has a Blu-ray player.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people say, who gives a shit about a Blu-ray player?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care right now because I'm not going to go replace my entire DVD library.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting thoughts.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you agree or disagree, send us an email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we'll get to the emails a little later in the program.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com Meanwhile, we've got to keep going through the news.
[SPEAKER_03]: And speaking of Nintendo Wii, very interesting... I don't know if this would be news or rumor.
[SPEAKER_03]: The thing is that it's coming from a foreign website.
[SPEAKER_03]: And not to discount what foreign websites might be saying, but we kind of get a little bit... Until we see a press release from Nintendo of America, we're not really sure what to think of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: But according to this website...
[SPEAKER_03]: and Siamite.de.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were reporting that you're going to be able to download Wii game demos.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can either store the demos in your flash RAM on the console or to an external SD card.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, what's kind of interesting about this is that, well, the Wii doesn't have exactly that much internal memory.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's got, what, about 512 megs?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: And by the time you start downloading all this other stuff that Nintendo's planning to put out, like the internet channel, you know, things of that nature, that stuff's going to start to fill up, especially with some of the other big virtual console releases.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: Where are these demos going to go?
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess there's the SD card, but still, it seems a little... Not quite.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, one thing to keep reading, and they're saying that there's support for USB hard drives and USB devices coming, but you have to have the latest update to be able to store stuff to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing is, though, is this update I think people are talking about isn't out yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: And from what the rumors I've been reading are,
[SPEAKER_04]: That update with the internet channel is going to support USB hard drives as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: If that's the case, then they can store them to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm sure you'll see a Nintendo hard drive of some sort that'll plug in via the USB ports on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it sounds like a little after the fact.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I really wish they would have put more storage in the system, but
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a little bit disappointing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would have thought they would have put more storage inside the actual system itself, but I mean, I guess, you know, they want to keep it cheap, so it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to keep it cheap, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Build a port for a hard drive, then.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's not what the SD card slot's for, really.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you can fit quite a bit on those little cards.
[SPEAKER_03]: and they were good enough that you can put any SD card in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, most people are saying, screw these official Nintendo SD cards.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to go buy the cheaper ones and use those.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been using the card for my camera phone to send pictures.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, I was digging through my phone the other day and I saw a picture of you at E3 Outpost.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really funny because you're leaning over the couch and going, rawr!
[SPEAKER_03]: But you can see Bobby Blackwolf in the background doing some busy work.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I send it to Bobby and I
[SPEAKER_03]: Drew like a big arrow in the paint channel.
[SPEAKER_03]: I put, who dat?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I've been having fun with the camera phone converter thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: SD card.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I put Zelda on it, just for fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though I know I can't play it on other Wii's.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just for fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I can say, I got Zelda in my pocket.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I'm lame like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so there is another story that came out very vague this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was coming from a magazine called Games TM.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, and... But wait, I gotta say that this is a very good point.
[SPEAKER_03]: James Patrick is saying 360 has no hard drive in its core bundle.
[SPEAKER_03]: True.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a good point.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they had a port for one, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: True, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: You got that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it does have some internal memory, but not that you can save games on, really.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just for, you know, updates and things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, so yeah, there is a very vague comment from the magazine.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says, something big coming to Wii Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, uh... How big is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it doesn't say.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell am I reporting as this news?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, what the fuck kind of news is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's something coming!
[SPEAKER_04]: Something big is on its way!
[SPEAKER_03]: Well...
[SPEAKER_03]: Reggie Fils-Aimé is about to make a big duty that you can download on your virtual console this Monday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen, I want my fucking Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_04]: TurboGrafx-16's great and all, but give me more Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where's my Kid Icarus?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where's my Guardian Legend?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where's my Super Castlevania IV, which they have overseas?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where's my Link to the Past, which they have overseas?
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: Alien Crush, which was a pretty badass TurboGrafx-16 game
[SPEAKER_03]: Supposed to be every Monday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but do we have to be getting TurboGrafx and Genesis every Monday?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, don't get me wrong, there's some good games there, but there's things I want more on the NES.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody in chat was saying Gunstar Heroes is rumored for this Monday.
[SPEAKER_03]: I imagine the four games we're going to get probably are just going to be games that are available elsewhere, but who knows which ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I tried using my credit card to put more points on my virtual console account, and it didn't work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shadow Charlie is okay with more Genesis as long as it's Streets of Rage.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Shadow Next Gen agrees with me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Link to the Past on Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shadow Next Gen also wants Super Metroid on VC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dark Knight wants Pilotwings.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are all good stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Proper T wants Super C. That was a pretty cool game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Super C, I think, is on GameTap.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think as well, with the Contra.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you can always check it out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want the Super Nintendo Contra, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: That wasn't called Super C, was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was something else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Super Contra, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was pretty cool, because it had, like, the Mode 7 levels.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So much like Immersion did with the Sony PlayStation 2 DualShock controller, another company has claimed that they want to take Nintendo the court over the Wii Remote because they say they have a patent for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a very similar kind of lawsuit, a company called Interlink, who has revealed that they have a device that's very similar to the Wii Remote that they've patented.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess they probably haven't created said device, but they have a patent for it anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: And basically, going to try to get some money out of Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Different company, same song, it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I hate when these companies do this stuff, because they totally create patents for stuff that they don't imagine that they're not going to even use, just because they probably hear that some company is making something similar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what if this did legitimately already exist?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it looks like crap anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be honest, looking at this right now, it looks like a TV remote.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all it looks like.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like it has an infrared emitter inside the actual device.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, controller, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then there's a receiver that would be an infrared receiver.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: If anything, I would say that the people that created a TV remote would be able to sue over the Wii remote.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there's enough different with the two devices that they probably won't win.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, now, it says here that, I'm reading through the complaint here, and this patent was filed by the other company on February 1st, 2005, long before anyone knew anything about the Wii, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: True, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so it was filed 2005.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't mean, though, that they weren't... I'd want to see when the patent was filed for the Wii remote.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because apparently the Wii has been in production for a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_03]: You use it in operating the computer from far away.
[SPEAKER_03]: They made it for the computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's probably to...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like one of those things that will let you run the PowerPoint shows from afar.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have one at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just a TV remote, though, basically.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's basically what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, isn't that what a TV remote is?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or a DVD remote, for example.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be basically what it is, because I use the PlayStation 2 DVD remote to navigate menus and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very similar to this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It uses IR as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just think that they're too different.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this is very similar to, say, a TV remote than it is, you know, the Wii remote.
[SPEAKER_03]: Raven's Dolphin says the Wii trigger goes through Bluetooth, not infrared.
[SPEAKER_03]: They will lose.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, these lawsuits that seemingly come out of nowhere when something gets popular, they make us angsty, and we get really angry about this stuff because we don't want anyone taking away our Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that means it's about time for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Since DarkSakura is not here tonight, Loki, you're going to have to start us off.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to DarkSakura for not being here.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to the ferret.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to say FU to RPM Racing because they're...
[SPEAKER_04]: Number 11 car had fucked up traction on it, so it kept slamming into the wall and I actually had to get pitted one lap because they black flagged me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you to Rob for the fact that he keeps playing initial D music.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is pretty good FU music, I like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, I would have to say... Gosh, I don't have a lot to be angsty about today.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say an FU to the rain and it being so cold out recently an FU to the fact that I'm spoiled by California weather so what's cold right now probably isn't really cold to other people so FU to the weather lately because it's been kind of crappy that's it, Miklatov left the room because he has a bad headache I guess DDR gave him a headache so Miklatov's not here to put in his FU so FU to headaches and Advil it doesn't work
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, let's go into our next story, which is about the Spike TV VGAs, if I'm not mistaking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you... Oh, these haven't aired yet, have they?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they're going to air.
[SPEAKER_03]: It taped on Friday, but it's going to air on, what, the 13th?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well...
[SPEAKER_03]: Spoiler alert!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, spoiler alert.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to ruin it for you right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's who won at the Spike TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: Game of the Year was Elder Scrolls IV Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best Individual Sports Game was Tony Hawk Project 8.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best Team Sports Game was NBA 2K7.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best Song was Lights and Sounds by Yellowcard and Burnout Revenge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Boo!
[SPEAKER_03]: Why boo?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yellowcard sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be honest, I like Today by Junkie XL way better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best Soundtrack was Guitar Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Studio of the Year was Epic Games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they give out a bunch of awards to actors and actresses.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like they gave Best Supporting Male to James Gandolfini in The Sopranos.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best Supporting Female, Rachel Lee Cook.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gamer's Choice for Breakthrough Performance, Rosario Dawson, and an award to Johnny Depp, just because he's Johnny Depp, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gamer's Choice is the guys that they gave to him.
[SPEAKER_03]: They just wanted Johnny Depp to show up at the award show.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know this is true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bastard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, we actually have someone on the line with us who actually attended the event and is going to tell us a little bit more about what happened on the inside.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Orange Lounge Radio's very own DJ Tyrant from STFU.
[SPEAKER_03]: You there, DJ Tyrant?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, how's it going, guys?
[SPEAKER_03]: Good, how are you doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_00]: My voice is a little shot from yelling at the awards.
[SPEAKER_03]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell us about how you got into the VGAs and how it all went down.
[SPEAKER_00]: I got an email from X-Fire and they had a thousand tickets to give out.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I just showed up and they gave them to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you just went right in and got to see all this stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: Were there a lot of celebrities there?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, there were just a ton of celebrities.
[SPEAKER_00]: I got to meet the guys who do Mega64.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I met them at an E3 a couple years ago, and they seemed really offended I didn't know who they were.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I know who they are now, but at the time they seemed really offended that I didn't know who they were.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: But somebody explained it to me afterwards.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, oh, that Tetris video.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyway, were they cool to you?
[SPEAKER_00]: They seemed pretty cool, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: They were...
[SPEAKER_00]: They were pretty nice to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about any A-list celebrities?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Mega64, with all due respect, is kind of like D, E-list, internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where do internet celebrities go?
[SPEAKER_03]: On the E-list somewhere?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you meet Samuel L. Jackson or Tom Cruise?
[SPEAKER_00]: I didn't get to meet any of the A-list celebrities.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So why is your voice so hoarse?
[SPEAKER_03]: Were you screaming and yelling and cheering at all these people?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, I was more booing at them than anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you were booing all the celebrities as they came out on stage?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, as RavensDolphin1 says in chat, I did boo 50 Cent when he came to present an award.
[SPEAKER_00]: What did you say to 50 Cent?
[SPEAKER_00]: I said, your game sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I mean, it does.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did anybody yell back, or could people actually hear you, or was it the place so huge they couldn't really hear you?
[SPEAKER_00]: I think some people in the first floor heard me and they laughed.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you were the heckler guy, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I was.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm reading a little bit of back and forth that's going on on Destructoid.com because you made a comment.
[SPEAKER_03]: You were talking about, in their comments, you were talking about how you yelled at 50 Cent, your game sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: His game did suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, DJ Tarrant wrote, booing yellow card saying, get off the stage, asshole.
[SPEAKER_03]: and yelled at Sarah Silverman, you're not funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, I think this stuff is kind of funny, but then somebody replied to you, dude, you were a total ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: I sat three rows behind you.
[SPEAKER_03]: You were wearing a blue X-Fire shirt.
[SPEAKER_03]: You were a huge asshole throughout the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Comments?
[SPEAKER_03]: Were you a big asshole throughout the show?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, I was.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll admit that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't see how anyone can take it seriously, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: The show, it's terrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you're right.
[SPEAKER_03]: All these celebrities are just coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: How many of them do you think actually play games?
[SPEAKER_03]: How much of 50 Cent's game do you think he actually played?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think these celebrities just show up to these events because they know it's something they can add to their resume and say that they were on TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_00]: Although the guy who was Superman in Superman Returns, I can't think of his name.
[SPEAKER_00]: Brandon Routh.
[SPEAKER_00]: He was obviously a big Warcraft fan when he introduced the World of Warcraft Burning Crusade video.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did he come out there and go, Leroy Jenkins?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did he do that?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, but he said he had played Warcraft 2 and mentioned a lot about how he liked Blizzard, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: It was good to see at least one gamer out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I cheered for Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_00]: I haven't played it, but they definitely deserve the respect.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a good game if you're into first-person shooters.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a good game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, anything else you want to say about the award show?
[SPEAKER_00]: Watch it and see if you can hear me during it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nah, they'll have muted you or bleeped you out.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why they don't air it live.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they're too chicken shit to air it live.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because these celebrities' egos would be damaged if, heaven forbid, they could pick up in the background some a-hole in the bleachers, no offense, going, your game sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they're doing that post-editing right now, bleeping you out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And probably blurring your seat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or maybe they'll work hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I made them work hard.
[SPEAKER_00]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's all that matters.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, and BlackWolf in our chatroom says the crowd noise will be fake the entire show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Most likely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was there a lot of thunderous applause?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did they have the lights that say, applause, applause?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or did they bring a girl on stage with big chi-chis?
[SPEAKER_00]: They had a lot of seat fillers, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of seat fillers?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like the people they pay to go fill in the celebrity seats when they go to the bathroom?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, they were all in the front row, it seemed like.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, thank you for the insider perspective.
[SPEAKER_03]: And hey, try to go to some more awards.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say, hey, if they do a G4ia this year, you definitely have to get in there and do some heckling, all right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll see what I can do.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks so much.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'll plug your show so the kids know to listen.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, I'll be giving away one of those Castlevania bonus sets this week on SCFU Thursday at 7 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's 7 Pacific, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seven Pacific.
[SPEAKER_03]: Indeed, it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good one, DJ Tyrant, and we'll see you on Thursday for STFU.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks a lot, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was our very own DJ Tyrant giving us the scoop on what went on at the Video Game Awards and how he was a big jerk.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't take celebrities seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like if Britney Spears had come out, I would have yelled, you know, where's your panties?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, because of all the pictures recently.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, forget it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anywho, back to some news.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I'm starting to think we should really curb from now on any stories that are from an analyst.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: The rumors come back up again from an analyst saying that Apple is entering the console market and they're
[SPEAKER_04]: Take on it is basically, we think that the video game market represents a distinct possibility for Apple, especially considering that it recently announced that the availability of video games for its iPod through the iTunes Store.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a reason!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's stupid!
[SPEAKER_03]: That's like, I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every fucking week on this program for the past almost five years, what do we sit here and do?
[SPEAKER_03]: We sit here and analyze the game scene.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what we do.
[SPEAKER_03]: And nobody's ever thrown money at us.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: These financial... If I got a degree, would they throw money at us in whatever these people have a degree in?
[SPEAKER_03]: Market analysis or whatever?
[SPEAKER_03]: And they don't even have to be... They're like the goddamn weatherman of the fucking...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's what Apple is going to create next.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to create their own line of sex toys.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to have the Apple i-vibe or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, that is my analyst's take on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because people like having fun, therefore they like being pleasured.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Feel the bass through the i-vibe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fireboma calls it the i-braider.
[SPEAKER_04]: Eyebraider, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, this is how ridiculous these stories are.
[SPEAKER_04]: I, for one, I will not be talking about any analyst crap from now on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, do you think it's feasible, though, that Apple could do a console?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Apple's going to do that in reverse.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they're going to put this Trojan horse in as a movie device, and then, hey, it'll play Zuma and Bejeweled, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not going to be able to run much anything else.
[SPEAKER_04]: And have you tried playing any of these games on the Apple iPod?
[SPEAKER_04]: They suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, I hate to sound like the fucking Apple hater, but the Apple, I mean, their line of computers...
[SPEAKER_04]: I will admit, I love my Mac.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love my little Mac laptop.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I consider myself bi when it comes to computers.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Apple sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like PCs other days.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't exactly... When I think, hey, I'm going to go play some games on the computer, I don't exactly think about my Apple computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's nothing wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they could come out with a game console.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just... I don't... I think it's too late in the game to come out with a new console right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think if they did it, it would fail.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be like, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: The Phantom, or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Pippin?
[SPEAKER_03]: BlackWolf says, apparently Tetris works really well on an iPod.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, I don't read.
[SPEAKER_03]: My iPod was the old-ass black and white one, and it broke.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm hoping I get gift certificates this Christmas so I can get myself a new one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Great, but I heard Bejeweled blew ass, though, and that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So great.
[SPEAKER_03]: And at the end of the day, it's bejeweled again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you know, you can't take this seriously as a console unless there's new things to breathe life into these consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I will admit, there was one time, you know, with Apple II, that they had good games on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you know, you had some pretty good stuff on the Apple II, but that day is long past.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: Little Britain
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a show that's run in the UK and also on BBC America.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's on BBC America here.
[SPEAKER_03]: DVDs do very well here, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually a parody of Life in Britain, and they've got a bunch of different characters in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It almost reminds me a little bit of a modern take on, say...
[SPEAKER_04]: Monty Python
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty funny looking from what I've seen so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell are you going to do with the Little Britain game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't get me wrong, I love the show, but I can't really picture it as a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, are you going to go around yelling, I am the only game in the village?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that was funny that you mentioned that, because actually that was one of the advertisements on the story.
[SPEAKER_04]: They said, you know, I am the only game in the village.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, there's actually one, though, one scene that I saw where you're riding around...
[SPEAKER_04]: Trying to basically scare away the other gays that are in the village so that you can become the only gay in the village.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically going to be a collection of minigames.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is there going to be a music game for rap for the one girl that goes, No, but yeah, but yeah, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know her that tells all the stories and stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, anyways, so the game is going to be, like I said, a collection of minigames presented in the format of an episode of the TV show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And since players can enter...
[SPEAKER_04]: You can get interactive with their favorite sketch show characters in a series of eight minigames featuring Lou and Andy, Vicky Pillard, Mr. Man, Emily and Florence,
[SPEAKER_04]: Majore Dawes, Daphne Thomas, Judy and Maggie, and Letty.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says, each minigame plays like a sketch from the TV show.
[SPEAKER_04]: To win the game, players must progress through all the sketches to the end of the show, or the credits will roll.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, um,
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, they have... And that's coming out here in America, too?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's only in the UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn, because you won't even be able to import that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, if it's PC, you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: PC, PlayStation Portable.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can get the PlayStation Portable version.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: The PlayStation 2 and PC versions will be out January 22nd.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then May for the PSP version.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we can import the PSP one, which might be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's his name from Buffy in it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anthony Stewart Head?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that his name?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is he in it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they've got examples here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's a screenshot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really great radio here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's one of the minigames where you're smashing objects.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Smashing frogs, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure it'll be a good game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anywho, so, kind of moving on to a completely different topic here.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we know that it has an HD DVD drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be, people are using it to copy HD DVDs to rip them to their PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the HD DVD drive uses a USB port and a connection, or USB connection, and can be, you know, you can do the
[SPEAKER_04]: 1080p connection over component cables, you can actually use a video capture card to capture that and then dump it, of course, to your hard drive for backup purposes only, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, you know, the PlayStation 3, I think, does the same thing with Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But later on, I suppose, when they're going to require the HDMI cables, that might be able to circumvent some of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But right now,
[SPEAKER_04]: You can dump them via that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sure this has the movie industry so excited.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's their own fault that they couldn't figure out a way to encrypt it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still don't know what movies I really want on HD DVD.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess I'm still waiting for the format to kind of take off.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the thing, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, there was a movie that I wanted, but it's only on Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's annoying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you're going to get a PlayStation 3 eventually, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got berated by the wife because she's like, I thought you said you weren't going to get one of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, but you just got excited about the, you know, Motorstorm games, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, moving on to some ads that were about the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were run by Circuit City, and Joystick picked up some of these Circuit City ads, running it under the headline, Circuit City Faults or Stupid Advertising?
[SPEAKER_03]: You decide.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's, again, on Joystick with a Q dot com, which is interesting because they talk about some things from the catalog that,
[SPEAKER_03]: PlayStation 3, Ready to Rumble, It's Hot
[SPEAKER_03]: Even if you have a wired controller, the Xbox Guide button glows green with what player you're in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, of course, in the picture, obviously it's posed.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they're not really playing the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: This isn't too hard to figure out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, of course, the anal gamer will notice that the lights are off, and so, in fact, the controllers are not plugged in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you see the one with the Wii, though, on there?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I missed that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a picture with the Wii saying that the Wii can be played without a TV because it has a built-in projector into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't that one of the old rumors about the Wii?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was one of the old rumors, but that's how... Somebody did not get the memo.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really bad, but... How does this...
[SPEAKER_04]: Get through.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, how does this get by without people noticing this stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: So seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because there's no gamers that work at Circuit City's proofreading department?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, here it is right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually, take a look at the story again.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says the USB port lets you plug in the game system to a project and play, or to project and play on awesome 11 and a half foot widescreen.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: That might actually be for the 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever, it's still wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, yeah, it says the turned-off Xbox 360 controller is playing Madden on a projection television supposedly attached to the Xbox 360 by a USB cable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously all that stuff's posed, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: People read a little bit too much into that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you may not be able to actually...
[SPEAKER_04]: have a projector built into your Xbox 360 or Wii but you can make your own Power Glove and that's what someone's done actually they have modified a Power Glove to put a black Wii remote on it and they've captured the hearts of geeks everywhere for about five minutes until the next video comes out with something else even more shinier I don't know it's
[SPEAKER_04]: It's stupid, but I'm sure someone was bound to do it at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm sure someone has commented on this video, It's so bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me see how many posts it took to say it's so bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I am actually surprised.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Eight posts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eight posts.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of things that are so bad, this is so bad it's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean like so awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, bad meaning good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get this.
[SPEAKER_03]: The DS Lite has some new decals being made for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can turn your DS Lite, you know, you can use the decals to change your DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're being sold by Sanrio.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can make your DS Lite...
[SPEAKER_03]: The Hello Kitty DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, how fun is that going to be?
[SPEAKER_03]: For the low, low price of 680 yen, that's about $5.90, you can get this from Sanrio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, so awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they look best, by the way, on the pink DSs, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Goody.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just more reason for me to get a pink DS Lite this Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, those pink DS Lites are going for a lot of money, actually, on eBay from what I've been hearing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, my customers... Aren't they still in stock in most places?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: eBay people are selling out of them quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, apparently Canada is blinging up your DS stylus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Future Shop, you can actually purchase a 18 karat gold stylus for the low, low price of $19.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: And wow, Neil, that would really suck if you lost that one because...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well something else I'm sure people are going to be paying a lot of money for.
[SPEAKER_03]: Depends if they decide to charge for this or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there is a huge, rabid fan base around the television show that used to be on the air called Firefly.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you might remember they made it into a movie as well called Serenity.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't really follow the TV show, but Extifer, my roommate, is a huge weed and whore.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, Buffy and Angel and all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I got dragged to see Serenity the day it opened, and it wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I did get an HD DVD player, I would buy Serenity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Serenity would be a good movie for HD, or any sci-fi movie, really, would be a good HD movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's not what I'm reporting on.
[SPEAKER_03]: What I'm talking about is that this has been licensed for an MMO.
[SPEAKER_03]: Multiverse has struck a deal with Fox to put the Firefly property into the MMO ring.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, keep in mind, this is very early on.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no development team yet put together like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they want to do a type of Star Wars Galaxy type game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they say they will make it unique and fun and interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it probably won't happen until 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that could be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's certainly a huge fan base out there that will at least check this out for Curiosity Factor alone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wouldn't you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd even check it out, even though I don't know much about the series.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, you know, Space Cowboys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely unique.
[SPEAKER_04]: And who doesn't love cowboys in outer space?
[SPEAKER_04]: You gotta love the fact that the show's been cancelled.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, and the series has been cancelled and it's not coming back.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not going to be a sequel to Serenity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but isn't that what happened to Star Trek?
[SPEAKER_03]: The original Star Trek got cancelled pretty early on and then they made a movie and it became huge.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then again, Serenity unfortunately did not quite have a huge box office success.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should have called it Firefly the movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eh, oh well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, that's our last story for this Part A of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: But don't go anywhere because we're going to be back very soon for Orange Lounge Radio Part B. And if you are a podcast listener, you just have to wait a couple days for Orange Lounge Radio Part B. We'll see you then when that's out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.