[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_14]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_14]: And now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio here on this special New Year's Eve special leading on into the year 2007.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're bringing on some special guests from all across the independent gaming voice community.
[SPEAKER_15]: We have some bloggers and other podcasters and folks who do other live shows and even dipping in and having some guests from the sci-fi and geek world coming in as well.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that's where our next guest comes from, yes, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely comes from geek world.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is Travis from Travis Donovan Live.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thunderstorm Warning, Tornado Watch
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh fun!
[SPEAKER_10]: And no power.
[SPEAKER_15]: No video games for you then today.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, and I just got my Wii today.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh no, how did you finally get a Wii?
[SPEAKER_10]: Went to EB Games of all places, and just randomly, after stopping at GameStop, and asked GameStop first, and they said no, they had PS3's in, but not Wiis.
[SPEAKER_10]: Went to EB Games and said, hey, do you got a Wii?
[SPEAKER_10]: And the guy just looked at me and went, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I said, hook me up, my brother.
[SPEAKER_15]: Random stroke of luck.
[SPEAKER_15]: What games did you get for your Wii?
[SPEAKER_10]: I got Rayman, the rabid one that everybody hates.
[SPEAKER_15]: We've heard some pretty good things about that from some of the other guests we've had on the program.
[SPEAKER_10]: I figure if everyone else hates it, then I'm going to love it.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, then we definitely want to know your opinion on some of the best and worst in 2006, because if your opinion is the opposite, then that should be kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we have ten boxes left.
[SPEAKER_15]: Please pick a box, one through ten.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, we'll go with lucky number seven.
[SPEAKER_15]: Lucky number seven, here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's open the box.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the category we want to know your opinion on is best game to play online.
[SPEAKER_15]: What was the best game to play online in 2006?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's going to be difficult, seeing how I didn't play a lot online and it would have been 360 only.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I'm going to take a book.
[SPEAKER_10]: or a page from my family here and I'm going to go with what they play online all the time and it has to unfortunately be the soul-stealing Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ah, Final Fantasy 11 then on 360, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, no, on PC.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, they're still playing PC.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, we're going to have to say the 360 version because the PC one came out a couple years ago but the 360 one was this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, well then let me change my damn answer.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, all right, all right.
[SPEAKER_10]: What then?
[SPEAKER_10]: Best game this year to play online?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, what the hell, Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gears of War!
[SPEAKER_15]: Very popular choice.
[SPEAKER_15]: Any particular reason why you chose Gears of War?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have it for the 360 and I played it online like twice and it was fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have you played the co-op mode?
[SPEAKER_15]: I hear a lot of people, I think the reason why a lot of folks really enjoy Gears of War is because of the co-op.
[SPEAKER_15]: And not a lot of games encourage co-op.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would play with you, Travis, at some point.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, that's just kinky and wrong.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, then, fine.
[SPEAKER_15]: The choice stands as it is, and I'm not going to play online with you.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, well, then how about this news topic?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd be very curious to know your opinion on this.
[SPEAKER_15]: Earlier this year, there was a TV station that used to represent gamers a long time ago that changed their slogan earlier this year, and that was G4 Television, and their new slogan as of earlier this year was, We Get Guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: You ever watch a G4 TV, Travis?
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately, I have accidentally stumbled upon it because on my channel listing it's awfully close to BBC America and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I accidentally tuned into it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you ever watch G4 Tech TV back in the day, right when they first merged?
[SPEAKER_10]: In its heyday, well actually before it merged, Tech TV was the bomb.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was the shiznit, as they say in the ghetto.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: for geeks and gamers out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then when G4 took over, it was fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was some bumps in the road, but unfortunately now it is what I like to call a partial birth abortion of a network.
[SPEAKER_15]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_15]: What went wrong?
[SPEAKER_10]: They have no idea or concept of how to program a network around gaming and technology.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're too ratings conscious, and unfortunately they have a talent pool
[SPEAKER_10]: which makes a West Virginia gene pool look like genius status.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you think that there's a need out there for a video game network or do you think online kind of fills that void?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, the internet of course fills it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It fills it extremely well.
[SPEAKER_10]: There are tons of sources whether you've got your GameSpot, your IGN, your 1UP, your Joystick, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: and print-wise, magazine-wise, you also have a plethora of magazines you can buy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Television-wise, it would be good to have somebody or a network that wasn't jockeyed one way or the other by advertising dollars to sort of twist their slant on gaming in the industry because I'll tell you right now, you can tell on G4 that the almighty dollar really does affect some of what they say on that network
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not a big fan of that network.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think what they've done to my holy grail, which is Star Trek, is ridiculous and stupid with that whole 2.0 shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pardon my English.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now they're showing cops.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was flipping the other day and I saw cops on there.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was like, wow, it's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why do you think then people continue to, in the gaming world, care about G4?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because, you know, I've noticed that once in a while game blogs and game sites run these stories on G4 television, and I can't help but personally wonder, and I know we've talked about it on our own program previously, why do people continue to care?
[SPEAKER_15]: If G4 is not giving the gamer world what we need, why is the gamer world continuing to give them free press?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, so long as you have any type of mass media outlet,
[SPEAKER_10]: everybody is going to try to take advantage of as many of those outlets as possible and G4 is one of those.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have the talking heads on that network which are there to shield their products and that's why people still care unfortunately about G4.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do find G4, I give G4 credit to be one of the very few Americanized networks
[SPEAKER_10]: that actually employ a she-male, Morgan Webb, and a spasmodic schizo with severe bipolar disorder, Adam Sessler, and the rest of their lineup.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I love how they steal British interactive television game shows and claim them as their own, i.e.
[SPEAKER_10]: that late night video game or that game call-in show that they do.
[SPEAKER_10]: which is a steal from a British show that they do over there.
[SPEAKER_10]: So long as they're on the air, game companies will use them as an outlet to show their products because the attention span of the American public is that of a fruit fly.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: They'll get their media anywhere they can.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, we here at Orange Lounge have given them too much air time as it is, so we need to move right along to the next topic.
[SPEAKER_15]: But thank you for your input.
[SPEAKER_15]: What did you think was the best video game of 2006?
[SPEAKER_15]: We're tallying it up tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: The best game of 06, again, I'm going to fall back on, is Gears of War, just because it took the first-person shooter.
[SPEAKER_10]: It really didn't ratchet up a notch as far as the style of gameplay.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's still the same run, duck, cover, shoot, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: The graphics quality, I think it's the first true game of 06 to take advantage of the next-gen console.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's going to be interesting to see how this plays out with the other next-gen console, the PS3.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't throw the Wii into the category of next-gen because graphics-wise it's the same, but the 360 and the PS3, you're finally seeing the developers get a hold of this, and I'm looking forward to 07.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think Wii tries to classify itself more as a new-gen than next-gen, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: The Wii is definitely revolutionary and it is going to be fun to play and it's going to be innovative and it's going to be fun to see how publishers take advantage of that as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: What was your worst game of 2006?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't have enough time on the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to go from a standpoint of a letdown as far as genre is concerned.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would have to be Star Trek Legacy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, wow, why Star Trek Legacy?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not so much, the story, the single player story missions are incredible, and they're fun, and the graphics are great, and it's great that you have the voice of all the captains, and that part's wonderful.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's killing this game from being as hot as Bridge Commander was on the PC, and as I went into it on my show, is...
[SPEAKER_10]: The multiplayer on this game literally sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it sucks big floppy donkey dongs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Half the time you can't even get into a game.
[SPEAKER_10]: You get kicked out.
[SPEAKER_10]: The connections are horrid.
[SPEAKER_10]: The lag times are not bad when you finally get a game.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the problem is getting a game.
[SPEAKER_15]: You think it's possible maybe the developers will push a patch out that hopefully will fix some of it?
[SPEAKER_10]: They were quick to push a patch out for the multiplayer on the PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: They literally had that out the same day it was released on PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: Legacy was a port from 360 to PC, so that was because they were having problems with GameSpy.
[SPEAKER_10]: GameSpy is well known for having compatibility issues with games anyways.
[SPEAKER_10]: If there was going to be a patch, it would have been out by now.
[SPEAKER_10]: and I don't think.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think Bethesda Soft is just taking CBS Viacom's money and saying, here, we gave you three games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for the money.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good luck and thanks for all the fish kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I know Star Trek is something near and dear to your heart because you do the sci-fi program here on Orange Launch Radio on Saturday night, yes?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not so much sci-fi anymore, but yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: What exactly can the fans expect to hear when they tune into Travis Donovan Live on Saturdays?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's great, being the station manager and such as you are, keeping up to speed with the shows, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do throw a little sci-fi and geek into it, of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm now getting to the point where I'm so pissed off with the morons in television and the morons on the Internet that
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm the angry, pissed off, motherfucking, hetero, white, middle-aged man.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm not so much middle-aged, but for your listeners, I would be considered middle-aged.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's sort of what Travis Donovan Live is all about now.
[SPEAKER_10]: The tagline is putting reality back in its place.
[SPEAKER_15]: What are you looking forward to most in the geek world in 2007?
[SPEAKER_15]: Not necessarily games, but anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm interested to see how well Vista plays out when Windows Vista releases.
[SPEAKER_10]: How well of an operating system that's going to be?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is it just going to be fancy new graphics and user interface, or is it actually going to be something substantial?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because nowadays it's so easy to steal information and corrupt data via the Internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just wondering how much more secure Vista is going to be.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's already been hacked from what I understand, so that's not a good sign.
[SPEAKER_10]: The rest of technology, I mean, that's up in the air right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Things are moving at such a pace.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's always fun to see what the Japanese bring out.
[SPEAKER_10]: They bring out robots to help the invalid.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm hoping soon they'll bring out a robot that'll help wipe my butt because, again, I'm a lazy American and I don't like to do that.
[SPEAKER_15]: On that note, I think we should probably say goodbye.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks so much for being on the program tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's end the call on the brown note.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_15]: or as we've called it on the show previously, the Brown Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_15]: We shall have to go back to the archives for that one.
[SPEAKER_15]: TravisDonovanLive.com for more information on the program.
[SPEAKER_15]: Saturday nights here on Orange Lounge Radio and podcast on your own site too, yes?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my God, you remembered the URL.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's my podcast via my site.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm also on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Search him out, Travis Donovan.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks so much for being here and best of luck to you in 07.
[SPEAKER_10]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully, you know, it'll be great.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, for those that don't know, you know, if you go way, way back in the broadcast history of myself and DarkSakura, we actually started on a show with Travis.
[SPEAKER_15]: He did a long time ago called Understation Alive, and he's still pretty funny after all these many, many, many years.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was the fill-in person slash most frequent guest.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, and I was the...
[SPEAKER_15]: I remember making the calls to pay phones in Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_15]: How did the payphone calls go?
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone answered one.
[SPEAKER_15]: We did get one.
[SPEAKER_15]: From what I remember, we had somebody answer it once, and we actually had a conversation with them.
[SPEAKER_15]: But then we called back, and the call mysteriously dropped.
[SPEAKER_15]: And we were theorizing that the Disneyland police had tapped our conversation and dropped the calls.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because you know Disneyland's got some scary security.
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole point of it, though, is that they are presenting...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's why all the stuff that happens around the park is called behind the scenes for a reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: The employees are cast members.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everything there is sent to present something, and a phone call, they don't want to get in the way of that.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, speaking of craziness, our next guests are crazy, but in a good way.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Franz Sheeran and Ron Wickman from Destructoid.com.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, we are joined here now on our Orange Lounge Radio year-end special with one, two, three people joining us from the website destructoid.com.
[SPEAKER_15]: Say hello, everybody, to Franz.
[SPEAKER_15]: Franz, you there?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is Franz from Destructoid.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, how you doing, Franz?
[SPEAKER_06]: Man of many words.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the voice you hear there is Ron, Graybush Workman.
[SPEAKER_06]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Graybush in the house.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for having us.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not a problem.
[SPEAKER_15]: And also joining us, say hello to Shir.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up, guys?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I don't have anything to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm boring.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_15]: We often don't either, but we somehow fill three hours every week.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm so fucking laid back.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, now you guys all, you know, you blog for the Destructoid.com website, but do you guys participate in their podcast as well, Podtoid?
[SPEAKER_15]: Occasionally.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, sometimes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Usually, Ron.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm usually, I'm turning into the comic relief for the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: They beg, but I'm like, you know, I have things to do, leave me alone.
[SPEAKER_15]: How many bloggers do they have over at Destructoid?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because when I'm looking at the list of people, it looks like I'm looking at a picture of The Last Supper or something.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's so many people.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are we looking at?
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably mid to high 30s.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, in January, we're maybe looking at over 40, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: A couple more people.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got well over a dozen people that post daily and consistently and stuff like that, and that's kind of our thing, what we're shooting for, is to update information, have
[SPEAKER_06]: Gregory, we made a joke last night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, we rarely own a website that posts at 3.30 in the morning every day.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got people that are up all night messing around with stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: So you guys really are an army of robots when you say that.
[SPEAKER_15]: It seems that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're turning into the detoyed army, I guess.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, well, we want to pick the army's brain here a little bit on some of the gaming topics in a little game we call Year in Review 2006.
[SPEAKER_15]: And so we have nine boxes left, because people have been plucking all the other boxes.
[SPEAKER_15]: And Franz, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which box do you want to open up?
[SPEAKER_15]: Box 1 through 9, any one of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: If there's a PS3 in it, I'm returning it, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll go with 9.
[SPEAKER_15]: Box 9, let's take a look.
[SPEAKER_15]: We want to know, Franz, what did you think was the most creative game in 2006?
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Most creative game in 2006.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Viva Pinata.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, no, Ron's actually got a point.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's one of the two games we played.
[SPEAKER_05]: Viva Pinata.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you get a game where you re-rate the engine to make it look more kiddy, and it's mating animals that dance around for the whole game, that's pretty damn creative.
[SPEAKER_15]: You said there was two going around in your mind?
[SPEAKER_15]: What was the other one out of curiosity?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, that was just the only game around Morkman's Blotting this year.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is Viva Pinata really for kids, though?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I know when I played it, I was like, if I was seven, my controller would be through the window right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be tough for kids to understand it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like Pokemon in the sense that anybody can enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I played Pokemon, and that was a great game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, and this is stuff in Viva Pinata that my Greybush ass couldn't figure out how to do, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was getting frustrated with these vinyadas.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was looking stuff up on the internet and people were feeling bad for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, here, I'll send you a vinyada.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm like, no, I want these damn mice to have sex.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Ron's in fucking Mensa.
[SPEAKER_15]: My vinyadas kept beating each other.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was like Lord of the Wise.
[SPEAKER_15]: Horrible.
[SPEAKER_15]: Those kept getting sick.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, Viva Piñata, most creative game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Franz, the news topic we want to know your opinion on, and, you know, I don't know if you have any friends over in the UK, but it seems like one of the recurring themes in 2006 is that our buddies in the UK keep getting the shaft.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's been the story of their lives.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's definitely true.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why does Britain keep getting fucked over when it comes to release dates or, you know, system launches, prices of games?
[SPEAKER_15]: Why do they keep getting picked on?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think, yeah, I think it's a shame.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, if Microsoft would jump on that and divvy up their sales a lot more, I think that would give them a lot more price.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, didn't the Wii just come out?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, the Wii couldn't even give them enough, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: They could barely do pre-sales over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it came out like two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay, and they're waiting until March, I guess, to do the PlayStation over there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they're not even going to get a taste of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, hell, half the United States isn't getting a taste of it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, it's important to note, too, that they ban games that's kind of
[SPEAKER_05]: PS2 PS2 PS2
[SPEAKER_15]: It was decent.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just, I think the problem with Ruler Rose, it was a full-priced title, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_15]: It was like a $49.99 they wanted for it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, so, yeah, that was the biggest problem is because PS2, you know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, that's just Atlus because they're retarded and still think they can get $49.99 for a PlayStation 2 game at the end of its life cycle, so.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, you know, I guess if Square can get $59 for a collector's edition of Final Fantasy XII, which has nothing special.
[SPEAKER_15]: by the way, nothing special.
[SPEAKER_15]: Final Fantasy XII, I love this in Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_15]: It is a sexy game, I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, and it's actually GameStop that thinks they can get $59.99 for the special edition of Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, they got it from me, but that's because I'm a corporate whore.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shira, it's your turn, why don't you pick a box?
[SPEAKER_15]: Now we have one through eight left.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll pick number three.
[SPEAKER_15]: Box number three, let's open it up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Box number three.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, this is a good one.
[SPEAKER_15]: What do you believe was the most disappointing game of 2006?
[SPEAKER_15]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm going to get a lot of flack for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Legend of Zelda Twilight Princess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why Zelda Twilight Princess?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, because Zelda is the type of game where everyone's like, this game is better than unicorns fucking pixies.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not so great, and that would be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about you guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's exactly how I described it on the last episode of Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like... Everyone's like, this is going to be the greatest game ever, and then I played it and I was like, eh, this isn't the greatest game ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: My only little comment for that is it came out two years late.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's part of the thing that makes it a disappointment.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is that the problem for you?
[SPEAKER_15]: Is that this is essentially a GameCube game with Wii controls?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no, that's not the problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just that I don't really like Zelda that much.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like games in that genre.
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked Ocarina of Time was okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked Majora's Mask like Wind Waker.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this one is just like boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no real character depth and I was just like, yeah, fuck this.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anybody else want to chime in on what they think the most disappointing game of 2006 was?
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: Rare didn't come out, did they?
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't they just release Viva Pinata?
[SPEAKER_06]: Viva Pinata?
[SPEAKER_06]: It is.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a Rare game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nomadrome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nomadrome for Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why Nomadrome?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it was garbage.
[SPEAKER_06]: It killed me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you played it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I didn't enjoy it, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just, you look at it, it's like $10 for this thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like a really bad, like... I only played a few minutes, it was that bad that I was just laughing, but $10 for a game that's a real bad twisted metal?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, Red Steel 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Red Steel was atrocious.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can you believe they greenlighted a sequel to Red Steel?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because I think a lot of people were really looking forward to it, and really like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Looking for all the new concepts and they're like, man, this is going to be the greatest game ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Ubisoft, when they released it, everyone was like, well, this isn't that good.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are a lot of things you could do better.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Ubisoft's going to take that into account, make a better game with the similar core gameplay, and it's just going to be fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I hope happens.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shir, the news topic I want to know your opinion on has to do with the price ranges for video game systems in 2006.
[SPEAKER_15]: We heard at one point that, even though I think most of us knew this was BS, but the Revolution was going to be $99.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is when it was still called the Revolution, not the Wii.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then suddenly it was $250, more reasonable, probably what we expected.
[SPEAKER_15]: But then all the way up to $600 for the PlayStation 3 or $500 for the low end, depending on how you look at it.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we've had systems cost anywhere at one point or another in theory or whatever it be, $99 to $600.
[SPEAKER_15]: How important do you think price is of these systems in the console wars that are going on here in 2006 and on into 07?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm glad I got this topic because I'm broke as hell.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this is just the perfect topic for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's a big factor for me when I'm buying systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: For example, I don't have a 360 because I'm broke.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like $400, and you can't play without live, really, and then it requires a yearly fee that I really don't have.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, $400 live comes with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut the hell up, Ron.
[SPEAKER_06]: You always miss that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You always see these press releases, and they're like, and then you've got to buy live.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it comes with it for $400.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, the gold package or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, who gives a shit?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to play games online, you can play with silver.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no difference aside from multiplayer games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't have four people on your Xbox playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gold's a better color.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So anyway, Wii's $250.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was going to be cheaper, so did everyone else, but I really didn't care, because I could scrape up $250.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't scrape up $400, because I suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, uh, the PS3 is just way out there, and even if you wanted to go on eBay, it's like a grand.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, uh,
[SPEAKER_06]: For six dollars, go buy a cheap remote, spray paint it white, and spray paint your GameCube white.
[SPEAKER_06]: You got a Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Neither one of them can play DVDs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't argue with you, Ron.
[SPEAKER_04]: They both have subpar graphics.
[SPEAKER_15]: But you can't play Elebits on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: He makes a point.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not going to drop that?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not going to push it out on the... I guess there wouldn't be any way to do it with controls.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're just lost.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, we've got to keep it moving here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for your input.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's move on over to Graybush.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please be a question about how to get rid of crabs.
[SPEAKER_15]: Please be how to get rid of crabs.
[SPEAKER_15]: One through seven, take your pick.
[SPEAKER_15]: I will take number four.
[SPEAKER_15]: Number four.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's open up case number four.
[SPEAKER_15]: Best downloadable content for a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, content...
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh god, you're going to rag on me on this one, but I hate to say this, but the damn UNO player packs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you a big Camp Nou cards fan?
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing I had the most fun with this year is all... Are you coming out of the closet, Ron?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm Ricky Martin all over again with this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just... I can't... Best downloadable add-on to a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Call of Duty map packs obviously were cool for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I thought you said Uno.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought we were going with Uno here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm just trying to think.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm, like, arguing back and forth here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd say Call of Duty map packs I probably had the most fun with, but the Uno stuff, like... I...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have to be a tie between the stupid add-on packs that actually got me to play Uno and stay up all night with people bullshitting on there and the Call of Duty 2 maps.
[SPEAKER_15]: Does it have anything to do with the webcams on Uno?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because, you know, that's one news story that didn't quite make our cut for being included tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: When they first came out, it was really funny because there'd be three or four of us in a room and we'd be like, oh, look, yeah, there's somebody's ass.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, look, somebody's boobs.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was like, I guess the novelty wore off real quick, but it was a really funny thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it was cool because we would, like, I could sit on my back porch and smoke cigarettes and play Uno, because the controller vibrates when it's your turn, and Uno's so hard you just hit the A button.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't even have to look at the screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, seriously, every many nights I'd be sitting outside smoking a cigarette, couldn't even see, but I'd be chatting on my headset, hit the A. When the controller vibrated, I'd hit the button and it'd throw a card out there, because it doesn't matter, it's Uno.
[SPEAKER_15]: Playing UNO on live is weird for me now because I feel like I'm always playing against LonelyGirl15 with the webcam.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, it's one of those things where I never expected to have fun ever, ever playing UNO.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never even expected to play UNO.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when we get in there, it's just a bunch of us friends and we bullshit and we have a good time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's not as much about UNO gameplay.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I remember when we added the new decks to it, it changed the game, and we started playing with strategy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like we're actually playing fucking UNO.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, those type of things where somebody's done something right if we're actually playing Uno.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, are you guys big on the shit-talking on Uno?
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, you know, drop four, motherfucker, and things like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but it's always joking.
[SPEAKER_15]: Reverse bitch.
[SPEAKER_15]: Speaking of fun games, the news story we wanted to ask you about would be Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because we obviously had Guitar Hero 2 come out this year, which is the sequel to a monster hit last year.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then they announced, and this is still a bit of a rumor status, but that there's going to be a quartet of new Guitar Hero games coming out through the next year.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, the one on the 360 and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is too much Guitar Hero too much of a good thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I've never played it because it's a video game and it involves me dancing around with a plastic toy guitar.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is nothing that's ever going to be cool about a grown man dancing around with a plastic toy guitar.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know I get you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sitting on the back porch playing Uno smoking cigarettes is fucking rad, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Dancing around with a plastic guitar?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be a rock star.
[SPEAKER_06]: is like the lamer version of DDR for me I know people love it and get into it but it's just like, you play it with a plastic toy it would be like me playing Call of Duty with a squirt gun, hiding behind couches Ron Workman's a communist Ron, out of curiosity Ron, have you ever heard of a Japanese game called Parapara Paradise?
[SPEAKER_15]: No Alright, just don't, don't ever look it up because you'll hate it Is it a rhythm game?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, it's based on this old Japanese style of dancing that was done by girls wearing these big tall boots, and they wave their hands around to Eurobeat music.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's something to behold, I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mine is one of those things, like, I would never let someone see me in public playing DDR unless I was completely just wasted, drunk off my ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because when I see people playing DDR, I'm just like, you look ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm one of those guys that's just like, look at that guy playing DDR, he looks like an idiot, and it's...
[SPEAKER_06]: I've always been like that, and Guitar Hero is kind of the same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not condemning it, but I can't see myself playing with a blast.
[SPEAKER_15]: But in the privacy of your own home when no one's looking?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe I would.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of like the Wii in a way, where if you play it at home, people are going to see it, and people like Ron won't want to play it, but the others will be interested, and they'll pick it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can see the 360 sales doing well with it, but six months from now, I don't see it doing well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when they come out with the wireless guitar?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that actually looks pretty tough, so maybe I'll get one when I do that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to go around now and I'm going to ask everybody what they believe the best game of 2006 was.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the worst game we hear at Orange Lounge Radio, we're tallying it up.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we'll start with the best game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Franz, what did you think the best game was of 2006?
[SPEAKER_05]: Cliche, but Twilight Princess.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why Twilight Princess over everything else?
[SPEAKER_15]: Waiting for Shearer's answer now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'll admit that it's not quite as good as I hoped.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the wolf part downplays it a little bit, but if you forget about that it's a Zelda game, and if you just pretend it was a completely new game, and you compare it to any other game from 2006, the gameplay is solid.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's not a lot to complain about.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a high nine, so I don't think it will ever top it, not even Gears.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a game that's topping a lot of people's list.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shearer, what did you think the best game of 2006 was?
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XII, hands down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game just ripped me apart.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got it, I played it for like 20 hours in the first like three days.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just played it non-stop.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have you always been a Final Fantasy series whore?
[SPEAKER_15]: Or was XII kind of your enabler?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, I played Final Fantasy VII, loved it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Played Final Fantasy VIII, fuck you guys, loved it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Played Final Fantasy IX, hated it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hated FFX and hated everything else after FFX.
[SPEAKER_04]: So FFXII was kind of like... Which would be FFXI.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, FF11 and then like the spin-off games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, true.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're just ever so crap.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I deleted those from my brain.
[SPEAKER_15]: FF10-2 doesn't exist to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so, you know, I really liked FF12, Rebirth of the Series, really interesting characters, amazing graphics, and I just loved it so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so good.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, dare I ask Ron Workman, best game of 2006?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to make fun of me, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: Burger King, Sneak King.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm totally fucking right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Come on, it was the best value of 2006.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the Burger King games were three bucks, four bucks, whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I could pay $4.99 or I could pay $5 for a new Rally-X.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let me think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, you're really going to lay into me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually bought that shit, didn't I, when I was drunk.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought Rally-X.
[SPEAKER_15]: So did I. Let's not tell anyone.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ron, best game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Out with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember it when I was a kid, you know, playing with a big steering wheel and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I really liked Viva Pinata and Call of Duty 3, I think, was underrated.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'd have to say, I mean, Gears of War, hands down, it's a no-brainer for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, and I'm not into the fantasy games like Zelda or Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing against them, but I just... You're a gun fan.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an amazing game to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Call of Duty 3 is the same way for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really immersive for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like how they've changed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of people...
[SPEAKER_06]: Call of Duty 3 definitely on your top 10 for the year at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it was a real late bloomer for me that I just wasn't expecting to be that good because I heard so much bad feedback.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like Call of Duty 2 because I'm a big multiplayer fan.
[SPEAKER_06]: My worst game of the year?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's go into worst game of the year.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ron, start us off.
[SPEAKER_15]: NovaDrome.
[SPEAKER_15]: NovaDrome!
[SPEAKER_06]: He smacked me in the face for making that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: They owe me $20 for playing the demo.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how I view it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm still pissed.
[SPEAKER_15]: What was so... I mean, because I don't know if it's just me, but they really hyped up these end-of-year Xbox Live independent title releases that they were going to do.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I wasn't really impressed with any of them, even Assault Heroes.
[SPEAKER_15]: I wasn't really feeling.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was kind of like, I'd almost rather play Rally-X.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ten bucks, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Rally-X, the deciding thing was like, I was like, I'll play this when I was a kid, whatever, you know, five bucks, no big deal, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: $10 on some of those games is a little tough for me to swallow.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's not that I'm tight with money about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if I could play the demo, like the Assault Heroes demo was pretty long, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've bought Pac-Man and Frogger and Galaga and all those, but Contra.
[SPEAKER_15]: Out of curiosity, how do you feel about the Wii downloadable stuff?
[SPEAKER_15]: Would you pay $10 for an N64 game?
[SPEAKER_06]: The last time I played a Wii was six months ago at a private show, and I've not played one since, and I'm not even seeing the virtual console stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that what it's called, virtual console?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, not even seeing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do know about the pricing, and it disappoints me that Nintendo's doing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess they can because their fans are, you know, I really hate to get into this, but Nintendo fanboys are pussies.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys should stand up and fight.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should fight Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should fight Nintendo to make better shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo's never going to make better shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to come out with subpar consoles and charge too much.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, Nintendo fans, you can address those cards and letters to Graybush, Care of Destruction.
[SPEAKER_06]: Run Graybush Workman, yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: but no, it's one of those things where Xbox Live is genius and the reason it's genius is because people are absolute assholes to Microsoft and they're not scared to be if they're pissed, they will flame them to hell and back or write it on their blogs or whatever
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you think maybe no one wants to stand up to Reggie because he'd kick your ass?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo is this golden cow that nobody wants to, you know, they're on a pedestal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Nintendo can't do anything wrong, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's some shit games out there on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody bitches about them like they would if it was a bad Xbox game, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki kind of went off on cars the other week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I think it's pretty fair.
[SPEAKER_12]: And all the Ubisoft games suck ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have officially boycotted them for all their Wii launch titles.
[SPEAKER_07]: What about Rayman?
[SPEAKER_12]: Rayman was just average, and that was their best game of the entire lineup.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rayman was my favorite, but I really wish that people would say, Hey, Nintendo, we don't want a system that only has the graphic power of an Xbox, an original Xbox.
[SPEAKER_06]: We want to be able to play DVDs.
[SPEAKER_06]: We want to have online multiplayer out of the box and launch games to back it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or maybe they don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't want to pay $10 for a Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: game we've bought 20 times before.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's dicking their fans over.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you add all that stuff into what you spend to have games and play the Wii and to track down four controllers for the damn thing, it's not any cheaper than buying a 360.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, we've got to keep it moving.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: You just sound like you could go all day long on this Nintendo thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll leave them to read the Destructoid.com blog to see your further love and adoration for all things Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fight for your rights as a gamer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shearer, what would you say is the worst game of 2006?
[SPEAKER_04]: Red Steel, because you asked me what the biggest disappointment of 2006 was when I said Twilight Princess.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Red Steel was the kind of game that I never really had expectations for.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw it, I was like, that could be cool, but it's probably not going to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I played it and it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just so bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: And even the multiplayer, like, I'm walking around, dinosaurs shooting me in the face.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, what the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: The controls were terrible, the guns were terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just hated it with a passion.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember the buzz about that a long time ago before it came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like, this is going to be really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, you can swing your sword around, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, man, multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like, this is garbage.
[SPEAKER_15]: Y'all heard about that whole, like, they're going to call you and you put the Wiimote to your ear and everybody's like, that's such a cool idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm playing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: At the time, they were saying you were going to be able to use a microphone that was in the Wiimote because I played it a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that disappeared quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which never came about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I was, like, my friend got it, and I was like, dude, let's go play it, and we're playing it, and, uh, like, the multiplayer, as soon as you figure out how to use your stupid sword, like, you run up to people, and you're just like, they're dazed, and you just shoot them in the face, like, 45 times, and it's so annoying, because you can't kill anybody unless you're using your stupid sword, and, like, multiplayer's cheap, uh, and the stupid ring thing is retarded.
[SPEAKER_15]: Was the game just rushed, you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I just think it was atrocious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they don't know what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said they were working on it for months, fixing it, so I think it just couldn't pull it off.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they were just like, yeah, fuck this game, this is terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what they did.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, you would think that they might be able to sell copies of Red Steel 2 if they just said, oh, Red Steel 1 was rushed, sorry, we'll make it better next time.
[SPEAKER_15]: But it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_15]: It wasn't.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was just bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Franz, what would you think was the worst game of 2006?
[SPEAKER_05]: This one's pretty easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Armado.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a game on the PSP, and all it is is you're an armadillo rolling around a mountain, and all you do is hit one button to jump at the right time.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the entire $40 game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I shit you not.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it's not even a homebrew.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an actual... It's an actual game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like a small company's first game, so I hate to knock it, because, you know... You're making shit up to get out of this easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody knows what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It caught my eye in game trailers and I laughed my ass off at it.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, funny enough, that's not, out of all the ones we've heard, that's not the first game somebody mentioned as the worst game that none of us had heard of.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be interesting to hear the rest.
[SPEAKER_15]: So is this why the PSP keeps getting flack for not having the same game power as the PSN?
[SPEAKER_05]: PSP's terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: That should be my disappointment about 6.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have good games.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just don't have enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have it right in front of me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to throw it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It cost me so much money, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: But Luminous, Metal Gear... Yeah, 360?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, keep going.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, we got to wrap it up here.
[SPEAKER_15]: What do you guys have planned for 2007 over at Destructoid, if you can say?
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of giveaways, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, super secrets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of bitches.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, lots of bitching, lots of prizes.
[SPEAKER_06]: We want to give away a Wii a week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we're working on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what we're shooting for right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we've got a big contest going with the Lord of the Rings people, I think, at Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we've got a big, big, big World of Warcraft thing coming at the end of the month.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: So be sure to check it out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Check it out, you guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: Destructoid.com for more information on all these giveaways.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sounds like you could just log into the site and win something free.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also, Podtoid.com for their podcast.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you guys have any side projects you want to pimp out while you're here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ron, do you want to print out your 45,000 of them?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't talk about them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Secrets about them.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're very good discreet peoples.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for having us, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely, dude.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks so much for coming on, you guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: And best of luck to you guys at Destructoid, all 45 or how many of you there are over there in 2007.
[SPEAKER_04]: or three thousand of us.
[SPEAKER_15]: Big thanks to those guys over there at Destructoid.com for coming on the program and especially to Franz because originally him and I were on another show called Cross Platform together earlier this year which is why I remembered him and originally it was just going to be him that came on but he was like, dude, you want to get some more people on?
[SPEAKER_15]: So he got some of his co-bloggers over there at Destructoid.com to come on as well and that was a fun little interview.
[SPEAKER_15]: I definitely need to check out more of their own podcast over there because I'm sure it's a riot so.
[SPEAKER_15]: So check that out over at Destructoid.com One of my favorite gaming blogs, by the way.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I mean that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the best site address ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like their little robot icon that they work into everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, who's coming on next, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have Godfrey from Gamertag Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, I'm joined here now by Godfrey from Gamertag Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Godfrey, you there?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yup, I'm here.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's going on, man?
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, not a lot.
[SPEAKER_15]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_15]: Everything good, man.
[SPEAKER_15]: Big fan of the show, man.
[SPEAKER_15]: Big fan.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're big fans of you guys as well.
[SPEAKER_15]: You guys have come a long way.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're, what, going to be two years podcasting pretty soon?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's going to be two years now in February, but I've been also recording before that around 2000, 2001.
[SPEAKER_09]: I used to have a
[SPEAKER_09]: Like a fantasy star online radio show.
[SPEAKER_09]: At that time, on the Dreamcast, it was like a big community.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I also used to help out these guys, GamingNoise.com, Chip and Zach.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I know all games, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: They used to do a radio show, too, at that time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, they were around.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just out of curiosity, Phantasy Star Universe was out this year.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you kind of get on board with that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I was playing a lot of...
[SPEAKER_09]: for like a good month, but then, I don't know, I wasn't feeling it like how it used to be with the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: It seemed like more strict.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last time on the Dreamcast, it was like more open, and I don't know, it just, I don't know, it felt kind of different.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if it was because of the next-gen consoles or, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just wasn't too thrilled with the online gaming on that.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, I want to ask you about this, too.
[SPEAKER_15]: You guys have had a lot of, like, Microsoft celebrities on your program this year, haven't you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Recently, we had an Xbox Community Awards, and we had a lot of people from the Xbox community, a lot of podcasters in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: And also, people from Microsoft came to the show to help us out and, you know, just thank the community that has been helping out throughout the years.
[SPEAKER_09]: Major Nelson was there, Trixie, Peter Moore was also part of it, Aaron Greenberg It's been a great year for us, man We've been busting our butts big time this year I want to thank everybody from Microsoft for helping us out Yeah, it sounds like it's really paid off for you guys So congratulations, those are some big names to have on your show
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, if we could do it, anybody could do it, you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody's just got to be dedicated, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want to ask you this as well, because your show is mostly centered around Xbox, but do you play Nintendo Wii, PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you play the other consoles, too?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I have.
[SPEAKER_09]: As a matter of fact, I was camping out, man, trying to get the Nintendo Wii during launch day.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was in line for at least 12 hours, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been playing that here and there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've only been playing Zelda for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: I downloaded a couple of Virtual Console games, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just waiting to see if I can have more games in 2007.
[SPEAKER_09]: and Winnie for WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_09]: I played that too in the Nintendo Party.
[SPEAKER_09]: They were here in Miami a couple months ago before launch.
[SPEAKER_09]: I liked that game a lot.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I got to play WarioWare E3.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was one of the few games that didn't have a mile-long line.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: I had a good time with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's different, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's cool to get a group of people to play together in there, you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's different than the other games in the PlayStation 3 and the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think that game's going to show us just why the Wii is a party console just as much as the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yep, I think so too, man.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, Godfrey, we've got to get to the game we're playing here, which is the year 06 in review, and we've started off with 15 boxes, but now we only have 6 left, so please, pick a number 1 through 6.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so tell them what's going on for this year, man.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, you've got to tell me what's going on in 2006.
[SPEAKER_15]: You've got to pick one of these boxes, 1 through 6.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me pick number one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's open it up.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: We want to know your opinion.
[SPEAKER_15]: What did you think was the best handheld game in 2006?
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, handheld.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, that's a good one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been playing a lot of BS.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to say, in my opinion...
[SPEAKER_09]: Animal Crossing was really cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been playing that a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me see what else I've been playing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Luminous, also from the PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know that came out, was it last year that came out though, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: But you did have Luminous 2 this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I haven't played it, but I've been playing a lot of Luminous from the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, so out of all those games you played, which one would you say was the best?
[SPEAKER_09]: Which version, from the Luminous or...
[SPEAKER_09]: on PSP or the Xbox?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, for any handheld system, which game would you say was the best?
[SPEAKER_09]: Animal Crossing, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had a lot of fun with Animal Crossing this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been playing that a lot, a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, yeah, I mean, that's the only game I've been playing a lot on the handheld this year.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's pretty addicting.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, you can go online with it and, you know, go visit other people's towns and it seems like it doesn't really end ever, that game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly, not only that, it's based on real time, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's like,
[SPEAKER_09]: I wake up and I'll be like, alright, it's daytime over here and I could go online and I might go to somebody else.
[SPEAKER_09]: The time is ahead in their town.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's say somebody from maybe Europe or Japan and their town is based on their time.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's like, oh man, it's nighttime over here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's cool because I know Animal Crossing has a great community too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if you've been checking out this couple of websites called AnimalCrossingCommunity.com
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, people can exchange their friend codes and exchange items and help each other out and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I find that really cool, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's different from a lot of other games handheld.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's unique and it has a huge community behind it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know that game was in the GameCube, but one thing that was missing was the online part.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, for sure, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but get ready, because I'm going to go to your town and do the same.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_15]: We want to get your opinion on a news story as well.
[SPEAKER_15]: Of course, we're going down the highlights of 2006, and I've got to say, you've got a good one here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, you have an audio Daily Double here for the news story, so let's go to the audio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome Kaz Harai.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_08]: The essence of the PlayStation DNA is real change.
[SPEAKER_08]: and the consumers are ready.
[SPEAKER_01]: Genji 2 is an action game which is based on Japanese history.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ridge Racer!
[SPEAKER_01]: Being based on history, the stages of the game will also be based on famous battles which actually took place in ancient Japan.
[SPEAKER_01]: So here's this giant enemy crab.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ridge Racer!
[SPEAKER_01]: and Mew attack its weak point for massive damage.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_08]: PlayStation 3 will retail for 599 US dollars, 599 US dollars, 599 US dollars.
[SPEAKER_08]: Giant enemy crab.
[SPEAKER_08]: 599, 599, 599 US dollars.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's Sony's infamous press conference from E3 where they got taunted incessantly afterwards.
[SPEAKER_15]: Godfrey, were you at E3 this year watching it online?
[SPEAKER_09]: As a matter of fact, I got together that day during the press conference.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm also part of Xbox MVP from Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a lot of community members that got invited to E3.
[SPEAKER_09]: We were there having a couple meetings talking about the Xbox and
[SPEAKER_09]: All of us got together and we wanted to see the press conference of Sony because that's when they were announcing the PlayStation 3 and Nintendo Wii during E3.
[SPEAKER_09]: We were watching it and it was very, very boring, the presentation.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Nintendo did a really good job this year presenting the Wii and also Microsoft with the Xbox 360, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sony was just straight up boring.
[SPEAKER_09]: I
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know why it was the hype of the system.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody was like, oh my god, the graphics are going to be amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And look, ever since E3, that happened.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look now, they've been getting a lot of bad press ever since.
[SPEAKER_15]: What do you think caused all that bad press?
[SPEAKER_15]: Was it the price tag?
[SPEAKER_15]: Was it the giant enemy Krabs line?
[SPEAKER_15]: The Ridge Racer?
[SPEAKER_15]: What caused all the bad press, do you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think everything combined.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the most was the
[SPEAKER_09]: The price, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, like, you know what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of people have been busting their butts, man, just to try to get a game because now games are like $60, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: $59.99, it's like people got to be really picky on what they're going to purchase.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's like people are like lining up, getting the PlayStation 3, and once they got it, it was like it felt like it was rushed, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Sony was under pressure big time because of Xbox, especially here in the United States.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know in Japan they're not.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're probably concentrating more on the competition with Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just feels rushed.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's like the online part, it's not like how it is with the 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think people are having a better time connecting online where the place isn't portable than the place isn't free.
[SPEAKER_09]: And now with exclusives, it's like Assassin's Creed is coming out of the 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like slowly, a lot of Sony fans are...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that slowly is going to pick up more people to get the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: And also they should lower the price, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: $600 is a little bit too much.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they were very gassed up that they sold a lot of units with the PlayStation 2 and they thought they were going to do the same thing with PlayStation 3 no matter what price it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: And look, now they're struggling, you know, it's like,
[SPEAKER_09]: I know they're going to learn from that, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hopefully, next year, their door is down on the price, man.
[SPEAKER_15]: They've got a lot riding, too, on Metal Gear Solid 4 and Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_15]: Kind of the only big, big, big exclusives I can think of that are left.
[SPEAKER_09]: As a matter of fact, I think PlayStation 2 this year, in the Christmas season, they had a lot of great games, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot like Bully, the new Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've been getting a lot of great games, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think...
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what they need, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: They need companies to create great games for the system.
[SPEAKER_09]: Especially first party-wise, they don't have no great games right now on the system.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nintendo and Microsoft are coming strong with the first party titles.
[SPEAKER_15]: Speaking of great games, that's a good segue into what we want to ask you next, Godfrey.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're tallying it up all night long.
[SPEAKER_15]: What do you believe was the best video game of 2006?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, to me, man, I think it was Gears of War, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gears of War?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I know it's not a perfect game, but I think graphic-wise, the sound, everything put together was amazing in that game, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: The only thing that was a little lacking was the story, but it's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I've been having a blast playing online with my friends and with my brother.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've been doing co-op and all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's
[SPEAKER_09]: That's, to me, the best game for 2006, Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think the sleeper hit also was Viva Pinata, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_14]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I think so.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Microsoft did a horrible job promoting the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they were promoting too much on Gears of War, and the attention just went away when Viva came out, you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: So I think that game is really fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Personally, I see this game more for older crowd because it's a little bit too confusing for kids.
[SPEAKER_15]: Godfrey, I would have never have guessed that someone who's been doing this radio program about the Xbox and the hip-hop community combined was secretly an Animal Crossing and Viva Pinata fan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's wrong with that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing at all.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's innovation, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Companies just got to come out different, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the same thing with music.
[SPEAKER_09]: When everybody's doing the same thing, it gets boring.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why I love Nintendo, what they're doing with the Wii Control.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just different.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like having a different experience while playing the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: You feel like when you're playing Zelda on the Wii, you think you're in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's totally different.
[SPEAKER_15]: Speaking of something totally different, what do you believe was the worst game of 2006, Godfrey?
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, worst game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Man, I have two choices.
[SPEAKER_09]: Either Superman from the Xbox 360 or this game too, Totem Ball.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was actually free for the Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: You could control with the Xbox Live Vision camera.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that was a really bad game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was playing it and I just got tired playing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: My arms were falling asleep trying to...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if you got the chance to play that game or not.
[SPEAKER_15]: I unfortunately did and was bored of it in about five minutes.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I unlocked one achievement, so after I unlocked that achievement, I was like, all right.
[SPEAKER_15]: There was one achievement I got really easy by playing the pinball game.
[SPEAKER_15]: There was another game in it that was like a pinball game, and I played it for like two minutes, and I got an achievement somehow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: As soon as you download it, you get an achievement, I guess.
[SPEAKER_15]: You actually played this piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_15]: Five points.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wouldn't waste my time on that, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a lot of great games on the Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't even bother with that one.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm putting you down for Totem Ball because you ran it a lot longer on that one than you did Superman.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cool, cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Out of curiosity, do you think the Xbox camera... Because, you know, Totem Ball is kind of like the camera game for Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_15]: Does the Xbox 360 camera... Can it serve a better purpose than this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I think so, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_09]: I know during the holidays, one of my good friends, he's a podcaster too, but now he works for Microsoft, Chris Palladino.
[SPEAKER_09]: His family, he moved to Seattle ever since he got a job at Microsoft, and during Christmas, they got together with his family in the East Coast and him in the West Coast, and they used the Xbox Live Vision camera to talk, and during Christmas, they went opening presents and all that, so it felt like they were together, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think by that or playing games like Uno online, I think it's a great purpose to play that game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Godfrey, thanks so much for being here on the show today.
[SPEAKER_15]: What do you guys have planned over there at Gamertag Radio for 2007?
[SPEAKER_09]: Right now, hopefully in 2007 we're going to launch we're going to still continue with the audio shows, podcasts and also we're working on a video podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're working on that and
[SPEAKER_09]: One of my staff members, Pink Sage, is also working on a project, like a Game Attack Radio magazine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right now we're keeping it on hold, but it's going to be really cool, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be something different, and we're still going to be concentrating on the community because there's a lot of websites that's not getting known, and we're trying to
[SPEAKER_09]: Support them so they can get their name out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to have a lot of interviews.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you guys planning to go to CES this year?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't think any of us are signed up for CES this year, but we're kind of holding out to see hopefully about the new E3 and probably that GamePro Expo and some various anime conventions we'll be going to this year.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just don't know about CES because usually not a lot of game content.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, well, we're planning to go to CES.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: and we also got invited to a community event in Canada by EA, the NBA Street Home Court that's coming out for the Xbox 360 also.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, we'll just wait for your video and I'll download it to my video iPod and it'll be like I was there.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to thank you and everybody support Orange Lodge, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a big fan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what we got to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: We got to get together all the podcasters and continue to work.
[SPEAKER_15]: We do a lot of talking about that, independent podcasts supporting each other, and that's what we wanted to do tonight with our New Year's special is really bring everybody together.
[SPEAKER_15]: So really, we want to thank you for being on board and coming on with this, especially you guys have...
[SPEAKER_15]: They had a lot, a lot of success, so we're very happy you haven't forgotten your independent roots.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tell everybody real quick how they can check out your show, if they want to.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, they could go gamertagradio.com, and we have all the shows in there, and also on iTunes, they could check it out and subscribe to the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, go there right now, everyone, gamertagradio.com.
[SPEAKER_15]: Godfrey, thanks so much.
[SPEAKER_15]: Happy holidays, and good luck in 2007, all right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Happy holidays.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, take care, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks a lot.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: I did when I got bored with it.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about you?
[SPEAKER_15]: Good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, you used to come on Orange Launch Radio way back in the day.
[SPEAKER_15]: You came on the Wednesday show with me, and we had a lot of fun there.
[SPEAKER_15]: But what have you been up to in 2006?
[SPEAKER_15]: We haven't heard a lot of you in 2006.
[SPEAKER_03]: A good majority of it has been World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_15]: World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you looking forward to Burning Crusade?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: You ready to open up a box?
[SPEAKER_15]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, there's five boxes left on the table, Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_15]: One through five.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which one of those do you want to open?
[SPEAKER_03]: Box number three, Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, let's open it up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, the gaming category we want to know your opinion on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Game I liked this year that no one else seemed to.
[SPEAKER_15]: The game you liked this year that no one else seemed to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's a hard one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't do a lot of console gaming this year, and everything that I did play on consoles was pretty well received.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know if I have an answer for that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_15]: We better think of something quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Elebits.
There you go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, Elebits did get some bad reviews from some gaming press out there, so I guess that'll work.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: That just kind of came out of my mouth.
[SPEAKER_15]: That works.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll take it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have never even played it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just watched it last night for the first time.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the one that came to most recent memory, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is why she hasn't been on the network in a year and a half, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cry, cry, cry.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: We still love you.
Yay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, what were some games that you liked that everyone liked then?
[SPEAKER_03]: Kingdom Hearts 2 came out this past year, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually did play that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Final Fantasy XII was really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Twilight Princess was great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't actually played it, but I've seen it played and it looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, just the bigger ones that everyone knows about.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here's a news story we want to get your opinion on and that would be, and oh, this is a good one for you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you a big fan of the Xbox?
[SPEAKER_03]: No!
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sure you're going to love this one.
[SPEAKER_15]: What we want to know your opinion on is, what do you think of the Halo 3 madness going on out there?
[SPEAKER_15]: Halo 3 was announced at E3 this year, and it's been building and building.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's been all this crazy press coverage leading into a release next year of the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: How important is Halo 3 to the Xbox 360 in 2007?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm pretty sure it's going to be one of the pillars.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure it's going to be one of the big sellers, but me personally...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't give two shits.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why don't you care about Halo 3?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I didn't care about the first two.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't play them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you just not a first-person shooter fan?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not really, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, Rice Princess, what, in your opinion, was the best video game of 2006?
[SPEAKER_03]: Something that came out in 2006?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so you can't do World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, dang it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to say Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a good game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kingdom Hearts is fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_15]: There wasn't anything you played that you were just like, what a crap?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't play crap, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_15]: Then just say Sonic or Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sonic or Bomberman, or both.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Then we're not putting anything down for you, and you suck.
[SPEAKER_15]: You need to resolve to play more games in 2007.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, my God, that's a great resolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I promise.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's move over to Extifer is joining us as well from our program.
[SPEAKER_15]: How are you doing, Extifer?
[SPEAKER_15]: Good, and you?
[SPEAKER_15]: Good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, you've become more of a gamer in 2006 than you were in 2005, huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: And why would you say that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because of your Wii.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_15]: My Wii has that effect on people, apparently.
[SPEAKER_11]: I play your Wii all the time, nightly, really.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't help those rumors that are going around.
[SPEAKER_02]: I watched him do it, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_11]: And by your Wii, I mean penis.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did I get that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Did I not?
[SPEAKER_15]: Best Game of 2006, Excite Truck Because I unlocked everything in it
[SPEAKER_11]: I played it for hours and hours, and I must like it because I played it for hours and hours.
[SPEAKER_15]: So amongst Burnout, Test Drive Unlimited, you choose Excite Truck?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why is this game so damn appealing?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because you know a lot of hardcore gamers are passing on Excite Truck because they say it's too junky.
[SPEAKER_11]: They need to play it more, is what I say, because there's a learning curve to it, but once you get past the learning curve, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I don't understand...
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not the graphics, it's not the trophies or achievements or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the actual gameplay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I really, really like the gameplay and I like the challenges and everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: and on top of that are all the achievements and all the other things that you get.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, well everyone here at Orange Lounge Radio is welcome to their opinion, even if they're wrong, which you are in this case.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, Excite Trek's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think it was underrated.
[SPEAKER_15]: I really do think it was underrated.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think when it came to racing games this year, I think I like Burnout a little more because there's more fire than there is in Excite Trek.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, no, no, Excite Trek was better.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, well what was the worst game of 2006 in your opinion?
[SPEAKER_15]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: Sonic the Hedgehog
[SPEAKER_11]: So where did Sega fuck up?
[SPEAKER_11]: They just, they went... See, and I like Sonic Adventure when it came out for the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_11]: I really liked that game, so I think they can do it right when they do 3D, but I just, I think their execution and the control and everything was just, it was too much this time.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they could execute it right, because I did like that other game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, well there's four boxes left on the table.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tell me which box do you want to open?
[SPEAKER_15]: Box number two.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what number two is.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, let's open up box number two for Extover.
[SPEAKER_15]: What did you think was the best retro revival of 2006?
[SPEAKER_15]: Meaning, the best game that made a comeback in 2006.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't have an answer for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: You better come up with one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that the best
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to say Bomberman Act Zero.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why Bomberman Act Zero?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because it was so goddamn stylish and they just raped all the gamers on that one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just have to give it to them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wasn't it Konami that made that game?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I think so.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hudson's Branch or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good job, is what I have to say.
[SPEAKER_11]: Best revival ever.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm getting an orgasm in my pants just thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, well, speaking of which, we want to know your opinion on news stories.
[SPEAKER_15]: The Nintendo console, because you've been playing a lot of the Wii, and one big news story this year was that originally that system was going to be called the Nintendo Revolution, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: But they changed their mind somewhere along the line, and they decided that
[SPEAKER_15]: The name of the console is going to be the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_15]: And folks just, you know, they went nuts.
[SPEAKER_15]: They said, like, you know, they made every Wii joke under the sun and still do to this day.
[SPEAKER_15]: What was your reaction when you heard that Nintendo's new console was going to be called the Wii?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it was a lot like everyone else's, like, huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't understand how you can go from Revolution to Wii, but then it really was a good business decision on their part, I think, because...
[SPEAKER_11]: People, it's different, you know, and you'll remember Wii.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, you will.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just one fucking syllable, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like, I said frucking right there.
[SPEAKER_11]: But anyhow, it's one fucking syllable.
[SPEAKER_11]: And there's also, you know, there's just, everybody knows what it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, it was easier to market, I think.
[SPEAKER_11]: When it was the Nintendo Revolution, it would, I think, be going back, you know, going backwards because...
[SPEAKER_11]: You're used to having video game consoles with those kinds of names.
[SPEAKER_15]: And penis jokes, have you been making a lot of Wii jokes this year?
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, yes, I have.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can you tell us one of your best Wii jokes?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, no I can't, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can say, though, that when I was waiting in line for the Wii, you pretty much heard every Wii joke you could possibly hear.
[SPEAKER_11]: and that was kind of amusing because everybody was just making them all night.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think a lot of them originated from our part of the line.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was sleeping.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: I played with my Wii and then went to sleep.
[SPEAKER_02]: We woke you up.
[SPEAKER_15]: It did.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, let's thank you guys to Extifer and Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you guys for coming on.
[SPEAKER_15]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's three boxes left on the table and, hey, three hosts for the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: So Dark Sakura, one, two, or three?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, well, um, two.
[SPEAKER_15]: Two, you want two.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, let's, uh, oh, you'll let this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an even number.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, here we go, box number two.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, the best party game of 2006.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, fuck, I don't play party games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um.
[SPEAKER_15]: Everybody in the studio is getting one they can't do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I changed my box.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you can't change the box.
[SPEAKER_02]: I returned this one for store credit.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, can't do that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wasn't there a game that people would get together at your house and play a lot this year?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: Madden.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'm going to have to go though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to go universal with party and say Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I got so many dirty letters from my friends and so many people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had someone going around in my village calling everyone a wanker and then I had someone also say shit face and it was great.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's so mature.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: and putting dirty t-shirts in my shop.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, the news story we want to know your opinion on, and that would be, remember when Bully, the game Bully on the PlayStation 2 was first released?
[SPEAKER_15]: Huge controversy when they discovered that your character, a boy, can kiss another boy in the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: What did you think about that whole controversy?
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought that I...
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, that's cool, but these people are stupid.
[SPEAKER_15]: What people?
[SPEAKER_02]: The people who were all up in arms over it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like Tack Johnson?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's somebody who just needs to get butt raped with a corncob.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do they need to do more of this type of content in games?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_15]: We need more hot gay action!
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you think gay gaming is fairly represented in games today?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: There are a vast number of people in the world who have normal relationships.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think there should be any distinction made between, oh, straight people are normal, oh, gay people, you know, big thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It should just be no big deal.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, so you think that they don't need to go out of their way to incorporate gay content into the games either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it should just be, you know, if you've written this character and this character sets off your gaydar...
[SPEAKER_02]: Have them fuck a guy, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Then everything should be like The Sims, where it's just play it however the hell you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Sims is the best, I think, way they've done it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's either or.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's tons of gay couples out there who adopt children, who get themselves artificially inseminated, who adopt.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that it should just be no big deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: It should just be...
[SPEAKER_02]: CookieMama
[SPEAKER_15]: Why did I think you were going to say that?
[SPEAKER_15]: Out of all the games, out of the Kingdom Hearts 2, the Final Fantasy XII, the Oblivions, the Gears of War, you pick Cooking Mama.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I'm still playing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I've been playing it, and I haven't put it down.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's so great, what's so freaking great about Cooking Mama?
[SPEAKER_02]: Pulling the head off a shrimp.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chopping up meat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you excited about Cooking Mama Wii that's coming out next year?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah, I want my Cooking Mama Wii.
[SPEAKER_15]: Worst game of 2006, Dark Sakura?
[SPEAKER_15]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Sonic, honestly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't help it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was complete and utter shite.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just was like, oh my god, it's a bad Sonic game.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you have been a Sega fangirl for the longest time.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I asked you what I asked Extifer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Where did Sega go wrong?
[SPEAKER_02]: First of all, putting it on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And second of all, really crap control.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just not... it's...
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, overall, it looked like it had a lot of potential, but there's so much glitchy bullshit in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think if they tightened up the control, or maybe even, I don't know if they did, but used the engine from Sonic Adventure, even with the glitches in that game, you could still play through it, and it was a good game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need to really have that tightness of control that Sonic Adventure had.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, well thanks for your opinion.
[SPEAKER_15]: We know you always like to interject it.
[SPEAKER_02]: My opinion is awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, there's two boxes left.
[SPEAKER_15]: One or two.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't be reading off the screen.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't see the screen.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Two.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm so glad you picked this one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Best sports title in 2006.
[SPEAKER_12]: Best sports title in 2006.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, I would think...
[SPEAKER_12]: Not Tecmo Bowl, they didn't release, well, I guess, Title Legends.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, Title Legends was last year.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would say, actually, probably Wii Sports, since that's really, you know, kind of everyone liked that.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was universally liked.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whereas, like, you know, any EA sports game is pretty much, you know, you're either a fan of it or... So Wii Sports was kind of that game that got people to cross over.
[SPEAKER_15]: Even people that were like, I hate Madden.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't want to play Madden.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which, you know, can be me sometimes.
[SPEAKER_15]: I loved Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, Wii Sports was fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Madden, I'm sure, on the Wii is probably pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know a lot of people were getting into that that don't normally like football.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't follow sports, so, you know, to play a sports game is just kind of, eh.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know who anyone is or what the team's strengths and weaknesses are.
[SPEAKER_12]: You kind of have to be a fan of the sport to be able to play the game well, because you have to know the strengths of each player and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: And since I don't do that, nor I wouldn't be able to be any good at it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have to ask you about this one, because I think Wii Sports would have been my answer to this too, but if I went outside that and wanted to pick an actual sports title, I think I actually would have picked Rockstar's Table Tennis.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you like that game?
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't really play that game that much.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, no.
[SPEAKER_12]: Table tennis, you know, I still have trouble thinking that that's a sport.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's fun!
[SPEAKER_15]: It was way better than, like, Top Spin 2 was.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was, like, one of the worst games I played this year.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would say if I was going to pick a sports game, I would... Well, that's even last year, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was going to say Project Gotham Racing 3, because racing is a sport!
[SPEAKER_12]: True, alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: And so, if I were to say this year, then maybe best sports game... Burnout's not a sport.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, what are your thoughts on the Eye of Judgment?
[SPEAKER_15]: Does the PlayStation 3 need this, or does it need to just vaporize like it seems to have?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know if it's vaporizing, but some other things that they were talking about releasing, like the GPS system for the PSP and the camera for the PSP, those are supposed to be coming out fall of this year.
[SPEAKER_12]: Where are they?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_12]: They didn't come out!
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I guess the GPS came out in Japan, but the more that you think about it,
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I can't see anyone actually setting that up to play a card game, which the game on the PlayStation 3 itself does nothing other than kind of visualize, you know, cards.
[SPEAKER_12]: If it was like holographic or something, that'd be pretty cool, but no, it's not.
[SPEAKER_12]: So why would you pay for a $600 console to play this really crappy card game that you have to set up this really elaborate set up to play?
[SPEAKER_12]: And to be honest, they also want you to buy these cards too, which...
[SPEAKER_12]: All anyone has to do is scan it into their computer and you can print it on a piece of paper and play it the exact same way.
[SPEAKER_12]: The whole idea is just utterly retarded.
[SPEAKER_15]: What would you say was the best video game in all of 2006, Loki?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's tough because there's a lot of games out there.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'd say my favorite game of 2006, the one I've been playing the most of, I'd have to say
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, oddly enough, it's a tie between, like, Grand Theft Auto Vice City Stories and Liberty City Stories.
[SPEAKER_12]: Even though Liberty City Stories came out last year, the multiplayer is fun on those.
[SPEAKER_12]: Then Saints Row would have to be up there, too, because Saints Row, I think, right now, Saints Row was the most fun for me on the 360.
[SPEAKER_15]: So which one of those would you put on the list?
[SPEAKER_15]: Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_12]: And why?
[SPEAKER_12]: Just because you love, you love those gun games.
[SPEAKER_12]: I love those Grand Theft Auto, I love sandbox games, and
[SPEAKER_12]: they're just really fun and Crackdown I think is going to be really fun next year but you know I don't know we'll see if Microsoft is able to capture the same kind of feel as that really it doesn't matter next year anyways because once Grand Theft Auto 4 comes out there's no trumping unless they really fuck it up which is possible because they've fucked up the multiplayer every single Grand Theft Auto PSP version that's come out yet we still seem to play it and kind of just you know accept the really glitchiness of the game and I don't know it
[SPEAKER_12]: It'll be fun multiplayer, I think.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, and the worst game of 2006.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh man, the worst game of 2006.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, everyone's saying Sonic the Hedgehog, and I think they're saying that because it's fresh in their mind, but actually Sonic isn't that bad of a game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, just the controls are a little bit crappy, but I wouldn't say it's the worst game of 2006.
[SPEAKER_12]: If anything, I would go with some of the Ubisoft titles for the Wii that are really awful, like Monster 4x4 World Circuit.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I'd say overall the worst game of 2006, it's got to be Bomberman because Bomberman, it was just a boring game and it wasn't really fun at all.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I don't know, it's just, it's bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, you know, if I were to, you know, peg a company as the worst company of 2006, it'd be Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well, there's one box left, so I guess I get to open it.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, here I go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey look, I got the million dollars!
[SPEAKER_15]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, now I got a best use of music in a game.
[SPEAKER_15]: and Hands Down, Elite Beat Agents.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, that was one of my favorite, definitely my top three of the whole year was that game.
[SPEAKER_15]: That game is incredible.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, you know, some people criticized it for the song list, but I thought it was actually kind of fun and it made you appreciate maybe songs that you had forgot about.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the covers were, you know, well done.
[SPEAKER_15]: And yes, even Ashley Simpson's song was actually kind of fun in the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: The game's got a great sense of humor.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's one of the most hilarious games I've played.
[SPEAKER_15]: and it keeps you coming back because it's got a lot of difficulty levels in it and multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_15]: The game is incredible and horribly, horribly underrated.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think more people should be checking out Elite Beat Agents.
[SPEAKER_15]: Absolutely the best use of music in a game in 2006.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then the news topic I have would be...
[SPEAKER_15]: The Horse Armor expansion for Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was retarded.
[SPEAKER_15]: E.A.'
[SPEAKER_15]: 's Pay-to-Cheat System
[SPEAKER_12]: It's dumb, especially when you have games like Ghost Recon, Advanced Warfighter, that the cheats are in there, and you still get achievement points.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, granted, you can't use them online, but it's easy achievement points.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're an achievement point whore.
[SPEAKER_15]: What kind of expansions would you like to see available on Marketplace in 2007?
[SPEAKER_12]: Saints Row would be, you know, what they're doing with Crackdown, for example, they're going to have actually portions of the city that they're going to add later on.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: They've built the game with that kind of expansions in mind.
[SPEAKER_12]: Saints Row would have been cool with some, you know, they're doing like maps and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: And actually, they've had some pretty good stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe more missions would be kind of cool or like a whole other section of the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: I definitely think in, as far as Xbox 360 goes, you know, they need more RPGs.
[SPEAKER_15]: They need their Blue Dragon this year.
[SPEAKER_15]: They need some of those other titles to come out.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I love SideQuest, man.
[SPEAKER_15]: Those downloadable SideQuest was an awesome idea for Oblivion and really, really adds just hundreds and hundreds of hours to that game.
[SPEAKER_15]: So it's great.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: That is all 15 boxes.
[SPEAKER_15]: We made it all the way through.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can you believe it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, my best and worst.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've got to say mine because we've got to tally it up, huh?
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: I wish Bethesda would make a game like Oblivion but set in modern day so I can have the guns and be able to exert my power over the woodland.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you think there will be an Elder Scrolls V, though?
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course there's going to be an Elder Scrolls V. I heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course there's going to be.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, well, my favorite game of the year, it's really close.
[SPEAKER_15]: I really want to say Oblivion, but, you know, it's a great game, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_15]: It would definitely be my number two pick, but I would say the best game of the year, it has to be Zelda, Twilight Princess.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, it really took...
[SPEAKER_15]: Everything that was about... Even though the game was developed originally for the GameCube, yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: It really does show what the Wii is capable of doing to what you always thought about the games that you played.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a prime example of that.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I think it really is kind of everything the Wii stands for.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it's absolutely the greatest game to have come out this year and well worth the wait.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, tons of playability and great puzzles and, you know, just fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a different playing experience...
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: My God.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think Bomberman would have been so much better if they just had compacted it to 50 megs and made it an Xbox Live title.
[SPEAKER_15]: The biggest problem with Bomberman is that it was a piece of shit game that they put out for $60.
[SPEAKER_15]: I love you, Konami.
[SPEAKER_15]: You did some great work this year, but this game was somebody made a really bad decision.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm thinking what happened is that there were some deadlines that had to be met so this game got out and it's just so obvious in the final product.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not even funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: The problem with some of these companies is they forget that
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_12]: And the whole thing with Bomberman is like, I'm all, wow, that looks kind of cool, you know, when they showed the videos and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: It would have been cool as like an action game, maybe like MDK or something like that, you know, where, like, let's just kind of branch the franchise a little bit off
[SPEAKER_12]: And then you could have the party mode or the classic mode or something like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're charging people $60 for what essentially is an Xbox Live arcade game.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's the only good aspect of the game is playing it on live.
[SPEAKER_15]: And because the game's $60 and nobody has it, so you can't even find people on live to play it with.
[SPEAKER_15]: They just made some huge mistakes with that game that just ruined it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Absolutely ruined it and made it the worst game of 2006.
[SPEAKER_15]: So now we've got to tally it up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's look.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's see, we're going to tally up the votes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's start with the worst game of 2006.
[SPEAKER_15]: It looks like, tallying it up, we had two votes for Totem Ball, two votes for Bomberman, but it looks like between Black Wolf, Extifer, and DarkSakura, Sonic the Hedgehog with three votes is the worst game of 2006.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry, Sega.
[SPEAKER_12]: It wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: But you know what, though?
[SPEAKER_12]: At least you get a second chance with Sonic and the Secret Rings.
[SPEAKER_15]: I agree they can redeem themselves, but seriously, do a focus group or something with this game next time.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anybody could have told you the controls were fucked.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, here's the thing, too, is they made this game like Shadow of the Hedgehog, and Shadow of the Hedgehog got shitty-ass reviews.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, the problem is you can only make a Sonic game so fast before it becomes uncontrollable.
[SPEAKER_12]: And just a reminder, some of the other ones...