Orange Lounge Radio
We're your hosts, Dark Sakura, Sky, and the Lowkey
Tonight, December 31st, 2006, it's our year-end special with guests from the Bobby Black Wolf Show, STFU, Video Game Outsiders, Pod Culture, Travis Donovan Live, Destructoid.com, and Gamer Tag Radio
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello everybody and welcome to another week, a very special week of Orange Lounge Radio
We are that podcast dedicated to video games, the gaming lifestyle, and gamer culture
My name is Rob Roberts, joining me as always, say hello to my awesome co-host back there, it's Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers
Yo
How you doing?
I'm amused
Amused?
Yeah
Are you amused at this year-end special we're putting on tonight?
Okay, among other things I'm sure
Among other things
Alright, also say hello to the one and only tech master, Lowkey
Hello
How you doing Lowkey?
I'm doing good
Awesome
Alright, well tonight we have a little bit of a different kind of show tonight, we've invited a lot of special guests to come on tonight
You're probably wondering why did we do that?
Well you know, we here at Orange Lounge Radio, we're dedicated to independent radio and giving everyone a voice
And we do that through the Skype line every week, taking your calls through our 800 number, your voice mails of the week that you leave at 877-GAME-OLR
The forums, the mailbag, all of that
And since we always talk about supporting other independent podcasts, we wanted to invite some folks that either we've worked with
Or even some folks we've never worked with before that just caught our eye
We wanted to invite them on tonight to just talk about the year 2006 and reveal
We'll get into that in a little bit, but it would not be an episode of Orange Lounge Radio, certainly not the last episode of the year
If we didn't start it off with How Was Your Gaming Week?
DarkStakra, how was your gaming week?
It was pretty fun
I played Cooking Mama at the doctor's office, which was entertaining
You were poking mama's steak at the doctor's office? That's gross
I was pulling the heads off of shrimp
I see
And then went to Roseville Golf Run last night
The horrible place that it is
And I played lots of Derby Owners Club until it pissed me off that the G1 race was for mares and I had a stallion
But my horse pole-beater is awesome
For those that have never played Derby Owners Club, because they don't have a lot of these machines everywhere
Please explain real quickly, for those that may not know, what is Derby Owners Crack?
The way the machine looks is you've got two, are they plasma screens? I think they are
I believe so
They're projection screens
Well, the one at Roseville Golf Run has a ton of burn-in anyway
But they're two screens side-by-side so that you get a very, very large widescreen
Then you have different consoles, they have one that's either four or eight
And you sit at that, you can pay money to breed horses
And then you train your horse, you race your horse
And after a while, after you start breeding your own horses
Off of your little cards that you get, you can get zebra-looking horses, albino horses
One person last night had one that looked like that weird, I want to say it's in the same family as Antelope
That's got the white jaw, the zebra-striped legs
One of the other jokes of God, to say, hi, I think I'm here
So what is so alluring about Derby Owners Crack?
You race your horses, it's crack, it's just addicting
I actually was playing this game
Why do people play Pokemon?
I was playing this game last night as well and I had a horse called Paris Hilton
Because you get to whip your horse as part of the game
So it's kind of fun to say, hey, I'm beating Paris Hilton
My horse was a throwaway, I named him Poop Eater
Which I guess DJ Poop Eater might appreciate, I didn't even think about it
But my next horse I'm going to do, if I get a mare, I'm going to name it Your Mom
So people say, what were you doing? Oh, I was with your mom last night
So, anyway
You're so mature
I played DDR Supernova
That machine sucks
I mean, the game was fun, it was pretty cool
Except the pads were, it was the same old crappy extreme machine that was at Roseville Golf Land
And the pads were shitty
And I think, though, when we were playing You're Not Here
I think I twisted my knee because on the last song
My right knee just started to really kill me
I'm sorry
That's why I stopped right, because you know me, I don't stop
And I was like, hell, am I old?
It was kind of fun to go back to the good old days
Because, you know, when the show started about four and a half years ago
Wherever the hell long we've been doing this now
We all met playing DDR at the arcade
Which some people who listen to this program may not realize
So it's kind of funny
But I went back to an old love
I played Drummania
I played a lot of Drummania
I have a blister on my hand, it's great
What do you think would happen if Harmonix put out Drum Hero next?
Would you play it?
Oh, hell yeah
As long as it plays like Drummania
I mean, honestly, it was a lot of fun
Now the thing is, they had a tall stool there, so I had to put it in auto-base
Although I did try to play with the base a couple times
And it's just really hard, because I'm short and the stool was not
So I just put it in auto-base and just played all my favorite
I was playing the old stuff more than I was playing the new stuff
But it is pretty cool
Anything else you want to share with the gaming week?
Um, no
Alright, Loki, how was your gaming week?
Well, other than watching Extrovert play Devil's Crush
Not Devil's Crush, Alien Crush
On the virtual console?
Yeah
It's Devil's Crush, though, because Devil's Crush is so cool
He says Alien Crush is the best virtual console game out there right now
Which I entirely disagree with
Well, Gunstar Heroes was a pretty-
I was actually pretty impressed at how well emulated some of these games are
Super Castlevania IV for life, yo
They need to somehow put Dracula X on there, because then that would be
Not the shitty Super Nintendo 1, though
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Alright, Loki
I, too, played a game with a horse
I played Oblivion
Final Furlong
No
I played Elder Scrolls Oblivion
Because I thought I had sold it back
But apparently I hadn't
So I just loaded up a new save game
And went around
And I was punching horses and deer
And basically destroying small woodland critters
And it was funny, though
Because when you start attacking a horse
They'll actually come after you
So I opened the gate and it chased me around for quite a while
And then a sheep
I managed to kill a sheep
And it made it roll it down the hill
And finally I stole a horse and jumped it off a cliff
And then the horse, no tumble to its death
Which was funny
And then a deer
It was funny because there was a deer from far away
And I was just far enough away where I could hit with my
You know, magical missile or whatever
Magic missile
So I kept shooting at the deer
And apparently the deer doesn't mind being caught on fire
So I thought it was funny
If there's any chicks there, I want to do them
I love Oblivion
You will only ever hear Bob say that
I played the demo
Because I am hell not buying this game
Novadrome
Horrible
Horrible game
It was awful
I would never play that game again
Why not?
Because the game looks like it's very cheap
It wants to be like a Twisted Metal type of game
But it's nowhere near like a Twisted Metal
It's just very boring and just very
I didn't even really know what the hell I was supposed to do
At certain points of the game
And it was dumb
It was really dumb
The arenas are very basic and stupid
It's just
No
I don't think so
Then of course, let's see
I played more Call of Duty 3 actually
More multiplayer in that
Because that's fun
And we've been doing the thing now
Where it's either the anti-armor class
Or the sniper class or whatever
And so it's either rockets, pistol, or sniper rifle
And we just play a match just using those
Who's we?
You and your co-workers?
Yeah, my co-workers and I will do it during lunch
And it's fun
It's really fun with rockets and stuff
Because I'll be driving Jeeps over them and stuff
And it's a lot of fun
Alright
Anything else?
No, that's pretty much it
Well, I've been playing a lot of the same old stuff this week
I went back to some really weird games
I went back and played 99 Nights
I have no idea why
But I think I just wanted to get more achievements
So I'm going to play that
But probably the only new game
I gave some time to this week
Was New Rally-X
Stop laughing
I really did get this
New Rally-X is cool
You know what's interesting though
It's getting a lot of shit this week
Because it was an arcade release
That kind of let people down
Because they had a bunch of independent releases
Hey, it's New Rally-X
It was a free game on a PSP game
The only reason I got it
Is because I do remember Rally-X
From when it was in the arcades
And I did kind of like the game
I did play Dig Dug and some of those other stuff
So I actually got it for the nostalgia value
The achievements are the easiest
I'm so close to having the 200 out of 200
There's only one more achievement I need
And that's the I get to round 7 perfectly
And I can get to round 6 perfectly
So I'm almost there
So probably the easiest achievements
Of any Xbox game I've ever played
In fact, I even put it to the test
Xtavor watched me play the game one time
And then I said
Here, you play on your account
And he unlocked 20 achievement points
Just like that
Playing one time through the game
Having no idea what the eff he was doing
He got 20 achievement points
Just like that
So if you want some easy achievement points
You whores
Go and play Rally-X
And you can increase your e-penis standings
By the way, if you are a new Orange Launch Radio listener
Check out our forums
OrangeLaunchRadio.com
And check out the OL Army section
It's our little clan we have across different video games
Dedicated to just playing games
And the number one rule of the OL Army clan
Is don't be a dick
So if you think you can do that
Then join the OL Army clan
And join with some players who aren't being dicks
And you can join our e-penis leaderboard
Which is provided through MyGamerCard.net
And you can see the standings of all the different people
And how many achievement points they have
Or as we say on the program
How big your e-penis is
Because that's pretty much what achievement points go towards
Is how big your e-penis is
Alright, let's get into some housekeeping tonight
Before we start bringing on the guests
First off, we want to say we've been taped for the past couple weeks
Because of the holiday
But we will be back live on OrangeLaunchRadio.com
We tape live on Sunday nights
I know a lot of folks listen to us through our audio RSS
Or podcasting feed
But we do tape live on Sunday nights
At 6 o'clock Pacific time
Check it out over on OrangeLaunchRadio.com
We'll be back live Sunday, January 7th
Also, speaking of live
This is a great show
It's a new show we have on Orange Launch Radio
That's live only
It's not podcast because it involves RIAA music
And you know you can't podcast that stuff
But it's Loki's brand new mix show
It's called Club OLR
Tell them really quickly, Loki
What they can expect on Club OLR
Fridays at 7 Pacific
Basically, it's three different mix shows
Kind of in one long block
The first mix show is basically
Dancing, club music
Some trance music mixed with video game music
So you have like long versions
Like I think for this week for example
We had long versions of some of the Luminous tracks
Some stuff from Luminous 2
Stuff from DDR
And then of course mixed in with other trance and dance
And club music and stuff
So that was pretty cool
Then the second show is called Fragged
And this one is hardcore music
It's basically got a lot of hardcore speedcore
Metal
You can throw some metal in there
Drum and bass
Just really you know
It's basically touted as music to kick ass to
You know the perfect thing to pop on
While you're playing a first person shooter
Or something like that
And the last one is the OLR Underground
And that one actually is kind of a smorgasbord
Of stuff normally
Stuff you might not normally hear on the radio
Like synth pop and stuff like that
Or you know theme shows
It's kind of what I used to do on the old live wire
Not necessarily all dance music
But just theme shows
And stuff you may not have heard before
I'm looking at some of the feedback
Because we debuted it for the first time
On Friday December 29th
I'm looking at some of the feedback in the thread
You got a lot of great feedback
23rd Magus says
Rock on dude
First broadcast kick some serious ass
Psycoon says
Whoa this is good stuff
You should post a list of what music you use
So I can go find it
And look at this from Vandalous
This is awesome Loki
Plan on selling some mix CDs sometime
I'll buy them from you
Otherwise may I contract you to make some mix CDs
I'm serious
I'll compensate your time and media
I love well done mixes
And your stuff is always fab
That's a great compliment
Thank you
No it was fun
It's a lot of work
But I'm gonna stick to it you know
And it's really
The whole point is to have something for everybody
You know at some point
You know maybe
Maybe you're not into trance music
Or maybe you're into hardcore stuff
I don't know
So that's what we have
The other cool thing about it
For the UK listeners
Is we rebroadcast it on Saturdays at noon
Or which is 8 p.m.
You know London time
So
Alright
So it's
You know a time that's friendly to you
To listen to it
So
Or if you're you know in the United States
You get to listen to it twice
So don't say we don't love you
Over there in the UK
Yeah we love you
Alright
Let's start off the show tonight
Let's talk about a little bit of news
Because even though it's been a slow news week
Because of the holidays and everything
There have been some stories
We're going to do something a little different from our usual game
Usually we all go around and we'll all share a little bit of news
But because tonight's show is a little bit special
And the focus of tonight's show is really our guests
We're just going to give Loki about 5 or 10 minutes
To just run down some of the latest news headlines
So Loki
Take it away
Tell us what's been going on this week
Okay so there's been new firmware that's been released
For the PSP
Homemade firmware
It's been cracked
Because you know the last firmware
They had the PlayStation 1 emulator added
And they've had stuff on the PlayStation 1 or PlayStation 3
You can download for certain games and stuff
Well someone's cracked that
And now you can dump any PlayStation 1 game
To play it on the emulator
So you've seen like Final Fantasy 7 and all that stuff
This firmware makes it possible
So that's actually pretty sweet
And they've had some pretty cool videos up from that
Of course
Now another thing that we've heard about is
Price drops in the 360
And what's going to make that possible of course
Is the brand new 65 nanometer processors
Which are going to be a lot smaller, a lot cheaper to produce
And a lot cooler
Of course right now those aren't ready
And so it's actually being delayed now
Instead of Quarter 1, 2007
It's going to be mid-2007
Do you think that's actually going to cause 360's price to drop?
For Microsoft it will
But they're not going to drop the price
At least not until Christmas
They just want to make money on their consoles for a little bit
They won't drop it until they have to drop it
So
So when Sony finally comes around and drops the price of their console
That'll be what Microsoft's response is?
Oh yeah
Definitely
Mario Kart 64 is one of the titles slated to head to the Virtual Console in January
Yay!
Toe-tai-way! Toe-tai-way!
We're probably going to get it at some point as well
In March
This will make you happy though
Additional classics coming to the Virtual Console
Also announced for Japan
Ice Climber
Kid Icarus
Yay!
And Zelda II Adventures of Link
Will be heading as well
And then of course more Genesis
God damn it Nintendo
God damn you
Give us a new Kid Icarus
Don't screw with the formula
Just a fun little 2D game
Like New Super Mario Brothers was
Just a fun little game that I can play on the console
Me love you long time if you do that for me
Please, Nintendo
Did you see the new things that they have
Over at the Club Nintendo Store
Whatever they have
Tingle's Balloon Fight
Not in this country
Yeah, not in this country
I have the thing tied to my Nintendo account
So every time I buy a Virtual Console game
It attaches to my Nintendo account
And believe me
I have almost filled up a second screen of channels
On the Wii
That's how many of those stupid Virtual Console games
I've bought on total impulse buys
Not a damn reward thing from Nintendo yet
I'm hoping
There are three months of Nintendo Power
Which is lame
Yeah, I got that a long time ago though
When I registered my GameCube
Whoopie-doo
Okay, anyways
Sega Sammy's going to be teaming up with Sanrio
To make some Hello Kitty games
Woohoo
Oh goodie
And that's all I'm going to report for that
Bad Batsumaru the game
K, thanks
Anyways
Capcom
They're slated to release
An amazing number of titles
77 new titles
Across all platforms
So, you know
Games on multiple platforms
Count more as one
How many of those will be Street Fighter II rehashed?
I don't know
I think these are new games
Seven of which, I believe
Are going to be for the
No, actually six
Are going to be for the Xbox 360
So that's kind of cool
Because they've had some good ones
Wait, out of 77 new games
Six for the 360?
77 games total
But those 77 games are on multiple platforms
So if they have something on like six platforms
That counts as six games
Oh, okay
I get it now
Two rumored titles
Of course were going to be
God Hand and Okami
But that ended up being a mistranslation
Of a press release
So, not going to happen
Tekken 5 has finally
Hit the PlayStation Store
In Japan
And Dark Resurrection
Definitely a really good title
For their kind of arcade service
Is that out in the US yet?
No, I don't think so
Jamie, are you going to get that on your PS3?
Because you're the only one that has a PS3
The Tekken Dark Resurrection?
Because I know you're a Tekken fangirl
Probably
Yeah, 1080p Tekken 5
So that's pretty cool
Pretty gin, Jamie
Pretty gin
I'm still holding out for Tekken 6 though
Alright
Anyways
Of course, not a big surprise
But Christopher Gens is talking about
Doing a Silent Hill 2
Yay
You just want more Pyramid Head
No
Okay
First of all
Red Pyramid is not my focus in Silent Hill
It's all the other creepy cool stuff that goes on
That makes me all happy
I love the psychological parts behind it
You know, I was checking something out
I was looking at the various game blogs this week
And I saw something that totally made me think of you
And I want to say I saw it over on Destructoid.com
That they ran this story earlier this week
About a pillow that involved Pyramid Head
Let me see if I can find it here
We're still taping live, boys and girls
So pardon the delay here
Here we go, I found it
There it is
It's a little homemade Pyramid Head pillow
That says, rape sweet rape
Aww
And I thought of you when I saw that
That's so sweet
I want to, actually somebody on DeviantArt
Put up a Pyramid Head plushie
And I want one
So it's funny
It's a bit of irony I guess
But remember last week we were talking about
The British sites getting penalized for selling
Halo 3 beta codes
Wait, wait, back up for a minute
On the Silent Hill thing
I heard that the writer
Or whoever they said was supposedly writing it
Came out and said
No, I'm not really writing it
So is it still kind of a question mark or what?
I think Christopher Ganz wants to do it
But you know
Alright
Anyways
So as I mentioned a bit of irony from last week
Where Microsoft was punishing those British sites
For selling Halo 3 beta codes
Well come to find out
According to the latest issue of GamePro Magazine
Microsoft will be selling Halo 3 beta invitations
With Crackdown
Their brand new game coming out in March
Or not March, February
And I mean personally I was going to buy Crackdown
Anyways
But this is more incentive to buy it
Even if you might not want to play Crackdown
You're going to buy it to get a Halo 3 beta
It's like rain on your wedding day
But Crackdown's an awesome game
You should pick it up anyways
So
But if you're not a fan of Crackdown
And you maybe have a PC
And were a little bit disappointed by Red Steel
You'll be happy to
A little bit disappointed
A lot disappointed by Red Steel
GoldenEye Source
The beta has been launched
And you can download it now from the official website
Which is goldeneyesource.com
And it looks pretty
Definitely pretty
And then
You know we report on this
Probably about every month or so
But
Brand new game coming to the Dreamcast
Kuros
And it's apparently a game
A new side scroller
Like shooter game
And it's kind of a
Black and white actually
Giving it kind of a gothic feel
Dreamcast fans look
I know you're really attached to your system
Dreamcast was a horribly underrated and great system
I understand that
But seriously you will not have another game
As good as Soul Calibur
Or any of those games that were as good on Dreamcast
You won't
You think these new games are going to be like
Classics
As good as
As good as some of those games you had on Dreamcast
For the benefit of our listeners
I'm frumping it Rob
Won't be Shenmue
I'll tell you that
You can get some talented people out there to do stuff
I understand
But you know
It's just
It's not going to be
Sega Swirl
My favorite game on Dreamcast was
Freaking Rainbow Cotton
Yeah but you're weird
Anyway
I like quirky games Rob
Anyways
There's another rumor going around
I think we mentioned something like this before
About the Playstation
Portable 2
And saying that there's going to be
Some sort of built in flash drive
Or hard drive into it
Well some more
Stuff coming out
From Samsung actually
A presentation that they did
Showcasing their 60 gigabyte
1.8 inch hard drive
It's not really a confirmation
However
There was a nice little
Illustration that they had
Showing a PSP
And it says
Tagline
Enjoy the movies everywhere
Look you could put arms and legs on the PSP
So it could vacuum my house
And do my fucking dishes
But nobody's going to buy them until they
Actually have more of those must have games
Metal Gear Portable Ops
Good start
Luminous yes
But needs more
And then
One last thing I'd like to mention
Because we were watching it before we started
The show here
And I highly recommend checking it out on
YouTube
Saints Row
Glitches the musical
And absolutely hilarious
If you haven't checked it out yet
You can check it out on the original
Website that came out on which was
www.cabel.name
Or just go to cabel.name
And I'm sure that they have a link on there
Hilarious musical
And all I got to say is
Where's my fucking car
Alright
Well as we promised
We want to bring on some special guests
To talk about the year 2006
In review
It's been a really interesting year
What would you guys say were some of the highlights
Of 2006
Not just in gaming
But just in your lives
That go around gaming
Like you know I think of one of the highlights
Being E3
You know every year E3 is one of the big highlights
And just us getting to go down to
The E3 Outpost
And everything and have a good time there
What were some of the highlights you guys thought of 2006
Corny
But I'm going to go ahead and say it
E3 was just getting to meet Chris
For the first time this year
Because she's been so much fun to hang out with
And going to Disneyland
Which is why you miss all the shows you do
Hey!
I love Disneyland
E3 was okay
I was just sort of sick the whole time
So
And you know
It's sort of like E3 was going out with a bang
I guess
Trying to anyway
But
That was I have to say among some of the fun
Good stuff
Loki
Being one of the first people in the United States
To actually be able to play the DDR supernova machine
At Konami's gamer day
Oh
Okay cool
That's right
And then the Wii
Alright
Of course some of that like fire burnt out
When the actual console launched
It was exciting and then it's like
Okay it's like just everything
Yeah but that's because you've allowed yourself to buy
A lot of crap games for that system
You should have just beat Zelda
You should have just played Zelda till you beat it
No I really haven't been playing Zelda much
What the hell
I know
Alright
Shame
Alright well look
What we want to do is we devise this little game
What we've got is we've got 15 boxes sitting up here on the table
And we're going to invite some other podcasters, bloggers
Just people throughout the community to come on
And open some boxes
And throughout the week we've taped some interviews
With some of our buddies out there
And some people we never have talked to before
But we thought maybe they'd want to come on and say hi
And be a part of this
So we want to thank everybody who came on
And let's kick it off
Jamie
Jamie who's going to come on our show first
And open up the first box
We have Bobby Blackwolf from AllGames.com
Alright let's go to the phones where Bobby Blackwolf is there
Bobby you there?
Yeah I am
What's up?
Hey not a lot
How are you doing?
I'm doing good
How was your holidays?
It wasn't too bad
How about yourself?
I did pretty good
Yeah you've had a pretty good year all around
Over at AllGames haven't you?
Well we're trying yeah
Well it seems to me that just recently I was on Dig.com
Looking at their podcasting list
And someone's kicking our butt by a mile on the rankings there
And I think his name is Bobby
Yeah I think y'all are joining him
What?
Y'all are coming up
Well you're doing pretty darn good there
For just one guy doing his own show there
Yeah it's hard to try to do it every week
And know that I have no net
But people seem to enjoy it so I just keep on doing it
Well very good there
Well Bobby you know you've been a long time friend of the show
We had a great time with you at the E3 Outpost this year
And just hanging and you know bringing us into the AllGames family
We've had an awesome time with everybody over there at that site
We definitely wanted you to be one of the first to play our little game here
Called the Year 06 in Review
So you ready?
I'm ready
Alright we've got 15 cases there
Pick one of the cases 1 through 15
Alright let's open up 7
Alright what did you think was the best voice acting in a game in the year 2006?
Now keep in mind Bobby had no idea of these categories in advance
This is all a surprise
The best voice acting in your opinion
Damn
You picked a tough one
Yeah I did
I screwed lucky 7 there
Cause Uno had no voice acting so I can't choose that
Well Uno kind of did have the people going you know F you draw 4 bitch right?
How'd you play any of the uh you know well you can't do Zelda either cause Link doesn't really talk in Zelda
Hey hey come over here
Listen one of the ones I actually was really impressed and I like some of the voice acting so far in Final Fantasy 12
Ahh Final Fantasy 12
Which may not be something a lot of people talk about cause it's an old PS2 game
But I mean I want to give that game a lot of props because I have been enjoying it
Final Fantasy 12 it's kind of interesting because you know it's such a landmark series the Final Fantasy series
I've personally been a Final Fantasy horror for the longest time
But 12 kind of got lost in this whole shuffle of next gen systems which seems like such a shame because it's such an awesome game
Right and you know that's why I'm not that far in it because I keep having to like look at other things that's going on
And stuff so I definitely want to keep playing it and get farther it's just you know right now I don't have the time to get into it
And there's so many side quests too in that game like I feel like I'm barely making any progress in that game at all
You know with all the people that you can talk to and the hunts and all that other stuff so
Do you have a favorite character in Final Fantasy 12? Ask me when I'm a little bit farther in the game
Alright I'm gonna tell you this I think it's all about Balthier by the way I don't know how far you're in it but he's the bomb
And he has a great voice actor I think that's one of my favorite performances of the year
Okay well since that was a tough category to pick a game for you get a really easy news topic
I'm curious about your thoughts the news topic that's in your case is bye bye E3
Of course the big news E3 2006 the last year as we know it quote unquote
What was your reaction when you heard the news about E3 you know kind of going away and changing for the new year?
You killed my birthday you bastards
Did that news come out on your birthday?
No but E3 was on my birthday
Oh that's right they're talking about changing the time frame to it too
Yeah so no to be serious about E3 for a second I mean it really got to be too much of a circus
And it was very hard for me to see what I wanted to see because I had to wait for
The old cash register jockey from Best Buy who got in and stuff and it was really people were treating it like the world's largest arcade set to free play
When it was really about trying to get business done and trying to show what was going on in the game industry
And things kept going behind closed doors people started like ramping back like the square presentation was not anywhere as good as it used to be
Yeah which is strange because the past two years before it it had been pretty awesome it was something I looked forward to seeing
But the square presentation I was let down by it this year too every single thing we saw was Final Fantasy something everything
Right well you see what the thing that got me was that all we saw in the square presentation was video
And I don't know how many E3's you've gone to but square has always put on this big huge theatrical production with the video
But it incorporated the audience it was in like 360 degree rooms
The first year I went they did that that was like the 360 thing I remember that
Right but I mean they had stuff where they had in each chair they had like a little LCD screen that showed other information
And I actually I probably should put these on YouTube I actually stunk my video camera in some of the early years to the square presentation and videoed the whole thing
And I should probably stick try to get some of that because it's on old VHSC tapes from my old camera so it's trying to get into a format that I can put up on YouTube or something
Because you're not supposed to have the cameras in there
Yeah you get big trouble for that
Yeah I think I have like three or four old square presentations on video
Awesome that's right now this was only my 33 this year but this is what you're like your 10th 11th E3?
This was my 10th I started going when they were here in Atlanta
Wow that's amazing so having been to so many E3's did you see this coming?
I saw that E3 was getting kind of worse and worse off and harder to get things done
And it just became more of a spectacle so I knew it was going to downsize some time but I didn't think it was going to downsize this much and for this reason
Yeah you know I don't know how Dark Soccer and Loki feel what they thought when they kind of saw that
But I kind of thought when I was walking around and looking at it I thought you know something's wrong here
When we have like this six hour wait to see the Wii and then a two hour wait to see Paris Hilton
I remember getting diverted by Paris Hilton's bodyguards and I'm like something is wrong with this picture
This is not about video games now
Right it was about a big arcade and a big festival and it was like the mecca for gamers
And so what they're trying to do with the new what is actually E3 is saying this is not for the gamers
We're not going to make this attractive for gamers to go to and in fact all the gamers are saying the new E3 is boring
But it's exactly what the industry probably needs
So you think this new E3 is going to be a good thing?
For the industry yes for the gamers probably not so much
So real quickly since we actually don't have this as one of the other topics
What do you think about the whole you know this new what was a game pro expo or whatever they're talking about
That might pick up that slack of what the gamers want do you think that's needed?
I think that those are needed because I mean gamers have been wanting to get into E3
But the problem is I don't think that the big companies are going to go into the game pro expo as much as they did with E3
Gamers want to go to E3 but E3 is not going to go to game pro expo
They're not going to bring the big lavish booths the booth babes may not be there in as much capacity as they were at E3
And so I think the gamers might get disappointed
So you think they'll have a lot of the same first year issues that a lot of startup cons have
You know cons that we've seen in their first year that have needed room to grow such as you know the video game expo and penny arcade expo and all those
Exactly
Alright well thank you so much for your thoughts on the E3
Now we're going around we're going to poll everybody today
Try to figure out definitively what in your opinion was the best game of 2006
Okay the best game which is why I didn't vote for this in the best voice acting is Oblivion
And the reason that I'm saying Oblivion and not any of those first person shooters that I'm sure everybody else is saying
Is because I have watched my girlfriend play this game for well over 200 hours
Wow
She's beaten the game like twice she's gotten all the achievements but she still keeps on going back in and saying oh there's another dungeon I can go loot
It's all the add-ons right?
Right well it's not even just the add-ons she'll finish the add-ons and then just keep on going and finding new dungeons and she's been playing for over 200 hours
So my thing is any game that is offline single player that can hook you in that much just like a World of Warcraft or an EverQuest could do
That deserves props because I don't think people are playing Gears of War single player offline for over 200 hours and still finding new things to do
Alright the interesting perspective how about the worst game of 2007 or 2006 we don't know 2007 yet but worst game of 2006
Sonic the Hedgehog
Oh ouch any particular platform or just in general?
Just in general
What went wrong? Sonic the Hedgehog used to be so rad 3D
Oh
But this isn't the first Sonic 3D game you can go all the way back to Sonic on the Genesis but that's where it went wrong
It was great as a 2D game but I don't think it's working too well as a 3D game and I liked Sonic Adventure but it was no original Sonic
Alright well I don't think you'll be the only one to pick that as the worst game of the year
Looking forward to 2007 you know you do a lot of work with independent press and certainly you know Orange Lounge being in this all games thing
and all games interactive and your own show kind of all pushing towards this independent you know news going into 2007
What do you think the impact is going to be of the independent gaming press in 2007?
Do you think they're going to be more relevant? Less relevant? Do you think their credibility was damaged in 06?
What do you think is going to happen in 07 with the independent media?
Some publishers will not understand it still but some will embrace it a lot more
Microsoft has done a lot with the independent press because Microsoft actually gets blogging and podcasting and independent sites
and there are places like you know I hate to say it because I know you're buddy buddy with them but Konami
the way they reacted to Kotaku, Joystick, whichever it was at E3
that shows that you know some people just don't understand the independent press because we're not as you know in the pocket as the mainstream press
you know we will actually say what we feel instead of what they want us to say about a game that's in a preview
and so it's really going to be interesting it depends on how the companies react to the independent press
but Microsoft gets it I think Nintendo is trying to get it but I think they're failing right now
based on some of the other independent press that I've talked to and Sony who knows
Sony just needs any press right now any good press they can get
Alright well tell us a little something about your show we want to let all our guests pimp their show so tell us a little something about your show
Okay well it's the Bobby Black Wolf Show we do it Sunday nights at 8pm Eastern 5pm Pacific
and we try our hardest to end right when Orange Lounge Radio starts
we're on All Games Radio we broadcast live on All Games Radio over at AllGames.com
it's basically like you said it's me without a net pretty much talking and then I read chat comments
I take live calls and basically I try to give my perspective on things because I can get a mic and get on the air
one of the things I'm going to be covering a lot in the beginning of 07 is XNA
because I am a programmer I've been in the programming industry a lot
and I'm really interested in seeing how easy XNA can make game programming for people who can already program
and so I'm kind of delving into that in some of the techy side of what XNA really is
I'll be very interested to see how this whole XNA thing plays out in 07
I think it's just a matter of time before the end of the year I think we'll see our first user created XNA game on live
do you think so?
well not on live arcade but there are people that have already created XNA games using the beta XNA because it's been out since September
you don't think anyone is going to break through that barrier?
not to get on live arcade not by the end of 07
not by the end of this year
by the end of 07 you think someone will break through that barrier?
I think someone will
it will be kind of like the net euro say hopefully that Sony did
where they took a couple of the best games and put them on a Playstation Underground CD
that would give some of those gaming CDs a little something extra as opposed to the same demos you can download online
that's a good idea
right because the thing that sets XNA apart from Xbox Live Arcade is because Xbox Live Arcade has that 50 meg barrier
well you have two gigs with XNA so most people making XNA games probably wouldn't be able to condense it down to an Xbox Live Arcade executable
so it may have to be on CDs
well I look forward to hearing more about this progress on your program Bobby
yep
Bobby Blackwell is always a good friend of the show thanks so much for being here and happy 2006 and best to come for you in 2007
yeah thank you and happy new year to all y'all
alright thanks so much to Bobby for coming on the show
it's Best Voice Acting in Bye Bye E3 were the topics he pulled out of that box
so it's kind of sad though that E3 is going to be different
it's not going to be the big deal it was before
but I don't know what do you guys think about that whole thing
well hopefully they'll do that well they have a bunch of alternate kind of events going on around that time anyways
and if anything I think the lack of the official E3 will bring more gaming events hopefully some in Northern California
and more is better I think
well big thanks to Bobby for coming on the show
we've actually been working with Bobby pretty much all year
we joined the all games community probably back in January or February I believe is when we joined up
and we've really had a good year working with Bobby's show and got to meet him in E3 he's a good guy
very knowledgeable
you know my other favorite thing of 2006 was meeting Bobby and Scott and Lawrence for the first time in San Jose
that was cool
that's true because we all went to the not Benihanas but some other type of place
just kind of kicked around
the almost Benihanas
and it was interesting because that was the first time I had seen Scott outside of television
so it was kind of interesting
surreal
yeah I remember seeing him on television I kind of used to watch that G4TV.com
and I was kind of like I don't know I don't know if I get this
but then having actually met him and interacted with him not only is he so knowledgeable with games
and you know just has a real passion for games
but you kind of learn more about how TV can really alter the perception of like what a real person is
you know and I know some other hosts previous hosts on G4 network across the board get some bad rap sometimes
Tommy Tallarico I met him at E3 and you would think watching him on TV like what a pompous ass
but no he's actually really cool he's really nice
and so I really enjoy that so it's pretty cool
alright
Jamie who's coming on next?
that would be DMN from STFU
alright please welcome to the show everybody DMN how are you?
hey
I'm doing fantastic
hey alright it's been a big year for you
yeah it has
you've gone from OLR fanboy calling in the show every week to having your own dang show on the network
yeah that's what I get when I bug you enough
would you say that one of the highlights of 2006 was coming out here to meet myself Dark Soccer and Loki?
that was actually quite a fun time despite all the crap that I didn't talk on the episode I appeared
well did you have a good time handing out the cookies and everything to the we line waiters when we did that whole thing?
oh yeah that was a blast
alright here's how it's going to work DMN we have 14 cases for you to pick from
and inside the case is a game category and news topic we want your opinion on so what's it going to be 1 through 14?
big bucks no whammies 14
14 here we go
alright your topic is game I most want a sequel for in 2007
this is a no brainer sneak king
sneak king? why sneak king?
well I got a chance to play it over the weekend and I have to say that for $4 it's ridiculously simple and actually a lot of fun
and I need another game to buy my dad and scare the crap out of him for $4.07
you know what's interesting is that game being $4 was better than some of the games that we were paying $5, $10, $8, $6 depending on what system it was
it was better than a lot of the games we were paying more money for
it was better than a lot of the games that were retailing for $40 which is kind of scary
that's true that's true because when you consider there's certain games now I don't want to name names
but Bomberman X0 that they're charging $60 for
tell him I got a hedgehog sorry
well we'll get to what you think is the worst game a little later in the show so sneak king
you want to see sneak king 2 in 2007
I do and I think Burger King would be smart to do it because those games are actually out selling Gears of War
well but wait a minute though that's a little bit of a warped statistic because you're putting the three games together
that's still pretty good
yeah that's still not bad
they're selling over a million copies combined which is incredible
do you think that there's another commercial entity that Microsoft should be hooking up with?
I don't know
no I don't know I like Burger King just because the king scares the crap out of everybody
I really don't see any other corporate icons
it did have a pretty freaky opening movie
oh yeah
maybe the jack thing from Jack in the Box that guy's kind of creepy too
that might work
alright here's the news topic we want your opinion on of course
PlayStation 3 very controversial device this year specifically the Blu-ray shortages
the Blu-ray diode shortages causing there to be delays in PlayStation 3's this year
was it a good idea for Sony to include the Blu-ray with their console?
I think it was inevitable
I don't think Sony wasn't going to go with the DVD format anymore
I think they stepped it up with the PS1
they said you can play games and then you have your CD player
PS2 was like you can play your DVDs your CDs and your games
so Sony almost put it upon themselves to introduce a new format
yes it's a cheap Blu-ray player
but I think Sony's problem was they were rushing to release this way too quickly
and had they have held off to Spring of 07 I think they could have had a better market share
but because they released in the holiday season they only got a total of
I want to say it worldwide 600,000 consoles if that to consumers
it didn't sell well and a lot of those PS3's actually went back on the shelves
because they wouldn't go for anything on eBay
how important do you think it is in the war on HD DVD
the Blu-ray is waging
do you think that being in the PlayStation 3 gives it an edge in that war?
yes I do I think mainly because the higher
I don't say the higher end because we all know the first generation players are crappy
but the higher priced ones are about $1000
whereas the low end PS3 is $500 which is half the price
and it's about the price of a pretty good HD DVD player
so Sony was smart in releasing at least a $500 price point on one of the versions of the PlayStation 3
to keep up with the HD DVD war
but looking at it, it's about $500 if you get a 360 on an HD DVD drive
so it's the same thing
we'll see what happens in 2007
what Blu-ray movie are you wanting to see really bad?
Talladega Nights
I have no interest to see anything really in Blu-ray HD DVD yet
I'm looking forward to seeing Silent Hill at some point
because that should be second
I did say over the weekend I did see Batman Begins on HD DVD and it looked really amazing
we're also taking everybody's opinion and counting it up by the end of the show
what do you believe was the best game of 2006?
The best game of 2006 was not a console game
it was actually a handheld game
I believe that New Super Mario Brothers is the game of the year
New Super Mario Brothers game of the year
now this is something I've seen in a lot of top 10 lists
but I'm not seeing Take the Cake in many polls
why does this game take the cake for you?
well if you've seen throughout maybe the past 5-6 years
any Mario game that's come out
either has the word party after it
either has something to do with sports
or is a 3D adventure that's awful
it was a breath of fresh air I think across all sorts of levels
to see a 2D platformer that was fun and somewhat challenging
what do you think was the worst game of 2006?
that's a tough call
I would have to say
yikes
you must have played quite a few bad ones
oh you have no idea
I would have to say
this did come out in 2006 technically
I would have to say Chibi-Robo
what's this?
Chibi-Robo
it was released in Europe in 2006
oh okay
why this game?
it felt like it was ripping off Katamari Damacy a little bit
and while it was a good idea on paper
it was executed poorly
alright well that's one vote for Chibi-Robo
is that it?
yes
alright we got marked Chibi-Robo
I've never even heard of that
I love bad games I'll have to look that up
it's for the GameCube
alright
hey I got a question for you also about 2007
now I know you've got a lot of loyalty to Nintendo
because you work for Nintendo
so let me ask you specifically about Sony vs. Microsoft
because Nintendo has kind of decided to go in this whole different direction with the Wii thing
so where do you see the Sony-Microsoft war headed in 2007?
I see it headed towards new formats
I think Microsoft's going to be
they're going to try to make some point of making games
for that HD DVD drive to sell it
I think Sony is going to be a lot more focused on the PS3
I think one with their marketing campaigns
and just the complete lack of games for their PSP
they need to scrap that
as I've said on my own show
that thing needs to be dead by the end of 2007
because the more money Sony puts into that portable
they're going to lose even more money on it
so you think the PSP is a done deal
because there's talk about they should re-release a PSP lite
kind of thing like Nintendo did
but you say no scrap it all
if you release a PSP lite I don't know what you're going to do
you're going to have to
I don't know how you're going to make that thing any thinner
or more portable
because the things already
you can hold it enough
and the screen's so big
and I know Sony's not going to let a sacrifice
dumbing down that screen
I realize we're talking kind of the end of 2006 here
but do you think Metal Gear Portable Ops gave the system the kick in the pants it needed?
No
No, you don't think it's enough?
Alright, well quick give us a plug for your show DMN
that you have here on Orange Launch Radio
Yeah, you guys need to listen
Thursdays at 7pm, Saturdays at 2pm
STFU with myself and DJ Tyrant
it's a lot quicker than this show is
What are you trying to say?
I'm trying to say it's 45 minutes and not 3 hours
I see
Of course listen to this show too
If you need something a little more compacted
STFU is in a much smaller package
What are you trying to call small?
Emphasis on small package with you DMN
Alright, in all seriousness
it's been awesome to have you aboard
and officially a part of the Orange Launch Radio family
and we wish a lot of success for your show in 2007
and I hear we're going to step it up
and do some more podcasting with STFU in 2007
so we can look forward to that as well, right?
Oh yes
Alright, sounds good
DMN, thanks so much for being on the program
Thanks, and you have nothing to talk about with small packages
It's been a very interesting year, our relationship with DMN
wouldn't you say?
He kind of started listening earlier this year
and now he has his own show on the network, it's crazy
He's a very interesting individual
It was cool to meet him when he came out here though
Who texts my phone with pictures of DDR cups
Yes, I got that text yesterday too
That's funny, but that was...
DDR cups?
Yeah, he sent this picture of a DDR cup from Burger King
for no reason to my phone
I want a DDR cup
Do they have those plastic cups
or is it just like their normal cardboard thing?
I think it's plastic
I'd have to check the picture again, but...
You know what's funny though
is actually since I do this retail site
like training for Microsoft
and they have free things
when you go through their training program
you can buy little chachkies and stuff
They have an Xbox 360 tumbler glass thing
I was thinking about buying
I should get one of those
By the way, while we're talking about DDR cups
we want to give a huge Orange Lounge Radio thank you
to our listener Misty
who sent us a copy of the DDR soundtrack
that they're selling at Burger King
and not only that, but
Misty's always been a really great supporter
of Orange Lounge Radio
She sent us a gift certificate for Live 365
so January is Misty month on Live 365
because essentially she's paid for it
So we wanted to say thanks to Misty
and she also sent us samples
of the jewelry she's been making
She's been making OL Army jewelry
and selling it on our forums
and we gave the OL Army one to Jamie
for her cell phone
and she's been using that
It's on my phone
It's orange-ing it up
So thank you, Miss
Everybody, thank you, Misty
Thank you
And thank you DMN also as well
for coming to visit
and that Wii line
when we went out and gave the cookies
and soda to the Wii line
That was fun
We met so many cool people
I hope some of them are still listening to the show
I saw
Was it the one chick that he gave
Was it a hat too?
Yeah
I saw her at GameStop the other day
Really?
Yeah
Did she recognize you at all?
No
I didn't say anything because I'm an ass
and I don't talk to people
but I saw her and I recognized her
She was in line with me and Chris
Yeah, she was cool
She was hanging out with us
Damn it
We should have emailed her
and brought her on the show
Oh, well, we'll get her next time
Well, if I see her again
I'll say hi
Alright, you do that
One more time
Let's say hi to some more guests
Jamie, who's coming on next?
That would be
John and Michelle
from Video Game Outsiders
Alright, and we're joined on the line
by Michelle and John
from the Video Game Outsiders
You guys there, Michelle, John?
Woohoo
We're here
Hey, how you guys doing?
What's up, you mother?
Happy 2006
Soon to be 2007 to you
That's right
Now, 2006 has been a really good year
for you guys, huh?
It has
We've actually kind of gone beyond
what we thought we would do
with this little podcast here
and we're enjoying it
Yeah, awesome
You guys just recently won
like an Xbox award, right?
We did
Podcast of the year
How about that, huh?
Very cool
Congratulations, you guys
That's awesome
Thank you
Was that something that was
like community-based
or was the community voted
or was that like an editorial
It was voted by people who
listen to gaming podcasts, I guess
and that's why it was important to me
It wasn't just some old fat cat guys
in a business room somewhere
It was actually by the people
That's awesome
I think it always feels better
when it's something from the community
Absolutely
That's great
What a compliment
How are you going to top that in 2007?
I have no idea
John wants to do a naked episode
That's not going to happen
We're going to do a musical, actually
There you go
Wow, all right
We'll go with that
Oh, the big musical episode, of course
But see, that's when you know
your shows jump the shark
So be careful
Yes, exactly
All right, well, we've invited you
guys on today to play a little game
We call the year 2006 in review
And what we've got, we got 13 boxes
on the table
And since there's two of you
Oh
We'll let you guys each pick a box
So, ladies first, Michelle
Why don't you give me a box number
1 through 13
We'll take a look what's inside
I'll take number 4
All right, box number 4
Let's have a look
All right, the category we would
like to know your opinion on
Best graphics in a game in 2006
The best graphics of any game in 2006
Best graphics in a game
I have to give it to a game
I actually do not like
Gears of War
Even though I did not like the game
I was blown away by the graphics
When I turned that on
I was like, wow, this is what
next gen is all about
And I know we're going to probably
have people yelling at me
for not liking Gears of War
But I'll get to that later
You know what's interesting?
Not from this audience
Because we've said some very similar things
on the program
I've said the same thing
I think the game looks great
But I was let down by the way it played
Exactly
Well, that's a big relief
Because at our show
We had a lot of people writing in
Like, how dare you hate this game
And you're crazy
Stop playing your Tom Clancy stuff
Tell them to sit down
People like what they like
Exactly
Sim it down now
I liked it
But the graphics were amazing
So that's my pick
Hey John, since you're on the line
You want to buy into this too?
What do you think is the best graphics?
I definitely agree with Gears of War
The second game that comes to mind though
Is definitely I think Splinter Cell
Is a close second
Double Agent
But yeah, Gears of War I'd say
Is definitely the best looking game
Of the year
Without a doubt
What is it about Splinter Cell
That makes it stand out to you?
You know, personally I was a little
Disappointed with Splinter Cell
I thought that the multiplayer
Just was horrible
Compared to what they did in the past
I loved K.S. Theory
Yeah, and it was a huge step backwards
But visually, I just
I look at Sam's noggin on the screen
With all the sweat and the detail
And the stubble
The lighting
I just love the character models in that game
So it definitely stands out for me
Alright, very cool
Well now, you not only have a pretty
Big category there
But you have a really big news topic
We want to know your opinion on for the year
Michelle
And this is a news topic that seems to be
Something that keeps going on and on and on
Throughout the year
And it's somebody we don't refer to by name
Here on this program
But we'll call him Tack Jomson
Okay
Alright
Alright, you know this guy, right?
He's somewhat of a bully
In the legal sense
And remember, he actually went to court
To try to stop the game Bully
On the Playstation 2
From even coming out
What is it about this guy, you think
Why do you think this guy keeps wanting
To pick on us gamers?
Why won't he just leave us alone?
Well, you know, that's funny
Because a long time ago on our show
I mentioned that this kind of violence
In video games
And I mentioned the game Bully
And John and Kyle, the other hosts
Shot me down
They're like, oh, nothing's become of that
And that's a fine game
It's really not that bad
But, you know, the angle of that
With the school kids
And I think that that's what's really
Getting this guy going
But to me, it's fine
I grew up playing violent video games
And I feel guilty when I kill a gnat
So I think the guy needs to back off
Well, yeah, and I kind of have an opinion
About this
I think it all comes down to parenting
And parents and all that in general
And I think that these are just like campaign issues
You know, I know Hillary Clinton
Kind of latched on to this
As a campaign issue
And I think like the soccer moms
I don't want to get political here
Soccer moms
I think that there's a certain demographic
That don't know enough about video games
And they just hear this stuff
And they say, oh, yeah, we should get on board with this
And we should ban this too
It's a bunch of crap, you know
And Jack Thompson doesn't know dick
About video games
He didn't even play Bully
He already decided that he hates it
And really, it's probably one of Rockstar's
Tamiest titles
You know, that's true
Is that he really seemed like
When they let them all sit down and play the game
He seemed kind of mad that
They weren't showing enough of the game
Like he seemed to know all this stuff about the game
But the game hadn't even out
How was he able to play it?
Exactly
Very interesting
You know, we've said a lot of the same things
On our show here
It all comes down to the parents
So I think it's very interesting
We have very similar perspectives there
But I wanted to ask real quickly too
About the whole Hillary Clinton
And other politicians
What do you think recently
And this is all kind of recently
In the November, December of the year
It's kind of been the Hillary and
Who's the other guy
Lieberman
Have seemed to come out
Kind of embracing the ESRB
Like almost that there's been a change in attitude
A little bit
You don't trust Lieberman
I'm from Connecticut
He ran as an independent
So we all are like
Whoever, who cares
And first of all
I want to back up here and say
You know
Our podcast is not political at all
Yeah, we try not to go there
Because we get the mail too
You take us down a road
But we never go down
You know
We just want to have fun
But yeah
I think this whole ESRB thing is a joke
Unless the retailers really enforce it
It's absolutely meaningless
And I see these kids trying to buy
Grand Theft Auto all the time
And I think most of them succeed
Some 50-year-old fat housewife at Walmart
Is going to sell the kid the game
So come on
It's on eBay anyway
I mean these days
It's really hard to control that
All right, all right
We better get off this political road
Because I can see people emailing us
I don't want to go down there
All right, all right
Then let's go to another box
John, it's your turn
Go and pick a box
1 through 12 now
I'll link to 12
How about 7?
All right, box number 7
Let's take a look
Most hilarious video game of 2006
Oh
Most hilarious
Okay, that's easy for me
It's actually Rayman Raving Rabbids
Whatever the hell it is
It's Rayman Raving Rabbids on the Wii
Yeah, definitely
That game is off the wall crazy
So it's one of those laugh-out
I have to be honest
I personally haven't played this a whole lot
But I did notice it was somewhat quirky
When I took a look at it
It's very quirky
What is it about the game that makes it so funny?
You know, it's just got this twisted art direction
Which I kind of appreciate
They really create these little mutant-looking
Rabbit characters
And you just kind of throw it in this little rabbit world
And it's just very bizarre
And it's funny, you know
And I think that's all it is
That's all I can say
All right, very cool
Michelle, would you agree
Or do you have a different pick?
For me, I don't know if this is on the console or anything
I'm going to have to go with OfficialLineWriter.com
What?
Yes
It's a little web game
Of this guy that's on a sled
And he goes flying around
And I laughed for like an hour
When I first played this game
Well, you're simple
We'll take it
It's PC gaming
It's a little PC game
I'm telling you
It's a gem
Try it out and you'll get a good laugh
All right, awesome
Yeah, you know
I was trying to pull up LineWriter on the Wii
When the browser came out
But now, I guess since they're going to make it an official game
They locked everybody out
Yeah, I can't wait for that
Yeah, it's a Flash issue
Because the Wii only supports Flash 7 or older
And that's like in Flash 9 or something
Oh, we had thought that they shut people out
Because they're going to be releasing the full version later on
As a game
Yeah, it's a newer Flash version
Yep
All right, and here's the story I'd like to ask you about
This is a little bit dated
This kind of goes back to way early in the year
But I don't remember if you remember all the furor that went on
When Microsoft announced that they were going to be creating this new system
Called the Origami
And for about a month, people were running wild
Like, oh my gosh
Microsoft's going to enter the handheld market
They're going to obliterate the PSP and the DS
And da da da
And then it turns out the Origami is just pretty much this fancy schmancy PC
And that's why the screenshot of Halo was on it
So this kind of bears the question about Microsoft entering the handheld market
Is this something Microsoft ought to consider in 2007?
Yes
I would definitely say so
You know, I'm a Nintendo fanboy
The DSLY has sold like 34 million units
Compared to the PSP, which is like 18 million
You know, Nintendo owns that category
And I think that there's definitely a need still
For a portable for an older market
You know, the Nintendo kind of is young and skews a little bit older
But not too old
And I think that Microsoft, it's ripe for the taking
Because they have the installed user base of the 360
And yes, I think they should definitely do it
Are you saying you want to have a dead or alive extreme volleyball on the go, basically?
No, I think that Microsoft's bigger plan though
Is like to integrate the Xbox Live market into the handheld
So I think that's where the magic's going to be
Where you can download movies or music or games
And then carry them with you in this portable device
Do you think that's something they might end up trying to do with Zune
Because of the iPod games and everything?
I do think that
Because the thing about the Xbox is that you can download movies now
No music is around the corner
The thing is you can't get it off the console
You can't take it with you
So some device is going to enable that
Be it the Zune or this other device that comes
So I think that's all part of the big picture
I definitely do
Michelle, what are your thoughts?
Microsoft, do they need a handheld?
I think they should really get into it
Because although the Nintendo DS is very cool
I do not like playing multiplayer on it
Because of the little friend code thing
Now one thing Microsoft does and does well
Is the Xbox Live community
And if they could get that on a handheld
I would definitely pick it up
Because to be able to just get up and go
And play with your friends no matter where you are
That's something that the DS just doesn't have
If you remember the DS didn't even get online
For about a year and a half
Yep, exactly
I agree with you there
That Xbox definitely knows what they're doing
When it comes to the online stuff
Very good
One more question for you guys
Actually two, it's a two-parter
We want to know, because we're taking a tally all day long
What do you guys believe is the best game of 2006?
Michelle, we'll start with you
Michelle, what do you think is the best game of 2006?
For multiplayer, I'm going to give it to Rainbow Six Vegas
But I want to talk about single player
Because to me, I was not into single player games
Until this game came along
It's oblivion
I've spent countless hours
And I haven't played the game twice
Everybody I ever talked to kind of liked the game
Except for people who didn't have time for it
So it seemed to have something for everyone
Worst game, do you want me to go right into?
Sure, why not?
We'll take your worst game
What do you think, Michelle?
Although there were worst games
It's going to be Gears of War because I had the most hype
Come on!
Yes, because I wanted that to be good
Because it had the capability to be good
And it just wasn't
So that was the biggest letdown for me
And that's why I gave it to the worst game
That is a gutsy, gutsy statement
It's a gutsy thing, everybody bring it on
You want to give out your email address, your gamertag?
Oh God, you can find us at videogameoutsiders.com
Oh, there you go
Orange Lines Radio
All right, all right
You know what, I would actually agree
I named Gears of War at E3
I said next to Spore, it was the game I was anticipating the most
Walking out of the doors of E3
Because when I looked at E3, I thought
Boy, the cover seems so neat
How one button will do all this stuff
But then when I actually sat down and played it
I was like, ugh, I don't like this
I want to just run out there and start shooting people
Like Quake or Halo
All right, John, what do you think was the best game of 2006?
Well, my favorite game by far this year
So far is Zelda for the Wii, Twilight Princess
Definitely the best single-player game of the year
It's just absolutely immersive
The art direction, the plot, everything about it
I just absolutely love, it's what I live for
And then my favorite multiplayer game, I agree with Michelle
It's Rainbow Six Vegas with a close second Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter
Because I think at the end of the day
That's the game I probably played the most this year is Ghost Recon
All right, interesting
All right, so we'll put you down for
It sounds like you're very passionate about the Zelda
So we'll put that down as the single-player game
Yes, very much so
Yeah, I would say so
Worst game, you want to hear my totem ball?
What the hell is that?
I wonder when someone was going to go to the Xbox Live
And some of their questionable picks this year
So even though the game was free
You still say it's not worth being free
Yes, it was an embarrassment to Xbox Live
You know, what is it about camera games anyway?
Everybody seems to want to do camera games
But it seems to me like no one's done it right
Well the iToy, the Sony iToy was pretty successful though
It was successful, but how fun was it really?
I know, exactly
Fun for like an hour and then it kind of, I don't know, the thrill is lost
It's a novelty
Well hey, best of luck to you guys in 2007
Tell our listeners really quick who may not be familiar with your program
Tell them a little bit about your show
We have a really stupid podcast
No stop
Basically we have a very relaxed kind of podcast
In the atmosphere if you're just kind of talking with your friends
We're not game experts, we're not in the industry
And we have a really great forum and community
And I think that's what makes our show so great as well
Yeah, we have awesome listeners
And there's actually a third host who's not here
Kyle Jones, and he's Canadian
Yes, he's our resident Canadian
So check us out, videogameoutsiders.com
We have a forum, you can download the episodes and all that
Show archives, blah blah blah
Videogameoutsiders.com
Alright, very cool
Check that out you guys, it's videogameoutsiders.com
Congratulations to you guys on an awesome 2006
Thanks for coming on our program tonight
We appreciate it
Thanks for having us
And we'll see you in 2007
Happy New Year
We definitely want to thank John and Michelle
For coming on from Video Game Outsiders
You know, that was one of those people that we contacted
We really didn't know them
But we just kind of thought we'd get along with them
Just because, hey, you know, it's two guys and a girl
That do their show, and they all met through a gaming community
And we know some of our listeners are in common
So it was very cool of them to come on
Without really maybe knowing who we were
I don't know if they knew beforehand or what
So it was just very cool
And I gotta say, that Michelle, she's got some pretty big balls
Naming Gears of War the worst game of the year
Well, I mean, it was kind of a disappointment sometimes
But maybe I need to play it more
I know it's fucking hard, though
All my coworkers that bought that game said
My God, this game is so fucking hard
I'm playing it on easy, and I can't fucking pass
To the goddamn beginning of the game
No, I mean, I can't say I disagree with her
I don't know if I would have called it the worst game of the year
But definitely one of the biggest disappointments
For me, personally
You know what, I'm gonna go on the record saying
I think the best game of next year is gonna be Earth Defense Force 2017
What?
It's the same game, you're fighting giant ants and robots and stuff
Okay, maybe it's not the best game, but it's a game I want
Alright, well, thanks again to those guys over at VideoGameOutsiders.com
They just released the whole Simple 2000 series over here
That'd be fun
Alright, you're looking at this whole other world right now, Logie
So?
As usual
Alright, who's our next interview?
Our next one is Brad from PodCulture
And I'm joined here by Brad from PodCulture
Welcome to the program, Brad, how you doing?
Beachy King
Hey, now this is a little different because PodCulture
Not exactly exclusively a games podcast
But you're still a games fan, yes?
Oh yeah
What kind of stuff do you talk about over there on PodCulture for those that don't know?
Basically just geek life
You know, it's me, a friend of mine I've known for I guess almost 20 years now
And my girlfriend and the three of us just sit around and talk about what TV we're watching
What games we're playing, what movies we're watching
That kind of stuff
Sounds just like what we do here, but a little more geeky
More in the pop culture business, I guess
Nothing wrong with that
Well, thanks for coming on the show today, Brad, and we want to play a little game with you
And it's called The Year 2006 in Review
So we have 11 boxes left, why don't you pick one of those boxes, 1 through 11
We'll open it up and see what's inside
Number 9
Alright, number 9, here we go
The best puzzle game of 2006, are you a big puzzle game fan?
I like some of them, yeah
Well, did you have a particular favorite that you would call the best puzzle game of 2006?
Well, I don't know if it came out in 2006, but I started playing it in 2006
We'll take it
Astro Pop
Astro Pop, I believe technically that was a release this year, so on Xbox Live Arcade
Yeah
Interesting choice, because some of those PopCap games, some folks say they don't belong on Xbox Live
What is it about the Astro Pop game that you like so much?
Well, I have ADD when it comes to games, so when it comes to trying to play something for a long time
I kind of lose interest in it a lot
So, you know, you can pick that up and just run with it
So, Astro Pop is one of those games that you really sit down and you only play it for a little while at a time
Mm-hmm
Alright, gotcha, okay, I can understand
Well, as we say, there are no right or wrong answers, it's your opinion
So there you have it, Astro Pop for best puzzle game
Aren't those achievements a pain in the butt, though, on Xbox Live? I don't think I have any of them
I haven't gotten any on Astro Pop
That's a tough game
Alright, well, we also want to know your opinion on a particular news topic
And the one we have in box number 9 is the PlayStation 3 line versus the Wii line
Of course, in November, big, big console launches
And you hear about this violent outbreak
I think there was this comic that put it so well is that there was this violent outbreak going on in the PlayStation 3 lines
Where people were getting shot and pushed into telephone poles
And then you go to the Wii line and it's like people are wearing buttons that say free hugs
And it's just, you know, kumbaya and everything
Why do you think there was such the radical difference between the two lines this year?
I don't know if it's just that Nintendo is more of a fun system versus the hardcore gamers on the P3 or what
I really don't know
Nintendo has always had more of a fun thing around their system
It's been less hardcore gamers than the PlayStation has been, at least to me anyway
So you think maybe when you say it's more fun, maybe the fact that there were more people in the Wii line
That were really dedicated and you knew that those people were going to be playing the Wii
Versus, you know, the eBaying that they say was going on in the PlayStation 3 line
Where half those people were camping to put it on eBay
Yeah, and you're looking at it where the system costs half as much too
More people are going to be able to afford to buy that to play
And, you know, it's more of a status symbol in a lot of ways
You know, I've got a PlayStation 3 that are rare
You know, it's hard to get a Wii, sure, but it's a lot harder to get a P3
I can agree with the status symbol thing
Because I think the media kind of made it to look like the PlayStation 3 was kind of this, you know, big status symbol
Especially, you know, when they were covering the lines and everything
So do you think some of that might have to do with the fact that the PlayStation 3 came out first?
You're only talking a couple of days there, really
I guess that's true
It was, what, a week, maybe a week, a couple of days
About like four days, yeah
I guess that's true
All right, well, hey, just out of curiosity, did you end up waiting in line for one of these systems?
No, I've never been a get-it-at-the-moment kind of guy
It's only been within the past four or six months that I've even got an Xbox 360
So you're going to wait this little war out and see what happens, huh?
Yeah, I didn't feel like fighting the crazy lines to get a Wii
I thought about getting a Wii, but I kind of looked around and then the day they went on sale I had to work anyway
And by the time I got off, everybody had sold them all out at the Target
Do you think if there wasn't all this craziness around the Wii still that you might have one right now?
If I had 250 bucks, yeah, you betcha I'd have one
I guess this is the wrong time of year to be asking right after Christmas
Oh, yeah
All right, well, thanks so much for your opinion
We want to get your opinion on a couple more things here real quick
We also want to know, we're taking a poll all night long, what do you believe was the best video game of 2006
In your opinion, using whatever criteria you want
The best video game that I've gotten, and this is kind of weird because it conflicts with my ADDN games
But Phantasy Star Universe, I've loved that whole series
And I picked that up because I love the Dreamcast version and all that
And I picked up PSU and I've had a blast with that
Are you playing more the single player or more the online in that game?
About 50-50, maybe a little more online
This game was a little bit, I think, overlooked
I agree that Phantasy Star Universe is actually a much better title than I think a lot of people are giving it credit for
In my opinion
I think part of the reason people are overlooking it is because it came out right around the same time that you had Final Fantasy XII
A real powerhouse RPG on Sony's PlayStation
Do you think people are overlooking this game?
Well, as far as I can remember, Phantasy Star hasn't been the big blowout
Hadn't had the fanboy following maybe that Final Fantasy has
What is it about Phantasy Star Universe that appeals you to that game as opposed to a game like Final Fantasy XII?
Well, having never played any of the Final Fantasy games
I create my own character, I go through it
It doesn't seem to be as complex
Or at least Phantasy Star Online didn't seem to be as complex
Now Phantasy Star Universe has a little more depth to it than the other version
I can see that
Where Phantasy Star Universe and Phantasy Star Online especially were a little more action oriented
You actually use the weapons, like you press a button to swing the weapon
Whereas Final Fantasy was always a little more weight, cast magic
It was a little more think about it in advance type thing
Think and then act as opposed to having to react to Phantasy Star Universe
Exactly
What would you say would be the worst game that you played in 2006?
The worst game
It's weird because it's a fun game but it's the worst controls
Is Sneak King
Oh, Sneak King, worst game, why did you say Sneak King?
Because it's hard as hell to control that damn thing, at least to me
So even for four bucks it's too much, you think?
Four bucks is four bucks, that's not that big of a deal
But it's hard as hell to just control it
Do you think it was a little bit of a throwaway title just because of the commercial tie-in
That maybe the people who developed it thought, it's a four dollar game
We don't need to
Oh, exactly
Alright, so I guess the quality showed up there in the end
Alright, well thank you for sharing your opinion with us there
So we got Phantasy Star Universe and Sneak King for best and worst of 2006
And we'll tally it up throughout the night and see where we end up
Brad, what are your plans for 2007 with Pod Culture?
Just going to kind of keep on doing the same old, same old
Or any big things coming up for 2007?
We've tweaked the format a little bit
We're starting to go weekly rather than bi-weekly
With the show and who knows what lies in the future
Trying to get the word out and getting some more people listening to the show
Awesome, well get the word out right now
Tell them how they can tune into Pod Culture for some more geek and sci-fi chat
Be over at PodCulture.net
Alright
And there's three or four different ways to subscribe to it
Got an iTunes link, ODO
And just the regular RSS feed
And we're listed on Dig and Pop Current and all that fun stuff
Alright, go give them a dig, PodCulture.net
Brad, thanks so much for coming and joining us on the show
I know you've been a longtime listener of Orange Lounge
And we appreciate the support
And we're glad to have you on to support your independent program as well
Thank you very much
Especially when you're looking at sales trends and what system is ultimately gonna be victorious
It's not going to be just the system that appeals to the hardcore gamer
But everybody in between from casual gamer on to maybe a mid-level
Yeah, I like video games a little bit type thing
So, big thanks to Brad for coming on and sharing his perspective on the best puzzle game
In the PlayStation 3 line and the Wii line
You know what the Wii needs to, what market they need to tap
Is the old people that go to the casino market
And you can get some games that they can actually gamble and win money
Ah, that's a lot of money right there for you
You could actually use the Wii controller to pull a slot on a machine
Exactly
I mean, World Series of Poker are tournament champions for the Wiis
And they honestly have that game out there
And how it uses the controller is beyond me
But I'm thinking there's a lot of people that shuffle into a bus and go to a casino
If you can bring that experience home
You know, maybe have the Wii puff out some cigarette smoke
Maybe that's that hidden feature of the Wii no one knows about yet
It'll blow smoke in your face
You are so strange
Alright, anyway, we're going to take a little detour here
Because we're going to bring on some more people in segment B of our show
But first, it would not be an episode of Orange Launch Radio
If we did not have our very own Dark Sakura
Providing us with her perspective
From when she surfs up the web, up, down, left
I mean, that's all she does at work all day, is surf the web
So she's finding the website for you
What she believes is the website of the week
Dark Sakura, where should the kids be pointing their browsers to this week?
I blame you for this, Rob
I blame you for this, it's so hardcore
This site of the week is one that Rob turned me onto
It's the Katerday Live Journal Community
Which I've been looking over
And yeah, I love Katerday
The only reason I still really go to 4chan anymore is for Katerday
So this one is community.livejournal.com slash Katerday
C-A-T-E-U-R-D-A-Y
And I'm looking at one right now that has a cat with one of those frilly head things
And a little wand that says
Be in your fairy kitty, plot in your death for this
Fantastic
I'm thinking in 2007 we ought to just change the name of the segment to
Dark Sakura's cat picture site of the week
No, no, no
Because that's all you ever pick
No, no, no, no, no, because I also picked Dr. Who's site
God forbid they come out with a cat Dr. Who site
Or Dr. Who gets a little cat companion
No, because he doesn't like cats
Well, what a bastard
But I got to say though, in all honesty, you know, you may think
Jamie's a little weird for her Dr. Who obsession
But she finally did her best to make me a Dr. Who fan this week
And it's actually kind of working
We've been watching season one and we're, what, like five episodes in
And I actually really enjoy it
It's a really good show
It really is good
We're actually more than that
We're on the third disc
So we're on the seventh episode in
Oh dang
I'm loving it
I think it's a great show
I can't wait to get to season two
This is my favorite episode for the first season
The Daleks
Exterminate
It was good, it was good
They should make a video game out of that
They actually have made Dr. Who video games
Yeah, but like a new one
Because it's all a, you know, new resurgence of Dr. Who
So they need new Dr. Who games, I think
We need to shoot the Cybermen the game
Well, we're getting what?
I heard we're getting a Battlestar Galactica MMO on 360
We're getting, you know, the, what else were they making?
A Firefly
You can't do a Dr. Who MMO
It doesn't have to be an MMO
I don't care if it's an MMO or not
Make a good, good platformer, good TV tie-in game
Well, Rob also showed me another show that made me giggle
He showed me the BBC Queer as Folk
Yes, because it was actually written by the same guy who did Dr. Who
And, well, the new series, anyway
And it made me just crack up
When the one person watched by teasing one of the main characters
Going ex-star-men-a
I was like, yeah
I have a sonic screwdriver now that I left it at home
You know the reason why I love the British version of Queer as Folk
Is I have a total crush on Vince
Who is the nerdy, nerdy one there
I don't like the other guy
I know, he's a, he's a
Do it, do it
Do it
Alright, anyway
But I gotta say that I like the BBC Queer as Folk more than the American one
Because it's more compa-
Like, it was over in, like, eight episodes
Which is better
I've only seen one episode of the US one
And that was with the lesbians getting married
Aww, isn't that sweet
Anyway, before this show gets any gayer
We better take a break
And we'll be back here on Orange Lounge Radio Part B to talk more about the year in review
Stay tuned, we have Travis Donovan from Travis Donovan Live coming on
We have some folks from Destructoid.com
We love that blog
And Gamertag Radio getting some representation up in Part B
Stay tuned, we'll be back after this
Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights
And is podcasted to the world twice a week
Stay tuned to our podcast feed
For the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio