[SPEAKER_09]: Tonight, May 15, 2011, PlayStation Network returns after a three-week hiatus, a new entry in a popular fighting franchise is announced, and a classic Sega Genesis video game is localized for a new release.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next couple hours with my co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_02]: First up, the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_07]: I am accomplished.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're accomplished.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I beat Portal 2 just now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_02]: I walked in like right as the ending was going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to spoil what happens, but I was like, oh, it's this part.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like this part, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the all of that part.
[SPEAKER_02]: I figured you would.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, also joining us tonight, say hello to the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, what is this you're eating tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: That looks burnt.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they don't understand what well done means versus, you know, torch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your pizza looks burnt or dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's certainly well done.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is this quadruple bacon pizza again?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's still triple bacon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Triple bacon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: How dare I increase the bacon?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, we're going to get into the show, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Blackwolf show at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very easy to hear the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: All you do is you go to allgames.com, and as long as you have Flash installed, it comes right up.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's very easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't have to worry about any of those complicated, getting it into your Winamp or iTunes or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very easy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob said it, we're easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you want to put it in WinF and iTunes, you can do that too.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's more information at allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, our chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very important to know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't use the normal All Games chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just the way we've done it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've had our own chat room for like nine years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we're Bethel.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus, we like being in charge of our own chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's a power thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, so chat.orangeslamstrator.com is where you can join us to chat with us live and give us your comments on what's going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Such as Breakman in our chat room tonight who says there is no such thing as too much bacon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I think, remember when we had the bacon party for one of your birthdays?
[SPEAKER_02]: And there was like all these bacon dishes here in house, that was too much bacon, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to say, actually, the smell is turning my stomach.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Sakura, why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I just beat Portal 2 and I played some well.
[SPEAKER_07]: And because certain people in our guild are going to be helping me run through a dungeon and learn how to tank on Rebecca Black.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still love the character and I still love people's reactions
[SPEAKER_02]: I played WoW WoW and more WoW.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm getting pissed off though because every time I try to play on Drenden I realize everybody's poor and nobody can give me the 300 gold I need to get flying.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll have to earn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do herbalism and mining.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how I did it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just go collect things for a while and then sell.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how you do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then I just need to get rid of tailoring.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, I don't want to fill up too much of WoW chat because there's a whole other show for that now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else you've been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: See any good movies lately?
[SPEAKER_02]: I see a Tron thing behind you and that made me think like, oh, Tron's on Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm supposed to go see Thor on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: With Becky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stay till after the credits.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what everybody says.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's only one character in that whole movie I care about seeing and he's only in one part.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's my dude.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no spoilers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: What have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just really two things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Portal 2 and Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: In Portal 2, I have Chapter 8 and Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's just Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: We decided to start playing some grenade launcher only games, which is kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, that's pretty much about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Portal 2 Mortal Kombat Mortal Kombat
[SPEAKER_02]: And I got my ass handed to me because I guess I'm just not good at fighters.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need more practice.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I was trying.
[SPEAKER_02]: First match was a little laggy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was a little bit disappointed at how kind of laggy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was one of those things where the frames per second suffer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like that's how Mortal Kombat kind of compensates for the lag is that your frames suffer.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then I played another match today and it was fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was very smooth and worked fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I guess it really is just about who you're connecting to.
[SPEAKER_02]: The service is a little bit wonky still.
[SPEAKER_02]: I tried to log in today and I got the PlayStation is down for maintenance message so I did it like four times and it finally let me in so kind of weird how that's working but whatever otherwise as far as new games go there is one new game I've been playing this week and that is a downloadable game on Xbox Live I believe it's on PlayStation Network as well but you know haven't really been able to tell for the past three weeks so it's on Xbox Live Arcade it's called Might and Magic Clash of Heroes I think is what it's called it's a that's old school
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, it's interesting because it's a DS game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a DS game a few years ago, but I have kind of lost touch of the Nintendo DS scene about four years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: There just hasn't really been a lot on the DS I really wanted to play that wasn't like a first-party game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But apparently this one was pretty good, and I totally missed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's out now on Xbox Live and apparently PlayStation Network, not that you'll be able to download that anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's a port of the DS version.
[SPEAKER_02]: And from what I understand, they've done some redone graphics and things like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But let me tell you a little bit about the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very much a puzzle quest, gyromancer, RPPG game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Role playing puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's another one of these.
[SPEAKER_02]: The battle system, if you watch somebody else play it, you're not going to understand what the hell is going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it has a really good ramp up in the single player mode to kind of get you used to things.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the best way I could explain it, it's kind of like Magical Drop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: But again, if you're into the Puzzle Quest 2 type of games where every battle is a full Bejeweled match, basically, this game is really right up that alley.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I would say, I actually found the game itself, the puzzle interface, to be kind of a neat little thinker.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's something a lot different from the Bejeweled-esque games, which pretty much a lot of the other games that are out there in the RPPG series kind of fall into right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe the lone exception is that...
[SPEAKER_02]: Puzzle Chronicles Puzzle Quest
[SPEAKER_02]: but uh yeah if you're into the puzzle games I really encourage you to check this one out because I think it would be worthy to your collection um not just a single player mode you can do Xbox Live matches I have not delved so far into that section yet so I can't say a lot but I can imagine that is definitely something that the DS version probably didn't have maybe it had it locally I don't know I could be totally misstating maybe someone shall correct me I don't know if it had internet play like I know DS has internet play
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox Live, Might Magic, Clash of Heroes
[SPEAKER_02]: But DarkSakura and I are going to LA.
[SPEAKER_02]: Long story.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we may or may not be back that Sunday.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we're going to try and make it back in time for the show, which would be good.
[SPEAKER_07]: No promises, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: No promises, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll let you know a little closer.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you have to stop by the cheese factory on the way back.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's still, what, about three weeks away?
[SPEAKER_02]: So, we got a little time to figure that all out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Meanwhile, join us on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, our website, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's move on I'm going to our chatroom, chat.orangeloungeradio.com CD Thunder in our chatroom says RPPG means Rob playing a video game, rated PG Rob playing PG I guess my Magic Clash of Heroes would be PG I mean there's cartoony sword fights, but no blood or anything like that Me playing Mortal Kombat would definitely not be rated PG Because I giggle all the time at the fatalities
[SPEAKER_02]: And I got to see the, uh, what is it called?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that called the Deadpool?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I know that's also one of DarkSakura's favorite comic pairs, but I think that's what it's called, the acid room?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I saw the stage fatality for that for the first time.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was gross, but I giggled.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to get my mom back over and show her that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're supposed to bring the game over.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my bad, I forgot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sky and Dark Sakura are going to Hollywood.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet they are going to be in a movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: What are you hiding from us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ranma says... A YouTube movie, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ranma says, Rob Roberts, Jamie Summers, and an all-new team-up special, Fear and Loathing in Los Angeles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we don't want to leave Loki out of all the fun stuff, but, you know, he has the baby.
[SPEAKER_07]: We can't stop here.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is Activision country.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gaming news, start us off, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there was like a firmware update today for the PlayStation Network, yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: 3.61, it's basically the update that makes you change your PlayStation Network ID.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was yesterday, but nobody knew.
[SPEAKER_03]: Today, yesterday, who cares, it all blends together, you know, I don't really give a shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you see, and I will say, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: According to this post, this post was made on the 14th.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be, oh, that would be yesterday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't know my days, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: So what can I say?
[SPEAKER_02]: They all just blend together.
[SPEAKER_03]: They all blend together, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: What day is today?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so yeah, firmware update.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, that, of course, led to the PlayStation Network starting to come up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I love this little, very official Kaz Harai video where he's, like, making a State of a Union address or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you watch?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the blandest fucking message I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, how bad?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, I hate kicking these guys when they're down, but I was watching it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was falling asleep.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is why people are drawn to Reggie Fils-Aimé from Nintendo, because you feel his enthusiasm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even when he's hawking such bullshit, like the Vitality Sensor or whatever, you at least really feel his enthusiasm.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's why he's very popular with gamers.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Kaz Hirai is very, just like, so vanilla.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, my name is Kaz Hirai.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I like to party.
[SPEAKER_03]: We here at Sony embrace fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hurrah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know my friends over here are now enjoying the fun PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Party time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fun, fun, fun, fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yesterday was Thursday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tomorrow is Saturday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, I actually want to play a little bit of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you watch this, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell me if this does not scream, I am a party animal.
[SPEAKER_01]: What is he doing with his hands?
[SPEAKER_01]: He makes these very, very distinct, like, this is the part where I'm going to clasp my hands.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's because the teleprompter tells him to.
[SPEAKER_01]: You think?
[SPEAKER_01]: Clasp hands.
[SPEAKER_01]: And now for the secret ingredient.
[SPEAKER_07]: And with the money that we have lost, we're going to actually be raising a few of our rates in the next few months to pay for this new teleprompter.
[SPEAKER_07]: We had to keep it on a separate network because PSN is actually still down and we're just put psychedelics into your breakfast cereal so that you'll believe it's back up.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, seriously, we had to work around the clock, because some dumbass put a giant clock in her server room, and we had to work around that damn thing because we couldn't move it out of the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: By we had to work around the clock, I mean everybody except me, where I went home and ate crayons.
[SPEAKER_07]: I especially like the green one, because when I cough it up later on, it looks like mucus, and I can gross out my kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it just reminded me of one of those...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really cheesy acting or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's reading off a teleprompter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because if you look where his eyes are fixated the entire time, he's reading a teleprompter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or he's staring into your soul.
[SPEAKER_07]: He can't.
[SPEAKER_07]: He has no soul.
[SPEAKER_07]: Only people with souls can stare at other people with souls.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's in the unwritten book of souls.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyways, yeah, the PlayStation Network, the first phase, I guess leading up to the full return by the end of May, included the following services.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously, the ability to sign into the PlayStation Network and Curiosity, including resetting the passwords.
[SPEAKER_03]: Restoration of online gameplay including PlayStation 3 and PSP Playback of rental video content Music and limited services from Curiosity Access to third party services such as Netflix, Hulu, Vudu, and MLB TV The Friends category and PlayStation Home Yes, thank god PlayStation Home was part of that I missed it so much
[SPEAKER_03]: Because there's so much partying going on in PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, it's fully back up throughout North America, which is awesome for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm just running home right now to go sign up on the PlayStation Network to change my password and play some games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, wait, I'm not, because I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then finally, Sony Online Entertainment announced that they're going to be offering their members a free month, which is great since it's been down for a month, and they're rewarding their players for the affected downtime.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess some double XP events for EverQuest and Vanguard, and they're going to be doing...
[SPEAKER_03]: and some special gear in DC Universe and Star Wars Galaxies.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did see, well the DC Universe one, it's like some stupid cowl thing that looks like you could be Batman or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Star Wars Galaxies, I'm surprised, I didn't even realize that was still up.
[SPEAKER_03]: But hey, learn something.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then finally, I guess Lifetime subscribers will get another load in, or I guess some more in-game currency.
[SPEAKER_03]: 500 station cash.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever station cash is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, you're right.
[SPEAKER_03]: My brain shut off for that whole thing right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So here's what I have to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not everybody's relieved to be back online and playing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is anyone still mad?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I have a feeling by next week no one's going to be mad anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just going to be forgetting about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: With E3 so close and around the corner too, this is still going to be fresh in people's minds when E3 rolls around.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's one of the disadvantages that Sony's going into this with.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: and you can say that the Red Ring of Death thing was a big debacle too but you know remember Microsoft kind of finally it took them long enough but they kind of you know came out and admitted fault for that and they were generally able to get over that whole thing whereas I don't know this is still really fresh in people's minds we're still going to have lawsuits after this that have yet to be settled and so on this is not over today I mean
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation Network is still not 100% back up.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't buy games online right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you're a developer, that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if you read one of the stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's some ridiculous stories regarding this whole thing, but I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: For me, it doesn't really matter because I'm never on PlayStation Network, so it just was an inconvenience because now I had to wait to activate my Steam copy of Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, technically I didn't have to wait, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: It was such a non-event for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm not on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't be on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, actually, this is late breaking.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's another video that was just released by Sony of Kaz Hirai giving an update as to what's going on on PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's take a look and see what's going on in this latest announcement from Kaz Hirai.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bueller Bueller Bueller
[SPEAKER_00]: Bueller?
[SPEAKER_02]: Publishers and developers obviously have been out quite a bit of money That's three weeks of lost sales and then some Again, the story is not back up just yet Apparently, Sony was not telling the developers and publishers really anything They only had the same information that the rest of us had Sony finally sent out a letter to its publishing partners It was sent out three weeks after the PlayStation Network went down Which is interesting Here's a clip of the letter
[SPEAKER_02]: Dear partner, as you know, certain PlayStation Network curiosity is, which by the way is how you pronounce it, not core-y-ro-city.
[SPEAKER_03]: Curiosity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Q, curiosity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once again, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whoa, you're so clever for putting a Q there and making me try to figure out how to pronounce a fucking thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and then they go over exactly what happened which really is all the stuff that you would have got just reading the internet and the various game blogs and what's going on let's see as a valued partner we aim to keep the lines of communication open so that you are aware of our progress
[SPEAKER_02]: Our focus has been to confirm the security of the networks, protect customer data, and get the services back online as quickly as possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will do our best to respond to all of your inquiries, and we will do everything we can to possibly support you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that is a load of crap, if I've ever heard it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We aim to keep the lines of communication open.
[SPEAKER_02]: From now on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Regurgitating what every news outlet has been saying for the past three weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I was a PlayStation Network developer, I would be so mad about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why weren't you up front with us sooner?
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's really going to give me pause in developing a PlayStation Network exclusive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony is really going to have to, as their game plan to get up and going again, they're really going to have to shell out money for exclusive agreements.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be interesting to see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, some other stuff with the whole PlayStation breach.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a rumor going around that a rented Amazon server was actually used to launch the attack, which is interesting because Amazon was having all their issues.
[SPEAKER_02]: The web service, not the...
[SPEAKER_02]: Not the same portion of Amazon that sells the books and CDs.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you have to remember, Amazon is a very large service, and they also sell web hosting as part of their service.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you might remember that a bunch of sites they hosted went down, which was a big deal for Amazon because they have service-level agreements that were being broken and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, according to Bloomberg News, they are saying that the hackers who actually hacked PlayStation Network rented a server from Amazon.com to do so, signing up for the service using fake information.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting theory, but pardon my ignorance, but how would this server be used to hack PlayStation Network?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, a DDoS is one thing, but that's not what we're talking about happening here.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is not a simple DDoS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody got in there, and the information got exposed.
[SPEAKER_02]: So how does that work using the cloud computer?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I just don't know enough about hacking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, any ideas?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, if they're brute forcing something, the more computers they have working on it, the faster it goes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it can be guaranteed that if this is true, you can see a subpoena will be going out to Amazon very soon to try and figure out whose credit card was used to sign up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, if that ends up being true, that was kind of dumb of the hackers to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they probably used a fake or stolen credit card.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll put fake names, but the credit card, we'll put a real credit card.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or a real credit card name or something like that Also, one other quick thing about this whole thing Retailers are saying that PlayStation 3 owners are just ditching the platform altogether and migrating to the 360
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what would be ironic?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hold on, just real quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know one of the stories that came out before they were saying that there was people that were hacking the PlayStation 3 using the... It's a new custom firmware called Rebug or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically it gave them access to the developer side of things where you can buy PlayStation content using this...
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently a lot of people were canceling their pre-orders for Brink for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of stuff going on in the used market, which I think DarkSakura is going to get into in a minute here.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, lots of PlayStation 3s being traded in, people going to Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, this is just from a source in Belgium.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I'm sure...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure there's an increase over normal, but I'm not sure if it's a, oh shit, PlayStation is damned situation yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: People, I mean, if you're that fickle that you're going to just dump your system because the network's down for a couple weeks, then whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's most people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then you're going to be fickle enough to buy the system again later on when there's something that you want to play on it, because that's what's going to end up happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: Live goes down every once in a while for a day and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't see people running out in mass selling their consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: But to be fair, it doesn't go down because somebody stole my credit card information.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's never been down for 22 days.
[SPEAKER_02]: True.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, there is a big difference to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I just think, you know, I do think selling your PlayStation on this alone might be a little bit throwing out the baby with the bathwater.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, there could be that exclusive that comes out that makes you kind of want to come back, sorta.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if you sell this and you mean it, then...
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, everybody has that right to make those types of choices.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I know too many people that sell systems only to buy them back when the game they really want comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of like the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're selling a 3DS back already, you really should question why you bought one in the first place.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's really the underlying problem right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, everybody knows the 3DS lineup right now is weak at best.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, but, there's going to be much better 3DS games by the end of the year between the Kid Icarus, the assumed Mario game that's going to be announced at E3, and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: There'll be more reasons to have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So why sell back a 3DS now just to buy one six months later?
[SPEAKER_02]: But there are people, I mean, and there are going to be a certain percentage of people that just feel so violated by this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've sworn off Sony.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this could damage the PlayStation 4 later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I don't know, I think it's a bit too early to really see the full ramifications.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it is so important more than ever this year to really see what Sony's bringing out the big guns this year at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not exactly loving the fact that Sony's PlayStation Network was down for 22 days that my credit card information was stolen.
[SPEAKER_03]: But at the same token, I kind of go... And they keep going back and forth on that crap, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're like, oh, well, we have no evidence that it actually was stolen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, but you still want to be sure and take all these safety precautions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, but we have really no evidence that it's been stolen.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going back and forth on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like saying, listen, it's been compromised.
[SPEAKER_03]: and be done with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't say, well, you know, there's really no evidence that they looked at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, they have the data.
[SPEAKER_03]: They stole all of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: They maybe just deleted the file and said, pat themselves on the back and said, good job me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hacked Sony.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I just, it's going to be interesting because later on this year, you still have some big, you know, The Last Guardian is a game that a lot of people are foaming at the mouth over.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's very, it's going to be like, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: Will people forgive us if the games are good enough?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be very, very interesting these next few months.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think DarkSakura has a little more to add to this whole retail angle.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, actually, there is a notice that, at least in the U.S., that 10 of the most popular online titles that were for PlayStation 3 dropped by an average of 7.4%, basically since the 20th of April.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then the same 10 titles saw a 0.7% increase on Xbox 360 for sales.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, one of the UK retailers was reporting that they had double the amount of PS3s being brought in and then half of those people picking up an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: That also sales of used titles have just completely been borked by PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: So like two coming in at four?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all fuzzy map it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, at any rate, most people really are that fickle.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's really people in general, I think, are just so fickle that they're going to not put up with any type of inconvenience.
[SPEAKER_07]: When high real life doesn't always work out for you, you're going to have to wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to the chat room at chat.orange.com for some feedback going on right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: GameGuru in our chat room says Red Ring of Death and PlayStation Network being hacked are only comparable in terms of showing the deficiencies that Microsoft and Sony has.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, because Microsoft was always a software company then they were getting into hardware.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, in Microsoft, though, I think that their response was a little bit better than Sony's.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, at least, granted, I don't think they ever really admitted how many are affected.
[SPEAKER_03]: Trust me, it's more than the 1% that they were quoting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's every single one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every single one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every single one launched.
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every single one will be affected.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you have one that's from the launch, you know, 2005 or whatever, and it's still working today, that's a fluke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trust me, I know every single one will die.
[SPEAKER_02]: Salacious Pop responding to something you just said a little bit ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Loki is under-recognizing the huge dude-bro contingent who only play Black Ops, Battlefield, Modern Warfare all day and that's all they play.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're Sony geeks and never got into Halo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, I would add to that, the Blu-ray player was enticing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: Like it or not, the Blu-ray factor being in the PlayStation 3 is still selling a lot of those over Xbox 360s to the dude bro contingent that Salacious Pop brings up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not the audience that would be listening to this show, but the people that are like, oh, this thing plays Blu-rays and it plays Modern Warfare?
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: well first of all your blu-ray player will still work and it's back up so what's the problem all of those people now that it took my credit card info so if you gave them your credit card info well on top of that just call the bank and change your shit you know a little inconvenience for your own security sorry you're gonna have to deal with it suck it up
[SPEAKER_02]: I still don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if somebody tries to use my number, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll call and cancel the card.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they'll trace it back to whoever did it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: If that happens, you're going to care when it happens if it happens at a bad time.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's not going to affect my credit.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not going to affect my finances.
[SPEAKER_07]: The funds will be frozen and I'll get a new card.
[SPEAKER_07]: And hopefully they'll catch whoever did it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Other than that, don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and I said this a couple weeks before on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: If somebody were to use this credit card information that's been stolen, you're really an idiot.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you're just asking to get caught for this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the FBI is on this now.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just waiting for someone to fuck this up and give away how this all kind of happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also the amount of information they actually got.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to take them forever to parse through that stuff anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, there is the risk that your identity might be stolen or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think it's very unlikely even still.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they'll catch them before they even come close to parsing through all the data that's on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree with this comment in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: DefectiveCandy at chat.ornersoundtrade.com says, If someone tries to use my credit card, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sucks to be them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm broke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was just thinking that, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really... I really...
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, wasting time freaking out over this is really exactly just that, wasting time.
[SPEAKER_07]: All you're doing is working yourself up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Selling your PlayStation 3 is going to mean you're not going to be able to play whatever that is that's going to come out later.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then you're going to have to spend more money to get another one if you want to play it badly enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: So in the end, lacking patience just makes you a loser.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, but at the same time, I can understand where somebody is going to sell their PlayStation 3 back over this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I just would say think ahead because you don't want to do something reactive only to get sweetened back by Sony later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: We also still don't know what they plan to do to kind of right the wrong and what they're going to give as part of this, I guess you could say, severance package or whatever to kind of come back to the PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't know?
[SPEAKER_03]: And again, I...
[SPEAKER_02]: If I was thinking of selling my PlayStation 3 back, I'd kind of be waiting until after E3 to make sure I really want to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not selling my fucking PS3 back because it's a fully backwards compatible PS3 with a 500 gig hard drive in it that I don't play on the PlayStation Network and hardly ever buy games for.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, I'm content with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I use it for Blu-rays.
[SPEAKER_03]: Great.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: If there's a Sony game that really is awesome that I have to have, I can get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for everything else that's multi-platform, you better believe it, I'm getting it on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because that's just what I play more.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's more convenient for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: PS3's hooked up to the front TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nelly wants to play Animal Crossing still.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel like it's been PlayStation Network all the time for the past three weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Believe it or not, there is news in other parts of the gaming world and I think it's time we took a trip there.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about Xbox?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about something going on in the 360 world, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: So along with that, there's also going to be some other updates including PayPal.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's coming on May 19th, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll be able to use your PayPal account to add funds for buying Xbox Live Marketplace materials and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Extremely interesting in light of everything that's going on at Sony that you can kind of use a middleman now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: you know use the connect to move your avatar around kind of like a talk show almost this sounds kind of weird to me because don't they have a video chat program as it is right now they do but you can't wave around as your avatar
[SPEAKER_02]: And ugly pedophiles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, as I mentioned, the XGD3.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the new format that's going to be for the discs.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other thing is, of course, they're going to be adding some more copy protection.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also going to be flashing all of those people that have flashed modded drives.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be flashing those drives back to their stock firmwares and going to be fixing it in a way where you can't change it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you can't easily change it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll get to that a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_03]: But...
[SPEAKER_03]: Neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that also saves me a step because I have one flash system still that we... It was left over from... I just didn't want to bother to flash it back.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now I don't have to.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to do it for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think about this news of what's coming out in the Xbox Spring Update?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, usually these updates are pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's at least one little tidbit in there where you're like, oh, that's going to be awesome to have.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like the, I don't know, like the USB storage or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this time around, I'm looking at the updates going, eh, none of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, PayPal, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know who would use that, but not me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd use it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: If I was buying a lot of content on Xbox Live, I'd use it because I sell a lot of shit on eBay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Usually, when I'm not dumping my funds back into my bank account, I usually have quite a bit sitting in my PayPal account.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess I can get that.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, I don't really use PayPal like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I use PayPal to pay for Skype, and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've been using Skype ever since they were a company based in the UK, and it was actually very easy to do the international funds through PayPal.
[SPEAKER_02]: so that's why I have a PayPal account I don't use it for anything else I use it a lot for just buying stuff online I buy a lot of stuff on eBay I buy a lot of stuff like subscriptions for things I'll pay for that that makes sense though for those people that actually use PayPal as a wallet from like eBay and things like that that is kind of a neat way to be able to buy the games I use mine for eBay and Dan uses it for his RC cars alright I get it I guess that is a little bit more exciting but I don't know
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about me again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am not excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's nothing in it for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, I don't buy a lot of download content anymore for games other than maybe like a Grand Theft Auto or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I probably wouldn't buy download content for a lot of things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I may or may not have bought Dance Central songs the other day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's just, you know, I have certain hardware configurations in various places that facilitate the ability to not have to purchase that stuff and yet enjoy the full range of content.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's the play's way I can say that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I really don't buy a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mainly because look at what I'm playing each week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Grand Theft Auto, Grand Theft Auto, Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's not any new content coming out for that, so there's nothing for me to buy.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Hero, anything they put out, I'll buy.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just the way it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let me move on to a story about something that maybe you'll be using your PayPal money to download.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: There has been an ESRB rating that's come out for the Genesis game Monster World 4 coming out on Xbox Live Arcade and PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, that kind of spilled the news a little early.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sega of Europe actually confirmed that they are bringing the game over to PlayStation Network and Wii Virtual Console so odd that they left Xbox Live Arcade out of that but whatever maybe something's happening in the future I don't know there's going to be a vintage collection that actually comes out later in
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they've been milking those Genesis games for all they're worth, and there's still people that'll pay five bucks a game for it, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: This collection's gonna have Wonder Boy and Monster Land, Revenge of Shinobi, Alex Kidd and Miracle World, Wonder Boy and Monster World.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, all those games have already come out on the virtual console here in North America.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the interesting thing about this, Monster World 4, it was never actually officially released on a console outside of Japan,
[SPEAKER_02]: and get this, it's going to be localized as a part of this collection.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Sega is actually localizing this ages old, what is this, 94, I think, game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't say that, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's when I graduated.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't write the news, I just report it.
[SPEAKER_03]: As trolls would say on the internet, Sega does when Nintendo don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: In other words, localizing an old game that maybe fans might want to play just because they can.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the best zing I've heard on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't say that.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Cho Aniki came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's not a Nintendo game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it wasn't Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, when Sin and Punishment, the original, came out, they didn't bother to translate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, a lot of those games didn't need translation, but this is really the first time that they've gone back and actually are going to translate a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I can't imagine Monster World 4 has the epic dialogue of a role-playing game, but it's probably got what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of a Mario-y style game, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sort of a side-scrolling adventure game, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's probably got a decent amount of dialogue.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of neat that they're localizing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time, if I have to buy this whole big collection with all these other Genesis games just to get it, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I gotta be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: well I don't know I hear Monster World 4 is really really good and I'm missing a lot by not playing it but my desire to go and pay money for this old 94 game I don't know I'm not like super excited about it I think there's other stuff in the gaming world my money would be spent on but I guess I'll wait and see when this comes out maybe everybody will be like you have to play it it's great and we were missing so much before a good game is still a good game at the end of the day right so alright moving on DarkSakura what do you got for us
[SPEAKER_07]: I have other news related to Disney.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm first going to point out something that I totally loathe that this article does.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, the article says, Disney Studio costs up $3 million for violating kiddie gamers' privacy.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Disney didn't do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was titles that had been acquired before Disney acquired Playdom, which is their online kids gaming thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So to say Disney did it, yeah, Disney may have accepted all the liability, but it wasn't Disney that did it, and I hate when titles are misleading like that, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: But at any rate, Playdom, which is the Disney Social Game Studios, paid $3 million as a settlement for titles that were there before Playdom acquired, I'm sorry, that were acquired by Playdom before Disney acquired it, were collecting kids' ages and email addresses without parental consent.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was posted without parental consent.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Disney coughed up the cash for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Curse of Acclaim
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and then Playdom bought out Acclaim.
[SPEAKER_07]: But actually the former Acclaim CEO, Howard Marks, is also being named in the case.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I would say, you know, whoever holds whatever rights are left, you know, Disney needs to go after them.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really tricky, especially when you're talking about games marketed towards kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what game comes to mind for me is that Smurfs Village game on iOS has taken a lot of heat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's a Capcom game, if I'm not mistaken.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Smurfs Village game, because of how easy it is for kids to get sucked into that game and buy the little Smurf berries.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just touch, touch, touch to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've heard these stories of kids spending hundreds of dollars on these dumbass Smurf berries to make things grow faster in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: 10 year olds who don't have a true concept of money don't understand that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And parents that don't have a concept of parenting don't understand that their kids are buying stuff through their phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's funny though because I think back to a time when I was probably like 14 or 15 and I was on Prodigy and Prodigy used to charge for using chat rooms and one month I ran up like a $90 bill in the chat room or something like that and my mother... Oh God, I never heard the end of it, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never heard the end of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we did the same thing in Prodigy but it wasn't necessarily because of the...
[SPEAKER_03]: The chat room, it was because the number that it picked to dial was long distance.
[SPEAKER_03]: No!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Love dialing.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, I used to have the hookup on AOL back in the day because I dialed in on an 800 number.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought you had to pay for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And had a free account.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, I thought you had to pay for the AOL.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was a chatroom host for Cartoon Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was almost impossible not to have a free account through AOL because you'd threaten to cancel or they'd just send you another 72-day trial or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a ridiculous amount of... 720-hour trial, that's what it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, boy, that's 30 days.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but I'm referring to back when it was like $3 an hour or something Back when it had just gotten out of DOS Ranma in the chatroom says Sky, if she didn't beat you with the belt, you got off lucky, lol No, all the abuse in my household was always emotional, never physical
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not abuse.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on and talk about release dates and what's coming out to a store near you, depending on where you live.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll start with the US.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not much this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: L.A.
[SPEAKER_03]: Noire on the Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 being the biggest title of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of a big title, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Witcher 2, Assassins of Kings on PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: coming out from Atari, The First Templar on Xbox 360, SpongeBob SquigglePants for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the game that's sort of like WarioWare, but here it's terrible, so, you know, keep that in mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Another terrible title for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: What a shock!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, shocker.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cake Mania Main Street for the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure it's all like the other Cake Mania games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fable 3 on PC this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's it Alright, moving on to Japan and what's coming out over there You get your version of Portal 2 this week on the Xbox 360 And the PlayStation 3, those coming out on May the 19th And yeah, those are like localized versions for Japan I don't know if they have all new voice actors or if it uses subtitles or what But yeah, they're getting their own version of Portal 2 So they can get in on the fun that we're having over here
[SPEAKER_02]: again that's on the Xbox 360 and the PlayStation 3 also coming out on the PlayStation 3 this week excuse me it's a price reduction not a new game but FIFA Soccer 11 moves into the best hit series from EA it's like it's a big price reduction in Japan this week moving on to the Nintendo Wii nothing this week what a surprise
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo 3DS Dead or Alive Dimensions finally gets its release this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm sure we'll be hearing some reports on that game and how it turned out because we'll be getting it soon enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also on the 3DS over there, Animal Resort, Dobutsu no Tsukuro comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Shadow Wars also comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trying to look at this Animal Resort and honestly when I see the box, the first thing I think of, honest, Africa.
[SPEAKER_02]: because it looks just like that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's putting out Animal Resort?
[SPEAKER_02]: Animal Resort is being put out by... Who is this?
[SPEAKER_02]: AQ Interactive is putting out the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But look at this.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's elephants you can take pictures of and hippopotamus.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like you feed them because there's little items there on the bottom and it looks like this guy is dragging a type of fruit to feed the hippopotamus.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this is adorable.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's apparently penguins in this.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now I kind of want it, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, for a 3DS title, the graphics are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of an interesting twist on Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet what this is is it's kind of like Nintenzu.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe it's like Anemon Snap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I was just wondering if the only reason I asked who made it is because there's a title coming from Ubisoft called Zoo Mania that looks similar to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm wondering if it's actually the exact same game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll have to look that up.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the Sony PSP this week on May the 19th, Akiba's Strip comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is... That's what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a game where you get people to strip.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you don't get people to strip.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, you do.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: By fighting them, their clothes will be removed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, that is what's really happening in this picture.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like she's wearing cat ears and no pants.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well...
[SPEAKER_03]: They do not have fully nude games on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Trust me, I've looked.
[SPEAKER_07]: The wife really wants one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, no, they sell them on J-List.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're X-rated UMDs, that's what those are.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they don't have actual PSP games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on, this is Japan we're talking about.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're very conservative when it comes to video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dead or Alive Dimensions, and L.A.
[SPEAKER_02]: Noire
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Kinect, Windows Phone and an array of other Windows devices.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, of course, they announced that they'll still be supporting the platforms that it's on already.
[SPEAKER_03]: The PSP and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I guess it says also Skype users with Link, Outlook and Xbox Live and other communities will be able to connect with Skype as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm wondering now if we're going to see Windows with Skype built in as a default program and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just think it's kind of neat that they're going to have...
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder if they're going to do the Avatar Connect with Skype.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Certainly this is going to be coming to the 360 sooner rather than later.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kind of surprised this isn't being rushed for the spring update because that's a pretty big addition.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand that I guess right now the Connect to video chat will work with Windows Messenger, but I don't know anyone that uses Windows Messenger.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not also on an Xbox So I don't know But you know the interesting thing about this We've been using Skype here at Orange Lounge Radio Since before podcasting I think we took our first Skype call Probably in 03 However old Skype is We were on that really early We're pretty loyal to the program Until it steals our credit card information Or something We're not going to go anywhere Until it out parties Kaz Exactly
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be very interesting because pretty soon we're going to be able to invite phone calls from people on their connects to chat with the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be something.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is pretty something, except the only problem is you still can't stream the show onto the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish there was something they would do about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not unless you have... No, you can't do it through Pandora.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it Last.fm that's on there or Pandora?
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last.fm's on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Last.fm.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think you can get it through there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you could hook it up to a PC, but what's the point?
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's hooked up to a PC already, then you might as well just use the PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Misty, who is one of our archive experts in our chatroom, says she knows we were taking them at least by episode 111, which would have been 04.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty sure we were taking them before that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so it was a while ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, be very curious to see what this kind of all pans out to.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people are saying they paid too much for Skype.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how much Skype is worth.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's worth nothing to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not paying for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: uh yeah I mean Skype doesn't really do ads and they're free you know it's it's they're gonna have to add ads to it at some point I think and I don't know how people are gonna feel about that well they have to have some I mean they're they have you know the Skype out services and stuff like that that's kinda neat you know um and you know if they're pushing the whole family angle and stuff hey now you can call your friends on their phones and stuff like that or I don't know
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, the Level Up event was held by Namco Bandai this week, and we want to go over some news from that event, including, and this makes me very excited, a new Soul Calibur game was announced, and I love the Soul Calibur series.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, Soul Calibur V was announced this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a little teaser trailer that was released.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me see if I can play a little bit of it here in Z Studio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a whole lot of characters showed up in there, but I think Nightmare's in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently there's a new character named Patroclus, who's supposed to be the son of Sophitia and Rothian.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game is going to be out in 2012 for the Xbox 360 and the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is set 17 years after the events of Soul Calibur 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, I guess there's going to be quite a bit of roster revision going on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Siegfried is also supposed to be in the game, so could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our kind should not exist in this world Not ever again
[SPEAKER_02]: So this trailer is more like the opening cutscene that you would see in the game, probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't really show a lot of gameplay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's your very typical announcement trailer.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope you still get to make your own character and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually didn't play any of the make your own character ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting tweet that actually came out in response to this.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game director, Daishi Odashima, actually tweeted this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I asked the company if we can call the game Soul Edge 2, but they said no.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that might give you an idea about where this is going also, because remember, the first Soul Calibur game, if you will, was really Soul Edge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also news coming out of the event, Tekken X Street Fighter hasn't even started yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep in mind there's two games being made.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's Street Fighter X Tekken and Tekken X Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently Namco Bandai has said they haven't even really started work on Tekken X Street Fighter yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: The quote from producer Katushiro Harada said, quote, we really haven't started on Tekken X Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_02]: things are going well with Street Fighter X Tekken and we'll have more on that at E3 we hope you look forward to that so I don't know maybe they're spacing the games out a little bit kind of interesting by the way speaking of Street Fighter X Tekken a new teaser came out for it this week and it shows Cammy so Cammy will be in the game which really doesn't surprise anyone I'm sure some other little bits and pieces that came out of that as well
[SPEAKER_02]: Ace Combat Assault Horizons coming out October 11th in the US and the 14th in Europe.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a new CG feature film based on Tekken called Tekken Blood Vengeance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tales of Graces and Tales of Abyss also coming out on the PS3 and the 3DS respectively.
[SPEAKER_02]: And wait for it, Naruto Shippuden Ultimate Ninja Impact coming out on the PSP because your life just wasn't complete without another Naruto game.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: And funny enough, totally ironically, I had no idea DarkSakura was going to pick this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was playing this last night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oom Jamalami.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I put in the one I thought was your favorite.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is my favorite song in the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, Umjermalami, yeah, and I did cover Parappa series, but I'm doing Umjermalami anyway, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Umjermalami was put out by Nana Onsha and Namco in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, the music died behind you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just YouTube's failing us tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's being uber fail.
[SPEAKER_07]: at any rate, it came out in Japan on March 18th, 1999 and in North America on August 17th, 1999 and yeah, it plays like Parappa, pretty much Namco released the arcade version and it had a guitar controller so that you could get the sensation of playing a guitar I mean, it's very similar to Guitar Freaks we've seen one of these machines, remember?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do!
[SPEAKER_02]: I do remember the machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had to get on my knees to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get your minds out of the gutter, people.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was made for kids, and I'm a little tall.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, it's like a Simon Says sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, their characters will do something, and then you do something.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you have to basically repeat whatever it tells you to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so through the game, you have a Chop Chop Master Onion from Parappa.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's where you get Dojo Casino.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all in the mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: And she goes, yeah, my guitar is in my mind!
[SPEAKER_07]: And then...
[SPEAKER_07]: But the whole thing is basically Lammy trying to get to her concert with her group Milk Can at the Chop Shop Master Arena.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so she has to put out a fire and babysit babies with Kathy Pillar, which is this song.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then fly an airplane.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then chop down a tree to make a new guitar.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then she actually, well, gets sent to an island, but in the Japanese version she actually dies and goes to hell.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I found a movie file of that to play for everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's my cue, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it is, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is where Rob stops texting on his iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, let me bring this up.
Distortion.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Two more minutes and I'm history.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's running in front of traffic.
[SPEAKER_02]: These interludes were so bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Slips on the banana peel that PJ Berry is eating the bananas.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cracks her head.
[SPEAKER_07]: And dies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stupid PJ Berry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stupid fat bear.
[SPEAKER_07]: No bitch or 2D.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I think every time I show up to this show, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then the credits roll.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is great.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, there's the guitarist!
[SPEAKER_11]: Come on, hurry, hurry!
[SPEAKER_11]: We need you out there!
[SPEAKER_11]: Not yet, not yet!
[SPEAKER_07]: And then she goes on stage with Teriyaki Yoko.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and that whole thing was cut out of the US version.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, they had her showing up on a desert island.
[SPEAKER_07]: and so it went into the whole Vital Idol song.
[SPEAKER_07]: And where she gets faxed back to life instead of teleported via fax from the island.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now I will tell you something, because I'll tell you why I would pick this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan and I discussed this today.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I was saying how I had a demo disc of this and it had...
[SPEAKER_07]: All of the stuff in the game just locked out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it had the original, you know... Because in Chop Chop Master Onion's song it said, you could play in hell and go far.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's on the demo disc, not on... Anyway, but all this was left in Europe and Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: But in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: people had to get a stick up their butt and have her go to an island.
[SPEAKER_07]: So anyway, you have four different ranks.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have...
[SPEAKER_07]: Good, you have bad, and you have awful, and if you get below awful, then your song ends.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the quality of music changes also with each one too.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now you can also get cool, and so you basically can freestyle unless you really screw up.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you keep cool by the end of the song, you'll get a cool ending to the level.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if it flashes good, then you go back into normal play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, for this one, you know, if you get cool, then Teriyaki Yoko goes, okay, you can go by yourself, and then you're in this tunnel, but if you drop back down to Goji, he goes, okay, well, you need me after all.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you also get different morphers to your sound.
[SPEAKER_07]: You get a flanger, you get a harmonizer, you get the wah-wah, you get distortion and a reverb.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're actually from different items you get.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, in order, it's a fire siren, a caterpillar rattle, Captain Fuss and Pepper's false teeth, who was the headbanging pilot in, I think, Stage 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh god, I love that stage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I play that music?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: That music was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I could never beat that unless I did it cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: That level, uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I could always get it to go cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me play a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Horns on!
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a trap level.
[SPEAKER_09]: This person's going for cool, too, so... Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: And so you also got a fever time so that when you enter a level after it's been completed, it brings up a chocolate screen with symbols.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you input everything in the right order, when the level is cool, the screen goes really crazy and symbols fly all over the place.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then you can hit those buttons repeatedly and get uber points.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, the arcade version was called Um Jammer Lamy Now, and it had a guitar controller, and it had the buttons for triangle, circle, X, and square are strummers in the middle of the guitar, and the L button is a slider at the top of the guitar, and there's a scratch disc at the bottom instead of the R button.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's really the same as the home version, and there is an ability to play with Parappa in that too.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you've got Lamy mode, and then you have your co-op, which is Lamy and Ramy, who is the dark version of Lamy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then you have Versus, which is Lamy versus Ramy.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have Solo Parappa, you have Lamy and Parappa, and then you have Versus, Lamy, and Parappa.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then you have a special mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically, you can just listen to any of the songs in good, bad, awful, or cool mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, of course, you could also do that if you had the PSX Play little program and could rip all your files, but I digress.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you also had, like I said, there were the changes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, I brought up the hell changes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: But for Paul Chuck in Stage 5, instead of chopping trees down for the fun, it was changed knowing that we're here for the fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, of course, Teriyaki Yoko, like I said.
[SPEAKER_07]: And... Lammy is actually wearing a camouflage t-shirt and has jungle makeup to show that she's in the jungle.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh...
[SPEAKER_07]: and then also the scene before stage 7 has Catty Cat and Masan riding a camel and the ending credits is an instrumental version of Keep Your Head Up and then Chop Chop Master Onion's music was of course changed the demo like I said has everything in it and then there was three soundtracks came out one called Make It Sweet which is all the music done by Milk Can and
[SPEAKER_07]: and there was called Ice Cream which was remixed versions of the songs and that was with Dread Fox as Parappa and then the whole original soundtrack which I've got somewhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, the game is super awesome, it's super fun and it's...
[SPEAKER_07]: Really great, but I still think it's stupid that they had to change it.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, GameVortex criticized it, and I think this is the best way of saying something.
[SPEAKER_07]: They said it was an unfortunate thing, and said, Did I miss some logical leap?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think our kids can handle such a basic concept as hell.
[SPEAKER_07]: The end.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, there it is, your classic game of the week, Um Jamalami.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, and I was none the wiser when I first played this game, because, you know, I wasn't really following the import gaming scene, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, I had bought a certain game, actually, it was at Anime Expo, and I talked my way into a demo disc, because I was so excited about this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, we are going to take a quick break here live, but don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got plenty more to come in Part B tonight, including some other new game announcements.
[SPEAKER_02]: In Rapid Fire News tonight, a big arcade collection has been announced.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, a big popular beta has been announced for later this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be huge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, we're going to get into some more lawsuits in Part B, some Portal 2 news, and, yeah, some more localization, or maybe not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unlocalized games that you can still buy locally That'll make sense in a little bit Anyhow, we're going to take a break But stay tuned guys, we'll be back with more Of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: and some discussions there in part A about PlayStation Network, of course, coming back online, although I don't know, it's still a little spotty for some people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Monster World 4 getting a localization finally, and of course the big story this week about Microsoft buying Skype.
[SPEAKER_02]: I noticed in studio here that Loki is playing Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks very nice on your laptop, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_02]: The graphics for that are pretty smooth.
[SPEAKER_02]: You must have a pretty powerful little laptop there, I didn't realize.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, are you enjoying the game so far?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like you're pretty far into it, from what I can tell.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I do Comic Insanity with Tiara, also known as Mar and Marvel, and Dan Shadow.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we have a new one coming up on Tuesday with our new format, where we introduce a few new segments and condense a couple other segments.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's new stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you can find us at Infamous.net, N-F-A-M-O-U-S.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you can also find us on Twitter at Comic Insanity, with no I.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, my podcast that I do with my buddy, Extifer, The Best Little Horde House in Azeroth, about all things World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not having a format switch this week, but I believe we're having DarkSakura on as our guest this week, so that'll be exciting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, you can check that out, www.hordehouse.com for more information about our little program there where we talk about the World of Warcraft, but never too seriously, because I'll tell you what, I've been kind of a jaded Warcraft player lately.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I have not been the most happy-go-lucky about the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know everybody's like, well then quit, asshole!
[SPEAKER_02]: But I've got too many friends that play, and how would I slay internet dragons without my WoW?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, more talk about World of Warcraft on that show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do not fap to Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although apparently, I don't want to give too much away, but apparently Extifer has been playing on a server notorious for the FAP chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he's going to give us a report on that this week, so that should be exciting.
[SPEAKER_02]: As a role player, you're going to really look forward to that, huh, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, let's get into some rapid fire news, some quick stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a lot of little stories this week that unfortunately the PlayStation Network was kind of dominating over.
[SPEAKER_02]: But let's get to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, some quick stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, by the way, your Twitter topic is coming up after this.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you haven't gotten your tweets in, you've got like two minutes to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Including one item that actually will be played on the PlayStation Network, Starhawk.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is the new, I guess, more futuristic sequel to Warhawk.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll be coming soon, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure it's going to be something they show off at E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I've been teased for a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: I even think there's some assets or something that leaked out about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But apparently... Oh, next year is when it's due out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be the same kind of format as Warhawk was.
[SPEAKER_03]: They even promised space battles at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not sure how that's going to really work, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, a single-player story mode and a build-in battle system will be coming to it as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, if you like that game, you may want to check it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know that the original game is really cheap right now, so if you want to check that out, it might be worth it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course...
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, yes, the developers of Splosion Man comes, uh, Splosion, uh, Ms.
[SPEAKER_03]: Splosion Man, and, of course, not to, um, you know, pass up capitalizing on what might be an internet sensation, um, you know, 2G1C, you know, might, some people may think Two Girls, One Cup, but no, Two Girls, One Controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, in this game mode... I try not to think about Two Girls, One Cup ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: uh two girls one controller it's a different mode that's going to be in the game you're actually going to control each uh one of the Ms.
[SPEAKER_03]: Splosion men um with one analog stick on the controller and you would detonate them with the you know trigger buttons I believe so um it's interesting um
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how that'll play, but it's something that they're throwing in that you can try out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then finally, as I was mentioning earlier, of course, a new update coming out for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's gonna reflash those people that had modified firmwares on their DVD drives.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, to combat that, of course, people out there have tools to get around things.
[SPEAKER_03]: And one hacker or toolmaker, I guess, Electron, has released eTool version 0.2.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a new tool for extracting and injecting the key from the light-on fat drives that were flashed with the new firmware by the beta dash.
[SPEAKER_03]: So because those firmwares, once they get flashed, it's unable to be read by popular programs like the Jungle Flasher and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So now this program will actually read the keys from that and it will also read flashed drives for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I have a feeling that this new format that they're going to be putting out there will get bypassed very quickly.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, I have a feeling it will be bypassed within a month.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's probably being very generous.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then, yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think that hack poses a pretty serious threat to all the research?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's one of the many.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Commodore Forever, they're working on a new firmware for their all drives, actually, and I believe that already is almost done.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just doing some further testing with the new XGD3 format.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm assuming, though, that that's probably bypassing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then there's also the X360 key, which is supposed to be coming out at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to emulate the drive altogether, and that, I think, is the worst threat they could possibly have because right there, that's playing game ISOs off of a hard drive without needing to really modify your system.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's plug-and-play.
[SPEAKER_03]: You plug it in between your drive and the system.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Diablo 3 Diablo 3 Diablo 3 Diablo 3
[SPEAKER_02]: Diablo 3 Diablo 3 Diablo 3
[SPEAKER_02]: It did finally go official, but it wasn't supposed to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this was leaked early from the Korean side of Blizzard Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a new follower system in Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: You actually hire characters to help you out in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: This kind of sounds inspired by Torchlight, actually, because you can kind of have the pet and one of the classes, you can get all these little demon followers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: But these followers will actually be in different classes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Enchantress, Scoundrel, Templars.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to be able to give these guys weapons, rings, and you'll even be able to give them their own skills.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, this really sounds like the pets from Torchlight, but maybe a little more fleshed out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Souls, this game is going to be hard as hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to come out October 11th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, this is the unofficial, well, I shouldn't say unofficial, but the don't call it a sequel, but it is to Demon's Souls, which was one of those hard as hell games on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the best hands down PlayStation 3 exclusive games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Souls is going to be coming out on October 11th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though there's been the PlayStation Network outages and so forth, that's not going to stop them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kai Hirono, who's the producer of the game, spoke with CVG saying that the outage caused, quote, some problems for the development, but that the team is, quote, in contact with Sony and is aiming to meet a street date of October 11th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's nice that Sony's talking to some of their people.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also, finally from me tonight, oh god, it's taken only 413 episodes of Orange Lounge Radio But finally, I get to report on a story about Lady Gaga And yes, it reports, I'm sorry, it relates to gaming That's right, Lady Gaga is coming to, I can't believe I'm going to say this either, Farmville Oh, I saw the ads for that
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Lady Gaga and Zynga a while ago had this whole donation for Japanese disaster relief going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I guess that partnership has grown into the May 17th opening of GagaVille.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is going to be a...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: At first, I kind of looked at this and I was like, oh, God, really?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is so gross.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I'm going to have to go and play Farmville again if I want to hear new Gaga songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, fuck you, Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to do this.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then I kind of thought about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, actually, considering that, like, you know, Gaga's fan base is a lot of like, you know, let's face it, like.
[SPEAKER_03]: Losers?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you Middle-aged to teenage girls And who's playing mostly Farmville?
[SPEAKER_02]: Middle-aged to teenage girls So whereas I'm not super excited about this They're targeting the right audience So it is really smart marketing Of course, just as a person who's not a big fan of Zynga products I'm not that excited, but I get it
[SPEAKER_03]: She was on American Idol the other day, and I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really don't understand the appeal of her, and I have no appeal of her as a person, her as an artist, her music.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's seriously lost on me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think her music's very catchy.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what it's all about.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think she's a very genuine person from her interviews and so forth.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's genuine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: How strange can it be?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of marketing machine behind it, yes, but she's a living, breathing piece of art.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how I see her.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's okay if you don't get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Art is meant to be interpreted in many different ways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Being as strange as possible is not art.
[SPEAKER_03]: How fucking crazy can I be?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, hey, I'm not fucking calling what I do art.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, if anyone calls it... I just keep thinking of Eddie Izzard now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to put poop on my head and sell myself to an art gallery.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I'm waiting for the full fecal suit from Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's on its way.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the path she is traveling.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe when she's in the retirement home 50 years from now, she'll be wearing a poop suit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please, it's just going to be... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: She'll have...
[SPEAKER_03]: She'll make some sort of suit out of some sort of dinosaur fossil.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come out there, you know, calling like an eagle or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take a giant dump on stage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Roll around in it and set herself on fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: Boom!
[SPEAKER_03]: Lady Gaga concert next year, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: alright look I can't believe I'm about to say this but this is too much Lady Gaga chat for our show so let's move on with some more gaming news do you never saw the link I sent the two links I sent you what's that well you know I keep up with the gal fashion and one of the companies that I like their clothes is actually Lady Gaga's working with one of the men's styles to release a bunch of t-shirts I get all my news from the fuck yeah Lady Gaga Tumblr anyhow and I sent you paper dolls
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: More gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, how about Angry Birds?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's on Chrome OS and the Chrome browser.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can actually play it now, apparently.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's free to play, has microtransactions, but the web-exclusive ones have Chrome bombs and exclusive Chrome levels and the pay-per-use Mighty Eagle.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: What, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I'm just reading our chat room, chat.orangelandradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: TigerClaw says, doing OLR should be considered an art form.
[SPEAKER_02]: And SalaciousPop says, OMG, Lady Gaga channeling Gigi Allen.
[SPEAKER_02]: He did all those, or maybe Alin, I don't know this artist, but he did all of those things that Loki just said, by the way, including the fire and the poop.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's already been done, Loki, so Gaga can't do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about gaming?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Minecraft stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, the creator, Marcus Pearson, has a poll on his blog about MinecraftCon, seeing if people would be interested in attending it in Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there is a...
[SPEAKER_07]: A no and a yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so far, no is winning.
[SPEAKER_02]: So... I will be bringing a bunch of blocks to put in front of the door to trap everyone in MinecraftCon.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm looking at the screen capture from, I'm guessing, from Minecraft and it looks completely... These people have too much damn time.
[SPEAKER_07]: So how about Mortal Kombat?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Minecraft con's not a terrible idea because, hell, they have cons for people that dress up like furry animals.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, if the furries can have their con... Mortal Kombat Collection will be... The original trilogy will be going on the Xbox Live Arcade and the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, of course, collection is spelled with a K. And it will also be on PC for 800 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does Lady Gaga have a convention?
[SPEAKER_07]: Would it be called Gaga for GagaCon?
[SPEAKER_02]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know Cher has a convention.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did I ever tell you about that story?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was in LA.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was in Woodland Hills specifically for work doing some stuff down there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was staying at a hotel and I get in this elevator with literally 15 people all decked out in Cher shirts and concert.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was kind of like, oh, is Cher in town?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're like, no, there's a Cher convention going on here at the hotel.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm like, oh, is she here?
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're like, no, she's in France.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: But she sent a video or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: if I can turn back time I literally walked into a Cher convention and despite what you may think about homosexuals I'm not like screaming ah for Cher like she's cool I think she's pretty fierce I want to watch the show about Chaz oh I don't yeah I don't really follow the Cher stuff but my mother loves Cher I got dragged to a Cher concert by my mother Rob I just love Cher she's so funny she's such a diva Rob I like your mom
[SPEAKER_07]: I want your mom to adopt me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't believe she's younger than me though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, Mortal Kombat Collection.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds great.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we didn't already have Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 on Xbox Live Arcade and Mortal Kombat 2 on PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: But didn't they stop selling 3 or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: They did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 was delisted some time ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it was delisted after they decided hey, we're going to re-release it again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha ha!
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, Ranma in our chatroom says, Gaga convention?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called the West Village, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: So noted.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to pick up that whole Mortal Kombat with the new arcade stick they're going to put out, though, because Mortal Kombat 2 especially was so awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they were, whatever happened to, they were supposed to be putting out an HD collection or something like that on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be all the Mortal Kombat games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's this.
[SPEAKER_03]: but this isn't this or this isn't that it's basically just hey look we're porting the shit straight over we're not doing anything to it hey you know what it's too much work to actually do something let's just release the old shit
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's go to some Twitter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's do it the Nintendo way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to the tweets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tweet, tweet, tweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every week you guys tweet us and we read your tweets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless you're going to tweet something that we're going to talk about on the show in about 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not Benji.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sends us a tweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well then who are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sends us a tweet saying, can I pre-F you?
[SPEAKER_02]: If so, F you to being at a place tonight where I can't listen to OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is screwed up.
[SPEAKER_02]: F that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would say though, just a tip, if you are a smartphone owner, especially like the iPhones, I'm not sure how well this works on Android and the other stuff because I'm an iPhone owner, but allgames.com runs on HTML5, so you can actually get the feed by just going to allgames.com on your iPhone or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So just saying, just for future reference.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby Blackwolf tweeted us that he has now sent the best email ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Funny T-Man tweets us saying this is a fun little Metroidvania type game I found.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm going to the link here.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's IndieGames.com and the game is called Hydra Castle Labyrinth Buster.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, maybe that's the author, I don't know, but Hydra Castle Labyrinth.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a freeware 2D platformer created by E. Hashimoto, who made Akuji the Demon and Guardian of Paradise.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's similar to La Mulana, uh-oh, I hear Dark Tetsuya running to download this immediately, and the Castlevania series.
[SPEAKER_02]: The health gauge and sub-weapon indicator are both displayed on the top left corner of the screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hydra Castle Labyrinth you can download from Buster's site hp.vector.co.jp this sounds pretty cool and it's only 1.25 megs I will kindly link this in our chat room so if you guys want to check that out there you go enjoy
[SPEAKER_02]: It sounds like Dark Tetsuya has already played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so not surprised.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: SJ100Matt tweets us a couple things.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of them is coming up a little later in the show, but the other one I want to mention this.
[SPEAKER_02]: With arcades being closed down, a new video game themed lounge has opened up in Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looks nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I heard there's a new arcade in San Francisco as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I can't remember for the life of me what the name is maybe somebody in chat will figure it out for me but there's a new arcade in San Francisco I think I haven't been to yet and now apparently there's this place called Insert Coins in Las Vegas it's a video lounge game bar yeah I remember seeing that huh that sounds kind of neat a while ago
[SPEAKER_02]: According to the website here that I'm on right now, Insert Coins will electrify all your senses with its revolutionary amalgamation of classic arcades, ultra lounge service, console video gaming, and the world's greatest video DJs, all under its 7,000 square foot roof, nestled in the iconic neon-laden Fremont East District of Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually sounds kind of awesome, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sounds like it's video games meets booze meets loud music.
[SPEAKER_02]: sounds awesome maybe this type of shit's ready to make a resurgence that's kind of what I'm hoping like you know I gotta say when I went to Portland one of the most awesome places I went to was the um barcade that they had there and I apologize I forget the name of it but it's just thank you ground control Dan's yelling it from the other room ground control yeah that place was isn't that place fucking rad Dan oh god Dan you gotta go oh my god it's it's beer and 80s games
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, Dan says road trip.
[SPEAKER_02]: We might just have to.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, you know, it's a bummer you're starting school that week because before we go to L.A., we could go to Portland and go to ground control.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, yeah, screw DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: You and I will go, Dan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan and I are going to go on a broad trip.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan said the first gayest thing he did was play rock band at Matt's party.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let me move on to some more tweets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spazinator PSN tweets us saying, PlayStation Network is down again as of 9pm Eastern, 6pm Pacific.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was like, well wait a minute Spazinator, maybe you just need to try it four times before you get in like I had to do earlier, but I'm looking at the official PlayStation blog, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, not even 24 hours after it came back up, PlayStation Network had to go back down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, yep, yep, yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: and that's all I'm going to say about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a whore.
[SPEAKER_02]: More tweets.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you call it a whore?
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Had to go back down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Tigerclaw sends us a couple tweets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oops, I guess I just reported on one of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'll read this other one about the Sony Online Entertainment senior producer is now the Zynga Austin GM.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's John Blakely.
[SPEAKER_02]: He did some projects including Star Wars Galaxies and DC Universe Onlines.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now he's leading Zynga in Austin.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he went from the dark side to the darker side.
[SPEAKER_02]: All from his LinkedIn profile.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Candid Critique sends us a tweet saying, Someone makes Counter-Strike Osama compound map.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay or nay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought something like this we had discussed on the show this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this isn't all too surprising.
[SPEAKER_02]: Give a bunch of gamers a blank palette and controversial things are sure to be made.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everywhere from nude patches to overly violent things to real life scenarios that may or may not be kind of tacky playing out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, and we get linked to this article here about the Pakistani compound where Osama Bin Laden, of course, I mean, unless you've been living under a fucking rock, was found and killed by U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Navy SEALs, is now a playable mod in, what is this, Counter-Strike.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I can go into Counter-Strike and play this game, and not only can I play real-life news, but I can get called every name in the book while doing it, because Counter-Strike has a really rude online community, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lastly...
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's a question for the host.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like these tweets.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're questions for the host.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what this really should all be about.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: TheBaconBits tweets us, IDK if it's been asked before, but what is your guys' favorite game soundtrack of all time?
[SPEAKER_02]: Personally, mine is the SMG OST.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm assuming that means Super Mario Galaxy OST.
[SPEAKER_02]: BaconBits asking, what is your favorite game soundtrack of all time?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: I...
[SPEAKER_07]: I really don't know, but I'd have to say maybe Bust Move 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it had a really good soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know it would have to be kind of a toss up between well I did like I listened the crap out of the Dance Dance Revolution 4th mix soundtrack when that was out because I actually bought that at an anime convention which is pretty awesome I'd say it's either between 4th, 5th, Max 2 or DJ Hero 1 because DJ Hero 2 is kind of dumb
[SPEAKER_02]: As tempted as I am to throw in a Bomani soundtrack like DDR3rd Mix, probably my favorite soundtrack ever, or Beatmania 2D X-Fist style, honestly, I go to the Super Nintendo, and there's three games on the Super Nintendo that for me all kind of tie, maybe one slightly ahead for first place.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I'm going to add Super Metroid to the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Super Metroid would be on my top three, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy 6, 3, whatever you want to call it would also be up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think just the slight edge, I think probably the greatest video game soundtrack ever made, ActRaiser.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the ActRaiser soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is beautiful, gorgeous music.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what actually I'd have to add to my list would be Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Chrono Trigger's got a pretty fucking sweet soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Link to a Pass is pretty awesome too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm gonna find my favorite piece of music in Chrono Trigger and send it to you to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, you do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But maybe next week during the break.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're out of music breaks tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, that's going to do it for the tweets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Twitter.com slash OLR if you want to get in early for next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the meantime, more news.
[SPEAKER_02]: And oh boy, it's the lawsuit segment time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is retarded, but a former Navy... Now, Loki, don't use the R word.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can say butt-tarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's retarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was his first seizure he had ever had, and it was violent enough to break a bone.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I guess he's permanently barred from flying the F-18 planes, which he was trained on.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he's suing them because he says Oblivion was designed that it exceeds the upper acceptable limit of...
[SPEAKER_03]: Bullshit, they're in the manual.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every fucking manual has a goddamn epilepsy warning in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, that is some serious bullshit right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, he wants damages for negligence, breach of warranty, and product liability.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's gonna lose.
[SPEAKER_03]: but yeah, every goddamn manual and fuck, every goddamn manual like, since games had manuals have had that warning in there, I think like from the Nintendo, well I'm sure they've had manuals for games before that, but like Nintendo, I think was one of the first you know series of games or whatever, they had manuals that had that warning in there because I always thought it was ridiculous, but I mean people have seizures because of flashing lights sometimes, but
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, just take some responsibility for yourself.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: I have thrown up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Portal 2 made me throw up.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to control yourself.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, some people have limits and you've got to control those limits.
[SPEAKER_02]: Turn the brightness down on your TV when you play Oblivion or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't blame a game for a problem that clearly existed before that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got person A who has zero inclination towards epilepsy, and you've got person B who doesn't know they have any inclination towards epilepsy, but they do.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you sit them both in front of the same product.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, of course, the one who has the inclination, whether they know about it or not, is going to react to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like how I found out I was allergic to bell peppers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: My mom eats them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I ate a bell pepper, my tongue swelled up, and I got sick.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Besides that, they're nasty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blackwolf in our chatroom at chat.orange.com says, at least he got the seizure while playing a video game rather than while flying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so like I said, would you rather he fly in a plane and get a seizure than crash into, I don't know, an orphanage, a mall, children, schools?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, let's talk about another lawsuit, and this one, oh boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a lawsuit against Chuck E. Cheese.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it for the fact that they got rid of all their good arcade games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I wanted to join in on that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, sort of.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a lawsuit against the ticket dispensing games at Chuck E. Cheese because it creates gambling addiction in little children.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lawsuit has been filed in California.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're looking for $5 million.
[SPEAKER_02]: The person who filed the lawsuit, Denise Keller.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's a mom, two girls, five and three years old.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chuck E. Cheese's arcade games are akin to slot machines, says the complaint.
[SPEAKER_02]: By offering tickets as a payout that can be redeemed for prizes, the machines, quote, create the same highs and lows experienced by adults who gamble their paychecks or the mortgage payment.
[SPEAKER_02]: The lawyer says, it's not about the money, it's about the kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: California law forbids gambling
[SPEAKER_02]: I get it, the Indian casinos are in Indian land, I understand that And the California lottery?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the lottery, so they don't ban gambling that well, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyhow, it does make an exception for payouts if the contest is predominantly a game of skill Which, as you know, these crane games and skee-ball games and so forth, they are of course mainly games of skill
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even understand the problem here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually would take an unpopular opinion somewhat with this and say she actually kind of has a point with this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do think this is probably not healthy for all children.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why sue Chuck E. Cheese over it?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's ridiculous because you absolutely have the right to not go there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet if enough people didn't go to Chuck E. Cheese and didn't go have their birthday parties at Chuck E. Cheese and let their kids have birthday parties there, they would probably have to get rid of these machines or the company would go bankrupt or maybe they'd go back to having legitimate arcade games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to know why, you know, all of these, because Ticket Redemption games have been around forever since I was a little kid.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's not forever, don't say that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, but why is it that we're just now getting somebody complaining about it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I really don't get it, especially when everybody else seems to be just fine with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: People can get addicted to anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not finished.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: The whole point is that it's a parenting issue.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't want your kids to participate in something, you don't take them there, or you don't let them play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Salacious Pop in our chatroom says, Many ticket games are a test of skill.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some ticket games are goddamn bullshit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Legend of Zaku says, Remember kids, America equals Sue the Bastard's Land.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, he kind of has a point.
[SPEAKER_02]: I almost think she's teaching these kids a worse lesson by going through with this lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is my opinion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's the way it is now.
[SPEAKER_03]: If people find an opportunity to make money, they're going to gamble their chances and do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, people can make the argument that they can be addicted to anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we get rid of everything?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because that's really what it's going to come down to.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get rid of these ticket redemption games, they're going to say, oh, well, I'm addicted to winning at arcade games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then you get rid of the arcade games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, I'm addicted to...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Riding in little motorized cars that they have at Chuck E. Cheese or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, then we gotta get rid of those too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, now I'm addicted to eating pizza.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get rid of pizza.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where does it stop?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's just people are gonna be finding anything to sue over.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this, unfortunately, is the latest in many, I'm sure, lawsuits that are gonna be
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: And if they cry and have a tantrum, then you give them a timeout or you spank them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it seriously that terrible to parent your child?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, shit, I know as being a parent, it's not that hard to say no.
[SPEAKER_03]: And not only a parent, a Mensa member.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: Can I lie and say I'm a Mensa member and just say as a Mensa member?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll get sued, probably.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some hilarious shit in here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just sorry to get sidetracked here very quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go ahead and read this comment real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: AkumaJP in our chatroom at chat.orangehauntry.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki is addicted to Grand Theft Auto for sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, I spend an unhealthy amount of my day thinking about Grand Theft Auto, playing Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_02]: I may or may not be addicted to World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: and let's face it, everyone is addicted to video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, it's not that I'm addicted to Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have fun playing Grand Theft Auto and I have fun modding Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is that a problem that I like doing something, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not like I can't stop.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're not allowed to have fun!
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just going to tell you something.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just really hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got to find, and my wife was reading this to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think this is it right here.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some rules or whatever that they have.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, member policies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you allowed to read these?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's not like it's some secret guide or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not masonry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, anyways, one of the things, yeah, you can't really say something as like saying, oh, well, as a member of Mensa, I believe blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that wasn't even the part that I thought was ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_03]: They give you a sample press.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kid you not.
[SPEAKER_03]: A sample press release of how you can form your own press release to send out to your local paper and your friends saying that you got in the Mensa.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm not that vain.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what though?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe in a suburbia town, in a big market like Sacramento, as much as we joke about ourselves, we are still the 20th largest market in the nation.
[SPEAKER_02]: But go to the Midwest, in a lot of those little towns, maybe it is kind of a big deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just like putting a big giant sign on my back that says, Nerd!
[SPEAKER_03]: Make fun of me!
[SPEAKER_03]: Beat my ass while you're at it!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, I'm not going to invite that kind of attention.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the next story up is DarkSakura's, but she's left, so... She has left the building.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk more about... Let's sue her for not fulfilling her obligations.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm addicted to garden burgers, and I was preparing mine.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm suing garden burgers.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to get rid of those crappy garden burgers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Goddamn you, garden burgers.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm suing you because I thought you were meat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Portal 2 Authoring Tools is now available for beta for PC gamers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up, Dan!
[SPEAKER_07]: I love you!
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: so for people who want to do more for Portal 2 Valve has Portal 2 authoring tools yay if you've got a PC you can do this it's free for anyone who owns the game on PC and it's in the tools tab on your Steam account so basically you'll just be able to go into everything character skins, single player co-op levels, sound effects, music, 3D models they are all there you can do them all but there's also that sounds nasty
[SPEAKER_07]: There's also an updated version of Faceposer and different example maps and instances to help you learn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, there's a new suite of command line compiling utilities.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want someone to make the Orange Lounge level.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make the Orange Lounge level, put it up.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why are you looking at doors?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking at something from online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something that Alan's doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's probably giggling that that came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently the PlayStation 1 Classics...
[SPEAKER_03]: They've been slow to sell.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really, no one's wanting to buy your PlayStation 1 games to play them on a device that most likely doesn't have buttons.
[SPEAKER_03]: But no, these are actually meant for the Xperia Play Phone, the PlayStation phone, if you will.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, apparently, I guess, there's only, um, you know, very few, uh, sales for each one.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're saying that under a thousand installs for each title, uh, Cool Porters 2, Destruction Derby, Medieval, Siphon Filter, and Jumping Flash, and most of those are actually only in the few hundreds.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, they're saying that also that, um, they're saying it's not really a concern since there's only a few, um, at the, um, moment, but PlayStation 1 titles, um, here are there.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's more coming on a regular basis, he said, and as a whole PlayStation as a content provider exclusive to the device.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's no real concerns.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a revolutionary device and it's shaking up the marketplace and we're very pleased with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, also it should be meant, you know, there's a reason why that maybe it's not working.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because, um, not necessarily on the marketplace, but you can get it for that phone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, there actually are other PlayStation emulators that you can download ROMs for, and those don't cost you anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: So maybe that's the issue.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think a lot of people are just buying the phone because, you know what, it's kind of cool to play other games with buttons.
[SPEAKER_03]: Xperia Play Fine
[SPEAKER_03]: Just because it has a PlayStation controller setup on it doesn't mean people are going to necessarily buy just PlayStation 1 games with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you can get a bunch of other games that support this type of controller mapping and you can play those just fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you ever thought that maybe a game that was put out 10 years ago might not stand up well against...
[SPEAKER_03]: some of the newer games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I think Sony's just losing touch there with what people want.
[SPEAKER_03]: Granted, Cool Borders is a pretty fun game and Destruction Derby's not bad on its own and Medieval's alright, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just they're showing their age.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know, Kazurai's a real party animal.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's hip to what the kids are into.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's got his finger on the pulse of what's hot.
[SPEAKER_03]: What gamers really want
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_03]: When he's not partying in his yacht.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about the Xbox for a minute and their Games on Demand service.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, you can buy full games through the Games on Demand service and download them to your hard drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Usually, these are games that have been out for a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't see a lot of stuff that comes out as they're new, but this is interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cave is going to be releasing Death Smiles 2X directly to Games on Demand.
[SPEAKER_02]: There will not be a disc release in North America.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game will cost $30, excuse me, $29.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not translating it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be straight up in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are buying basically the import game, but playable on your Xbox 360 through Games on Demand.
[SPEAKER_02]: But because it's a shooter game, it's not like you need to have a real thorough knowledge of Japanese anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to have no knowledge of Japanese, seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to launch Tuesday, May 17th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Facebook is where they announced this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boy, what a sign of the times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cave announced this on Facebook, saying, quote, It will be giving this format a try for getting some of our Japan-only shooters released overseas.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of people that really like import games and would like to be playing them, and it sucks that the Xbox is region locked the way it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: And import games are fucking expensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: So $30 for a game like that, even if they aren't doing any translations whatsoever, it's awesome because you're saving yourself probably about...
[SPEAKER_02]: 50% of the cost of an import actually more than that probably this would actually kind of discourage some of the hacking because sometimes people hack their systems to play import games that's the reason why I hacked my original Playstation 1
[SPEAKER_02]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe I'll get it when it goes on sale, eventually.
$30?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not super good at shooters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, you know what's interesting about this?
[SPEAKER_02]: By not getting a disc release, you won't be able to get it through Gamefly or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or rental.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to either pay the $30 or don't play.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see how well that goes over.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, let's go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every week you guys send us emails.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com DarkSakura dives in the mailbag head first and pulls out a few emails that she says, hey, you guys should be writing us more emails.
[SPEAKER_02]: First email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, OLR crew, AZHP here with a question for you all.
[SPEAKER_07]: After having done this radio show for a long time, do you ever get that itch to work closer to the video game industry?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, not at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I know that Loki works in distribution, but do any of you feel like you would enjoy having a hand in a game's development rather than simply reporting the news and your opinions?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or do you prefer to stay at arm's length and pay no mind to the man behind the curtain?
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely, and I've already pitched the idea that I want to pitch an idea to Konami to...
[SPEAKER_03]: you know it's tough actually going up to them and saying listen I want to fix your franchise because they don't really take kindly to that kind of stuff but reimagine and modernize a franchise I suppose would be the better way to do it but yeah I'd love to do that but uh at the same time you know I have a day job so it'd be kind of hard to quit a day job to go work on a game and god knows they're not going to actually listen to one person that has an idea about how they can
[SPEAKER_03]: improve a certain franchise because I'm sure they get thousands of emails from people that do something very similar but if they were ballsy and wanted to take a chance that'd be pretty cool
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: So, OLR men and women, what are your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you content to admire the industry from afar or do you want to dive into the trenches?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yours truly is EHP, OLR's premier gold star recipient and general grammar advocate.
[SPEAKER_07]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've started a scientific poll on my Facebook to prove that everyone appreciates boobs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aside from the insignificant outliner data, the results support OLR's hypothesis.
[SPEAKER_07]: Feel free to share it in chat so that I can obtain more data and I will copy it into chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, I actually, if certain things require a relocation on our part, I'm planning on applying with Valve, Nintendo, and Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because what I want to do is publication.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gee, I wonder if she might be thinking of relocating too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm wanting to do publication, like manuals, advertising, anything that's going to go into digital or physical print.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to admit, I'm a little torn on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I honestly have to say no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think there's a lot I could contribute on the front lines.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not a programmer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not an artist.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, I have ideas about games, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people kind of do it a little bit better, and I'm okay with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would have no problem being an advisor personally.
[SPEAKER_02]: A tracker.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell, having done this show as long as I have, I think I could probably get away with being some type of games analyst.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time, I have a day job I rather enjoy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I make a decent amount of money.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really see myself leaving it anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, I'm not going to lie, especially from the journalism ends of things, if I ever had the opportunity to host a show about games, especially on TV, although there's such little demand for that, I don't know how that would ever happen, I would jump at that opportunity in a heartbeat, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I worry I'm starting to get a little old for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of that stuff is targeted towards...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, 20-somethings and teens.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now I'm starting to enter my mid-30s.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't know if I would really be wanted for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would tell you what I would love, love, love to do more than anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would love to host a game show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially like a throwback to the old Starrcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Rob's here with Bob Barker.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even something like Nick Arcade or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You want to be painted orange.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Bob Barker, but I also love Gene Rayburn from old 70s match game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I would say...
[SPEAKER_07]: You know who my person is?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude from Press Your Luck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Peter Tamarkin.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, I would absolutely leave my day job in a heartbeat to go be a game show host.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, I actually had an old boss who thought she heard of some TV station casting for who wants to be a game show host.
[SPEAKER_02]: and she told me I could take leave from work to participate in that show and she said that it's possible to be arranged unfortunately that show didn't turn out to be legit but if they ever had something like that I'd go on it in a heartbeat absolutely
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time, you know, we've been doing Orange Lounge Radio as a hobby for nine years now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just radio in general, you know, I was on Understated Nation Live before that and was doing college radio before that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, the radio industry especially is highly competitive.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I kind of like the fact that we get to do radio on our own terms.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we're not the biggest show out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people, even after nine years, have no idea who the fuck we are.
[SPEAKER_02]: But nobody gets between me and you.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely, which is why we'll probably be independent forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's, I think it's the way at least ye small but loyal few like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's how we roll.
[SPEAKER_07]: That and we have Shermie.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll always have Shermie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan says we'd sell out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think he's full of crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it happened and you guys didn't take the money, I would kill all three of you
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dan said that on the mic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he might have got picked up.
[SPEAKER_02]: My husband likes to just come in here and shout things.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said if we didn't take the money, he'd kill all of us.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will say this, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's definitely, I think...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think one thing we always want to make sure we do here at Orange Lounge Radio is we don't want to rest on our laurels too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think if there's ways we can push things forward and push ourselves more and push the hobby forward, we're going to try and do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm not saying anything, but trust me, we're always thinking about how can things be even better than they are right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Better.
[SPEAKER_02]: But on our terms.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very important on our terms.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Destructoid article that's linked by... I was getting my... Originally scheduled for launch sometime this month, Nintendo has pushed back the already late release because it should have been ready when the damn system was out of the 3DS eShop until June.
[SPEAKER_07]: According to the company, North America will get it June 6th and Japan will get it June 7th.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, we get it first.
[SPEAKER_07]: Neener.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, technically, it's sort of at the same time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was emailing a friend about this, and I also mentioned the big three addresses by Microsoft, Sony, and Nintendo, respectively.
[SPEAKER_07]: I realized that the eShop will open on the day Microsoft and Sony talk, June 6th, USA, June 7th, Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: How clever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba.
[SPEAKER_07]: Last two emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm glad they finally got it back up.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is called Thoughts on PSN.
[SPEAKER_07]: They got it up.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Michael Patcher did a 24 plus minute video on how this will impact Sony.
[SPEAKER_07]: A very interesting watch.
[SPEAKER_07]: He certainly feels that while they lost money slash sales, they'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the link and I will copy it into the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: But for those listening, it's GameTrailers.com slash video slash episode dash 215 dash patch.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess P-A-C-H is how it's written on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dash attack slash 713900.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they're giving...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm giving the analyst video time now, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I assume if you just go to GameTrailers.com and search for his name, you'll find it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, yeah, but I... But, I mean... Ben Thoreau!
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to be a hater, but how is this guy any different from the indie podcasts out there and all the speculation they do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I realize maybe he went to school or whatever, but... I get played by Morgan... What was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Webbrush or whatever?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm really not trying to be a hater.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, everybody's got to make a living.
[SPEAKER_02]: I get that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't... Like, why is his...
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, the guy is wrong more times than he's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just reading the email.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm responding to the email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Listen to the podcast every week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's from Sepwin.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will say this, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do kind of agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Sony is going to recover from it in the long run.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they're going to feel a lot of hurt.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the real question might be, is Sony going to find this worth it to do it all over again with PlayStation 4?
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think at the end of the day, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they will recover.
[SPEAKER_02]: If Apple recovered from the antenna thing, if Microsoft recovered from the red ring thing, they'll come back.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Sony.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know they've already got a business, they've already adjusted their business model to accommodate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you know that PSN is back up?
[SPEAKER_07]: And did you know that it still does not deliver tacos?
[SPEAKER_07]: I am sad, frown face, all caps, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had to yell.
[SPEAKER_02]: That possibly is the best email ever, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is very sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was my Caps Lock voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want tacos as part of my PlayStation Severance package.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can we get on that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I only got four emails, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we need more emails.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why you didn't get tacos tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Send me more emails so that Rob will get me another taco.
[SPEAKER_02]: Send me emails so that DarkSakura buys me a taco.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll buy you a taco if you buy me a taco.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan says he's going to make tacos next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, we're almost to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not just yet, but we will be there in just a moment.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: But first, two more stories for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this is kind of neat, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: As part of the Xbox indie service, it's been very unpredictable when games are going to be released on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of like, well, they're up for review now, so it should be out hopefully soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess such events like the Indie Games Winter Uprising will be more coordinated.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess some of their titles were missed on that because of the release date whole thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're saying also it's kind of mixed a positive feedback according to the development community.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some people like the decision and saying that the chance to schedule a release helps them plan the game promotion more sensibly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Others noted that scheduling would likely lead to an open stampede to release on specific days like Friday and a game of chicken trying to figure out the best time.
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like we're okay right now looking at the numbers, but we were having a skippy period for a minute there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, moving on, but otherwise there's not a lot we can do about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If the cable's not going to cooperate, then it's not going to cooperate.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we move on with one last story here tonight before we go to the Skype line, which if we're still skipping is really going to be a hoot and a holler tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: uh anyhow uh they're not it's just a straight up release of the Super Nintendo version so don't expect anything fabulous to be changed that means you're not going to have the extra dungeons and stuff in the DS version but there you go uh it is coming out no price announced yet but everybody is speculating it'll be 900 Wii points 800 for a Super Nintendo game and that 100 point premium for the special of the special games which honestly Chrono Trigger it's probably worth it so uh I'm sure there'll be a lot of people checking that out
[SPEAKER_02]: and especially if you were too young to remember Chrono Trigger or just never got a chance to play it back in the day, you really should check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I sometimes hate on it on the show because I don't think it's the best Super Nintendo RPG because I love Final Fantasy 3 too goddamn much, or 6, whatever you want to call it, but it's really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really good.
[SPEAKER_07]: You want to know what's great?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now keep in mind that I got the game in 95, 96 when it came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, first of all, my friend loaned it to me and then he moved.
[SPEAKER_07]: My save file is still intact.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, a lot about those batteries were only ever guaranteed to last five years, but most people I know with old NES cartridges, those things still work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's just a lithium battery.
[SPEAKER_07]: It depends on how much you used it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, as long as you don't have the game on 24-7.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, our Saturn batteries, however, have burned and burned and burned and burned.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are going to now open the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to really hope our live transmit issues don't get in the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the Skype... Oh, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hiccups.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Skype line is now open for your calls if you want to give feedback on any of tonight's topics or anything else that might be on your mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at that, it's already ringing.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will of course also go to Loki with some last minute stories in between calls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the one and only Ranma, how's everyone tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who else gets in first on this show?
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you Ranma?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're happy?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why are you happy?
[SPEAKER_02]: I start a new job come tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, well, that's a reason to be happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: What kind of job are you going to be doing, if you don't mind me asking?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll still be doing tech support in the school district, but with a different company with a lot more pay and better benefits.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, more pay and better benefits are always a good thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: What I see is it's probably going to be like a simple controller with a touch screen in the middle of it kind of preset for certain buttons to do certain things according to the way the game is going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can actually agree with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It seems like almost everything has a touch screen in this day and age.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty much every smartphone these days has one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I was talking about earlier when we were talking about the new Nintendo console in the first place, the touch screens on the printer devices and those things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I've seen those.
[SPEAKER_02]: so yeah I don't think the touchscreens will be that expensive it's just you know all this other stuff too you know pretty much so what do you what are your expectations for the new Nintendo console we are only three weeks away from E3 they're saying it's going to be on par with the 360 and the PS3 just show me what it can do
[SPEAKER_10]: and what and the features that's it I'm a very simple person with basic needs I mean if there's gonna be some great gaming on it I will pick up the console if it's going to be the Wii second gen with more more shovelware it can stay on the shelf and collect more dust
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know the golden rule of OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: A system is only as good as the games that are on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, indeed.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a problem with the 3DS right now, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know I left my 3DS here after the show last week and never bothered to come get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, actually, that's a lie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did try to come by Monday, but nobody was here because I was in the neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quite understandable.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't really miss it that much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I took mine out of my bag because I didn't like lugging it back and forth around because I'm not using it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I have no one to street pass with.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, darn.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to street pass with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take it to E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Try a street pass with people there.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to loiter outside E3?
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby will street pass with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm going to loiter outside E3 just to street pass.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to walk around with a big cardboard sign.
[SPEAKER_02]: I should do this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Big cardboard sign.
[SPEAKER_02]: Media not good enough to get into E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please street pass with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be fun.
Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anything else on your mind tonight, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, in regards to PAX East 2012.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I expect this to be announced soon, but I don't know if you know, but next year, PAX East is the same weekend as Anime Boston.
[SPEAKER_10]: Same city, two separate convention centers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's going to be a mess.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is bad planning.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the problem is sometimes when the conventions have these dates, it's like take it or leave it, you know?
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's probably what it boiled down to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: But here's the thing, this was announced at Anime Boston's Masquerade, and I actually talked to a few people that are staff, and that was it, that actually verified this, but it will not surprise me if this changes.
[SPEAKER_10]: They made the announcement that if you purchase a pass for Anime Boston 2012, it is good for entrance to PAX East 2012 as well, and they will have shuttle buses going between both convention centers.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a little weird to me considering the attendance caps that PAX keeps hitting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, why would you want to, you know, because if everybody who goes to Anime Boston gets a free pass into PAX...
[SPEAKER_02]: That's less people that can go to PAX.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that seems like, if I were on the PAX, I wouldn't agree to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I were behind that show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I figure it's like, you know, you got so many gamers going to this convention.
[SPEAKER_10]: You got so many anime fans going to this convention.
[SPEAKER_10]: Give them a free pass to check out the other side, per se.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, then why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is the other half going to be true, too?
[SPEAKER_10]: It would not surprise me if it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: But correct me if I'm wrong, Anime Boston is going to be at the old convention center, the Heinz, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the Uber one that PAX was at this year is where PAX will be.
[SPEAKER_02]: What if everybody decides to go to Anime Boston one of those days?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean that Heinz place is going to collapse.
[SPEAKER_10]: Honestly, with the numbers that PAX East generates, I find that hard to believe because I'm planning to do PAX East instead.
[SPEAKER_10]: And knowing how some fans are, how lazy they can be per se, no offense, but to be perfectly honest, I don't think a lot of them are going to take shuttle buses to go 15 minutes across town to another convention and then come back.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the two needs to move.
[SPEAKER_02]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_02]: They shouldn't be the same weekend.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, but this is what I'm hearing from a lot of my sources that this could be the end for AEB.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, then move.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be tricky.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be an interesting weekend next year.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am curious to see how this is all going to play out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still a long ways away, all things considered, so some things may change.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't doubt your sources, but I'm still skeptical.
[SPEAKER_02]: It seems like wishful thinking on Anime Boston's part.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, it wouldn't surprise me as if, like, AB says this is what they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wouldn't surprise me if Paxix comes out and says, yeah, you buy one of our badges, it's not good for AB.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe they're trying to be all buddy-buddy, friendly-friendly, because you have two different convention companies in the same town.
[SPEAKER_10]: fighting for Top Dog, or in this case, a one-legged ass-kicking contest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and I was going to say, you'd think in most situations the two would be fighting each other, but I'm sorry, anime fans, Pax, with the people that come as far away as they do, you know, all the way from, like, Florida, Georgia, Alabama, and all, like, the southern east states, you know, because that's still the closest thing they've got.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anime Boston's going to get their ass handed to them if they stay that same weekend.
[SPEAKER_10]: and you're absolutely right but the funny thing is there are people that travel as far south as Florida and Texas that come up to Anime Boston.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do they do it?
[SPEAKER_10]: For the guests.
[SPEAKER_10]: But for next year you may travel way across the country for the guests but as for me I'll travel way across the country to check out these great games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: True.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: We gotta let you go to get more calls but thanks so much buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey no problem dude.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Later.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki any last minute stories while we wait for a call?
[SPEAKER_03]: The Royal Wedding
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it will allow players to replace either Prince William or Kate Milton.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, I can be Princess Kate?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can be Princess Kate, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: In their first public kiss following the royal wedding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says the scene's offered free, clearly an attempt to subvert otherwise rational people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure how I feel about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go back to the phones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I thought I had a call.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess I missed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can keep going.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, apparently there's going to be some other footage and stuff that's available.
[SPEAKER_03]: But seriously though, I've played Ysar 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a cool concept, but it's so terribly executed.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's such a terrible game.
[SPEAKER_03]: My favorite is how the camera cannot frame you properly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Deathwishing I'm playing a very amazing gem of a game that people need to start playing again Freelancer
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a PC game from 2004, I believe, and it's kind of, say, like, EVE Online, minus being an MMORPG, but you can play with, like, 200 people online at once, and you do missions, I think, like, Neverwinter Nights kind of style, you know, you can do missions and stuff, all that, but it's space combat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, that Nintendo thing, I'm...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of looking, I'm totally seeing fail in the future.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why so negative?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's like, they're saying, oh, it's going to be like on par with PS3, Xbox 360, but then you see the thing about, oh, we're going to be inventing some new peripheral where you can like feel things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, oh, great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of think the feel thing is bullshit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I truly think the feel thing is bullshit.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not coming from the same source that originally leaked the news about the Nintendo Wii Next system.
[SPEAKER_02]: That came from a different source.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the feel stuff holds about as much weight as the fact that the revolution was going to project 3D graphics.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_04]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_04]: True enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if...
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of think the whole, like, touch, I think that's just, like, weird, crazy fanboy bullshit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I truly do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet you don't frickin' Nintendo things for us.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was gonna have a button that says, give Nintendo money.
[SPEAKER_04]: If there's anything in there, it's gonna put money regardless.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's gonna sell.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know for a fact it will.
[SPEAKER_04]: They got the soccer mom market on Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but will you buy one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you own a Wii?
[SPEAKER_04]: I owned a Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had it for three months and then I was like, wow, this is the most gimmicky piece of crap I've ever owned.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I gave it to my cousin because I didn't want to sell it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I gave it to some kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would use it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you worry you might make the same mistake with a new Nintendo system?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know I won't because I'm just going to switch to PC Master Race.
Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you sure, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: What could Nintendo announce on this thing that would make you be like, maybe I should get this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um... That they're actually gonna make a new GoldenEye that isn't stupid and handle like ass, and my ship just blew up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, have fun in the PC Master Race.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, DeathWishing, we'll be looking for your reactions after E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Have fun, whoever's gonna, like I was gonna pack seats or whatever, have fun with all the Japanese weeaboo's at Anime.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, we will.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's gonna be some great, like, crossover interviews and things like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: I... I really think Anime Boston's gonna be forced to move weekends.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know...
[SPEAKER_02]: I know there's only so much convention center space and so on, but think outside the box, people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, 1-877-GAME-O-L-R or use your name on Skype as Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the meantime, more last minute stories from Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's an NES cartridge that's being developed.
[SPEAKER_03]: That will turn your NES into a MIDI synthesizer.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called Chip Maestro.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was actually part of a Kickstarter program.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for $50, you can grab one of these cartridges.
[SPEAKER_03]: It plugs into a MIDI keyboard, and you can start creating your own 8-bit sounding music using a keyboard.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, and then, of course, um, there is a new Xbox Live and PlayStation Network game that's been announced.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, Jeremy McGrath Off-Road.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, no word on what the game is exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously, it's gonna be a Baja Racing type game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually being, um, developed, I guess, uh, from the people that did Baja Edge of Control for THQ.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I guess they've also done some work on the MX vs. ATV series so they've got a good pedigree there but don't really know that many details about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: People are kind of hoping that it's maybe a spiritual successor to Ivan Ironman Stewart's off-road racing game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game was fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got another call coming in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: You've already called the number.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey guys, it's CD Thunder.
[SPEAKER_02]: CD Thunder, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I have a couple of things to talk to you about.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There must be like hella lag going on here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: The two games I want to talk about, Perfect Dark and Gold 9007.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some classic games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I like them both, and...
[SPEAKER_05]: The Perfect Dark is basically like a space version of the GoldenEye 007, if you know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are some old games.
[SPEAKER_02]: These games have been out a very long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you just kind of getting around to playing classics, like rediscovering old stuff, kind of like our last callers playing some PC game from 2004?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you rediscovering classic games?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you finding these through the new versions of GoldenEye, Perfect Dark Zero, or what has piqued your interest in these games?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you're the guy that called in a few weeks ago and you just recently got a 64, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, not recently, but a few Christmases ago or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, but you don't have a lot of the new systems, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I remember you.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, you've got all the classic stuff in your house.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, a lot of the good stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're gaming in a time capsule, but that's not necessarily a bad thing because there's a lot of shit out there right now, and so it really gives you time to focus on the classics.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you're kind of rediscovering a lot of these games like they're totally new, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty cool, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to be living in a bubble like that sometimes, because there's a lot of real crap out there right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, tell us, how was it playing Perfect Dark and Goldeneye for the first time?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Goldeneye I actually had a lot of fun with.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked the James Bond, so since it was James Bond, I really liked it a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, a lot of the levels are really difficult.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: and with Perfect Dark it's basically... Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the Perfect Dark is basically like a space age version of Goldmine 007 except you play as a woman and you have on-screen reloads but in Goldmine 007 you have off-screen reloads.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the bitch can't jump.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, she can jump only a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they made a new GoldenEye.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think one of the previous callers brought this up.
[SPEAKER_02]: They made a new GoldenEye last year on the Wii, so you'll be playing that in about 2018.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they made this game, and a lot of people aren't really fans of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, they say it blows.
[SPEAKER_02]: It isn't like the original at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do you think people are so partial to the original GoldenEye?
[SPEAKER_02]: What is the charm in the original GoldenEye?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, because it could be maybe because they like the movie, and because of that they like the game, and since they remade the Goldeneye 007 on the Wii with Daniel Craig, they're thinking it's a reboot of the original, so maybe that's one of the reasons.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, buddy, we're going to let you go to take some more calls, but I'm just going to leave you with this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't bother with Majora's Mask.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not nearly as good as Ocarina of Time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just so you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_02]: You too.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or use name on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I really do mean it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes I kind of wish I could just kind of go back in gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, seriously, Super Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's so many good games on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I probably still have yet to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And some folks in chat room vehemently disagree with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkToagak in chat says, Majora's Mask is orgasmic.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell is Sky talking about?
[SPEAKER_07]: Majora's Mask was annoying.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, I always thought that Ocarina of Time was a little bit overrated, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I liked Ocarina, but my favorites still link to the past.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's wrap up with last minute stories, Loki, if you had anything else.
[SPEAKER_07]: His last minute story is Portal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had nothing else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm getting a private message about Square Enix might be going bankrupt, and I do remember reading the article online, I don't have it up in front of me, but I think they reported huge losses recently, and I assumed a lot, well, I
[SPEAKER_02]: I think part of it, they were trying to say, might have been the tsunami, which makes sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, everybody heard from that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think a really large part of it that I don't think was really announced in the report was the utter, dismal, cataclysmic failure of Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because keep in mind, that game was supposed to come out on PlayStation 3 by now, but it hasn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, I think Square is probably way...
[SPEAKER_02]: and overestimated what they were going to make last quarter.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think a lot of that has to do with Final Fantasy XIV, honestly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm getting more information.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you to the person who's messaging me right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me pull up this link in our little browser box here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and of course it's all in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't read that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why you should use Nifty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah, I could use Nifty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or I could use Google Translate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do-do-do-do-do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XIII apparently plays into this as well, Final Fantasy XIII not quite selling as much as they thought I'm translating it now
[SPEAKER_02]: 16 billion yen extraordinary loss and damage the earthquake did stop them to some development they are attributing this to Final Fantasy XIV and postponing that let's see, they're thinking though they say the business environment is rapidly changing yeah, they do cite Final Fantasy XIV multiple times here
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XI I guess it talks about that Final Fantasy XIV wasn't the same quality as Final Fantasy XI and they actually apologized for the unusual situation it has become.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we told you when we first reported on Final Fantasy XIV heads were going to roll.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XIII too it sounds like might be delayed too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that's going to do it for Last Minute Stories tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we're all done.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, this is the part where we go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_02]: But first, I'm going to thank all you guys for listening to Orange Lounge Radio tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: And remember, if you like what you heard, you know, we got into this during the email bag, but we don't have big corporate dollars behind the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do this just because we like having a show, hanging out with each other, and hanging out with you guys every Sunday.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, tell some friends to come join the party.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Open invite.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, we hope to hear from your friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell a couple friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: and spread the word about Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can keep having this show for free.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll start with the portal-loving Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: My final thought is we never did FU's of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, we didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, we didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shit, I guess we should do that now then, shouldn't we?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't care?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, we can do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, here they go.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to this little patch of eczema on my right hand ring finger.
[SPEAKER_07]: The end.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to the woman that wasn't watching where she was driving and hit the back of my car.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't!
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to hangovers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a bad one this morning.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, there you go, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: We did the F yous of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: My F you of the week, or not my F you, my final thought is weekend's already over and that makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: He who controls the spice controls the universe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that does it everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you again for listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's say we do it all again next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sound good?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, have a good night everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_09]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_09]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!