[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight, May 22, 2011, some PSP games are rumored to be remade for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: An anticipated 3DS title is delayed, and will Nintendo's new home console be equipped with a camera?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the show where every gamer has a voice and this is episode number 414 for May the 22nd of 2011.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ho.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard you got drunk last night.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dan coming to say hi on the show?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, he's currently just... Alright, well I have to introduce the other host that's here that's not Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello to the one and only Techmaster, Loki!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I'm definitely not Dan.
[SPEAKER_15]: How are you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's good, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's new with you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just sitting at home.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're boring.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, I started some projects.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, more projects.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm ponding projects.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I started my three foot tall paper craft statue of the portal turret.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I keep forgetting you're building your own portal turret.
[SPEAKER_04]: That kind of cracks me up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, as soon as I get the design correct, because right now, unfortunately, the 3D model I ported over using Peppercura had a lot of internal stuff, because it was actually a full 3D model with the actual guns and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: This turret's not going to have the doors open with the guns showing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it still tried to create papercraft pieces for all that stuff that you're never going to see, so I had to filter out the stuff that I didn't need.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I played some World of Warcraft and slept in And then I went to a very gay Jewish party
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, can I say fuck that Rapture guy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, fuck him in the ear, and fuck CNN, and fuck MSNBC, and all these websites that give him attention, and, like, make people want to tweet about it and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And look, I'm no better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I made my fair share of Rapture jokes, but I'm not talking about, like, snarky Facebook posts, because that's what websites like that are for.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, like, you know, there's real news going on in the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I realize this is a video game podcast, but I'm on my soapbox I made a funny picture It just astounds me that some asshole can come out and say No, really guys, it's gonna end May 21st, so sell your shit I'm totally surreal For real, for real, real
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I'm going to just say the world's going to end on Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be really fucking ironic.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to all die on Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now listen to Orange Lounge Radio if you want to hear more of the gospel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't it allegedly supposed to end December 2012 because of the Mayan calendar?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's always supposed to fucking end.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, on top of that, too, this is...
[SPEAKER_13]: Me getting into a little bit of technical history.
[SPEAKER_13]: If I am right, the Mayans used a lunar calendar, meaning that their months are on a different basis than it would be on the Gregorian calendar.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because right now, it's like halfway through the Jewish year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but I'm sure no one would jump to conclusions in saying that the world's going to end on a specific date.
[SPEAKER_03]: They obviously have some scientific fact to back that up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, what are we, savages?
[SPEAKER_03]: No one just goes out spouting random garbage like the world's going to end yesterday and it doesn't happen without any sort of...
[SPEAKER_03]: Proof.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is just the irony to me is that they can't find the dude.
[SPEAKER_13]: Camping was named Harold Camping.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that the family radio, the site that he's like the president of, is down.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I posted in the chat room the picture that I made about the URL being raptured.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_13]: You're my crack dealer now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which, by the way, I need you to look at my setup later.
[SPEAKER_15]: I will.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I played some World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_13]: I put Rebecca Black on hold.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I am now playing Bladwyn, who is a shammy, who I'm kicking butt with.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: One of these days I'm going to actually read a comic book and then be all like, I should be on Comic Insanity.
[SPEAKER_13]: I did that on Comic Insanity this morning too because Shadow was talking about Final Fantasy IX and he and Tiara were like, oh, Final Fantasy IX.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm like, I don't play it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I got up and got some coffee.
[SPEAKER_15]: DoorPrize
[SPEAKER_13]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: When you're in the top office, you go in behind a file cabinet is a door that leads you to three more vitrified doors and then where the Borealis dock is.
[SPEAKER_13]: So you'll get the door prize thing for listening to Cave Johnson rant like a madman and then finding the remnants of the Borealis.
[SPEAKER_13]: I did that.
[SPEAKER_13]: The next one I'm doing is Smash TV where you have to break all the 11 monitors that Wheatley's jabbering at you at.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of those are pretty hard.
[SPEAKER_13]: The key to doing the Wheatley ones is lasers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I know that, but I'm just saying some of the ones that had no lasers.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I've got to go back and get the turret symphony.
[SPEAKER_13]: The turrets practicing singing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have that one.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I also need to get secret transmission, which actually, there's two secret transmissions in Portal 2, I found out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_13]: and everybody listen up when you're doing the aerial faith plate test the big one with all the room full of faith plates and GLaDOS shoots garbage at you you take
[SPEAKER_13]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: but you also go back and when you launch into the one that's on the ramp but your other portal is going to be on this thing across from the part jutting out and it busts you through a window and you find another Ratman Den and if you've got the radio with you it will play a modem sound and what that does is it actually translates into an image if you've got a decoder.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because, you know, they had the whole ARG thing going on, the alternate reality game, that was basically connecting to a BBS with an old 33K modem or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_13]: And all these images and stuff would go through.
[SPEAKER_04]: I miss BBSs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a BBS for Orange Lounge Radio where I can play Trade Wars 2002 all over again.
[SPEAKER_13]: The other one is when you're in the lower labs and you're playing in commentary mode, you'll find a developer commentary that's nothing but modem noise and it's a picture too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, it's not a picture.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's them talking about part of the development of Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, this is important.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nerds in chat, I need to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you still download Telguard and stuff and set it up to run off of Telnet or whatever?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that possible?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we need to make that happen.
[SPEAKER_13]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, come on, there's so many retro gamers out there that I bet there's still a gemstone server running somewhere.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ooh, I haven't played that in forever.
[SPEAKER_03]: The third achievement is by picking up the broken turret that gets launched in there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, yeah, turret dactyl.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, if you launch a turret with an aerial faith plate, you get an achievement for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that I've done.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know I did that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't do that one either.
[SPEAKER_13]: I need to do more co-op.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't played enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll play co-op with you, but I'll probably end up throwing up all over Shermie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, he's a cat.
[SPEAKER_13]: I watch the Human Vault section, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Black Wolf in the chatroom says, yes, and there are lots of Telnet BBSs out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: OMG, I want an OLR1.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, really bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, come on, you guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: Somebody in the chatroom, do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob will do it, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll do it, because I want to be the sysop.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I always wanted my own BBS when I was a kid, but my mom wouldn't let me get a second phone line.
[SPEAKER_13]: So let's set up the OLRBBS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I want an OLRBBS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me make that happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_04]: We have like two different conversations going on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of them very modern with Portal 2 and the other one not so modern with BBSs and Telnet and The Pit and Trade Wars.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually... Legend of the Red Dragon.
[SPEAKER_13]: I actually did try to play some of the DAC, but my computer farted on me while I was trying to play the Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I tried playing Darwinia.
[SPEAKER_13]: That game's confusing.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it gives me a bit of a headache.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I'm gonna have to probably take a whole bunch of Midol and try playing it again.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because no, it really does give me a headache.
[SPEAKER_13]: The modeling in it, and the colors, makes my head hurt.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, sadness.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sadness.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, stuff like that's always done it to me.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then I played Buy Shermie Cat Food the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: The end.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish I could say that I played exciting stuff, but I haven't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've just played Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: And a brief bit of Portal, because I was trying to test something on my graphics card.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because for some reason in Grand Theft Auto on my PC, it decided, hey, you know what, I'm going to run really slow now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was like, what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why are you running slow when you're running perfectly fine just, you know, all the other days?
[SPEAKER_03]: And it ended up that I was trying to overclock my laptop's graphics card, and I think the program running in the background slowed things down, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I did a cooling mod on this thing, so I actually have the fans kicked up, and there's a big old intake vent in the back now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I normally have, like, a cooling pad that go on the bottom of this, but I don't have it with me right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's running much cooler, and so now I can actually overclock the GPU when I get a chance.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't really bothered to make it stable yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, but I will be playing later on tonight, once I get done moving some stuff around.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a leaked copy of the Duke Nukem Forever demo that I will be checking out, because Duke Nukem Forever is awesome, and the fact that I can play a part of it
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't realize it already had leaked.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, they have an internal demo that's really, really buggy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the real one's out, what, June 3rd or something like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not new.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game's like two years old, and I'm just now getting around to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the Williams Pinball Hall of Fame Collection I played this week on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually had this game on the Wii a few years ago, and there was like a year difference between the releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of them came out in 08, I think, and the other one came out in 09.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I played the newer one, the 360 one, which was also released on PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's old pinball games, and they're classic tables.
[SPEAKER_04]: Redone for the 360
[SPEAKER_13]: We had one in my garage.
[SPEAKER_04]: The old school Black Knight, Pinbot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody knows Pinbot because they had an NES game of Pinbot so you can play the authentic table.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pinbot's actually kind of a crappy table.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like it's a cheap ass table.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bride of Pinbot is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like Bride of Pinbot but that sadly is not in this compilation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Neither is Theater of Magic.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually Jackbot is the best of the bot ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's, no, not in the collection either.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's some other interesting tables.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think about 12 tables in all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Certainly the
[SPEAKER_04]: I sound quiet?
[SPEAKER_04]: I shouldn't sound quiet?
[SPEAKER_04]: No?
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody in chat says I sound fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, live radio, the joys of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, I'll turn myself up just a wee bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other things about the compilation.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of weird because some of the games are free, and then some of them will cost you credits, which is odd to me, that you just don't get everything for free at the start, but I guess it wants to give you something to work towards.
[SPEAKER_04]: But as far as the important stuff, the translation itself, you know, it works.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit pricey probably, you know, considering it's, I think it was about 40 bucks when it came out, you know, just for 12 tables when you got Pinball FX that offers, you know, some pretty competitive tables at a good price.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now that the game's kind of old, you can probably find it really cheap.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you are a pinball fan, you should probably pick it up because it's a good compilation of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, continuing to play some of the games I talked about last week, like Might and Magic, Order of Chaos, or whatever it's called, the puzzle game on 360, and some other stuff, like Mortal Kombat, which I've had very mixed success playing it online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes it's very laggy, sometimes it's pretty smooth, but every time I lose horrifically, because I'm really bad at Mortal Kombat, and that makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not going to be here with the show next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're actually going to take the week off because of Memorial Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm actually going to be out of town on top of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So sadly, we will not be here next week, Memorial Day.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm hating you right now, Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm being hateful and judgmental.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will make it up to you in three weeks.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: In three weeks, it's going to be more awesomer.
[SPEAKER_13]: I need to find 50 bucks to get a Duffy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to be going to the happiest place on earth twice within a month's span.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's just the way it works.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hateful, jealous, judgmental.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, deal with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, Hearts
[SPEAKER_04]: so we're hoping we can kind of get some reports from him and interject that with our own sassy commentary and the rest of your voices on the internet through Twitter and so forth so we're looking at doing some type of E3 specials we're not sure exactly what time yet but that will happen the week of E3 I've already been limbering my eyes up
[SPEAKER_03]: So I can roll them like nothing else when I see the Nintendo press conference.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's gonna roll it like a Katamari.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll be like, oh god, seriously?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is your great idea?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have low expectations for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see if they can limbo under that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm really hoping we can get Loki to come to the show whenever Nintendo's press conference.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ideally, well you'll have to work whenever.
[SPEAKER_04]: When is the Nintendo press conference?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's during the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: I technically don't work when those are going on because I'll stop what I'm doing and watch it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I want to get your immediate reaction to those press conferences.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'll be on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, what the fuck is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's your great idea?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to do some type of like where we are commenting on the press conferences as they're going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you can like download it later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like a Rift Tracks type of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: We can do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's technically possible because they do syndicate that stuff later on so that you can rewatch the actual videos and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we could do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nah, too much effort.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would say that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so we will not be here next week on Memorial Day weekend, sadly.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will be back the week after, though, which happens to be the Sunday before E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's when the news is really going to start to roll in.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I think we're going to get to a story on this later.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the developers is doing their press conference Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're kind of getting a jump on everybody else.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it's going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, the news will start flooding in in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_13]: I might actually do a little bit of commentary on my Tumblr as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: All across the internets.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're looking to have one million viewers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get into some actual gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's still a lot going on in the gaming world ramping up to E3 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's go to Loki who's going to start us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, Sony announced their titles that are going to be a part of the Welcome Back program.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, the Welcome Back program includes a free 30-day trial to PlayStation Plus for all PlayStation Network users.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, they're going to be giving out a 30-day trial to Curiosity, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Her Curiosity, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm calling it Curiosity.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then also, apparently, two free PlayStation games and two free PlayStation Portable games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of the free PlayStation 3 games that are available for North America, because it's a little bit different in each region...
[SPEAKER_03]: Dead Nation, Infamous, LittleBigPlanet, SuperStardustHD, and WipeoutHD plus Fury.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I already own two of those, so that's going to narrow down my choices of what I'm going to get.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Same here.
[SPEAKER_03]: For PSP owners, I guess, you'll be able to get LittleBigPlanet on PSP, Mod Nation Racers, Pursuit Force, or Killzone Liberation.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then of course they're going to have a selection of On Us movie rentals through the PlayStation Network and I guess existing PlayStation Plus subscribers will receive an additional 60 days of free subscription and existing Music Unlimited Premium Trial subscription members will receive an additional 30 days of free music as well and also an additional 30 days
[SPEAKER_03]: Plus time lost for existing members of the Music Unlimited Premium Basic Subscription fee free of charge.
[SPEAKER_03]: And in home, of course, they're going to have 100 free items in home.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can one of those items be useful clubhouses?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_03]: In Europe, they're going to be doing some slightly different titles.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to have Ratchet & Clank, Quest for Booty, Wipeout HD, Fury, Dead Nation, Infamous, and LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, on PSP... Actually, the titles are the same on PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess it can be slightly different for each region.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which begs the question, since PlayStation Network accounts are free to create, I had three of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I guess I get six games because I had three accounts created.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there going to be a thing where maybe you have to have used a credit card in a transaction or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because technically, I mean, I could download some free download content or something like that and never had to buy anything, but I'm still out of, you know, the three, four weeks or whatever it was down.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if I share a PlayStation with somebody else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, my significant other lives with me and we share an account.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I'm sorry, we don't share an account.
[SPEAKER_04]: We share a PlayStation, but we have two separate accounts.
[SPEAKER_04]: So will I get to get two and he'll get to get the other two?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, that's what I'm thinking
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Either way, let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I have LittleBigPlanet already, and I would never... I wouldn't want to download it, because I have my really rare LittleBigPlanet with the band music in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I'd probably pick up Infamous, because that looked pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the rest of the PlayStation Network games, I just don't really care too much about those.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe... I don't know, Dead Nation looked alright, or Wipeout...
[SPEAKER_03]: I really don't care, but if I can pick six titles then I'll probably get everything and then we'll see what Japan has whenever they get around to come back up.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, some other fun stuff Sony related.
[SPEAKER_03]: The PlayStation Network, they had opened up their website for changing your password, and apparently the sign-ins, they've disabled them because they found a potential exploit that people could use to basically hack your account.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, now keep reading.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I guess it allowed people to go some roundabout way to change their password and get access to their account.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very minor and it got fixed pretty quick, but it's just you can't keep making these mistakes.
[SPEAKER_03]: You really got to be on your toes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love this comment in our chat room from Islander.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, OLR, a lot of people...
[SPEAKER_04]: on home right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, it's like I3 Linder, but I'm saying... Blender?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's a little B. Okay, Blender.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blender says, by the way, OLR, a lot of people on home right now are having freezing issues when they get a new item.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some sort of bug since the relaunch.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, home is freezing whenever you get a new item.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hacked and people have started stealing virtual currency.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's, I guess, some Sony run internet service provider called Sonet.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had some virtual points or whatever and people apparently stole roughly 100,000 yen or $1,200 worth of virtual points.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it says no personal information was compromised or any other accounts.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, it's still kind of pathetic that you're having multiple accounts assigned.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, there's another story that I don't even think was on here where they had another account, another website that got hacked and became a phishing account now, a phishing website.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, man, Sony is just the Internet's bitch right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the Japanese government refuses to let Sony relaunch the PlayStation Network there.
[SPEAKER_03]: They haven't given approval for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it says, apparently, the Ministry of Economy, Content Industry says the government refused Sony's initiative to...
[SPEAKER_03]: to launch the platform again.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says as of May 13th, Sony was incomplete in exercising measures that they said they will do on the May 1st press conference.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says the details of which the measures haven't been enacted yet were not released.
[SPEAKER_03]: The source added that the government wants clear terms of what Sony is planning on doing to protect its users.
[SPEAKER_03]: Credit card info saying there were similar cases in the past that were caused by other firms and we're asking Sony
[SPEAKER_03]: whether their measures are good enough when compared to countermeasures taken in the past.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that sounds fair enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of a big deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, the country's basically saying, no, you're not coming back up because you're not proven that you're secure.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then as we keep hearing all these stories about other facets of the company getting hacked, it's kind of not helping their case.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, you know why the Roman Empire fell?
[SPEAKER_13]: The Roman Empire?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dreamcast 2 Overlooked
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, let's move on to some more hopeful news.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, not all the news that comes out of Sony these days is bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this could be possibly giving us a sign of some things that we could look forward to at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I gotta say, man, Sony... Sony is gonna have... I mean, I realize Nintendo has just announced that they're showing a new fucking console at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I am still most interested in Sony's prefs conference.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really am.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it's either gonna be...
[SPEAKER_04]: The biggest, like, redemption ever, or it's gonna be just the nail in the coffin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, there is so much writing on Sony's press conference this year, I can't even, like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm really curious to see what their thing looks like.
[SPEAKER_04]: This might be one of the things that they're going to announce at the press conference at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently there's a God of War portable collection that is going to be coming out to the PlayStation 3 in Asian regions in July.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a press release that was sent by Sony Computer Entertainment Taiwan and picked up by International Gaming News websites.
[SPEAKER_04]: So apparently the God of War PSP games Chains of Olympus and Ghosts of Sparta are going to be revamped HD Chinese and English language options and will be released on July 7th in Asia And of course a lot of people kind of their minds go well if it's coming out in Asia why the heck isn't it coming out in the rest of the world So this could be something that's being announced In fact And I mean if it's going to be in England or you know if it's coming out in Asia you can import it even if it wasn't coming out right away
[SPEAKER_04]: God of War 3
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony, in fact, unveiled a new initiative this week where certain PlayStation Portable titles will be ported to the PlayStation 3 with improvements made that are, you know, like exactly what we're hearing about the God of War collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, in my mind, this confirms the God of War thing because, duh, of course they're going to do the God of War game.
[SPEAKER_03]: They already showed off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Monster Hunter Portable 3
[SPEAKER_04]: The question is, what other games might be included as part of this?
[SPEAKER_04]: What are the other, like, huge PlayStation Portable titles that could be a part of this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just throwing it out there, maybe Metal Gear Acid?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think they would do Acid.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that they would do the last Metal Gear Solid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, the last one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Peace Walker.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Peace Walker could be one, certainly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we'd learn about that pretty quick if that was going to be the case, because Konami would probably announce it during their press conference, which would be the Sunday prior.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm certainly looking forward to the... Unless they're told not to say that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm certainly hoping that those Final Fantasy remakes would be a part of it, although I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_04]: uh that would nah plus I'd be a little bit irritated because I already bought those I would see that maybe uh you know Dissida or um you know oh yeah that I bet that's that's a big one or the other Final Fantasy game the seven spin-off Crisis Core thank you yeah yeah
[SPEAKER_04]: So those are definite contenders from Squeenix, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_03]: And who's to say they couldn't just do some of these as download games?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that would make sense to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe the Half Minute Hero games as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is all but certain to show up at E3, so it's just a matter of what titles and when.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what's great about it, though, is like some of those games, you know, that were kind of, they're just all right, you know, with control-wise because they didn't have a second analog.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, now we can fix that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or that little nub thing that the PSP has kind of starts to wear on your finger.
[SPEAKER_04]: Am I the only one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I can't use that thing for a long period of time because it hurts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just the texture on that button is yuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually had a replacement so I could, you know, put on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I never had a problem with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I guess it's just me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, DarkSakura, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_13]: There's some Mortal Kombat news out there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Basically, with the PlayStation 3, you had the Kombat Pass so that you could... You'd have to have it to play online, but you can only, of course, use it while the PlayStation Store is online, which, of course, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it's being waived until everything is pretty much back up full-time.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I didn't even really think about that until I had heard about this story because I cashed in my pass because I bought the game the day it came out or I had Amazon deliver it the day it came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I cashed in my pass that day and the next day is when PlayStation went down.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I never had a problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was able to play online.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it didn't occur to me that, oh yeah, with the store being down, you can't redeem those passes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you didn't get this game on launch day, you were screwed.
[SPEAKER_13]: So they're actually waiving the need for the pass until the PlayStation Store is fully operational.
[SPEAKER_04]: And good, that's the right thing to do, but I don't feel sorry for them for the amount of shit they probably got from their fanbase and threatens of lawsuits and so forth, because that's what you get for putting these passes in the game in the first place.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really doesn't just end with Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a growing trend.
[SPEAKER_13]: Capcom, Capcom, Capcom, Capcom.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, actually, you know, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Capcom isn't doing that at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they're doing that with their download content.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're doing it with their DRM.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, their DRM with their download content sucks, but they're not one of these companies putting out this, oh, we've got to buy it new in order to play online for free.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that's kind of bullshit.
[SPEAKER_03]: THQ, THQ, THQ, and now Warner Brothers is kind of following suit with EA.
[SPEAKER_03]: So those are your evil three right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: since the Super Nintendo days to be quite honest honestly I think if what's gonna happen here the whole reason they're doing those online passes anyways is trying to recoup some money they're losing from piracy because if you want to play it online you gotta pay the $10 which some people have no problem doing especially if they've pirated the game but I don't know I still think it's dumb
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, and it's especially dumb that when I am supporting the company and I buy it new that I get locked out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_13]: They realized they probably had to set everything up before they could announce it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, but there were certainly a few days there where they probably got a lot of shit from people.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just saying they deserved it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even still though, someone bought that copy at one time, so they already made their sale for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why do they need more money after the fact?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because someone else decides to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be like, oh hey Rob, I watched this DVD once and I'm going to loan it to you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Should the company get money for that?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, because they already bought it once.
[SPEAKER_03]: They already got the money made from that.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they wanted a pay-per-view service or something like that, then they should do something different.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me go to our chatroom at chat.orangelandtrader.com TigerClaw in our chat says, Not only that, anyone who bought a game that comes with a code for some DLC in the box, they can't redeem it until the store goes back up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, like, funny enough, although I redeemed the combat pass, I did not redeem my reptile original outfit that I got for buying the game, but I don't, you know, I'm a little, it's a stupid costume.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I'm not, the Barbie features, I'm not so bent out of shape about, you know, it doesn't really impact the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: but I mean it's certainly still a valid point maybe some other games had DLC that were impacted by this so there you go Frisbee in our chat room flat out says DRM is a poison it's such a bummer because I get why companies have to do it I mean obviously piracy is an issue and it is something that has to be dealt with but it just sucks when the people that get affected most by the change is the ones that are trying to do everything legitimately
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_04]: It never ends.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: New story, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: hmm could possibly maybe I don't know adding DS or DSi download games to the virtual console or whatever they're going to call that because now you'll have your touch screen and your one screen in your controller and your other screen is up on TV but then of course I have to say is why would you spend more money on a controller which I'm assuming is going to be at least a hundred bucks you know when you can buy DS or DSi
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm black
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because when I heard about this, I was thinking more of the Kinect-style features, but I guess that doesn't work if it's on a controller, does it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't really think that one through.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_03]: This sounds like this console is going to have gimmicks out the ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, what possible gimmicks can we throw in on this thing?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got motion controls, it's got a touchscreen, it's got a camera on it, it's got, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: Microwave, I mean, what else can we throw on this fucking... I just have to see how they're going to use it because I'm going to tell you this much.
[SPEAKER_03]: All the Nintendo gimmicks that have been out there haven't been that great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, the motion control stuff, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then you get all these launch games that are all these just waggle this, waggle this when it could have been just a button for all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or, you know, just the Zapper or the Wii Fit balance board or Motion Plus.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, a lot of it is just rehash, you know, or...
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a gimmicky game that's not really that original.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just all this extra crap that you don't really need in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if they're throwing in all these gimmicks, they gotta be doing something really smart with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the problem why it seems like there's so many gimmicks as well is because we're in that rumor phase where people are just fucking making shit up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm not even sure I totally agree with this rumor.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's just somebody making a good odds prediction.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Half the stuff they promise will not make it at launch or at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they're going to promise you all this stuff that this console is going to be doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, that feature is not done yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not going to be out for six months after the console is released.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't release a console that's halfway done and then your sales are pretty shitty as it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then stuff that's promised at the launch of that stuff, you know,
[SPEAKER_04]: it's just delay after delay I'm not quite as negative as Loki is on this issue really Nintendo really only needs to do just a couple things to make me buy the new system as long as it's high definition and capable of pretty graphics and it has a new F-Zero game on it and it has a type of controller that's not quite so gimmicky where maybe I understand there's going to be some gimmick of some sort but as long as we can kind of tone it down a little bit I'll be in I'm fine
[SPEAKER_04]: Even like 2 out of 3 ain't bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they don't really give me an F-Zero game, I guess I can't be that upset.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I really want it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really, really want an F-Zero game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now would be a perfect time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless this whole touch thing ends up actually being true, because I don't know how you'd incorporate that into an F-Zero game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But again, I think the touch thing is utter bullshit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's total bullshit, but I guess we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: 360, Sony, Nintendo
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: At least that's what the rumors say.
[SPEAKER_04]: The official Microsoft statement says,
[SPEAKER_04]: and are proactively reaching out to customers that may be impacted to replace their console.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any Xbox 360 owners receiving this error are encouraged to contact us at xbox.com support contact so we can verify if the console has been impacted.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Using that whole fact that they send information over the internet automatically about your console to Microsoft, they're able to tell exactly who's affected by this and send them replacements.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if it's the original 360s, but they've all Red Ringed by now anyway, so that's why it's such a small number.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is one of the original, I think, drives.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the, either the Samsung, Hitachi, or the... Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember the last one there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Toshiba.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, also speaking about Xbox 360, PayPal has been rolling out in certain territories.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's an automatic update that was going out, and it's going to certain regions first, and now you can actually use PayPal as a billing option on your console.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can do that for Microsoft Points and other types of marketplace content.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently...
[SPEAKER_04]: That has all been rolling out over the past week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember updating my console, but it might have been done when I was around.
[SPEAKER_03]: They haven't been, like I didn't get an update on Friday for my consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, just certain regions right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: May 27th is when Avatar Connect is scheduled to come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that is the, if you are too shy to use voice chat, or I'm sorry, video chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you know your Connect has video chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you want to use fake people instead to chat, you'll be able to do that on the 27th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on with another news story and then we'll get to the release dates.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, going back to Microsoft, there has been word about something that according to our show role is the Connect Fub Lab.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I have fubby fat fingers and I think I meant to type fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had to give you a hard time.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Connect Fun Lab might be revealed at E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: They are going to be doing a lot of stuff for the Connect, but there is a source that said that something called Connect Fun Lab is in the works to be revealed there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not really sure what it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's also another possible Connect title that's called Connect Me that's on the Australia Classifications Board and has Microsoft as a publisher.
[SPEAKER_13]: Crimson Alliance and Fusion Genesis
[SPEAKER_03]: Fusion Genesis, I know what that is.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's another Fusion Frenzy game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Crimson Alliance, that sounds like another Crimson Skies game, which sounds kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Fusion Frenzy, no!
[SPEAKER_13]: Crimson Alliance is by Certain Affinity and they did Age of Booty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still don't know if that's what it is, but... Fusion Frenzy!
[SPEAKER_03]: It's terrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't make another Fusion Frenzy game.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're all terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, hopefully that isn't what it is, but I'm a little more worried about Kinect Fun Lab Because I thought that this year was the year we're going to see at E3 what the Kinect can really do Alright, we've seen all the Nintendo rip-offs, now let's see what the Kinect can really do It can really rip off Nintendo now I hear Fun Lab and I think, oh goody, it's a lab full of mini-games Fun, fun, fun, fun
[SPEAKER_13]: or it's all puppies.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's all lab puppies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope Fun Lab has to do with genetic mutations of people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make your own monster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, create your own alien or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want fucking minigames.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly, that would be Fun Lab.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then you make them fight through Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, and it's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all virtual.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not real.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: A magic pen gel where I draw with my hands.
[SPEAKER_04]: I smear paint to make creatures like it's a monkey smearing poop on the wall.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fun Lab.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would play that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Monkey Poo Fun Lab.
[SPEAKER_13]: Monkey Poo Fun Lab.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around the world and look at some release dates.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft,
[SPEAKER_03]: Kung Fu Panda 2, another movie tie-in game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this one, it's a little weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're doing something different on every single platform.
[SPEAKER_03]: The PlayStation 3 game is just a PlayStation 3 game.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Xbox 360 is getting a Kinect game.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Wii is getting a U-Draw game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then DS is just another regular DS game.
[SPEAKER_03]: so those will be out later this week and then let's see here this is fucking slow today other fun stuff like what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like this is updating.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like Monkey Pooh Smear.
[SPEAKER_03]: Monkey Pooh Smear, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Monkey Pooh Smear is coming out this week on all platforms, including the Atari.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looks very exciting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I'm trying to see what else we have here.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a really small week, but I know it's more than just those two titles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on, cooperate.
[SPEAKER_03]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dungeons & Dragons Daggerdale for PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, Naughty Bear, the Gold Edition, in case you didn't buy that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's coming out now with all the download content at a budget price on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: NASCAR 2011 on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been delayed a little bit, so now it's finally coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Paws and Claws Pampered Pets 2 for Nintendo DS out this week as well and Murder in Venice kind of an adventure game that's also for DS Cake Mania Main Street that's on DS this week and that is pretty much it
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, we have some news for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_13]: For overseas, in the U.K.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it's actually just a few games.
[SPEAKER_13]: On the 24th, we have Dirt 3 for Xbox 360, PC, and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we also have Kung Fu Panda for the DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: And on the 27th is Gladiator Begins on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_13]: And on the 30th, we have Fable 3 for PC, which, why it's taking so dang long to come out, oh well, we don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fable 3, I will go ahead and warn our UK viewers.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, I've got friends that love, when I say viewers, it's listeners.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've got friends that love Fable 3, but it's really not all that great.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fable 2 is so much of a better game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: Fable 2 is alright, but Fable 3 didn't look like they added too much stuff to it, so I passed on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't trust anything Peter Molyneux says.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's full of shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: That means he needs to probably go potty.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Except every time he potties a new game comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: and uh well I have really nothing else on for UK I mean there's they list games but they don't put dates on them like Back to the Future Double Vision is on the list but they didn't put a date on it so that's all and speaking of uh stuff that's coming out
[SPEAKER_04]: Akai Katana Shin Red Katana New Death
[SPEAKER_04]: Here, people discovered a Bloodsword that takes human sacrifices to unleash its mass-destructive power.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be Redsword Death, then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, this is an existing game that's already been out.
[SPEAKER_04]: The 360 version will have new stages, new characters, and a new system, and the graphics will fit in a 16.9.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm assuming this is a prior PlayStation 2 release.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that is coming out this week, and it's a shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, it's a shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Cave.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you expect?
[SPEAKER_04]: Warrior's Legend of Troy
[SPEAKER_04]: Dynasty Warriors, but with the Trojan horse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not the Trojan condoms, but the Trojan horse.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be a whole other type of game.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the PlayStation 3 this week, Hiro no Kakira Aizoban Akane Hiro no Suyoku comes out this week from Idea Factory in regular and limited edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this game is an adventure game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to see what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, it looks like every other.
[SPEAKER_04]: Infamous goes into the best series, meaning it gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobunaga, Noyabu, Tendo, and a power-up kit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Woo-hoo, come out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's $124 if you want both of those to import.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Totori no Atelier, Arland no Rekken Jushutsu 2 goes into the Best Hits collection as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So some price reductions this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to the Nintendo systems, taking a look real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo Wii, Pandora's Tower, Until I Return to Your Side comes out on the Wii this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course I hear Pandora and I go, wait a minute, wasn't it what they call the Kid Icarus games over in Japan?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pandora's... I thought this was called Pandora's Adventure or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't Kid Icarus called that in Japan?
[SPEAKER_04]: But that is not what this is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is not like a Kid Icarus game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's some other type of game on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's in a black box instead of a white Wii box.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, ooh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going on to the Nintendo 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: One Piece Unlimited Cruise SP comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And lastly, going to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_13]: Shutsugeki, Kid Icarus, Hikari Shinwa, Palthena no Kagami, Light Myth, Palthena's Mirror
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, the game I was reading on the PSP, Shutsugeki Otomatashi no Senjo 2, comes out from System Soft this week on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is a strategy game that involves anime chicks in hot outfits.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, like, okay, look at these screenshots, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: You get, like, hot anime babe, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you have, like, anime babes in, like, little maid outfits, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: And then it's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Driving in the streets with tanks and airplanes.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a very manly sort of game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hot anime babes and then tanks and fighter jets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pre-ordering it today.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on and go over a couple more news stories, and we'll get into the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura's picked a very popular series tonight, so we'll get to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: For now, though, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, this is kind of disappointing, because this was actually a game I was looking forward to checking out once the delayed Nintendo Store for the 3DS was released.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, but yes, like all things delayed, there are more delays.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Mega Man Legends 3 Prototype Version, a demo for a game that's not even finished yet...
[SPEAKER_03]: will be delayed from the 3DS eShop launch on June 6th.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is terrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they haven't really said yet when it's going to be released, but I guess you have to wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is for that demo, basically, of the potential Mega Man Legends 3 game that might come out should enough people pay to get this demo concept of what it could possibly be.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, you know, we may make this game, but you have to pay for this demo, and we may, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be honest, I'll probably buy it anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as, okay, here's my little stipulation, I guess we won't really know, because of course we're not going to get told, but my wish is as long as the game I'm not buying here in the DS shop ends up being a part of the actual full game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do not want to be paying for what will be the first two chapters of the retail release.
[SPEAKER_04]: A side story or a leading into game, those are fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: A case zero is perfectly acceptable.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't want something that's just going to end up being the first chapter of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Capcom was also behind the Dead Rising case zero, which was actually a pretty cool little idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: So my hope is they're going to get this one right too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to hold my breath.
[SPEAKER_04]: LA Noire is a game that a lot of people are talking about this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's a very kind of different sort of rock star game from what I understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: People are going into it expecting 1940s Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not quite what they're getting.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the game seems to be pretty well received.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless you're one of these people that are affected by the overheating.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, firmware 3.61 on the PlayStation 3 is causing certain Sony consoles to overheat when playing L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is according to Rockstar's own customer support.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quote,
[SPEAKER_04]: mostly on older 60 and 80 gig fat models oh shit I have one of these models primary reports seem to be that updating to firmware 361 will cause playstations to overheat there have been various reports of this on a few different games now all reporting their playstation 3's turning off or red lighting after having installed 3.6.1 or 3.61 excuse me yikes well now if you're an xbox fanboy pointing and laughing and kicking sony while they're down hold it
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: There are reported instances that Microsoft's system is having issues with this as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rockstar, of course, was blaming Sony originally, but now that the Xbox stuff is coming to light, they've changed a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's their latest statement.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've received a very small number of customer support questions about PS3s overheating or shutting down while playing L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire.
[SPEAKER_04]: At this time, Rockstar Games and Sony can confirm that neither L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire or firmware update 3.61...
[SPEAKER_04]: are causing the PS3 hardware to overheat.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are both committed to working hard to find solutions to this and any issues that may arise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if that isn't the vaguest fucking thing I've ever heard, it's not the game and it's not the system.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's really nothing else between that that would cause your system to overheat.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just you is really what I'm hearing in that statement.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not the system and it's not the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just you.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not me.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, what the fuck kind of press release is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not say, we recognize the problem and we are working on a solution?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, how hard was that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Very hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not like Sony hasn't got bigger problems right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ugh, this is more just that corporate bullshit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, stop it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just be real with the consumers.
[SPEAKER_04]: We see through your crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to go back into a time when gaming wasn't so full of such asshattery and bullshit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's a segment we call the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where we turn back the clock, take a stroll down memory lane, and find a classic game in the archives that DarkSakura says, Hey!
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen up, brats.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should be playing this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or I'll set your PlayStation 3 on fire myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: You won't even need Ellie anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll have my engineers invent combustible lemons that'll burn your PS3 down.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is the classic game of the week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_13]: Mother.
[SPEAKER_13]: Mother is, uh... Well, as we all know, is the precursor to Mother 2, which came out over here as Earthbound.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, um...
[SPEAKER_13]: This was... It came out on the Famicom.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it came out in...
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm trying to find the year and it doesn't list the year on here.
1989.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, 1989.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it was actually published by Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was produced by Miyamoto and written by Shigesato Itoi.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it has some fantastic names behind it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was developed by Ape and Panic Softica and Nintendo Tokyo.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: They localized that.
[SPEAKER_13]: So there is an official localized prototype of the game, and that was actually put out by DemiForce.
[SPEAKER_13]: They used the ROM data that was from the prototype, and it's being put out as Earthbound Zero.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that actually made it out in 1998.
[SPEAKER_13]: The game itself has field maps and a battle system.
[SPEAKER_13]: It doesn't use an overworld map.
[SPEAKER_13]: It just basically... Sorry, my throat's getting messed up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ninten
[SPEAKER_13]: So when you are on the field map, because like I said, it doesn't have an overall map, just has field maps, you will be attacked by enemies, and then you go into battle mode, where it's a first-person view, and you attack the creature or whatever, like a lamp, through the different menu system commands, and you have different actions for different characters.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you also...
[SPEAKER_13]: can do different moves in order that are based on the character's speed statistics.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you also, of course, get experience and level up that way.
[SPEAKER_13]: And if you lose all of your hit points, then you go to the hospital and you have to pay to revive your characters.
[SPEAKER_13]: And if every character dies, you don't lose your progress, but you go back to the last area that you saved at with only an intent alive and half of your money.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's kind of crappy, huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: So at any rate... That's harsh.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds harder than the pirated version of Earthbound where it would delete your own saved game when you got to the last boss.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, after doubling the difficulty?
[SPEAKER_13]: At any rate, the game talks about a married couple in America who vanished after a dark shadow covered their town.
[SPEAKER_13]: Two years later, George, the husband, returns mysteriously.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then he starts studying in complete seclusion and his wife Maria is never heard from again.
[SPEAKER_13]: So you fast forward to 1988 where there's a 12-year-old boy named Minton who is attacked by a paranormal event.
[SPEAKER_13]: SmartKid
[SPEAKER_13]: So at any rate, he finds out that an invading race is, an alien race is, you know, invading.
[SPEAKER_13]: And so they go to the world of Magicant where the ruler there, Queen Mary, asks Nintendo to find her a song called The Eight Melodies and play it to her.
[SPEAKER_13]: Play all the songs to her.
[SPEAKER_13]: So he meets up with a dude named Lloyd and a girl named Anna.
[SPEAKER_13]: And she dreamed about him.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's the start of the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you keep, you know, going through and you duel some dude named Teddy.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, uh... You have to, uh...
[SPEAKER_13]: It's actually funny because you have to, um, the queen tells you about an alien named, I'm hoping that I'm pronouncing this right, but I think it's Gigu, that's spelled G-Y-I-Y-G or something, but it's Gigu, which is actually the same way it was initially romanized for Earthbound in the unreleased translation.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, it pretty much, you know, more fun, going saving the universe.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the game actually did get a re-release in 2003 with Mother 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the tagline was, No Crying Until the End and a Guaranteed Masterpiece.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it was actually designed by a Japanese copywriter and television personality, Shigesato Itoi.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the inspiration for the game was from John Lennon's young mother.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he also wanted the game to have a name that wasn't game-like.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't know that part.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: and I like this quote here it said that the last parts of Mother were not tested for bugs and balance issues and when talking about it at a promotional event he humorously stated when we got to fine tuning the difficulty there I was like whatever so yeah there's a lot of people and I've started playing it a while back but never really got too much further into it who says this is a game that you have to grind and grind and grind and grind to get through
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Phil Sandhop, who said, and I'm quoting, once the NES squatted in the pipeline and shoved the game aside from its appointed time, I believe that the marketing execs just decided that the game would be too expensive to produce and unsuccessful without marketing, and that's why it fell into oblivion.
[SPEAKER_13]: They were doing a lot of stuff in localization, which was removing blood from enemy sprites, which was a censorship thing they had at the time.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they were going to extend the game's ending.
[SPEAKER_13]: So at any rate, Demiforce, as I mentioned before, found a beta cartridge on the internet, and they collected enough money to buy the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember when that happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was in college and that was all going on.
[SPEAKER_13]: And so they actually had to do modified versions with the copy protection disabled and renamed it Earthbound Zero so that it could separate it from Earthbound.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they actually put everything out.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, I thought it was neat that they bought the rights to do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: The music in it was done by Keiichi Suzuki and Hirokazu Tanaka.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it was actually released on CD and cassette by Sony on August 21st, 1989.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it had 11 tracks.
[SPEAKER_13]: And 7 of them are vocal remakes.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it's got the eight melodies on there, one called Pollyanna.
[SPEAKER_13]: And actually, on February 18, 2004, the soundtrack was re-released, digitally remastered, and songs from it appear in EarthBound, Mother 3, Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_13]: Melee, and Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_13]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_13]: So there's actually some pretty...
[SPEAKER_13]: Big names that were included with the CD, including the St.
[SPEAKER_13]: Paul's Cathedral Choir.
[SPEAKER_13]: It sold 400,000 copies in Japan, and in two polls by Famitsu, it was the 9th best game for the Famicom and the 38th best game of all time.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was the 4th most-won virtual console game in June 2008, according to Nintendo Power, and moved up to the 2nd most-wanted.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, it was called Dark and Mature.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mother or Earthbound Zero?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Original.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most folks in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: have never seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good pick.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a great series.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, that series had a lot of rabid fans.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does seem ridiculous that Nintendo really just kind of let it die.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I think I get some of the reasons behind it, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like...
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a pretty cute little RPG franchise that Nintendo had, and it's just kind of a bummer that they couldn't work around some of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand maybe why things can't be re-released, but it's a bummer they can't get the same kind of concept and the whole modern RPG thing and kind of make it work with the new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But maybe some things are just left better as classics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, we're going to go ahead and use this opportunity to take a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: But don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be right back with plenty more of Orange Lounge Radio right after a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming up after the break, we've got stories about Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, some folks find that game highly offensive.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to talk about who and why in a little while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some other Portal 2 news and E3 news already starting to come in.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you can actually go to one of the press conferences.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to talk a little bit about that when we come back after a quick break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to get into those in just a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, some quick plugs for some other projects that we do, which we actually referenced already at the top of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we're going to sell them again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't really advertise anything on this show except our other shows.
[SPEAKER_13]: So here's your commercial.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what's your show?
[SPEAKER_13]: Comic Insanity, which is at Infamous.net, N-F-A-M-O-U-S dot net.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we talk about comics, but we also have a new segment where we talk about a classic comic of the week.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we also have what Shadow calls the Random Encounter, which is talking about an old RPG.
[SPEAKER_13]: Classic RPG.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Throwing a little video game spin in your comic show.
[SPEAKER_13]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're trying to leave us, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, never, never, never, never, never.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is my big baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your big nine-year-old crying bratty baby that says shit a lot.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, gonna have to wash this mouth out with some lye soap.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, but yeah, we talk comics and it's me and Maureen Marvel and Dan Shadow and we're awesome!
[SPEAKER_13]: Listen to us, we go live every Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, if you like the WoW chat that we do at the top of the show sometimes during our gaming weeks there's a whole other show I have with my buddy Extover all about the World of Warcraft it's called The Best Little Horde House in Azeroth www.hordehouse.com and I promise you this week actually, well, the show that's on the feed right now because we tape Thursdays and we post Thursday night the show that's on the feed right now is the one with DarkSakura on it so it's a great episode I promise on this week's show
[SPEAKER_04]: There's going to be a shocking revelation that I'm going to get tons of shit for.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be a hatin' on Rob episode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, I was in my pajamas the entire time.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, HordeHouse.com if you want more information like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I have not quit WoW and I have not resigned my account, so get those thoughts out of your head.
[SPEAKER_04]: I always threaten to do it whenever Blizzard does something that pisses me off, but I have yet to.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it's not that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow, let's get into some rapid fire news and then we'll get into the Twitter topics after that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some quick stories that we want to throw at you, although we don't have a whole lot of time to discuss them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, No More Heroes, Heroes Paradise is coming August 16th.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe a new Carmageddon being announced at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Coming from Square Enix, apparently they have a countdown on the Carmageddon.com website.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it is counting down to June 1st, so maybe an announcement...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so weird, because when I think of Squeenix, I don't think of Carmageddon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think of role-playing games and dudes with big hair, but I keep forgetting, oh yeah, they have Eidos now, and that's where the Tomb Raider comes from and all that other stuff, so it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then finally, if you have a homebrew-enabled PSP, there's some pretty cool stuff you can do with that, including the PSP 3D plugin version 2.0.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been released.
[SPEAKER_03]: It enables 3D for select PSP games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is of course the old school cyan red glasses that you can wear.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you can actually play quite a few games in 3D.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've just added support for Crisis Core, God Eater Burst, FIFA 11, and the third birthday.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's a pretty extensive list of games that actually are supported by it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Despicable Me, Ape Escape, Ridge Racer 2, Ratchet and Clank Size Matters, Grip Shift...
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots of big titles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Dead to Rights Reckoning, Star Wars Battlefront, Elite Squadron.
[SPEAKER_03]: A little bit of a mix of everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Including Eye of Judgment Legends.
[SPEAKER_03]: Still won't sell them all the copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to our chatroom at chat.orangelandrea.com Dungeon Buster says, Carmageddon was so fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Amiga777 says, Carmageddon was Eidos' baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just that when I think of Squeenix, I don't really think of Carmageddon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think of role-playing games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I realize they've done some other stuff throughout their history that wasn't quite like that, but I just, I don't know, I think of the other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then Eidos is kind of the company that
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if that's just they had a lot of paint to polish on it, or maybe they decided to do more with it than they had originally.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: But the iPad version of the game will come out a little bit later than the iPhone version.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is because of the higher resolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: Square does say one thing they are doing, redoing some of the artwork for the higher resolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's pretty awesome, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: So take a look at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alan Wake is apparently getting a new game on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not quite what you'd think.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not like a sequel or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's a game called Alan Wake's Night Springs.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a rumor right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's nothing that's been confirmed.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: This makes a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alan Wake was a pretty...
[SPEAKER_04]: XBOX LIVE ARCADE
[SPEAKER_04]: Alan Wake really reminds me of Twin Peaks, but as a video... And when I say Twin Peaks, like the old show from 1990 with Kyle MacLachlan and David Lynch was the guy behind it, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who killed Laura Palmer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alan Wake kind of really reminds me of that a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Twin Peaks had a show within a show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was called like Ticket to Love or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like the soap opera within the show that would explain some of the things that are actually going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Alan Wake has something just like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Night Springs.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess that...
[SPEAKER_04]: Show within a game is getting a spin-off.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it'd have a show within a show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is not Alan Wake 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is not more download content for the first game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So whatever this is, it is something new.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming from Capcom, we've talked about Monster Hunter on the PS3, but now Monster Hunter Dynamic Hunting is coming to the iOS systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: Capcom did announce it for June.
[SPEAKER_04]: Monster Hunter Dynamic Hunting, it's coming out for the iOS devices.
[SPEAKER_04]: A new intuitive control system.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will not use the typical D-pad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray, because I hate D-pad translations on the iPhone, because there is no D-pad on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that'll be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can use horizontal slashes and vertical slashes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of a whole different little way of doing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably more information to come at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, how about some rock band news, too?
[SPEAKER_13]: There's some Lady Gaga, Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: On this new download content pack is going to be Lady Gaga Pack 02.
[SPEAKER_13]: Born This Way, Love Game, and Paparazzi.
[SPEAKER_13]: And there's also a couple of... Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Didn't mean to burp on the mic.
[SPEAKER_13]: There also will be a pro guitar upgrade for Alice in Chains Roosters and the White Stripes, Dead Leaves and the Dirty Ground.
[SPEAKER_13]: And two individual songs that are by Foreigner, Hot-Blooded and Urgent.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, those are in there.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then there is Super Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I always love an excuse to be able to play Lady Gaga on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, DarkSakura, sing along.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's hear the voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't be afraid of your voice, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: You were born this way, baby.
[SPEAKER_13]: Later.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not drunk yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Super Street Fighter 4 Arcade Edition is going to be coming to Steam and they had some issues bringing it out for the PC but now it's going to be on Steam and it will be $40 there are pre-orders available too and there's not going to be though any download content for Super Street Fighter Super Vanilla Street Fighter 4 I should say but the game will have a 10% discount for the Super Arcade Edition bringing it down to $36
[SPEAKER_12]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_13]: And the last of my batch of news is Dynasty Warriors Gundam 3 has a release date.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's in Europe, by the way.
[SPEAKER_13]: It will be on July 1st.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it's basically all the mobile suits.
[SPEAKER_13]: You have 50 playable and upgradable characters, 70 playable and upgradable mecha, or the mobile suits, I should say, including the mobile suit Gundam 00 and mobile suit Gundam UC.
[SPEAKER_13]: You also have three new gameplay systems that are Partner Strike, Emergency Dash, and Recovery Gauge.
[SPEAKER_13]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Gundam.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gundam.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I hate to bring it back to Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, this is an important question.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very important.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, you don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I apologize to the haters out there as well, but this is actually related to technology.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you see the commercial for Google Chrome with her in it?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't watch TV, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all over YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love how you're totally using Yiddish now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Talk amongst yourselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give you a topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lady Gaga, neither Gaga nor a lady, if certain rumors are to be believed.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, no, like the, and there's a Google Chrome commercial for, it's like a guy who, and you keep seeing the search box fill in with these different terms, like how to speak French, plane ticket to Paris.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's like, the whole thing is about like a long distance relationship and how Google like helps them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, what is a truffle?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really adorable and like, oh my god, Google does like the best commercials.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like people tell me that Chrome is a good... You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I upgraded to Firefox 4 and my personal opinion is that it's absolute and utter fucking shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it has slowed down my computer, certain websites are bored, Instagram, Firefox 4 is shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: See, Firefox 4 hasn't done anything...
[SPEAKER_04]: Firefox 3 is fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was a huge Firefox fan and supporter up until version 4, which is crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have switched to Chrome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will now never look back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I did Chrome in the very beginning, and I was like, this is kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now Chrome is great.
[SPEAKER_13]: See, none of my stuff's been borked with the upgrade.
[SPEAKER_13]: I still use my Fire FTP.
[SPEAKER_13]: I use everything.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, by the way, since we did talk about Lady Gaga's involvement, do you know that George Takei has a video out now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the It's Okay to Be Takei?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's Okay to Be Takei.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that whole law in, what is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Kentucky?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wherever, but fuck, place it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haha, lol, not anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bend over.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's...
[SPEAKER_04]: I've decided that I want him to be my gay daddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: For real, me too.
[SPEAKER_04]: He should be all of our gay daddies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then whenever we... Logan, don't you want George Takei as your gay daddy?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then when we're naughty, he goes, oh my, you've been naughty.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Him and Betty White need a buddy comedy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't George Takei and Betty White need a buddy comedy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, they do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would be their opening day.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: And he really does have just like a sexy voice, especially considering his age.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he always has had.
[SPEAKER_13]: God.
[SPEAKER_13]: He has a voice that could melt like.
[SPEAKER_13]: He has a voice that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You hear his voice and your panties come off, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm getting a look.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm trying to think of what a super dense metal is that's hard to melt because he could melt it.
[SPEAKER_13]: He could make steam out of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, how did we get on this subject?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, and that Kentucky Law?
[SPEAKER_04]: Total bullshit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it's okay to be TK.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want the mug.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I love the little Star Trek emblem on it, all in rainbow.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't even see that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I kind of want one.
[SPEAKER_04]: My birthday's coming up, just saying.
[SPEAKER_13]: The website is itsoktobtk.org or .com or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, we got on a tangent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tangent train.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Loki's like, I'm doing other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, don't forget about the asexual people too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I totally missed my reference.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's probably a good thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on with the Twitter topics for tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
Tweet, tweet, tweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm actually being rude and I'm like totally ignoring chat comments right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, chatters.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just, I was really into the whole George and Betty buddy comedy talk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kai Judo in the chat room says George and Betty should have a podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely they should.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw says, George Takei may be best known for Star Trek, but he made a contribution to Star Wars doing a voice for an episode of The Clone Wars.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bob Coffee says, I wanted the powers to be, or that be, to make that Sulu Excelsior series happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would have been a win.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that George Takei is involved with the Star Trek fandom the way he is.
[SPEAKER_04]: He just gets it.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's just awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the first Twitter topic tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is from, and I'm horribly going to mispronounce this name, and I apologize in advance, but it's Ramaditya Knight sends us his first tweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's me playing Scars of Time with my flute, and we're linked to a YouTubey, and this better not be a Rickroll.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's play a little clip of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see one of our listeners playing Scars of Time on the flute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me fast forward a little bit here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not bad!
[SPEAKER_04]: Now this is not like a sideways flute, this is like a pan flute.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, he's playing on the tin whistle.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very authentic.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what the setup is for this video.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like he's in a classroom or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some lady holding the mic there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this camera person is making me dizzy.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just turned the thing sideways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that theme.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a great video game song.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you don't know Scars of Time, you need to pause this podcast and go onto YouTube and either look at this guy's rendition or go just find the original song like ASAP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to some other tweets here from SSJ100 Matt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard about this earlier in the week too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what you guys think of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what sucks up the most internet bandwidth in the US?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, did you hear this story?
[SPEAKER_04]: Then let me have you guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think takes up the most internet bandwidth of anything?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, I'm assuming you heard this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so DarkSakura, since she didn't read it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, if we want to go with all of the hype, I would say Illegal Downloads.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a really good guess, actually, probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about AFTA?
[SPEAKER_04]: What legal thing do you think takes up the most bandwidth?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, if there's one particular site that's eating up more bandwidth than anybody else, who do you think it is?
[SPEAKER_04]: YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Both good guesses, but actually, the most bandwidth in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: is Netflix on video game consoles right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: S2100 Matt links us to an article about that Netflix is the top user of bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the internet, nearly 20% of peak hour downstream traffic in North America is used for streaming video over Netflix through a home video game console representing the most usage of any source.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a testament to how fast this whole technology and the game console stuff picked on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know, game consoles are selling for the mere fact that you can use them as instant Netflix boxes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't lie to yourself that this isn't a selling point for a lot of 360s and PlayStations and Wii's of the... Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hiccups are killer.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Wii's of the world, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo really had to get on with Netflix with the whole Wii, and I'm sure their next console will be on it as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: The three game consoles that support Netflix, the Wii, Xbox 360, and PlayStation 3, accounted for the majority of that usage.
[SPEAKER_04]: When combined, consoles accounted for 66.3% of the figure, or 19.7% of overall downstream usage.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And no, Amiga, it's not porn that is taking up the most bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a really good guess, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to some other tweets.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S tweets us and says, Hey, if you go to www.freeplayday.com, you can get a free $10 play at Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boy, I just did a total commercial for some website.
[SPEAKER_04]: If that wasn't Ranma S and I knew he's like a legitimate person, I would have thought that was a spoiler.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: I've gotten like five $10 off coupons from Dave & Buster's just by being in their little club thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: So they've...
[SPEAKER_13]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same card ever since then, and it has given me problems.
[SPEAKER_04]: When I went to Times Square once, I went to an OLR lunch with some of the OLR listeners, like Zaku, Ranma, some of the people you've heard call into this show before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Went to lunch with them and some others, and they saw my card get borked by the system because I didn't roam it, so I had to get it saved, and then it happened when I came back.
[SPEAKER_04]: So long story short, I've used the same card for 10 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Dave & Buster's has this program where once you spend a certain amount of chips, you go gold.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't wanna go on Wednesday night This is serious business
[SPEAKER_04]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll take Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan and I can have date night at Dave and Buster's.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I don't have classes on Wednesday night anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I have to get up at 8.30 in the freaking morning on Monday and Wednesday to go to astronomy, which I don't need astronomy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't get me started.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't want to go look at the planets?
[SPEAKER_13]: I have no need for astronomy as a designer.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your major?
[SPEAKER_13]: Graphic design.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I already have... You need to know how to draw lines.
[SPEAKER_13]: My degree will be here in like a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm officially a graduate.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: You didn't get a letter in seven degrees saying, sorry, you need some astronomy.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let me go to a couple tweets from Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tigerclaw is funny because he tweeted us a couple things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, dude, you tweeted us stuff that's going to come up later in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So he tweeted like seven things.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you only get two, Tigerclaw, but I'll read these.
[SPEAKER_04]: These are the ones that caught my eye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Harmonix is announcing a new game at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll file this between Dunn, of course, but, I mean, it's official.
[SPEAKER_04]: Harmonix is going to announce something new at E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: What does go between Dunn, of course?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance Central 2 apparently is going to go between those two.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm wondering if there is actually like something else with this as well they have said it is not Rock Band 4 that is confirmed and apparently there was an interview with Game Informer saying quote rest assured that Harmonix is still developing new ideas and concepts to advance the Rock Band franchise and we look forward to sharing them when the time is right
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think Harmonix is all about Dance Central necessarily.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there'll be something new from them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of hope it's a DJ game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope it's a DJ game too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they should just do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Konami refuses, then you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: When they fall asleep at the wheel, as they always have with their series that could do great here, then let Harmonix do it better.
[SPEAKER_04]: For real.
[SPEAKER_04]: One other one I'm going to read here.
[SPEAKER_04]: L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire, we were talking about earlier in the show, it is banned if you live in the UAE.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yep, there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: United Arab Emirates, the game magazine there, I'm sorry, the retail chain, Geekay Games, I keep reading it as Geeky Games, updated their Facebook saying, L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire has been banned.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, the UAE, the United Arab Emirates, their National Media Council.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't say why they've banned the game, but they've banned it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It probably has something to do with dead woman beaver.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just taking a speculation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just guessing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dead animals are nothing to, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dead animals are nothing to ban a video game about.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is it Winona's brown beaver?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think her name's Winona.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't played Eleanor yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that does it for Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter.com slash OLR if you want to send your shit early for next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just outed myself as a Primus fan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, let's get into some other news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, this is kind of... I don't know...
[SPEAKER_03]: Zynga Frontierville Oregon Trail
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course the learning company, the people that hold the rights to the Oregon Trail They're none too happy about the fact that Zynga is basically ripping off their game And even calling it the Oregon Trail expansion I mean, granted, yes, the Oregon Trail is a real thing But it's also very, very, very, very similar to the Oregon Trail game
[SPEAKER_04]: Usually I would go off on a tangent right now about frivolous lawsuits, etc, etc.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, it's Zynga and I'm just kind of like, eh, let them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I watched the trailer and that damn thing is, you know, if not a really lame version of the Oregon Trail that you would see on Facebook, it is basically everything that's part of the Oregon Trail.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I realize the Oregon Trail is like a historic thing, but the other tricky thing about it is that Oregon Trail is actually on Facebook as a game right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: BlackWolf in our chatroom says, unpopular opinion, the actual trail was called the Oregon Trail.
[SPEAKER_04]: I doubt they have the rights to everything related to that historical event.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not an unpopular opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's so many other game companies that need to be advocated for that I don't feel the need to save Zynga right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zynga.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to look at this trail, er... Hopefully I don't get sued because I said trail.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to look at this trailer real fast here.
[SPEAKER_11]: and a carpenter for fixing the wagon and such like.
[SPEAKER_11]: And a doctor in case folks come down with the Rocky Mountain Scoots.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can leave messages and fancy presents for your friends so they'll want to visit your expedition every day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I gotta be honest, this really does look like the Facebook game, the Oregon Trail Facebook game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, especially with the hunting thing and the whole fact how you invite your friends to go on the trail with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I think they have a point, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really can't help zing on this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seeing video of any Zynga game being played makes me hate Facebook.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I have hatred of Facebook, you know, thanks to Zynga.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, invite your friends!
[SPEAKER_03]: I fucking hate when people invite me to shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I do with people that invite me to shit?
[SPEAKER_03]: I ignore it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And perhaps block you from sending me invites for shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will not play Facebook games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I deleted all mine You guys would be impressed I didn't even play GagaVille I didn't play it I'm sorry, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: She's sold out, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: She's sold out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're teaming up with Zynga for shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't give a shit if they donated money to the Tsunami stuff, but they donated it through you or you donated it through them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just think it's retarded that you're...
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, but I'm not going to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am not going to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Loki, you hit the nail on the head.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was smart because it's going after the target audience.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't mean to sound like a sexist, but it's a bunch of women playing Farmville.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's who a lot of Gaga's music appeals to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most, not all, most of the Gaga haters are straight men.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it's just...
[SPEAKER_13]: I did, however, find an incredibly hilarious screen capture.
[SPEAKER_03]: Madonna, back in the day, did some really weird shit, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: She was really weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: She sold her soul to Pepsi, and then they just fucked her over after that whole like a prayer thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Gaga is like, you know, Madonna to Eleven.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just... Seriously, she's fucking... No, she is.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's actually more like Marilyn Manson than she is Madonna.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's just fucking crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know what happened to Marilyn Manson?
[SPEAKER_03]: People stopped caring!
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's what's gonna happen to Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_03]: People are gonna stop fucking caring.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I gotta admit, her... I'll never stop.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love her.
[SPEAKER_03]: Her early music was okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But each song that comes out after that, I care less and less about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, she starts making up stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, anybody can use spout out non-words, you know, in a song.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's easy to do, but it's just, I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, for example, Born This Way totally sounds like an anthem, you know, a gay anthem or something like that, that she, you know, crafted on purpose so that it gets played in gay clubs to make sure that she has, you know, the gay demographic.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that's all it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, it's just figuring out how to, you know,
[SPEAKER_04]: I did find actually one interesting marketing thing that she did where they were giving away a can of monster fuel now I have to ask this since you talk about how Gaga's music gets weirder and weirder and I really hope I don't get screwed by clicking on random YouTube links but have you heard that Lady Gaga has a new song on her album called Scheisse which is German for shit so she literally has a song called shit on her new album let me play a little bit for you
[SPEAKER_10]: Now that isn't weird at all!
[SPEAKER_13]: Except, like... Wait, wait, wait, keep playing that for a second there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry, it just sounded like a different song for a second.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did they... It sounded like another...
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki made me play Gaga, you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: He made me.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Whoever did this thing should have used the Ashet instead of the B. Yeah, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_03]: If that picture right there doesn't make her look like a Satan blow-up doll, I don't know what to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, she was on American Idol the other week as a mentor, which is just like, okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: You mad?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm not mad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just rolled my eyes.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's like, okay, oh, it's my time on camera?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to say something crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's like, okay, that wasn't really helpful at all, but thanks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what the hell she was wearing, but it was something retarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to stand for such gaga-hating on this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's a genius.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's a saint.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please.
[SPEAKER_04]: A genius?
[SPEAKER_04]: She's a genius.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, we're talking about her on a fucking video game podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: You bought all this crap hook, line, and sink.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, as an almost genius, I take offense to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I fucking knew this was going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a fucking mistake.
[SPEAKER_04]: Revoke his Mensa membership immediately.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, seriously, she's not a fucking genius.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's good at marketing, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: There are people that are in the magazine business that are good at marketing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Steve Jobs is good at marketing, but he's not fucking... Well, okay, he is fucking crazy, but he's not fucking... overtly fucking crazy, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: She's a fad.
[SPEAKER_03]: She'll go away.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's what's gonna happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Madonna never went away, neither will she.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, Madonna never went away.
[SPEAKER_13]: She showed everyone what the character looks like.
[SPEAKER_03]: She went away, same with Cher.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cher, they're both gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cher turned 65 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cher's eligible for Medicare.
[SPEAKER_04]: Feeling old?
[SPEAKER_03]: She'll go away.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even care.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100 Matt in chat says, fact, there will be a Gaga video game sometime in her lifetime.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I hope so.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, I hope so.
[SPEAKER_03]: There already is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is Gaga-ville, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we've all seen her cooch.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like... Is she wearing it on her face?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I swear to God, you know, sometimes I wonder that she's just relocated her vagina to her face.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it would not surprise me.
[SPEAKER_04]: How did we get from the fucking Oregon Trail to Lady Gaga's vagina on her face?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zynga.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: I bet you anything that's going to be the next album cover is her with a...
[SPEAKER_03]: VJ Face It will be her coming out of her own vagina That'll be the Elmar right there She'll be coming out of her own vagina She's like, I'll be born!
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, you need to see last night's I swear this will be the end of it, guys You need to see last night's Saturday Night Live performance Because she was on Saturday Night Live And she did Born This Way, her song And what she did during the performance She actually got pregnant And gave birth live on stage To a bunch of glitter During the performance
[SPEAKER_04]: It was an art piece and it was brilliant.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was brilliant.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was moved.
[SPEAKER_13]: By the way, this is the last of the Gaga for me.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what she did to everybody who was camping out in line?
[SPEAKER_13]: She bought them dinner and donuts and coffee and signed autographs and took pictures with people waiting in line.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because she's a nice person.
[SPEAKER_04]: She genuinely likes her fans.
[SPEAKER_03]: She genuinely likes her fans.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: That still doesn't make you a fucking whore.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you call what she did on stage art, then I'm sorry, a peep show is fucking art then.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's more peep shows out there than there are gaga, so I guess we have that to be thankful.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't hate on peep shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's one thing you'll never hear me ranting about on this program, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would never touch your sacred pornography collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would never.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is nothing sacred about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we get back to video games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is very important.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to go from Lady Gaga talking about very important video game news such as this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cat Food Maker Friskies has released iPad and Android games for your cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is why Gaga's podcast has to end.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we have to talk about tasty treasures, party mix-up, and catfishing.
[SPEAKER_04]: iPad games for your cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: In iPad, pussy play with you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, you know, I watched the little video and it is super adorable.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would get this for Shermie if I had an iPad and she didn't have paws.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, this looks so cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your little pet can touch the food and it splits up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Catfishing Catfishing
[SPEAKER_04]: Now Salacious Pop, my significant other in chatroom says, I am not buying Maruko, our cat, an iPad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to that I'm saying, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not buying Maruko an iPad.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're buying me an iPad and maybe I'll let your cat play with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: My birthday is June 26th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's so cute.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm getting you a Takei mug.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, but in all seriousness, there's a lot to laugh at here when you're talking about kitties playing games on the iPad, but at the same time, it's oddly fucking fascinating that we are now to the point where we're making video games for the cats.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're free, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I would hope so because they're kind of commercial games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: The games do keep score and your cats can compete to see who has the best reaction time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Your cat don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: My cat gives a shit all over the floor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I'm not sure if they're free or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't see.
[SPEAKER_13]: They can't be more than a dollar.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure they're not more than a dollar.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're probably free.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because given the simplicity of the games, they're probably free.
[SPEAKER_13]: See, look, Shermie is not sleeping anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: She's looking up and listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shermie's like, fuck yeah, mommy, I want that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, mommy wants an iPad, baby, so you have to wait.
[SPEAKER_13]: Tell daddy that mommy wants an iPad.
[SPEAKER_04]: She only wants an iPad so she can shit on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what your cat will do.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your cat will be like, what's this game?
[SPEAKER_13]: Shermie, do you just want to shit on everything?
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw How long till they make games for dogs or ferrets?
[SPEAKER_13]: Byron D. Zero said something even funnier.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Rorschach and Deadpool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because they played the same music that they played in part of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Salacious Pop in our chat room says, This is a game for people who make their cats real Facebook pages and then comment with meow meow on their IRL profile with coworkers and shit on them.
[SPEAKER_13]: Those are the people that creep me the crap out on Facebook when they do that for their pets and their babies.
[SPEAKER_13]: Your baby can't speak.
[SPEAKER_13]: And if your baby can speak, it's not anything intelligible by most people.
[SPEAKER_13]: Your baby doesn't need a Facebook.
[SPEAKER_13]: Your cat doesn't need a Facebook.
[SPEAKER_13]: Your dog doesn't need a Facebook.
[SPEAKER_13]: Your children, probably, even if they're up to seven years old, don't need a Facebook.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe the baby hit random buttons and autocorrected everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I'm actually still on the German alphabet website.
[SPEAKER_13]: Portal!
[SPEAKER_13]: Portal 2, Offended People.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you know who the people had offended?
[SPEAKER_13]: The Adopted.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because of all the cracks that GLaDOS makes in the game about the character being adopted.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, of course, I like it in the end when Wheatley's doing, goes, Fatty!
[SPEAKER_13]: Adopted Fatty!
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like, you are adopted and that's terrible.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, basically this dude named Neil Staple was playing Portal 2, and he's the adopted father to Zoe, a Chinese orphan, and got pissed off when GLaDOS was going off on Chell for being adopted.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course, also overweight people and idiots are offended too, because they also talk about all that.
[SPEAKER_13]: And probably trash is insulted, and probably turrets.
[SPEAKER_13]: So yeah, it's the adopter who is insulted, not the adoptee.
[SPEAKER_13]: Again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh wait, do we have local news story on this that we can play?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, I love these.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love when local news media like completely misrepresents video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is going to be amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I'm going to play this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: And if we're lucky, maybe somehow Loki can turn this into Lady Gaga chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: And tonight, a father is shocked at the insensitivity he says he witnessed.
[SPEAKER_00]: Here's the clip.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's wrong with being adopted?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well,
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, the quality of this is rather shit, and it's really quiet, so I don't know if I should really play the whole thing, because it's not really coming through.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe I won't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let me see if I can crank it up some other way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on one sec, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Live radio is tons of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I have wave up as high as it'll go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't get that any louder.
[SPEAKER_04]: What a shit little...
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll play some of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's too quiet.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can't hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me go to YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: See if I can find it real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: WBTV Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Find Portal 2 being adopted.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I'm going to see if this works better.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have discovered a popular video game making fun of adoption.
[SPEAKER_00]: And tonight, a father is shocked at the insensitivity he says he witnessed.
[SPEAKER_00]: Here's the clip.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's wrong with being adopted?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, well, um, lack of parents.
[SPEAKER_00]: The game is called Portal 2, and it's only been available for about a month.
[SPEAKER_00]: Regina Mack just talked to the father who shared this, who saw this with his daughter.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I bet he was shocked and really surprised by something like this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, no idea, particularly because this is a game that builds itself as educational.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's rated E for everyone.
[SPEAKER_10]: As we said, Neil Staple was playing the game with his 10-year-old adopted daughter when they saw the clip tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: He says he and his wife are still searching for a way to try to explain it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't know what to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still don't know what to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Neil Staples still can't believe what he heard while playing the video game Portal 2 with his 10-year-old adopted daughter Zoe.
[SPEAKER_04]: They really do make this look pretty terrible, I gotta admit.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, like, I feel like this is, like, really taken out of context.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's, like...
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to remember, they're taunting everything about her.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, no matter what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to be honest, I don't think they ever really proved that she's adopted.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I just kind of feel like this is really selective hearing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my biggest issue of what's going on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I watch this news report and I go, wow, this game's fucking rude.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I've played through the game and I didn't get that impression at all.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's E10+.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not a baseline E for everyone.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, in other words, the 10-year-old daughter, since she's not 10+, she's 10, probably shouldn't have been watching.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's 10 and over.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not over 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: God damn you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: You always gotta fucking disagree with me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you hear that?
[SPEAKER_10]: The character in the popular kids video game is actually taunted for being adopted.
[SPEAKER_09]: It literally pokes fun...
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, and you literally proved that you're an idiot.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's Chinese.
[SPEAKER_09]: She obviously doesn't look like us.
[SPEAKER_09]: It throws the question, the most ultimate question that that child is ever going to have for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it just throws her right in the living room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is he going to cry?
[SPEAKER_03]: I really needed attention.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why I contacted the news, because I needed attention, because I'm an idiot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_10]: But he'd heard.
[SPEAKER_10]: Neil immediately cut the game off, hoping Zoe hadn't heard the cruel joke from a video game billed as educational and appropriate for everyone 10 and up.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it says rated E for everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I was thinking maybe it's rated E for everybody except for orphans.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're not an adoptive parent, it's probably not that big a deal to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you are an adoptive parent, it was literally the worst thing I could possibly have heard.
[SPEAKER_07]: But did Zoe hear it?
[SPEAKER_07]: She's sticking to her guns that she didn't hear it and to me that message means she's not ready to talk about it and I'm not going to force it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_10]: Eyes rolling too much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Neil says they steer clear of that part of the game and hope their daughter never feels like she's any less because she's adopted.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't imagine my life without her.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, she's just such an awesome child.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's just made our lives so much better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now again, we did say this game was edgy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Surely there'll be a counterpoint to this, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, surely they tried to reach out to Valve for comment, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's because you have to sort of figure out a way to get out of every single room.
[SPEAKER_10]: We did contact Sony, who distributes the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: They told us to contact Valve, the company that actually created the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have not heard back from them.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're passing the buck onto somebody else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, oh!
[SPEAKER_03]: Bitch!
[SPEAKER_10]: That is so not the way it works.
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, Sony doesn't distribute the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's EA that distributes the game, idiot.
[SPEAKER_13]: God, you're fucking... Send me the link to that place because I'm going to type one hell of a rebuttal.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Since they didn't respond back to our claim, they're wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Having interned in local news as long as I did, I mean, I know this means a lot, but by trying to contact them, they probably gave a couple hours tops.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I watched that piece and I agree, Portal looks pretty fucked up.
[SPEAKER_13]: The website is WBTV.com Email them all.
[SPEAKER_13]: Email them, please.
[SPEAKER_13]: Email them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think honestly the part that they kind of leave out that kind of irritates me is that if you're going to play that game with your kid you kind of have to be able to explain it all to them and you have to explain that these characters will mock anything to try that's what GLaDOS does she mocks everything what's next is somebody going to be upset because the game called them fat
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it's just a little silly
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I actually am going to email them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that was my story, so... Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I'm not complaining about that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ubisoft, you know, they're looking at maybe taking the next step with some of their franchises.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead of leaving it in the hands of people that may not be able to do their franchises well in the motion picture world, they're going to go ahead and form...
[SPEAKER_03]: Ubisoft Motion Pictures They're going to adapt some of their biggest properties Assassin's Creed, Splinter Cell, and Ghost Recon into 3D features
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm very disappointed though that Rabbids were not part of that Because honestly I think that would work much better as a 3D animated feature than some of this stuff But whatever They said in addition to the trio of feature projects, the studio is reportedly developing 3D CGI animated series Oh, they are!
[SPEAKER_03]: Based on the Rabbids properties, awesome!
[SPEAKER_03]: So they comprise of 78 episodes, 7 minutes a piece.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's almost like they're little trailers that they have.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: But seriously though, they should get their own full length theater or theatrical movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Couldn't be any worse than some of the other stuff I've seen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, two other quick E3-related stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, Konami.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think this was brought up earlier in the show, but let's just throw it out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are going to be doing their E3 press conference a little bit early this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to be doing their press conference, I believe it is the Sunday beforehand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is on...
[SPEAKER_04]: Pre-E3 show 2011, and it is happening... Is there really a press release that doesn't have the fucking time of the event in here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Konami today announced the venue picks for the company's first annual global pre-E3 show 2011.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: at the times listed below.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so they're going to be doing their press conference on the Thursday beforehand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give bloggers and people a chance to talk about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can attend live if you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to actually be renting places in Los Angeles, San Francisco, Toronto, Sao Paulo, Mexico City.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're getting international with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: See now, my only thing about this though is they said it's like live viewing parties.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now are they just watching the press conference or are they actually going to be able to play games there and stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: They aren't really saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes it sound like they're just going to be able to watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like you'll just get to be able to watch this.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can register online for a chance to attend.
[SPEAKER_04]: The place here in San Francisco they're going to be doing at is Temple Nightclub.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not familiar with that place, but I imagine it's at 4 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of early.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they probably have to pick a time like that because 4 o'clock would be 7 o'clock on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what time would that be in Japan?
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be 8 a.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: the next day, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe that's why they're doing it at that time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, they're doing a pre-E3 show 2011 and talking about these venues they picked.
[SPEAKER_04]: So facebook.com slash Konami if you want to go to the viewing event or you can just watch it online.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it is a little weird, because G4, don't they have the exclusive E3 pass or whatever?
[SPEAKER_03]: Usually they do for, I know they've done Microsoft's conference in the past.
[SPEAKER_04]: Technically, though, the press conferences aren't a part of E3, so that's why Spike probably paid money for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, everybody's going to be able to watch that live, as long as you have basic cable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, I'm sure it'll be streamed over Justin TV everywhere, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, with that, let's go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week you guys send us emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com is the place to send your emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: And DarkSakura is going to dive in the mailbag headfirst and find some emails to read for us today.
[SPEAKER_13]: First email.
[SPEAKER_13]: Greetings, OLR.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's your friendly neighborhood turtle.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have no game-related comments or questions this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just wanted to send hearts your way and say that OLR is the best and only gaming podcast that I currently listen to.
[SPEAKER_13]: And whoever is responsible for putting the podcast up on the internet says doing an awesome job.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: I literally don't allow myself to do anything else Sunday nights until the show is posted.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus, the other thing that made it a lot easier, I changed the way I write descriptions, so I don't actually have to think of a sassy commentary on what happened during the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just basically post the first five stories from the show roll, and then that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's reading the descriptions?
[SPEAKER_04]: Our subscribers?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think they really read the description.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could be wrong, but in the interest of getting it up faster, I just...
[SPEAKER_04]: and we don't edit the show either I mean I have to edit it to take out the middle part where we play copyright music and just clean up the beginning and end but as for like the actual content in the middle it's live radio we don't really edit like something has to go really really wrong or somebody has to say something really really bad for us to edit and I don't remember I haven't edited any content out in easily a year at least so
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I guess this doesn't really apply to you anymore, Rob, since I know you've got the trial.
[SPEAKER_13]: But Holly D sent an invite and said any of us can use it to play Rift.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, she's been pimping out on Horde House on the forums over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's desperate to get her Corgi and the other little rewards that she can get, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, it's there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe I'll look at it, but I really can't.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have no time.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you liking Rift?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to plead the fifth until later.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can say without a doubt, though, that it is better than Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was still writing my angry email to WBTV.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, we have another one from Holly.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's, but you gotta admit, there's a ton of people doing it out of being purely fickle.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's a lot of people, there's just, that's how people are.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can understand it.
[SPEAKER_13]: For every, you know, one person who's got true, authentic integrity and turning it in, there's gonna be 25 other that are gonna just be, I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, okay, to continue.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I say this real quick though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's where the line is between fickle and yeah, I meant it.
[SPEAKER_04]: When a game like The Last Guardian comes out, are you going to rebuy a PS3 if you sold yours back?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you mean it and you stick to your guns, then you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: You have every right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's your money.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should spend it on what you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: To continue?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: I stopped playing WoW because of something Blizzard did that I find unacceptable.
[SPEAKER_13]: It doesn't matter that I like the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not going to put money into a company that treats its customers badly and I really feel this is why people are abandoning ship on Sony.
[SPEAKER_13]: Holly D. Like I said, I think that for every one person that's got a legitimate reason with actual integrity behind it, the rest of them are sheeping.
[SPEAKER_04]: you know and I would fully admit there's been times I really would want to leave Blizzard but I kind of feel like I'd be being one of those fickle people like I just go right back six months later when that patch comes out that I really want to play so I don't know it's tough when you stick to your guns that's pretty admirable
[SPEAKER_04]: Outro Music
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, and no, I'm not, don't hear me wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not knocking vegans, but there are some people who like do it for a couple weeks and they're like, this is too hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got to go back to eating chicken, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I personally, I've tried to go vegetarian.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't even go vegetarian.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's too hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't get enough protein.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know how to get protein, I just still wasn't getting enough of it Anyway, I don't know when I just started comparing Blizzard to being a vegetarian, but okay Next email Hello guys, first of all, congratulations on your awesome show I listen to it at work and it makes my hours go by faster I would like your opinion on these two topics One, games with poor or no control configuration options Yeah, that sucks
[SPEAKER_13]: and games that don't allow you to pause the cutscenes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you and good luck with your show.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's from... I'll just say... Cadius.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish the emailer had given us some specific examples of games like I know there are games like that that don't have the custom and I know I've gone on this tangent on the show before like games that have the really whack controls that you just can't recustomize and yet now I'm drawing a total blank like I can't remember any of them I'm sure a chat room will help us out here this is why I love having a live chat
[SPEAKER_04]: And then cutscenes, yeah, that's kind of annoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or unskippable ones, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Mortal Kombat, story mode, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can pause cutscenes, but you can't skip them.
[SPEAKER_04]: unless it's your second time playing through which I think is really weird because what I don't like is that in Mortal Kombat if you are stuck on a certain part you have to keep watching the cutscene leading up to it over and over until you beat it if you turn off the game because if you just hit retry you don't have to watch the whole thing over and over but like sometimes I get so frustrated I need to walk away for a little bit and then come back and the last thing I want to do when I come back is watch the cutscene again so yeah
[SPEAKER_13]: By the way, Xenocore says no vegan diet, no vegan powers.
[SPEAKER_13]: I loved that whole scene.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's from Scott Pilgrim, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see what you did there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Moving forward.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, OLA crew.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is...
[SPEAKER_13]: and Ramadija, I guess that's how I hope I pronounce it right, a blind gamer from Indonesia.
[SPEAKER_13]: I sent you some emails a long time ago and this email will absolutely be the sign that I'm still following you until now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Great show as always.
[SPEAKER_13]: Although I cannot contribute my thoughts like the other listeners because I cannot play games like others do, I hope I can still be part of OLR's discussion with my personal thought about video games.
[SPEAKER_13]: I consider myself as one of the veteran gamers because when I was a child, video games were so easy to be played even without my sight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, can I interrupt for real quick?
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the name of the emailer again?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ramadija?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that the same person that sent the Scars of Time flute thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, okay, like, don't invalidate your opinion just because you have, like, a challenge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, in watching what you did with the Scars of Time thing, clearly you have a love and passion for video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that makes you just as much of a gamer as anybody else with just as much a right to your opinion as anyone else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just throwing that out there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_13]: so I would like to share the enjoyment I've gotten several months ago it was when I found the Angry Video Game Nerd I love Angry Video Game Nerd and imported the DVDs from the author I don't know if any one of you ever heard about AVGN it's a series of classic video games featuring James as a nerd that plays old video games actually he reviewed Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles the DVD sets recently and it was hilarious but my favorite that he does is the Friday the 13th review so funny anyway
[SPEAKER_13]: He reviews the negative sides of games with badass style.
[SPEAKER_13]: You'll see and hear a lot of fucks and shits in there, beer included.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just Google it or go to Wikipedia for more information.
[SPEAKER_13]: He linked a video.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to share it because this show is very enjoyable for me even without my ability to see what's happening on screen I don't know what will happen to me if I am not blind and able to watch those
[SPEAKER_13]: I believe you all can find some amusement there too now on to me like I said that I am blind so I cannot play video games the same like others but I do enjoy online games text based and right now I'm playing Blade of Eternity and the link is bladeofeternity.com and reach level 148 besides I do enjoy video game music and I love playing some of them using my flute just go to my YouTube channel it is the same guy yeah
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to spell it out.
[SPEAKER_13]: R-A-M-A-D-I-T-Y-A Skywalker and watch.
[SPEAKER_13]: My favorite is when I played Scars of Time from Chrono Cross.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, that's all from me.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hope this email can be read and I will get more friends to talk about video games.
[SPEAKER_13]: I only have a few local friends that understand English and stuff I like anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cheers from, and I hope I'm pronouncing it right, Ramaditya.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think that's Ramaditya.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's how I said it too, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's very sweet.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love the Angry Video Game Nerds corruption.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hater.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a whole nother layer, but I'm not going to get into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it actually has nothing to do with that show specifically.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know that makes no sense at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just, I'll tell you another day.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, all.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, it's another one from Holly.
[SPEAKER_13]: No offense, Holly, you email us a lot.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, all.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't panic too much, but SE just got hacked too.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was ready to flip out having played Final Fantasy XI, but it turns out that they only got email addresses unless you're a Canadian.
[SPEAKER_13]: They got resumes for 350 Canadian potential employees too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you, Holly.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then the last one.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, I did hear about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, somebody needs to catch these hackers.
[SPEAKER_04]: At some point, these hackers are going to get too bold.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let me warn you, because this might not be the same person that's doing the Sony stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: How much bolder can you get?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I know, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: But the problem is, one of these days, hacker, you're going to get sloppy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it doesn't matter which video game website you get caught hacking, you're going to get blamed for the Sony thing by the mass media.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you don't believe me, go watch, go re-watch that zany local news report about Portal 2 to watch the way that the media will construe things to get a story.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can say whatever they want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if you had nothing to do with the Sony hack, if you get caught hacking Square Enix's website, you'll be the Sony hacker.
[SPEAKER_04]: Watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand hackers gonna hack.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've always said on the show, I'm not trying to infringe on your freedom to hack.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Watch it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I shouldn't say your freedom to hack because whoever hacked the Sony website did a fucked up thing and that's not acceptable.
[SPEAKER_13]: You just totally made me think of Life of Brian.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like, well, you can't physically have babies, but we'll protect your right to have them.
[SPEAKER_13]: Eric Idle's character.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like, so we'll protect your right to hack.
[SPEAKER_13]: You just can't hack.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: Last one.
[SPEAKER_13]: There is still no taco delivery service on the PSN now that it is partially... Now that it is partially... It has a sad... Clearly this is an email written in all caps.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's from all caps Bobby.
[SPEAKER_13]: All caps Bobby has a sad frown.
[SPEAKER_13]: The end.
[SPEAKER_13]: I saved it for last.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it for emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com if you want to email us.
[SPEAKER_04]: But try to not use all caps.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like it when Jamie reads all caps emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, how about you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, apparently the Fox Entertainment Group has an FCC filing that points to possibly a new video service coming to consoles.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're saying that Fox Entertainment Group and its multi-channel video programming distribution partners have shown intent that they're planning on broadening their platforms that they offer content on.
[SPEAKER_03]: and that it will see subscription and on-demand video services available directly to wide-marketed consumer electronics devices such as game consoles sometime in the near future.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, maybe something that will be announced later on, maybe something that's, you know, time of, like, a capable provider or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't we have enough video services on consoles at this point, though?
[SPEAKER_03]: We do.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Between Netflix and Hulu.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although Hulu Plus kind of sucks because of their ads.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know I'm not a fan of ads and paying for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one or the other, not both.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, one other story for you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we're going to get into the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoopee!
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I lie.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to get into the FUs of the week and then the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, let me read this quick story about Kid Icarus Uprising, which of course is the 3DS Kid Icarus game that's coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Some other stuff that's coming out of this though is that Nintendo is going to be using fan Miis on a float that will show up at the Goshogawara Tachi Neputa Festival that happens in August.
[SPEAKER_04]: Miis will be joining Pit and Patena and there's a whole page in Japanese on how you can create a Mii on your 3DS, save it and send it into Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: So yay, me's on parade!
[SPEAKER_04]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get into the FUs of the week before I forget.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week on this show we do a little bit of ranting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck you to WBTV.
[SPEAKER_13]: Logi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck you to my new portable hard drive that's USB powered for deleting said data on portable hard drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: One I didn't want to.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, why is this not working?
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I looked on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it's empty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, it's never doing that to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I think I blame partly my 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had to create a 360 data partition in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not really a data partition, but usually they'll do it without erasing any data.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it decided.
[SPEAKER_13]: But you used mine and mine was fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but my 360 was being retarded and didn't want to see the drive until I did that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now it finally sees the drive.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, too bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU of the week goes to Loki because he doesn't like Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's brilliant.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's a hater.
[SPEAKER_04]: If that's my FU of the week, then that means things are going pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about FU to Headaches?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I had a bad one yesterday and I kind of was antisocial at a party because of it and that's never any fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like being antisocial.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then FU to Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's get to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Every week we give you guys a chance to call in and share your voices.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes it's the same people that call every week, and that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's open for all right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm actually really proud of this line, and I would like to read it from my email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, go ahead, because the phone's not ringing yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's item number five.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you want to hear my email so far?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, sure, what the hell.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm cutting you off as soon as the call comes in.
[SPEAKER_13]: To whom it may concern, first and foremost, I am an adult, a fan of video games, and female.
[SPEAKER_13]: I am friends with several adopted friends who were shocked you gave attention to the single person Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I need to rephrase that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Basically, I've got friends that are adopted that play Portal.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't care.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I said my friends play Portal too with me and think adoption jokes are just as funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm cutting you off because you're getting a phone call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the phones at 1-877-GAVE-OLR Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, this is X-Link.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, X-Link, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, doing good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to call in and chime in for a minute about Blizzard and their customer service.
[SPEAKER_01]: Somebody said they didn't like the way they were doing it, but actually, every time when I have talked to somebody through the customer service through very few problems I had, of course, playing WoW and whatnot, I had really good service, including an item that I ordered from their store.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do tell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Share a little more about your positive experience.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we often have a lot of negativity.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's hear something good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I'll talk about the store.
[SPEAKER_01]: Somehow with my PayPal account, instead of putting the right address, which was on there, they somehow got my old address.
[SPEAKER_01]: This was before I moved.
[SPEAKER_01]: And before I got changed, I didn't realize it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I realized it the night after the order was placed.
[SPEAKER_01]: I called in but unfortunately the package had already shipped so they had to wait for it to try to be delivered and then they can cancel so they whoever was at the door thank god there was nobody there living there in my old apartment at the time so it got sent back to them but they were they not only replaced the old package with a new one but they also refunded the money to my account which I thought was a little odd but hey it was you know so I technically got the item for free but
[SPEAKER_01]: The guy who walked me through and tried to help me as much as he could, not only did he do it through the phone in a very positive and nice fashion, but also kept up with quarterly, like almost every few hours by email, which was very nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I mean, he did flood the mailbox like every three to four hours.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like one email in the morning, one email in the evening saying, here's what we got.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here's what we're going to do.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here's what the game is.
[SPEAKER_04]: So constant communication.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not okay for the two lines to be crossed.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, I trained for nine years in customer service.
[SPEAKER_04]: I trained for a large, large call center here in the area on customer service.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'll tell you, one of the things that we were really big on was making sure that information was always communicated to the customer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Communication is so key, I think, because people don't call into places or email or whatever to hear, I don't know, or there's nothing we can do about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They want it resolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why you pick up the phone and call somebody in the first place.
[SPEAKER_01]: and it was it was really cool because he's like yes sir no sir and he had a very positive attitude it's like it's like almost that he was like talking to my talk to like a best friend or a good friend about something he's like yeah you know hey it happens you know no problem let me look into it uh hey what's the got place to unfold um i promise i'll be right back and if i don't i got your information right here i'll call you right back and we'll walk we'll try to see what we can do
[SPEAKER_01]: and it was very nice and a lot of companies most times when you call it's kind of like I don't care I'm just going to do it's more robotic and you know it's like why did I do this in the first place when I'm just going to do this through email and just probably get the same response so
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, look, I don't know what Holly's thing is with Blizzard right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know specifically.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I might, but I wouldn't try to tell it on the show for somebody else anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I can tell you where I come from.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, we play WoW together.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know I love WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't have a fucking podcast about WoW if I didn't love World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: But sometimes I get a little negative on Horde House because Blizzard just makes these decisions as a corporation that you just look at it and your jaw is just dropped.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, what the fuck are you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me give you an analogy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, like let's assume you've got a friend and like, you know, this is your bro.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's your guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's one of your best friends, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: And suddenly this guy starts dating this girl and you just don't like her because she's drama and she just
[SPEAKER_04]: ActaVision
[SPEAKER_01]: There's been times when I've seen some of the stuff they're supposedly going to do inside the game, and I'm looking at the stuff and announcements, I'm like, what the fuck are they doing with this shit?
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously, are they going to actually make us pay for all this stuff that should be free in the first place?
[SPEAKER_01]: And I love listening to other people's, also other people's podcasts, of course, I listen to yours too, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: but it's kind of funny hearing that people come up like you would say something and you'd be like okay I can't believe Blizzard's doing this what the fuck and then somebody else on the same line going you know what I think Blizzard's going overboard with this and this is stupid and I can't believe they're actually doing this because they're trying to get more money into the pot so to speak so I think they could do a lot of this stuff or you know everything doesn't have to be quote unquote a premium fee I think that's taking a little overboard
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what's funny is that, yet again, we have a case of the worker bee is doing a great job.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the worker bee, in this case, being the customer service reps you interact with.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're representing their company very well.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem, when we talk about issues we have with Blizzard, it is not with the worker bees.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's with the queen bee.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's with the people up top that are making the decisions.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're just... Don't hit your head.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Face palm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give me that picture of Captain Jean-Luc Picard face palming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's...
[SPEAKER_04]: God, half the stories I read on Horde House need that caption.
[SPEAKER_01]: Any MMO Any MMO goes through this
[SPEAKER_04]: and WoW just happens to be a big one but any MMO goes through this love-hate relationship with their fanbase, my god, look at Final Fantasy XIV right now, hello like the same problem
[SPEAKER_04]: What, Rob?
[SPEAKER_01]: Final what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, I got to wrap up so we can get more calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: But thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anything really quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, anything else real quick you want to get out?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing else.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, then bye.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to read you the line that I'm proud of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, go for it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did I hang up?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I hung up.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hang up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did I hang up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: The character in the game is, as admitted by one of the other antagonists, a moron.
[SPEAKER_13]: The same antagonist is a passive-aggressive homicidal computer that takes steps to discourage the character being played, not the player.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's also insults slung out towards overweight people and those of lower than average intelligence.
[SPEAKER_13]: Should they also rise up in protest?
[SPEAKER_13]: Should the fatties and morons also call your station and expect the same coverage as the adoptive parents?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, that's a very good point that the story overlooks, is that the character is supposed to be a moron.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is not somebody you're supposed to model yourself after.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is an idiot bully.
[SPEAKER_13]: As it said in the game, designed by the greatest minds of their generation to create the dumbest moron who ever lived.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that perspective.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: And maybe I'll try to hang up on you and not succeed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would ask if there's any last minute stories, but Loki left the room real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think he's chatting with Dan about something real quick.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is he chatting up my men?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're doing gaming something in the living room.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't do anything kinky in there!
[SPEAKER_04]: Without taking pictures.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's only porn if you tape it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, Loki's coming back.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_13]: He's chatting up my husband.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, real quick, there's some leaked video that kind of shows off some of the new features for FIFA 12.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're kind of making it more realistic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now they have... Apparently, you can do some... They have unexpected behaviors that will happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, for example...
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, a defender coming in, offensive player making a move that flips the player.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, apparently you can get injuries and realistic injuries.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to have better dribbling and basically kind of a whole new engine that they're putting in place here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me get to the phone because we've got another call coming in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Laundry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yo guys, it's Unicorn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Long time no see.
[SPEAKER_08]: How y'all doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it has been a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you doing, buddy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just trying to make that paper, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Make it rain.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, what's up?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not much, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just blowing some time trying to get through L.A.
[SPEAKER_08]: Noire without cursing my head off and waking up the entire neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_13]: Tell us a little bit about L.A.
[SPEAKER_13]: Noire.
[SPEAKER_13]: I actually have a question real quick.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is time enjoying being blown?
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're a dirty girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's off the hook tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talking about L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire a little bit because it's not a game I've played yet because I didn't think it would be something I was interested in because I'm not super into the whole Grand Theft Auto thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's cool and all, but I'm just not very good at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But in listening to Bobby's show before us tonight, he doesn't really play these types of games either, but his callers are like, no, dude, this is like a throwback to an adventure game.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think of L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, so you guys actually haven't covered it on your show yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought I was chasing behind all my shows I'm trying to get in touch with.
[SPEAKER_13]: Can I ask you a question?
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you find the period specificness of the game a little bit bothersome?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, actually I enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I didn't know what Dan was playing at the time, and then I was hearing the guy make in the comments about Jews, and I was like, what the hell are you playing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, that first game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't even think of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's quite livid, he is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you should call the local news media and tell them how offended you were.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't give a shit, because it's a period-specific game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just didn't know what he was playing at the time, so I was like, what the hell are you listening to?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that guy is a racist, so of course he's going to curse it up a bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, anyway, so let me get back to the game a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I can't say we haven't covered L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we've talked about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just none of us have yet to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we can't tell you how it is as a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm relying on you, my friend.
[SPEAKER_04]: How is L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire as a game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us a little bit about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let me set it up so I can describe it and be as rhetorical as possible, but you get all the information in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: It plays like Grand Theft Auto, but it doesn't play like Grand Theft Auto in the fact that you are a police officer and you're not supposed to run amok, which is the whole game.
[SPEAKER_08]: The focus is on police investigation.
[SPEAKER_08]: and the process of police investigation.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the highlighting of the facial animations and using that to be able to tell if people are lying or not is the main focus of the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's CSI 1940s, basically.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds like Law and Order in 1940s.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's exactly what that is.
[SPEAKER_04]: All it needs is dong dong.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, this game, if you're not going to cheat your way through it and use the online stuff, it truly is a mental game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to think your way through it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you can still get through the game and still fail left and right, but you will get a completely different experience because you didn't really...
[SPEAKER_08]: if you investigate a person and you're able to draw information out of them you have more things to use and search for later on in the case until you come to the end of it so am I hearing you right that you can't really lose this game it's just that there will be hallways you never go down if you don't do it well correct interesting yeah so the replay is in trying to do the cases better
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm having a ball.
[SPEAKER_08]: I even slip into jargon every once in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's the way we are in the house here, role players.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've got to flex their role play muscles.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the life of a pig, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've just got to deal with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game was on my radar, certainly, because everybody's been talking about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I was like, oh, it's a rock star game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't usually feel those so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure they're great games, but I'll never probably get into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: So like all the billboards are where they're supposed to be and all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say, I'll get the anagram in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says, this sounds like Ace Attorney.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it like a Phoenix Wright type thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's actually closer to that than anything else.
[SPEAKER_08]: You do have to drive from point to point.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they add the Grand Theft Auto things by responding to calls.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'll hear a call for officer needs support, this and that.
[SPEAKER_08]: You roll up on a bank robbery or somebody's trying to rob a convenience store.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, Officers and Chase, you gotta cut them off.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that's all in there, as well as your standard stuff of driving your car.
[SPEAKER_08]: But...
[SPEAKER_08]: The focus is on the investigation itself.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, for instance, for example, one of the cases involves a woman and her niece getting put in a car while they're drugged and the car goes over a cliff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they survive it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you do your interviews to figure out what's going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: You later on tail her and figure out she's got ties to the mob and she's going after the guy that drugged them and put them in the car.
[SPEAKER_08]: if you don't get to the spot if you get there in time you can catch them in the act of trying to toss the place and arrest them if you don't if you take too long to get there you have to deal with the aftermath and you have to use your CSI skills to figure out what they were looking for
[SPEAKER_08]: so yeah it's the way they put the gameplay in there plus later on the order that you investigate the locations determines who's available when so if you go to like for instance there's this grocery you have to investigate but for some reason they're closed until like 2-3 o'clock in the afternoon so if you go there too early you'll miss your chance to do something else like catch this one guy while he's in the bar you have to go hunt him down later yeah so the entire case is interwoven like that like a big twist-a-plot but
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me ask you another question real quick before we let you go because I want to make sure we can free up for more calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I've heard a lot about how this game really seems to be pushing that line between game and movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I've heard about some cases where it's actually being considered art.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think somebody, I don't know, some gallery or something was actually kind of putting this game on display or what have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think about this game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this game really pushing the envelope between what is a movie, television, visual art, and a video game, which not everyone considers art if you're Roger Ebert?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, let me say it like this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was watching, you guys familiar with Red Letter Media?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, Red Letter Media is the guys that went behind Mr. Plinkett and ripping apart the Star Wars trilogy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Their movies, their reviews are extremely in-depth.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they started up a show, and they mentioned the fact that movies have become the lowest form of entertainment.
[SPEAKER_08]: as far as outlook and what you expect from them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some people aren't willing to throw $10 at a bad movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the way movies have been going now, maybe they're not making as much money as they could be if they're spending more time writing scripts and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are doing that in gaming.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that has stepped up as far as the public eye is looking for entertainment.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is just going to add fuel to that fire.
[SPEAKER_08]: The fact that the...
[SPEAKER_08]: Facial expressions add so much to the way you're trying to... I mean, literally, I was second guessing almost every decision I was making on whether these people were lying or not based off what I knew about the case.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it was driving me nuts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the way they added, there's a small audio cue that lets you know whether or not you picked if they're telling the truth, if you doubt their answer, or if they're flat out lying.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have a little three-note piano thing that lets you know when you pick correctly, incorrectly, the instant you push the button.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it just adds to that suspense when you're waiting to hear that tone.
[SPEAKER_08]: And when you miss it up, you just want to go rage comic all over the thing, but it's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love every minute of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well you guys have sold me that I need to check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if I'll drop $60 for it, but I'm certainly going to rent it and check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, definitely worth the rental.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Xenocore, I've got to let you go so we can wrap up the show, but take care and thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ain't no problem, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll take it easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do love hearing from you because we've been talking about great voices tonight, such as the one and only George Takei.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you have a great voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was very well done.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you hear how excited Jamie got?
[SPEAKER_04]: The ladies love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to do it for the Skype calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had a couple long calls there, so we're going to go ahead and close up.
[SPEAKER_04]: But thank you guys so much for calling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to those who didn't get through, but please send us emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: We always appreciate emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's wrap up the last minute stories and then get on out of here for the night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so last story here.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have... Kenji Unifune is actually in the new Japanese RPG Hyperdimension Neptunia MK2.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the sequel to the Hyperdimension Neptunia game that came out, I believe, last year and over here in March.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, he plays...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's going to do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to now go around and get everybody's final thoughts as we wrap up for the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_13]: I want Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pinkberry's closed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the time we're done with the post show.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you going to do with the week off?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to be sad that the season of Supernatural is over for two whole weeks and then go back to the episode where Sam had no shirt and no soul.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is all about just what...
[SPEAKER_04]: Get you going tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't hate, my friend had to wait in line for four hours Not hating, I'm not hating, but you have to bring me back a Duffy
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not bringing you back a Duffy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I'll bring you back a Star Wars preview or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know I'm teasing.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're a good girl.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know I'm teasing.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Loki, your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully I'll play some more games this week other than Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what are you going to do with the week off?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have an invite to go to the new members party for Mensa, but I don't know if I'm going to.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to go to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, I can only imagine the type of people that are there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We want pictures of hot Mensa chicks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, I'm just picturing old... Look at that Mensa booty!
[SPEAKER_03]: I just pictured old people playing cards and boring card games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't want to play Bunko?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not Bunko, they're like playing... Canasta.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cribbage and hearts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan plays Cribbage.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can play Cribbage, I can be a Mensa.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll play Cribbage with Mensa people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I joined up just to get the plaque.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's really what it was all about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now that I have the plaque hanging at my desk at work, the rest is all optional.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's going to do it for another week of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry guys that there won't be a show next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We hope this is enough to hold you over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look forward to this.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's very, very likely going to be multiple shows during E3 week, so look forward to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll have more details on that when we come back in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: As always, thank you for listening to Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are a free show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't charge you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We really don't do commercials outside of the ones for our side shows, which I think is okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: So please help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell a friend.
[SPEAKER_04]: Leave a nice review on iTunes, Five Stars, or whatever podcast website, podcast alley, anywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Until next time, we'll be back in two weeks with another edition of Orange Lingerie.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those of you in America, have a wonderful Memorial Day holiday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Be safe.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those of you going to Fatima or whatever conventions are going on that weekend, don't get too drunk.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for those of you not in America, have a great Sunday night next week without us.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Thanks for watching!