[SPEAKER_22]: SYNCHRONIZES LOVE IS WHAT WE GOT TO DO ALL THE TIME WE'LL BE TOGETHER CAUSE IT'S YOURS AND MINE FOREVER WE'RE IN THIS RUN DAY DON'T YOU TAKE MY HAND I WON'T BE YOUR MAN SO TONIGHT WE'RE GONNA DANCE THE NIGHT AWAY ONE AND ONE IS TWO DON'T YOU FEED YOUR CREW SYNCHRONIZES LOVE IS WHAT WE GOT TO DO ALL THE TIME WE'LL BE TOGETHER
[SPEAKER_22]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_22]: S, Actdeft,
[SPEAKER_17]: Toto, I have a feeling we're not in Kansas anymore.
[SPEAKER_29]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, Ramani Talk, and then some.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, mostly the, and then some, part of that.
[SPEAKER_29]: Orange Lounge Radio is created by a bunch of potty-mouthed adults.
[SPEAKER_29]: Orange Lounge may contain sexual, perverted, and mildly retarded content.
[SPEAKER_29]: You probably shouldn't let your children listen to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, I will spank your child.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you're not going to do your job, goddammit, I will.
Spank your spanker!
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, here's to my big opening.
[SPEAKER_03]: A sphincter says what?
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm super, thanks for asking.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, you little bitch troll from hell.
[SPEAKER_22]: What am I doing here?
[SPEAKER_22]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dodge this.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is a tasty burger.
[SPEAKER_26]: Look, you stupid bastard, you've got no arms left.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yes, I have.
[SPEAKER_26]: Look, just a flesh wound.
[SPEAKER_10]: Searching for a boy in high school is as useless as searching for meaning in a Pauly Shore movie.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yeah?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I hope your babies look like monkeys.
[SPEAKER_27]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got a sniff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Skye.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm playing it for the bartender, so suffer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate you!
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are live, and this is episode number 62 for September the 28th of 2003.
[SPEAKER_07]: And tonight, the cable is working.
[SPEAKER_07]: We promise here on Orange Lounge Radio, we won't scare you with any monsters.
[SPEAKER_07]: What, what?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is episode 62, the most fresh-smelling Orange Lounge Radio ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can opener is in... No, it's in the second drawer down.
[SPEAKER_07]: Second drawer down, not including the cutting board.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: and now in the Orange Lounge kitchen, Iron Chef Sakura and the mystery ingredient today is rice oh shit the mystery food today is eel
[SPEAKER_07]: What is someone cooking Asian food to do with rice?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys want another microphone?
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys can have this one here.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys might want this in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, where was I?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is episode number 62 for September the 28th of 2003.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're tuned into the Bimani Scene's most F-Zero whoring radio station of all things Bimani.
[SPEAKER_07]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_07]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_07]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers, you know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm playing with an eel.
[SPEAKER_07]: In that corner, say hello to our tech massa, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm playing with a solder gun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, he's got a gun!
[SPEAKER_08]: And it can burn things.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also with us tonight, say hello to Puppy!
[SPEAKER_07]: This is my third week in a row, it's a new record!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, it's a new record!
[SPEAKER_07]: Say hello to RKDN42.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good to hear.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also with us tonight for her first real show since last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're just going to write off last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Say hello to ViolentHyperGirl.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_07]: Or as I call her, ViolentHyperGangbang.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we have our whip again tonight because I forgot to take it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you not bring the whip?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's there.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: No one can hear you, puppy.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's only been a week.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, we have a whole shitload of Imani news to talk about this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously, Max 2 came out this week in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did everybody here get the chance to play it?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: No?
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody but Aaron.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aaron will have to live vicariously through our stories.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: You played Max 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have... You got the first four unlocks, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, actually, if I...
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be talking about Max 2 USA tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, we have the Orange Lounge Radio premiere of all the Max 2 USA exclusives.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to be playing those throughout the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we ripped them ourselves, so... They're a little amateurish, but they got the job done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good job!
[SPEAKER_07]: We got those and a whole lot of other stuff to talk about tonight, so we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cage match, possibly a list list if we have time for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All your favorite FUs of the week coming up a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_07]: And...
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie Cooking, for all of you out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: She'll be holding it up to the webcam and you can lick your screen.
[SPEAKER_07]: So to get our webcam address, head on over to our website, www.callybomani.com, click on Orange Lounge, and click on Chat, and then our chat room will be more than happy to give you the link to the webcam, because it's got a really long URL and I don't say it over the air.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, we'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to start off with a little bit of ecstasy, bad routine, and busy child.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_18]: A little better you and me A little better set you free A little better
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll be your dream
[SPEAKER_18]: A little bit of ecstasy
[SPEAKER_01]: Get busy, child.
Get busy, child.
[SPEAKER_21]: Get this inside!
[SPEAKER_21]: Get 50,000 Get 50,000 Get 50,000 Get 50,000 Get 50,000
[SPEAKER_22]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio Because real radio makes Captain Jack cry
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello and welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 62.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we're playing Max 2 USA MP3s tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: So in that break you heard A Little Bit of Ecstasy, Bad Routine, and Busy Child.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're just going to hit them in alphabetic order.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got 15 songs to play tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Five breaks we usually do, so we'll have just enough to put us through the rest of the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, speaking of Max 2 USA, it's the big news this week, Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_07]: We haven't had a new DDR game in the USA for over a year.
[SPEAKER_07]: We haven't really seen any new DDR of any kind, unless you live in Europe.
[SPEAKER_07]: You haven't seen any new DDR of any kind since Extreme in January.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this is like big news this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, what'd you guys think?
[SPEAKER_08]: Best damn home version ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it's got so many licensed tracks that are unique to the game that they actually...
[SPEAKER_08]: Put some thought into what songs to put in and actually did a good job of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, but this is better.
[SPEAKER_08]: Max 2 is 20 times better.
[SPEAKER_08]: Spine, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any particular favorites?
[SPEAKER_07]: They had Xenon in it and I pissed my pants when I unlocked it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You didn't spoil, I went and spoiled the list.
[SPEAKER_07]: I went on Wednesday morning and read the whole damn list.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just wanted to know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wanted to know what the hell was in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't even go online Wednesday until like the night when I was halfway through unlocking it when I was going to go online and see how far you guys were into it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully you were listening to us on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_07]: We were playing live.
[SPEAKER_15]: I didn't even care.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't care if it's a spoiler or not.
[SPEAKER_15]: Two words.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tomorrow Perfume.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tomorrow Perfume was an excellent choice for an unlock to the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to start off with a bitch, and it's my one bitch about Max 2 USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: Otherwise, the game is fucking fabulous, but this is my bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Almost one out of every three songs has been in a USA release before.
[SPEAKER_07]: Including, like, half the unlocks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, when I unlocked Afranova... Okay, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: When I unlocked Put Your Faith in Me, I about threw a brick through the TV, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, if Loki hadn't have bought this brand new TV, I would have put a brick through it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I was just like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: Put Your Faith in Me?
[SPEAKER_07]: At least it wasn't the jazzy groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if you're going to repeat something, repeat a good song.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's my one bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Otherwise, I like the game, but I just felt a little...
[SPEAKER_07]: Cheated My Baby Mama
[SPEAKER_07]: One of the coolest things, one of the things I freaking love about Max 2 USA is those fourth mix songs, Conga Feelin', Dream a Dream, In the Navy, third mix, fourth mix, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Those songs have been completely reinvented.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yes, the fact that they're in 60 frames a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they have background videos.
[SPEAKER_07]: Background videos fucking rule.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm almost a little disappointed that there weren't more of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I was a little surprised that, like, Heaven didn't have its video.
[SPEAKER_31]: Yeah, I thought there would be a video for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so they probably had licensing issue problems.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, give it to them.
[SPEAKER_07]: They probably had to pay a lot more to license the videos.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Days Go By video is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki made the Rice Crunch Retreat.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_07]: Favorite video.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know how many songs actually have music videos, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: If you do the counting, six.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's only six.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I thought there were more than that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the two Captain Jack songs, Conga Feelin', Whistle Song, Love at First Sight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Days Go By, and Four Strings.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, maybe there is eight, because that's seven I just named.
[SPEAKER_07]: Four Strings has a video, and then there's... Yeah, Four Strings has a video.
[SPEAKER_07]: Four Strings has that video that has the trains in it and the green wall.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nobody knew what video it was when you saw... Oh, yeah, you have to look at the Four Strings video.
[SPEAKER_08]: The steps to that song are really good.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the one... You know how everybody thought... Look at the freezes.
[SPEAKER_07]: You remember when the early, early...
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, you remember when the early, early pictures of Max 2 came out and they had the trains and everybody said it was Chemical Brothers Star Guitar?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was actually the Four Strings video.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was done with that game in one hour.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was just like, eh, I'm over it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: If we had, like, a working dance pad in here right now, I think I'd still be playing it every day for exercise.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah, doubles?
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: My ignition pad, mine, that I got as an alimony payment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and we've heard about that pad so many times already, we don't need to hear it again.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're right, we don't need to hear it again.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, I mean, just the random old non-stop is keeping me playing it every day.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what, if I had a dance pad to play it on, not just controller, I'd be playing it every day too.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know what's weird, is I think between this, and I'm going to get into this later, between this and RVGL's recent turnaround, I'm like totally into DDR again, it's scary.
[SPEAKER_08]: Except for the whole wobbly pad thing on Extreme and RVGL, I played one game on it and I was like... Other comments on Max 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: You haven't been able to play it yet, Aaron, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully during a break we'll be able to sneak it on so you can see it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Favorite video?
[SPEAKER_07]: Puppy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to go with...
[SPEAKER_08]: In the Navy video.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would say it's a tie because I love Conga Phelan.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love Vivian.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's a fat Shakira.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love her.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Dream of Dream is so cool too, like the flying car.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a flying car in the Dream of Dream video.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I have to say Conga Phelan though because like...
[SPEAKER_07]: They changed... One thing you may not know if you haven't picked up Max 2 USA yet, they changed all the backgrounds for the fourth mix and before songs that have videos.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Conga Feelin', Dream of Dream, they all have new backgrounds that are stills from the music video.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Dream of Dream background is the best DDR background ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the...
[SPEAKER_07]: The Konga feeling video is like this shot of Vivian, and she has her mouth open and her eyes squinty.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks scary.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's a throwback to the original 4th Plus video, which was the girl with her mouth open.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the way they got the freeze frame and the video... The videos were ghetto.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were ghetto.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like a cum shot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like Konga feeling, because Vivian's got her mouth open.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's like, oh yeah, baby!
[SPEAKER_07]: What about Captain Jack's background for Dream or Dream?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dream or Dream was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's just like... He's like, scary monster man.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shittiest background.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shittiest new background.
[SPEAKER_07]: The love at first sight video is scary.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should watch the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would say... I don't want to watch the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shittiest background is days go by.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't... Because that shot of the guys in the car, they like keep showing that in the video.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're actually... It's because they're the singers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, well, I... You can't really see it much because the videos are so low-res, but they're actually singing the song in the background.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't like the Dream Dream background.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's a video, though, that I need to get the whole thing of, though, because... Yeah, that's the worst video.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, no...
[SPEAKER_15]: But no, for Days Go By, the whole video, I really want to see it because it's supposed to actually have a whole story to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, it has subtitles too, which somehow, I think they totally edited the Max 2 USA one because it has no subtitles.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I think they totally picked and chose different clips.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because if you notice, if you watch the Kylie video, they had to edit that too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because they had to edit it to go with the edited song.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think this is also turned into widescreen on the...
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't pay that close attention, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought they changed the ratio so that it wouldn't show where the actual subtitles would have been.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_07]: They may have done something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to comment on Max 2 USA with the rest of our listeners, www.callybomani.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Click on Orange Lounge and click on Chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be playing Max 2 USA MP3s throughout the evening.
[SPEAKER_07]: We also have the three brand new songs in DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's my next question.
[SPEAKER_07]: What did you guys think of the brand, brand new songs?
[SPEAKER_07]: They've never been in DDR before.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, the Konami originals that have not been in any game yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like Forever Sunshine and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Forever Sunshine came out of my ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like a liquidly brown goo.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what that song was.
[SPEAKER_07]: We found a singer that sings worse than Paul Eteri.
[SPEAKER_07]: We didn't think it was possible?
[SPEAKER_07]: I gotta tell you, Try to Love You, I actually like that song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Try to Love You has the chick from Let Them Move singing, and it's actually a really damn good song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Forever Sunshine.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first time I heard it, it was like, eh, but it started to grow on me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Forever Sunshine is awful.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has Miss Piggy singing it, is what we were saying on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ernie, Forever Sunshine, come here.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish they would have taken that one new song from Lesson Mode and actually put that into the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: The biggest letdown is not having that song in the game as a playable song.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's one we didn't rip.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's one thing we've got to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have an MP3 of it, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually just played through that whole section of Lesson Mode just so I could play that song in its entirety.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know one thing that also impressed me about Max 2 USA I've got to say?
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you watch the credit sequence?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: The credit sequence is actually really cool because it goes through all the stock videos and just plays them.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, dangers with the video?
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't show videos or characters at the same time.
[SPEAKER_15]: When they do the three... I'm sorry, I'm talking about the busy videos.
[SPEAKER_15]: When you have three dancers and then all the busy stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: And they all do their own dance, so it's really stupid looking.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sometimes they'll do the same dance.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you like the dancers overall, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you think it was a good feature?
[SPEAKER_15]: I liked that they were all cleaned up and cel-shaded.
[SPEAKER_15]: They were really nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: The characters looked gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cel-shaded rage is fucking pimp.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think they totally stole that idea from Step Mania, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: They could have, but somebody is insatiated.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what, they did it better in the USDDR, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'll tell you what, the best thing about those characters is when you get extra stage playing Max Unlimited.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, they're seizuring!
[SPEAKER_07]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, hello, seizures.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: 23rd Magus says in the chat room, the best song in the game was the Midnight Blaze remix in the menus.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was an awesome mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, kind of a disappointment that that wasn't in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Was that the same one from VRare?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate System SF.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know you hate System SF, but you'll get into it later.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like that new Kind Lady remix.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was actually kind of hard, and it was fun, and I liked it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to have that next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Next week we're going to have the US VRare 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie has it, and she's going to bring it next week for us.
[SPEAKER_07]: After the show tonight, by the way, Night Style, original soundtrack, we're going to play it for you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because we've been playing bits and pieces for you guys throughout the week, but I know most of you guys listen to the Tonight Show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't it go up on MGG, the first disc of Night Style?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, we had the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: We got it through a different source.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of our studio regulars got it for us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll need to get a copy then.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't copy tonight, but I can get it for you during the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_07]: Anybody else want a microphone now?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, who wants... Anyone else want to comment on Max 2?
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Bradley?
[SPEAKER_07]: I know you haven't played it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bradley, you have anything you want to say on Max 2?
[SPEAKER_07]: I know you got a little bit out on Wednesday, but... Jamie!
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you have to say about Max 2?
[SPEAKER_07]: She's cooking.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm, like, stuck with the microphone?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else is there to talk about with Max 2?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's something, um... The non... I'm actually glad they took out OEs and replaced them with non-stops.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because non-stops are much better.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jason Enos is brilliant.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I forgot.
[SPEAKER_07]: The information screen is like the best part of the unlocks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Completely.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is so hilarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: And supposedly, the rumor is Jason Enos wrote all those himself.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, we know he did for Max, and so we kind of assume he did for Max, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_07]: But those things were the funniest damn things.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: And there's one for every damn song in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and they're funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of them are kind of generic, but some of the ones that use the worst puns ever are so great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, that was part of the unlocking for me, was just getting to do the bad puns.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_15]: I didn't get a chance to check it out because I've been kind of busy, but I'm going to be using the workout mode in the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it looks like it was tweaked a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you looked at workout mode?
[SPEAKER_07]: They did change it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was not able to find non-stops though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I heard a rumor that non-stops were in workout mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: We couldn't find them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, maybe that's what we did wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'll tell you what though, they totally changed the interface.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, the interface in workout mode looks better than in the in-game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has like the stars and the flashing red background.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's pretty.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it's pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's got the little spiral swirly thing and it makes it look cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of like how Max 2 USA feels a little bit like a hybrid of Max 2 and Xtreme, like with all the Xtreme videos being in there and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But what's interesting is that when October 9th, we're only like two weeks away from it, we're going to be seeing the Japanese version of Xtreme, and we here at Orange Lounge Radio, of course, will be getting that.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to do another launch party.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another big promo for that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but the problem is, we don't know what day we're going to get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You may not get it for like three weeks after it's released.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we're hoping we're going to get it within days of its release.
[SPEAKER_07]: It could be...
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll get that later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Loki will get into that later, why War is on a hiatus for a little while.
[SPEAKER_07]: DDR Extreme Japan, it's kind of like, wow, it's going to be interesting because Max 2 USA, for once, it's like it's taken a lot of the good things before the Japanese can do it.
[SPEAKER_31]: Yeah, we actually beat them to things.
[SPEAKER_07]: The cell shading characters, some of the songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Background movies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although if you heard this, this is kind of news that came out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: DDR Party Edition, the one that's going to come out after Extreme.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if it's the end of the year or first quarter next year.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's kind of going to be a Best Hits 2, basically.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's going to use music videos.
[SPEAKER_07]: That could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's been confirmed that Conga Feelin's going to have its videos, so who knows what other videos we're going to get now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably the same four we have in Max 2 USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: Could we get Butterfly's video?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because Butterfly has been confirmed in the mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: That could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just no.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's frightening.
[SPEAKER_08]: And whose phone is ringing?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going off it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hear a tone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bad song in that mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: Spice Girls' Wannabe is going to be in DDR Party.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has like two new songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of them is a beat for you song and the other one is Spice Girls.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's in the new Euro.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's in the new Euro game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck the Spice Girls.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck their music.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why do they have to prolong their song's life?
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, people are spreading rumors that the Korean songs will finally make their debut in Party.
[SPEAKER_07]: I doubt it too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Never gonna happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop wanting those old pieces of shit songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: If they were so good, they would have brought them back.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get over it.
[SPEAKER_07]: FaceSucks, I will give you that, but Bakuo and... What's the one, wherever you go, what's the slow one?
[SPEAKER_07]: Buell, Buell, BuellSucks, but like Wah, Bakua, SongSuck, MaskTime.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, one of the Sacramento regulars had a routine to be old, it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_07]: In the chatroom, Holly is posting parody lyrics to Wannabe.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to be my butter, you got to spread on my bread.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's very cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Tell Me Tell Me had like the funnest trick double steps ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't do trick doubles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, Starion.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Bakua had the worst double steps.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bakua had horrible double steps.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, it would be nice if those show up on Party Edition, but I'm not going to hold my breath over it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it would be nice.
[SPEAKER_32]: Maybe Petit Love will come back.
[SPEAKER_32]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_07]: If that happened, I would break the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: If Butterfly is on it, okay, then SmileDK is coming back to a home release.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get Petite Love on here.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I don't think it'll happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: We need bass solo songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, Extreme will be out in a few weeks, and there's a couple new tracks in Extreme.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: A Stupid Barber A Stupid Barber has been confirmed What the hell is that song?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's by Soda It's by the same one who did one of the songs Is it Do It Right?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's also one of the songs in Max 2 USA What?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Show T?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's one of the Hidden Max 2 USA songs, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just can't think of the name.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm looking it up right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I Need You.
[SPEAKER_07]: That one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I Need You was by him, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: With the piano in the background?
[SPEAKER_31]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_31]: Oh, that one.
[SPEAKER_31]: Right, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, um... Okay, so what's this you're going to play for us, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the track that was in the lesson mode in X2.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think... I heard it be called Overloaded.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, that is Lesson 2, we're calling it for now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It might be overloaded because that's the one lyric in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that is Lesson 2 in Max 2 USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it fucking rules.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what if that's a stupid barber?
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be, no, just no.
[SPEAKER_07]: I doubt it, but that would be cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's the other thing, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's one of the things we can look at.
[SPEAKER_07]: Since, pretty much, you can guarantee Extreme, the Party Mix, Max 2 USA, and Dancing Stage Fever are... Whatever their one is going to be called now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if it's Fever or not, but anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're all sharing the same song list that was in Max 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you pretty much eliminate all the songs that have been confirmed for the other games, and you're left with what's in Extreme, which one of them is Max, period.
[SPEAKER_08]: Another Max?
[SPEAKER_07]: Max period.
[SPEAKER_07]: The problem is if that appears in DDR Extreme, it's going to be pretty much guaranteed that that's going to be DDR Extreme was the last arcade version because they never release Maxes on the home versions at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that would be my guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to go out on a limb here, and I know Loki's going to yell at me for it, but I think Max Period is a red herring.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think it means anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it'll be nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think it's going to be a song.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I would love to be proven wrong.
[SPEAKER_15]: Mine didn't break.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even remember when it broke.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe that song was Max Period.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my gods.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to move your jacket right here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, we're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to play some more Max 2 USA stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: When we come back, we're going to finish up any talk on Max 2 USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to talk a bit about some other games and some other arcades in town.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to talk about 2DX as well when we come back.
[SPEAKER_07]: After this group of Max 2 USA MP3s, we're going to hear in this break, start off with Days Go By.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you're going to hear Forever Sunshine in this break too.
[SPEAKER_07]: No!
[SPEAKER_07]: No, God no.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's only a minute and 28 seconds, but I feel an obligation to our listeners who haven't been able to hear it yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: They can say they've heard it, so here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you really want to scare the crap out of them?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's okay, because after that we get one of the coolest 70 songs ever, Get Down Tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do a little dance.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: People don't need to buy laxatives anymore, because all they have to do is listen to that Sunshine song, and it'll make them poop.
[SPEAKER_22]: and Forever Sunshine.
[SPEAKER_22]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Listen, Frog.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, is that song worse than Let Them Move?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that song worse than Let Them Move?
[SPEAKER_07]: We will find out.
[SPEAKER_07]: We will find out after the break.
[SPEAKER_15]: We should make the chatroom vote.
[SPEAKER_22]: Days when I couldn't live my life without you
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio With the Ping Pong Boys
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, welcome back, boys and girls, to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 62, playing Max 2 USA MP3s all night tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: In that break, you heard Dirty Vegas, Days Go By, Shell Y with Forever Sunshine, and Miss Piggy, and KC and the Sunshine Band with Get Down Tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I have to make a comment on the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: For your response to Biohazard, don't diss fucking KC and the Sunshine Band.
[SPEAKER_08]: You are... That is the best fucking song ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: I do have to agree with half of what he says.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think Let's Groove is funner to dance to, and funner is a word, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gotcha, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't stand it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't stand Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_07]: I cannot stand dancing to that song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Before we went to the break, we said we were going to settle a debate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which song is worse?
[SPEAKER_07]: Forever Sunshine, or Let Them Move?
[SPEAKER_07]: The chat room has voted, and I will reveal what they have voted, which one is worse, but I just want to hear what you guys think, and why.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aaron, we haven't heard much from you tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which song's worse, Let Them Move or Forever Sunshine?
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess you guys should know my opinion on this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did freestyle.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I did freestyle to let them move.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we all know how that turned out.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I guess I could say Forever Sunshine is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: But is it worse?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Aaron says Forever Sunshine is a little worse.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just a little, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Better close.
[SPEAKER_07]: Puppy, which one's worse and why?
[SPEAKER_08]: Fred or Sunshine, just because it's... I can stand Let Them Move.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I turn the volume down a little bit, but... No, this song is just... Ew.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, which is worse and why?
[SPEAKER_15]: After dealing with Let Them Move for three and a half, nearly four years?
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let Them Move is still the worst.
[SPEAKER_15]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: Bradley, which song is worse than why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let Them Move is worse.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because this woman in this song can actually sing alright, even if she sings weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: But in Let Them Move, she just screeches.
[SPEAKER_22]: Which makes it much worse.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, which song is worse than why?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they need to do Let Them Move Ska, which would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let them move, let them move, sweet, sweet baby.
[SPEAKER_07]: They could totally do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They could, like, you know, I don't know, get, um, I don't know, get some ska band to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, there's plenty of... Get Tom, or was it, um, Mr. Brian in the final band?
[SPEAKER_07]: Get him to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah, we should have put Crash in there, too, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: That wasn't an option.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, what's your answer?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: I dislike them equally.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, honestly, I hate Forever Sunshine because it's happy, and I don't like happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's happy like Poppy, like, look, the sun is smiling, the clouds are smiling, the little furry animals are smiling, everybody is smiling happy, happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: to Scream Scream Badly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I just... All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Me, personally, as much as... Now, I can impersonate Muppets to both of them because I can do Miss Piggy with Forever Sunshine, but with Let Them Move, I can also do Elmo loves Para Para.
[SPEAKER_23]: Let them move.
[SPEAKER_23]: Sweet, sweet.
[SPEAKER_23]: But...
[SPEAKER_07]: Let Them Move is by far worse.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love imitating Miss Piggy more than I do Elmo, so Forever Sunshine is way worse.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, Let Them Move is way worse.
[SPEAKER_07]: Forever Sunshine is better.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually somewhat enjoy Forever Sunshine in a campy musical sort of way.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, so I think it was even.
[SPEAKER_07]: We had Loki, Bradley, and me said Let Them Move.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, because Jamie also said Let Them Move is worse.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was four, and then you two said Forever Sunshine.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you guys think the chat room said?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let Them Move.
[SPEAKER_07]: By an overwhelming majority, well, mostly overwhelming, the chatroom says Let Them Move is the worst song.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the way you guys voted.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it matters because it's still banned from the station.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let Them Move is banned from the station.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know about Forever Sunshine, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if I put that in or not today.
[SPEAKER_07]: I put a bunch of new Max 2 USA MP3s in today.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if Forever Sunshine is one of them or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, ViolentHyperBurpGirl.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was impressive.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, it was a double.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get into 2DX news and speaking of bad songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, the Night Style soundtrack came out like just a week ago, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I have to admit something, and this is hard, this is painful.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need to sit down for this.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know, the last time I sat down to admit something, I was admitting that I like Paula Terry's version of Dive.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you know that this is bad, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was a song that I was somewhat surprised to see on the Night Style soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I forgot that this song was in Night Style.
[SPEAKER_07]: But when I was listening to this song, I realized that in the context of 2DX, I actually kind of like this song.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that song is... Don't say it!
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't say it!
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop kind of like bag...
[SPEAKER_07]: You fag!
[SPEAKER_32]: I'm sorry!
[SPEAKER_32]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_32]: But I like bag.
[SPEAKER_32]: I apologize to my mommy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie likes bag too?
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll only be good when it gets remixed by 2MB.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where the hell has 2MB been?
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's just like, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: That personality, der.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where has 2MB been?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, seriously, it's just like, after 5th Mix, I quit, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: We need to get 2MB here to take all those shitty songs that Naoki, the other personality, keeps making and re- No, wait, 2MB is not Naoki.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's- it's you and the- Ah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ha!
[SPEAKER_07]: You tricked me!
[SPEAKER_07]: How dare I?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we need to get him back to, like, fix.
[SPEAKER_07]: I absolutely agree with Brack2000.
[SPEAKER_07]: He says, Bag is bad for DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why I hated Bag before.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is an acid song to dance to.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bag should have been in Parapara.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was not fun at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Bag in 2DX would actually be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't played it in 2DX yet, but I think I'd actually enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I found that on the Nightstyle OST, I actually enjoy Bag.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, Loki!
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the truth, and I believe in telling the truth on this show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also on the Nightstyle soundtrack, there's some great stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: A long version of Golden Horn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: A long version of The End of My Spiritually.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's not a typo.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not spirituality.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's The End of My Spiritually, if you listen to the lyrics.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yes, I agree in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's scrolled off the screen, but Logic Board is awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I agree with Jamie when she says, more men with nice asses need to dance to bag and wear a kilt.
[SPEAKER_07]: And would that be a military-style kilt?
[SPEAKER_10]: Full traditional.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: How does Sweetest Savage sound?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the other athletics one, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's interesting because when you hear things on the Nightstyle OST, it sounds a lot different than those MP3s that were leaked before.
[SPEAKER_15]: Please Don't Go needs to be in DDR.
[SPEAKER_15]: Imagine how fun that would be on the little scratchy parts.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, why can't they take songs from 2DX like Please Don't Go and put those into Max 2 USA?
[SPEAKER_07]: Instead, oh my god, VJ Army would kick so much ass in DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why don't they take those instead and put them in instead of repeating fucking Put Your Faith In Me?
[SPEAKER_07]: And what I don't get is, they're like, you know, in-house music, so why... I mean... I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pay your artists their little, like, peanut or whatever in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dancer X broke it down on DDR Freak the reasons why, and he was basically like, you know, you can have the repeats or you can have nothing or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm like, you know what, I'm sorry, I respect their decision or whatever, but I don't agree with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they could have taken more 2DX songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what they're saving it for, because...
[SPEAKER_07]: as, you know, it's going to take another year before we see Max 3 or Extreme in the U.S., whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: If we even see it at all, they may not do one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why is it that, like, you can have... And by then we're on 9th and 10th style.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why is it that you can have, like, a person, like, say...
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Healing, this guy goes by the name Healing Vision, or a guy that goes by the name Utter Dude, or the guy, you know, this Matt, I forget his last name.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why can they pump out really quality, and this is talking about better than, you know, home version.
[SPEAKER_07]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to catch you on something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rumor is, it has not been confirmed that KOA actually did those steps.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rumor is that KOJ might have done quite a few of them, especially the things that are going to show up in Extreme later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's even worse!
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm just saying, the same people who've done all the steps before are probably still doing them for DDRMAX 2 USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has not been confirmed that KOA has been doing them in-house.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to notice that a lot of the new original songs in Max 2 kind of get stuck with a lot of fucking freeze arrows, and you remember what happened in Max 1 with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, here's my suggestion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dear Konami, when you're going to put out Max 3 or Extreme or whatever the next thing is that's going to come out in the US, there better be something else.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please have an edit bank.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, seriously, go with the databank just like last time.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is what you need to link up to the old mixes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck this repeating put-your-faith-in-me stuff just because the damn song was in Konomics.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bring up an edit bank that has steps to songs like Dark Black Forest, Japan, things that were in earlier mixes, and there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now people have a reason to get those old mixes because they want to see the databank.
[SPEAKER_07]: And not only that, here's a few other things you can do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Put in challenge mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: Challenge mode back.
[SPEAKER_06]: But instead, set it up like drill mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not just challenge mode, I want a story mode to go with it, written by Jason Enos.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, that's retarded.
[SPEAKER_15]: We do not need a story mode because then we'd be going back to one of the worst Konami games ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dance, dance, dance.
[SPEAKER_15]: With a little stupid RPG mode in it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ugh, that game sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dance, dance, dance.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dance, Dance, Dance started the Bimani thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: It did not begin with Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_15]: The style of game came with Beatmania, but the whole music game thing started with Dance, Dance, Dance, and the game flows.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, yeah, challenge mode for sure, but set up like drill mode, because in that way you can have drill mode as being both a training lesson mode thing and a challenge mode at the same time.
[SPEAKER_07]: And drill modes are fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it takes you a long time to go through and you can incorporate that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That and the unlocks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't make a song get unlocked after ten songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, we play like a full two sets of songs, you know, five songs each, and we get an unlock.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's recorded.
[SPEAKER_07]: But what do you say to the people that disagree with you and say, you know what, fuck the unlocks, just have it all to begin with.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why do we even waste our time unlocking things?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just blow your load in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because there's no point in playing the game then if you have no purpose to play the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, what about playing the songs and dancing to them?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what you do in DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to have a goal.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to get boring faster.
[SPEAKER_07]: What would you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, I think, but we know this is never going to happen because Konami of America is not going to put out an arcade machine, but let's say KOJ does this.
[SPEAKER_07]: An F-Zero type unlock system where you have to go back and forth between the arcade and the home version to unlock things.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be cool, but it'll never work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because they'll never make an arcade version.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'd be interested in your suggestions as well for Max 3 USA or Extreme, whatever it's called.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, let's just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_07]: www.caliabomani.com, click on Orange Lounge and click on Chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Once I get the freaking cabinet done in here, and you see how I have the sim set up with all the songs, and there's going to be unlocks in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is how the damn game should be, like my home cabinet.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to have quality songs in there because I don't pay licensing rights to anyone.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should make multiple machines and then sell them.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should go suck my cock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, what time is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to record the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: NoStylin has a great one.
[SPEAKER_07]: He says the unlock should be nude images of Konami staff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jason Enos.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but there's, okay, there's a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's talk about some of the other stuff that's also that they could have done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another thing I came up with a while back was routine videos.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something similar to like, you know, where you have ParaPara, where you've got freestyle, which would be the standard, you know, basic trick maniac, you know, for old school people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, then you've got, like, you know, routine mode, where it's another set of steps, but it goes with, like, a dancing character on screen where you do what they do, and it kind of goes with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, like, uh, learn how to freestyle like Mel B?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, see?
[SPEAKER_10]: See, the problem with that is that... The problem with that is that now you're going to have a bunch of little unshowered teeny-bopper idiots freestyling exactly the same routine, and that's really bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, as opposed to a bunch of stupid Asians peri-peri?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, seriously!
[SPEAKER_09]: Cara is dead, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: It was cool until they made the videos and put it on the machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would be fine with Konami doing a learn how to freestyle like us thing as long as, and I preface this with a disclaimer, views and opinions expressed by me do not express those that weren't on the video, as long as it's not 8-Ball.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I can't make a comment.
[SPEAKER_15]: I cannot make a comment.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll take your silence as your comment.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I still have stuff to say about that idea for freestyling.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, then they're all going to...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, it's better than, um, so basically it's gonna be based off of that routine there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gee, like, no one bases their routines off of, like, music videos or anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: No one emulates anybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're all original.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then again, do you really want people just imitating the home versions?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's better than watching people hump the bar, jump over the bar, run across the screen, hand slap, knee drop, and act like idiots.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I don't mind people jumping over the bar for the few times that they miss and nut themselves.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well that's fine, but other than that though, well other than freestyle mode or whatever that would be, my other idea was, now StepMedia has kind of done this, they have a mode in it called Mines, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's steps that go up, like arrows and stuff, normal, whatever, I don't know if it's randomly generated or whatever, but there's also steps that you can't step on.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you step on them, you lose health.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is what I've been saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: If DDR is going to come back in Japan, it needs to be competitive.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've said this like five out of the last ten shows.
[SPEAKER_07]: DDR needs to come back competitive, as a competitive game, as opposed to, let's have fun and hold hands and dance and play cooperative.
[SPEAKER_23]: Everybody dance!
[SPEAKER_07]: And it needs to be fucking hardcore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or, you know, like they have Second Mix Battle, needs to be something like that in there, they need something like Dance Magic, they need just anything that's competitive.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want, I want at the very end of each battle round, there'd be smoke coming out of the middle of the city, and strobe lights!
[SPEAKER_07]: Strobe lights, lots of strobe lights.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly, I want, I want Unison, I want all that shit back.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want Second Mix version Dance Battle.
[SPEAKER_07]: DDR has gotten fucking tame as it's been going along, and it's time for DDR to get mean.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you know how easy tournaments would be?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know how easy and common tournaments would be?
[SPEAKER_07]: They should have tournament mode, where it's just already set up in the cabinet.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else could they have?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, definitely like some new sort of unlocks, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I liked kind of like Max USA's unlocks.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, where you could get it by doing the songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: You had to do a lot more songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: You had to do 500 songs to get Drop the Bomb.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was worth it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you could do other little stupid things to get them, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_07]: They need to find a happy medium between Max USA and Max 2 USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because Max would say, I got tired of playing like 500 songs to get the next unlock, but I also got tired of playing just 10 songs and getting the unlocks super fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they need to kind of balance it out in the middle there somewhere, and that'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's funny because when Marin in the chatroom says, Get mean, DDR, runs around biting people, rawr, it makes me think, if they want DDR to get good, just inject a little SARS into it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rawr!
[SPEAKER_07]: Rage.
[SPEAKER_07]: Induce rage.
[SPEAKER_07]: DDR Rabid Wolf Mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I think we're going to take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to do some more.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, ooh, ooh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's a really great idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a song similar to, I think it was in Space, no, not Space Shelf 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was in that Buster Move game or whatever that we were playing a while back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dance Summit?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dance Summit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where if you do good in a song or do perfect or whatever, that the song changes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like it kind of remixes itself.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it would be cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, we're going to take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_07]: In this break, we're going to hear Heaven.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a big one because this was the number one requested licensed song, Please Get It, and Konami did it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They got Heaven.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to hear the mix of that that's in DDR Max 2 USA, and then we're also going to hear I Need You, which is one of the songs, is a Konami original that has not been in DDR or any Bomani game before.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then we'll also hear Keep On Lifton, that song from Beatmania 3 that made it into Max 2 USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: When we come back...
[SPEAKER_07]: Since we haven't gotten around to it yet, we usually kick off the show with it, but a lot of people have some stories they want to tell.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to get into how was your day, how was your week when we come back.
[SPEAKER_20]: Baby, you're all that I want When you're lying here in my arms I'm finding it hard to believe We're in heaven
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_26]: Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: And you don't stop.
[SPEAKER_26]: Come on.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: Rock Over London, Rock Over Chicago, Orange Lounge Radio It's a good place to listen to the music
[SPEAKER_07]: Makes me sad, Wesley Willis, dead and gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: I cry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, as promised, now's the part of the show where we go around and talk to our guests and we talk about how was your week and how was your day.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I know some people have some exciting things to talk about.
[SPEAKER_07]: I, for one, I want to talk about, well, we'll get to that when we get to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who wants to start tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: You always do, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_07]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't know you always did, but fine, do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie's shoving a peanut in her mouth.
[SPEAKER_07]: What if other people want to go first today?
[SPEAKER_15]: Screw them.
[SPEAKER_15]: My week has been okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've been sleep deprived all week.
[SPEAKER_15]: I haven't gotten more than four hours of sleep a night.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I crashed really bad on Friday night.
[SPEAKER_15]: I stayed up as late as I could.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was supposed to play Phantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_15]: I barely had enough of an attention span for Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, uh,
[SPEAKER_15]: I passed out like at 2 a.m.
[SPEAKER_15]: Got up at 11.30ish, something like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: I went out and hung out with Iguana Girl all weekend, well, all Saturday.
[SPEAKER_15]: And we bought iguana food for Moo.
[SPEAKER_15]: And watched, like, Life of Brian and Jay and Silent Bob back-to-back while cutting up greens.
[SPEAKER_15]: My fingers turned green.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was scary.
[SPEAKER_15]: I played DDR Thursday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my gosh, okay, you have to realize the past like three weeks, I go here, Jamie, do you have anything Bomani related you want to tell us?
[SPEAKER_22]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: You made an interesting live journal entry, and I know you keep your live journal friends only, but maybe this is one you wouldn't mind sharing, kind of about what you were saying about... 40 minutes of DDR is 306 calories burned.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that's just like, you know, on the medium mode on workout, on workout mode.
[SPEAKER_15]: on the old Max.
[SPEAKER_07]: Max USA 1.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, because that was before I got my Max 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: It was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was really tired and everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, this was Thursday.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, take that back.
[SPEAKER_15]: It wasn't Thursday.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_15]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: But anyway, it was...
[SPEAKER_15]: I was still really tired, and I've been so tired all week that I really haven't been able to put much more effort into it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, you know, that's how, when I first started playing DDR, I played for an hour every night.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, more than an hour.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would do like two hours of nothing but not stopping on second mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I'm thinking that that's what I'm going to do again.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, better living through DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, I'm going to lose weight if I play more DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll lose weight again.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I'm going to get back into playing and mixing that with going to the gym.
[SPEAKER_15]: And Saturday, I got milk tea and boiled peanuts.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I don't know how many people know anything about living in the South, but I haven't, for years, I haven't been able to find boiled peanuts until I moved out here.
[SPEAKER_15]: And so I started shopping at the Asian food stores.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I was like, boiled peanuts.
[SPEAKER_15]: And they were, you know, fresh boiled peanuts and everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: They were really good.
[SPEAKER_15]: And anyway, I got some goodies.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have lots of them at home.
[SPEAKER_15]: Picked up some treats for people.
[SPEAKER_15]: But boiled peanuts, that was like the highlight of my weekend was boiled peanuts.
[SPEAKER_15]: I never get them.
[SPEAKER_15]: The one thing that I wish I could find is blood peanuts in a can.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've not been able to find those anywhere outside the South.
[SPEAKER_15]: So that's been my... Yeah, and I've been busy with other stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: The really crappy drama thing seems to have subsided, which I'm pretty glad for.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was drama?
[SPEAKER_15]: There was drama involving a site, but it's pretty much resolved.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've just been feeling really crappy all week, you know, in general, but it hasn't been a bad week.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, and they can't hear any of your commentary because you're busy sucking nuts.
[SPEAKER_15]: The look on your face is great.
[SPEAKER_15]: My nuts are good.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're safe for consumption.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're done?
[SPEAKER_15]: Geez!
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm just saying, are you done?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you done?
[SPEAKER_07]: Aaron's got her hand out, so... Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_32]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_32]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_32]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_32]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aaron, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_07]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well, for those of you who know, X and I sent, aka Claudia, has officially got me addicted to Initial D!
[SPEAKER_03]: Boo!
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn her.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I spent a total of at least $10 on the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because it's only like 40 cents at the MU to play.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's five tokens to a dollar.
[SPEAKER_10]: So two tokens per game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, five games for $2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, I started school this week, and workload 57, English 57, which is a stupid little remedial English class, feels just like high school!
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm stuck there.
[SPEAKER_10]: For a quarter.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to interject real fast, because the chatroom won't shut up about this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chatroom, I assure you, we will play Overloaded in the afterbirth again, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, ViolentHyperGirl, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Holly says, can I have your salty nuts?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, sorry to interrupt.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you want to finish?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually didn't get lost on campus for my first day of school.
[SPEAKER_10]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_10]: And I've also become quite popular in the dorms after playing piano so many times.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you're already popular in the dorms, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_10]: Not that way!
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, other than that, we kind of settled in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Our apartment's cooled down considerably.
[SPEAKER_10]: Davis has only been hitting upwards of, at best, 90 this past week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's been pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything special today?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, not really, other than it's good to be on Orange Lounge when there's no internet problems.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's nice to be here on a week where the station works, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: For those of you that missed last week, you're better off, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just trust us.
[SPEAKER_07]: We wrote it off.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what's interesting about last week's show, and I didn't realize this until I was going back and clipping it down for the archives?
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: We did not take a single break last week at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you didn't notice that?
[SPEAKER_10]: We never...
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't notice that we did two hours straight.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you think about it, even though a lot of people were kind of like, oh, you guys only did two hours, you know, with all the problems, even though we dropped you guys 37 times thanks to Comcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you think about it, with two hours straight of content, you know, throw breaks, you didn't lose that much of a show, so shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's my point, shut up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see, other than that, I've actually had my room to myself.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm supposed to be sharing my room with my friend, but she hasn't been home.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lucky you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, does she have a boyfriend?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, she's been spending... See, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what always happens in college, is that, you know, my roommate was the same way indoors, that he was rushing a fraternity, so he was sleeping with all his boyfriends.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we all probably know what he was doing with all of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, no, he also had a girlfriend that lived upstairs and he was staying there sometimes because the one time she came to stay there, I had a fit, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: I was just like, I don't feel comfortable with her being here in the morning when I'm waking up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just like, that's weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, okay, so anyone else want to talk about their week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so you're done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bradley, you have anything you want to share about your week and your day?
[SPEAKER_07]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_07]: How was your day, Bradley?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's caught on the other one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take it away.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unchlorial.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't do all that much this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I... Every so often... Most of it was being lazy for most of the day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Punctuated by...
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching.
[SPEAKER_08]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, if you're out there and you want to hire somebody, Arcadian42, Bradley, hire him.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, most of it's because I'm stupid and it took too long to do stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, and let's see, what else?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else I did this week?
[SPEAKER_07]: What else might I have done?
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I don't think I went anywhere any time this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except for Wednesday, I came over here and played some DDR Max 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Since I only have the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have a US PS2, so I got to experience that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: He went to... He went away.
[SPEAKER_06]: Went far, far away.
[SPEAKER_06]: To get power.
[SPEAKER_06]: Staying in.
[SPEAKER_07]: There he is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I should have made him get me something too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I should have sent him a shopping list.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, go back!
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't go anywhere yesterday.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought I went somewhere yesterday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now I can't remember where I went.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I might have went to Walmart.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I went to Walmart today.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn, I'm so forgettable.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can do one thing and I forget what I did.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, actually I went to the post office to mail stuff I sold off.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then today I watched the debate from Wednesday for the governor's debate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Them being silly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it was sort of okay, not all that great of a debate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Arnold didn't really impress me all that much.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was more impressed by when he was on, what's his face, Larry King.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was a bit more... No, no, he was on Larry King like two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's pretty much my week.
[SPEAKER_09]: So exciting!
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, thanks for sharing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry you're just jumping up and down.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, we'll put Puppy on the spot since he dared to leave the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Puppy, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_07]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_07]: Traitor!
I need the other mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Give me the other mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, this week, I started classes, yay, and I spent most of my time playing this guy until I got Max 2, and then I spent all the time playing that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and the occasional initial D binge, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, uh, yesterday I went to Roseville to play F-Zero for, yes, for nine straight hours.
[SPEAKER_08]: Call me an addict, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: Was the price down to four tokens by then?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: For the first two days, it was six tokens a game.
[SPEAKER_31]: And they also didn't have the real cars until Saturday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_31]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_31]: As I finish chewing my candy.
[SPEAKER_31]: Yeah, hello, you're on the radio, don't eat.
[SPEAKER_31]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_31]: So I spent nine hours.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played 37 games.
[SPEAKER_08]: In a row?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: I knew that was coming.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had to.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was like the cursed number of the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, uh...
[SPEAKER_08]: I started from scratch on a brand new card and worked my way all the way up to the highest rank possible as a master class license.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got all the way up to that.
[SPEAKER_31]: And I took all the records on five of the six tracks on Time Attack.
[SPEAKER_31]: And then, yeah.
[SPEAKER_31]: And then today I woke up at 1.30 and then sat in the apartment and then came here.
[SPEAKER_31]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_31]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_31]: Anything else you want to share?
[SPEAKER_31]: Random non-stops have been keeping me up late at night because it's just ridiculously fun.
[SPEAKER_31]: Even though it screws you over with things like Subaru Dark Reverse Stealth.
[SPEAKER_07]: The one time we played it here on Wednesday when we were broadcasting, they got a really easy one.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was like all standard songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: You haven't played it enough then.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some really fucked up things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, you have a second to tell us about your week and your day?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_07]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't do a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stopped doing LiveWire because Thursday nights only four people are listening to me and I work on it for three hours and that's not a very good mix so I'm taking time off until I feel like doing it again and then it'll be Wednesdays.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then today I've been soldering and for some fucking reason in the last five minutes the solder gun does not want to melt the solder, period.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm trying to clean the tip.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I think that's what's wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, um... And, uh, let's see... Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: You should ditch your class to listen to my show, 23 Magus.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't fucking mention shit if it's out of your control, dumbass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, if I wasn't dead with the computer and the modem, I wouldn't do it, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, the whole world would listen to me, too, also.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, what else?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, also, today I went and shopped and got some more controllers so I can work on my pads.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got all the wiring done on my pads, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, um, they should be done hopefully next week, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's been going really slowly.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, um, that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_08]: Been doing much... Oh, went and played F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need to talk about my week of my day.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't eat right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, my week of my day.
[SPEAKER_07]: My week is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw a lot of movies this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been hanging out with Joey who's been on the show the past couple weeks and he likes to watch a lot of movies at home so I've been catching up on all these movies I didn't see.
[SPEAKER_07]: I finally saw Resident Evil for the first time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, though, on Thursday was when Roseville Golf Land finally got Max 2, and that made me as happy as a little girl.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or not Max 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the hell am I talking about?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm torn between food and making sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_07]: Golf Land got F-Zero, and I was so excited because I've been wanting to play F-Zero in the arcade for so long.
[SPEAKER_07]: And F-Zero in the arcade is awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I love how it links with the home version.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can practically unlock all of...
[SPEAKER_07]: Olive AX for your GX if you play enough in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: So after playing F-Zero a lot, and I like to play it where you ride, too, where you go move with the thing when you put the seatbelt on.
[SPEAKER_07]: I only did that a couple times, but they have a motion machine at Roseville Golf Line, so it makes it more fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't like doing the motion on the harder courses because it's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since the steering wheel itself doesn't move with the rest of the seat, it's ridiculously hard to steer.
[SPEAKER_07]: A little bit, yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't do it anymore, but it was fun the first couple times to go, Anyway, did you play all the courses?
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't played them all.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I've been trying to just play them in a race and try to unlock them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love Aeropolis.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love the one on the home version.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's one of my favorite tracks, so I had to play that a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I've been playing the Outer Space one a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Green Plant is fucking crazy.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_31]: Okay, the last course is fucking crazy, and it's like four minutes long.
[SPEAKER_31]: Yeah, it's only one lap, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_31]: It's three laps.
[SPEAKER_31]: Really?
[SPEAKER_31]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_31]: Yeah, it's like, the average race on that course is like four and a half minutes.
[SPEAKER_31]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, F-Zero was cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: It got me to go to Rozo Golf Land, and when I was able to play there, it was a Thursday night, about 8 o'clock, so there weren't a lot of kids there, and it was nice and quiet, and DDR was so loud, because not a lot of games were going, and I got to play Conga Phelan on 4th Plus, and I got to blast the shit out of it, and I had so much fun playing DDR, and I haven't had that in a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I'm actually on good terms with Rozo Golf Land again, and I'm going to be going there more often.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a revival!
[SPEAKER_07]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually, I kind of want to bring back like how we used to go there once a week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of want to bring that back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just don't know when.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe Thursday nights.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then you can warn the boss of 2DX.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, actually, Scandia fixed their 2DX machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Scandia fixed some of their stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I kind of have to share time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, as of yesterday, 2DX still sucked.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: I couldn't play right side very well.
[SPEAKER_31]: I failed Deadline Light 7 because the freaking keys stuck so much.
[SPEAKER_31]: It was ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_31]: And then I ended up playing Left Side Auto Scratch so I could just pass songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty much all I have to say about my day and my week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think what we're going to do, we're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_07]: And when we come back, we'll talk a little bit more and then we'll get into the cage match.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to join our chat room, head on over to our website, www.callybombani.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Click on Orange Lounge and click on Chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: and you can join in the fun and we'll be right back in this break we're going to hear some more Max 2 USA mb3s such as where did we leave off last time we're going to hear Love at First Sight the Kylie song more deep version 2.1 who's tapping on the mic stop more deep version 2.1 and take me away into the night we're going to hear all those this break we will be back
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_22]: Take me away, find a place for you and me You're taking me higher, high as I could be Take me away, forever you and me Take me away
S, Actdeft,
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We put your thing down, flip it and reverse it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 62 in progress.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm joined tonight by my lovely co-hosts, DarkSakura and TechMassaLoki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also in the house, Puppy and ViolentHyperGirl.
[SPEAKER_07]: Black Lab, and we call him Puppy.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's not Black Lab here, he's Puppy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, yeah, it's funny when everybody starts calling me that, and then I start getting called that in person.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, see, he has a flashing foot.
[SPEAKER_07]: On DDR free.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I get the seizure foot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I may not have much longer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Arcadian 42.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I am vivid.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, we're just sitting here.
[SPEAKER_07]: We were kind of talking about Mass 2 USA earlier, and we're playing all the songs for you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have the last batch coming up the next break, which will include Will I and Tomorrow Perfume and Try To Love You.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's probably the best batch of music coming up at the end.
[SPEAKER_07]: One question that came up in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, what?
[SPEAKER_15]: How do you try to love somebody?
[SPEAKER_15]: Doesn't it just happen like diarrhea?
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe like...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even want to try and guess.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't get that trying thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're just supposed to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why don't you write Konami a letter?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: We should all write one big letter to Konami about what we think they should do with DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting question came up in the chat room, kind of going back to Max2USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: Favorite licensed song?
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um... Licensed?
[SPEAKER_08]: Favorite licensed song?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh... I'd have to say... No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Max2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Max2, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um... Actually, I'd have to say that, um...
[SPEAKER_08]: A little bit of ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought it would be very fun for the stubs, but they actually did a really good job with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's like, the slowdown in it is like era, and it's like, whoa, shit, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: ViolentHypergirl hasn't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Arcadian42, best licensed track.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_15]: The one you just played.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take me away into the night?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let them move with the best one on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let them puke.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_22]: She even seems to agree with you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love Will.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know I saw she even put it in the chat room, which is why I said it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let them boobs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys are weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chat rooms are weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: www.callybomani.com It's no silent.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course it's weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to bring this up real fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's some interesting 2DX news that hit this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys have been wondering where 2DX7 style is?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you guys want to know when...
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you guys want to know when 2DX7Style is coming out?
[SPEAKER_07]: After you vote for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the deal.
[SPEAKER_15]: And order it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But MontyStyle put out the news this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, you want to run down by it?
[SPEAKER_15]: I glanced at it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I didn't bother translating the page yet because I'm just going to order it from Himaya.
[SPEAKER_15]: But there's a big voting poll, and if enough people vote, then they're going to put out another 2DX7Style.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, and you know, I don't know if they're going to get enough.
[SPEAKER_22]: Isn't it supposed to be like 7th and 8th?
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't it supposed to be something like 7th and 8th style mixed together?
[SPEAKER_15]: That's the rumor.
[SPEAKER_15]: But you know, I'm not horribly excited.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I know that not enough people are going to vote for it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: If enough people vote for it, then it'll be good.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I'm just going to order it from Himeya anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because you already know about my trouble with Konami style.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, you don't have the right kind of credit card.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to revoke your 2DX controller order.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bite me.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what's interesting is that a lot of this came up because 2DX, they announced that they're going to make new controllers.
[SPEAKER_07]: And suddenly people went, wait a minute, Konami, why is Konami making new 2DX arcade style controllers if they haven't put out a home version forever?
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's kind of where this came about is that it was like, okay, now maybe since they're doing these controllers, they're going to do a new consumer style too.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, with the new controllers, though, then I might have to toss down the $400 to order mine from Himea.
[SPEAKER_15]: Unless you want to make me one.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll pay you to make me one.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to see the information on that, you can head on over to... I'm just going to tell you to go to BimaniStyle.com because they have the links there on their front page, which isn't loading for me right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bastards.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have the links to Konami, the site that you'll need.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, how about a cage match, you guys?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope it happens, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really want 7th Style at home.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want Beauty of Silence so bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: What makes me sad is that they'll probably cut all the licensed tracks if they're having to scrounge to do this, and that makes me a sad little panda.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where the fuck is my Dance Maniacs home version, you bastard?
[SPEAKER_15]: I just want to play Last Message at home.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like one of the few seven stars I can pass.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can pass, like, Last Message.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can pass that and Monkey Dance.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, uh, what's the other seven I can pass, Rob?
[SPEAKER_15]: Please don't go.
[SPEAKER_31]: That's what I thought.
[SPEAKER_15]: Breaking my fingers working on Love Me Do, I gave up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh my god, my finger's bleeding!
[SPEAKER_14]: I cannot play the 2DX anymore!
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh my god, I am the sock!
[SPEAKER_14]: I have no arms!
[SPEAKER_15]: What was that movie that that was from?
[SPEAKER_15]: It was called The Kids.
[SPEAKER_15]: That movie sucked, but this isn't movie discussion, this is... Oh.
[SPEAKER_10]: In response to Nostalin, the Eurobeat song sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why are you singing it?
[SPEAKER_15]: I like your Obeat.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like your... And you know, we need to do a shameless plug here for our forums that nobody goes to anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_15]: The only thing that lives on the forums anymore is the quote thread, which is... I think the last thing that I saw in the quote thread was me trying to do chat para para.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: If the forums don't work for you, at www.callybomani.com, click on forums.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can also visit our Orange Lounge Live Journal, where we post a lot of things.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we would like people to post more, so it's not just always Jamie announcing her show in the Live Journal.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's username Orange Lounge, all one word on Live Journal.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't even announce my show anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: I get DarkSakura to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so you get your minions to do it for you.
[SPEAKER_15]: My hordes of fans do my bidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: If that worked, I would do that all the time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, we're going to do the cage match.
[SPEAKER_07]: So last week...
[SPEAKER_07]: and New Orange Lounge Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I win because it went no better.
[SPEAKER_07]: The way the cage match works is that three songs get put in, you vote for your favorite, and it wins.
[SPEAKER_07]: Last week was interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because of the Comcast problems, we weren't able to get enough voters from our chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we combined their votes with in-house voting, which we haven't done in a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we're going to go back to a strictly chat room vote tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: So make sure if you want to vote in tonight's cage match, you're in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: www.calibermoney.com, click on Orange Lounge and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Last week it came down to a tie between Loki's latest remix and Jamie's song, and I picked Jamie's song because I felt bad she hadn't won in a while, and I liked her song anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got the pity vote.
[SPEAKER_07]: She got a pity vote.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki's song didn't suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: Quit saying it.
[SPEAKER_14]: He says his song sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: It didn't suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's last week's winner and the first song you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Free Fall featuring Jan Johnston, who I rather like.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this song is called Skydive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, we're only going to play a clip of it because it did win last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, here you go.
[SPEAKER_22]: Skydive
[SPEAKER_22]: All my favorites, my low end screams my name Take his hand, I'm afraid to run, run, run to you I'll be your one and only, one and only
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, that was last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jan Johnston with the band Free Fall with a song called Skydive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Next up is Loki's pick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, what did you pick for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: Guess what came out this week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep, that's right, Ayumi Trance 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's right, I picked another Ayumi Trance song because I'm lazy and I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you get to listen to Naturally, the Whippinbird mix, because Naturally is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, here it is, song number two in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Ayumi Hamasaki from Cybertrance 3 with Naturally.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoy.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, gang, that was song number two in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_07]: New entry, Ayumi Hamasaki from Cybertrans 3 with Naturally, the Wittenberg mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go around, see what the room thought of it, starting off with Who's Got a Mic?
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's Transtastic.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, 9.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, Puppy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, it's cool because it's Ayumi, but I kind of like the original.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the original naturally better, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, but this is still good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, ViolentHyperGirl.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's cool just because I like Ayumi.
[SPEAKER_07]: And on a scale of 1 to 10, you give it a... Probably like a 7 or 8.
[SPEAKER_07]: 7 or 8, so 7 and a half.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can do halves, it's acceptable.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, 7 and a half.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on, Bradley or Loki, whoever grabs the mic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bradley.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it was pretty rockin'.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not my favorite song on the new Trance CD, but it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: 8 and a half.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Motherfuckin' controller I slashed across the ground and that's bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, I give it a... I don't give a crap because I picked it randomly out of the CD I downloaded, so... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I give it a 9.
9.
[SPEAKER_07]: I give the third sex a 10!
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so there you have it, the votes for Yumi Hamasaki with Naturally.
[SPEAKER_07]: But remember, the ultimate decision is up to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: and head on over to our chat room, www.callybomani.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Click on orange.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mental note, or you can write this down somewhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: Flash game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ferret sex, the flash game.
[SPEAKER_07]: When the website comes up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll work on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: When we get our other website up, which we've been needing to do for a month.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or even just like an animated gif or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: What, puppy?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, next up is my pick, and I've got, I assure you, what will go down in history, it's a Rob Classic pick tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I'm afraid, I asked, now, don't blame me, because I asked the room, do you want my pick tonight to be something trance, or something booty and foul?
[SPEAKER_07]: And they picked booty and foul, so, this is the song you get.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this is something, if my baby mama can make solo bass, I think this song can make solo bass.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this is my pick for tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a group call, and I have to thank the Ice Queen.
[SPEAKER_07]: He recommended this one to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ice Queen recommended me to this one.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is Fanny Pack with a song called Camel Toe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Camel Toe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm... Yes, these are my cups.
[SPEAKER_17]: Outro Music
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, that was the last song in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_07]: My pick, Fanny Pack with Camel Toe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you Ice Queen for picking that one out for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie!
[SPEAKER_15]: That was so ghetto booty.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god, Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, you need to be spanked for that song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not by me, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll talk to somebody who's not here tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: On a scale of 1 to 10?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't think that numbers can quantify it.
[SPEAKER_15]: It gets a B for booty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I guess it translates to an 8.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, Erin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Erin.
[SPEAKER_10]: 8 for good laughs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Puppies!
[SPEAKER_08]: Just the fact that the name of the song is Camel Toad is ridiculous in itself.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: What next?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, next thing you know, there's going to be a song called Blue Balls.
[SPEAKER_07]: There may well be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie's threatening to write it right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be the next Politary song.
[SPEAKER_07]: The next remix I make will be...
[SPEAKER_07]: Insert song name here.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Blues Balls Mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, it'd be even better if it was a blues song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let Puppy finish his thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a thought?
[SPEAKER_08]: He has to give a number.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't know I would... 3.159.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, Bradley.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just because.
[SPEAKER_05]: Best song ever, 10, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, yeah, you know, the white in me says seven, but the ghetto black in me says ten.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what's that average, too?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nine point nine?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, er, nine, wait, nine and a half.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's recap.
[SPEAKER_07]: For those of you that haven't voted before, you have to send a private message to me in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to send it over private message or it doesn't count.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you say it publicly in the room, it doesn't count.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I know we have some new chatters in there tonight, so I'll type out how you do that for those of you that don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: And sorry, but you can't vote for Holic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's recap, shall we, real fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: Song number one, last week's winner, Free Fall featuring Janz Johnston with Skydive.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, song number two that you can vote for tonight is Yumi Hamasaki from Cybertrans 3 with a song called Naturally.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, and song number three you can vote for tonight is a band called Fanny Pack with the song Camel Toe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm, I wonder what's gonna win.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, vote now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Place vote now!
[SPEAKER_07]: In the meantime, Loki, why don't you tell us what's going on in the sim world?
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn piece of wire doesn't want to go through my hole.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, in the controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hole in the controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: Asian, I kid you not, Asian mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: All the music in it must be sung by an Asian singer.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it has to be, you know, in, you know, Japanese or, you know, Chinese, Korean.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's, it's, it's trying to, um, they're trying to basically spark interest for Turning Mix 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: So basically this is going to be the, this is going to be the poorly run, um, Stepchild that's in the middle.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: For this Asian mix, it better be really, really good Japanese or Korean songs, because we all know where Chinese pop went, or is going, and, you know... But it seems like, judging from the last remix, a lot of people don't have that good a song taste.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, technically, you can have Russian music, too, because part of Russia is in Asia.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we can have Tattoo!
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, and obviously, the only good, honestly the only good Chinese songs there are, are basically slow songs and some trance slash techno, but not much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I haven't listened to Tide Pops though, not very much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, India's in Asia too, so Dollar Mendy all around.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tunak, Tunak, Tunak.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, get over Tunak Tunak already.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: That song is fucking used.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, hello and welcome to a joke that is fucking moldy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sick of Tunak Tunak.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's play Magic the Gathering and listen to our, you know, Lilith Fair music while we, you know...
[SPEAKER_07]: You mean Dungeons and Dragons?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, what useless songs are going to come out of this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, it's horrid.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to see a gazillion Ayumi songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you think I'm going to jump off my ass to make you your stupid Max 2 USA license tracks, think again.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't care because I haven't played Step Mania in three months and I am not going to make your stupid tracks.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you're going to have to wait for DDRUK to make them because they're good at everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though I made them the last two times and they took credit.
[SPEAKER_06]: to a credit because they said, oh, they were out of sync.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're out of sync.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not just that Yumi songs.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's probably going to be a lot of stupid Pop Finkel, SES, Shinhwa songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Last call for cage match votes in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have a challenge to issue.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want Dragon Ash or Malice Miser.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would love to see some visual K done or...
[SPEAKER_15]: I would love to see just some good, you know, uber goth J-rock make it into the turning mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: See how they pull that off.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, you know, have like the Beast of Blood video playing in the background or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: What am I going to do with it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like this?
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Would you guys like to hear who got the cage match tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because we have collected all the votes.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I just try to wrap it up quick now because we tend to do FUs in cage match back-to-back, and I have to close out all the private messages for FUs as if you needed to know that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't gotten any more votes.
[SPEAKER_07]: So here is tonight's winner.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys ready for it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is a tie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, lovely.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, the way the rules go is that the host whose song did not tie will break the tie.
[SPEAKER_07]: And tonight, song one, song one that tied was Camel Toe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Figures.
[SPEAKER_07]: Song number two that tied tonight was... If the damn thing will play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me guess, a Yumi?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it was a Yumi.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it means... So it goes, Jamie gets to break the tie.
[SPEAKER_07]: And she gets to break the tie, and hopefully she remembers the favor I gave her last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: But not to influence her vote or anything.
[SPEAKER_15]: Give it to the butt.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give it to Camel Toe?
[SPEAKER_07]: Give it to the booty.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, Camel Toe is this week's cage match winner.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, Camel Toe wins by a vote of one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I also call.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: That be the FU music for the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, that will be the FU music for the chat room tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, if you want to visit our webcam, www.callybomondi.com, click on Orange Lounge and click on Chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: The site you can see on the cam right now is Puppy hunched over with a microphone, Loki soldering in the background, Aaron has been on and off the cam, and Jamie hides from the cam, so she randomly holds objects up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, guess what's coming up when we take this break, kids?
[SPEAKER_07]: After this break.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on, we do it every week.
[SPEAKER_07]: FUs.
[SPEAKER_07]: We all know it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why do we have to guess?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's the fun part.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_15]: I have a microphone now, so just play my damn music.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we're not doing any FUs yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're taking a break first.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: In this break, we're going to hear more Max 2 USA music, and this is a lot of... You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't understand why they don't just let me pick all the music.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: For Max 2?
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: I meant, like, in general.
[SPEAKER_15]: I should, like, petition Konami to let me pick everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: The only thing that some of those songs are good for being picked for is, like, picking noses.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're all really good songs, though, so go ahead and play them.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: In this break, you're going to hear a lot of songs that were requested.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tomorrow, Perfume in this break, Will I, and SFMP with Try To Love You.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell a friend we're on the air.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be back after this.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_24]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_20]: Will I ever love you again?
[SPEAKER_22]: Will we be together again?
[SPEAKER_22]: Thought the love we had was strong
[SPEAKER_22]: Tell me what's wrong What did we go wrong?
[SPEAKER_22]: No, no, nobody's love, no, nobody's love, no, nobody's love, yeah, baby, love
[SPEAKER_22]: Bitch, get a new song.
[SPEAKER_27]: An open letter from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio episode number 62 in progress.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Jamie, do you know what time it is?
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I don't have the music queued up yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're supposed to take longer than that to answer the question.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's time for me to throw a ferret at puppy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, now I'm ready.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, what time is it?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh-uh, you're no fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: You weren't ready.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's time for me to get a ferret thrown at my hand.
[SPEAKER_15]: Stop throwing ferrets at me!
[SPEAKER_00]: I haven't really had that bad of a week, but... Okay, stop that.
[SPEAKER_13]: First off, a big F you goes to Puppy for throwing a ferret at my boob.
[SPEAKER_13]: And for throwing a ferret at ViolentHyperGirl's ass.
[SPEAKER_13]: But you were the target.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it's your fault.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's your fault for... Stop it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Another one goes for the rice I was cooking for being too wet.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's my fault because I put in too much water.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't help it, you know, the rice was just so hot.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it couldn't help being moist, you know, because I was touching it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was rolling it around and making balls with it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, another F you goes to being hot, because I am right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Another one goes toward my laundry for not being dry, so I'm drying it again.
[SPEAKER_15]: Another F you goes toward ferret sex.
[SPEAKER_15]: Another F you goes toward all the people who are not signed up for my message board.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's roleplay.darksakura.com
[SPEAKER_15]: I think I'm going to throw on there, by the way, a sexual roleplay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to make it hidden for all of you people who are into the kinky crap.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's going to be one for tops and one for bottoms.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then the sadomasochism.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll throw that in there, too.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's forthcoming.
[SPEAKER_15]: Other than that, I'm really... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fuck the sheriff who was...
[SPEAKER_15]: Freaking following me and tailgating me.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then it passed me.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I was going to speed limit.
[SPEAKER_15]: I freaking hate the double standard.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then the tow truck.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's not one of those typical tow trucks.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is one of the ones with the flatbed.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like huger than God truck.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it was right on my ass the whole time here.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was like, okay, you need to get off.
[SPEAKER_15]: You are not a hemorrhoid.
[SPEAKER_15]: I am too young.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then, um...
[SPEAKER_15]: Really, I think that's about it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yeah, a big FU goes to my sleep pattern, which is going to hopefully be corrected.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I got a really cool hat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, next up is Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, anyways, I think I'm wrapped around you here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm trying to get to my first FU here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just have to find something.
[SPEAKER_07]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, can you turn down the music, like, off?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, first FU of the week goes to Konami, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Mainly the group System SF.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know who the fuck you think you are, but I don't like you blatantly ripping off other songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really, I don't.
[SPEAKER_07]: This piracy stuff has to stop.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, this song I'm going to play for you is by another group.
[SPEAKER_07]: with a very similar name to System SF.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's called System F. They predated you by five years.
[SPEAKER_07]: So here's their song.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's also their very big hit song called Out of the Blue.
[SPEAKER_07]: See if this sounds familiar.
Out of the Blue
[SPEAKER_26]: What kind of disco was it?
[SPEAKER_26]: I don't know, could it be something that was maybe on, I don't know, Be Rare 5?
Something that's gonna make people scream.
Star, Star, what's it called?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's freaking feelings won't fade, you goddamn retards.
[SPEAKER_07]: You didn't do anything to change the song at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: You blatantly stole it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't say that you covered it because, well, there's no singing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come up with some original shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure Look to the Skies will probably rip off of something else, but I have to find it first.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you're lucky for now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm about to expose you.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyways, yes, I am very pissed off at the fact that you blatantly ripped off Out of the Blue.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, that's enough of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And sorry about the Bumani Cell thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another F you to them for having their goddamn music on their front page.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate that goddamn music.
[SPEAKER_07]: Be like DDR Mania X and keep it turned off, unless I want it turned on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or changes to something else, you know, something catchy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, FU... One little comment, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: I thought that the whole deal of having, you know, music play on your main page went out when people stopped using GeoCities.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it came back with people using Flash on their pages.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um... It came back with Zynga.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Shockwave, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyways, no, but mine still rocks, other than their little music.
[SPEAKER_07]: Change the music and you'll be perfect.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um... An FU for, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see, first off, for the stages at RVGL still being kind of slanted.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of not quite flat, so that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to the fact that, let's see, I don't know, I'm not too angsty.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to the stupid drivers because I hate you everywhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's all types of drivers and I think I yelled at you all today.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to quote Jahi on this one.
[SPEAKER_07]: A hole in your muffler does not make a modification.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, but anyways, um... F you to, uh... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got thrown off when people start talking.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: After you, the stupid bitch that, like, ran over our curb at work, it, like, um, totally shattered it all, and now my friend's probably gonna get blamed for it, because, you know, they have a giant bus, and, you know, it's gonna look like the bus ran over it, even though it's the delivery man, so that kinda sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, fuck you, the G4, because, um, you still suck, you haven't heeded any of my advice, and, you know, you can burn in hell.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't even have any new programming.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're talking about what happened at E3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: E3's been over for a while now.
[SPEAKER_07]: E3 is not breaking news, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: And to say that you have new daily content is a lie anyways, because you film your shows like once every month.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then repeat them over and over and over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, playing full motion video, or not necessarily full motion video, but playing...
[SPEAKER_07]: Video game screenshots to music does not constitute a show.
[SPEAKER_07]: So please stop.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, um... What the hell are you... They're eating Mike and Ike's with chopsticks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop being Asian.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't think she can help that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not talking about puppies.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, um... Uh... Yeah...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, F you to our racist neighbor.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have anything to bitch about right now because it doesn't come to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_07]: This song makes me want to eat some beef.
[SPEAKER_07]: My FUs are pretty quick this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: FU to the fact that everything in this goddamn town closes so early.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate that shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I know I've said FU about this before, but I'm saying it again because it's still true.
[SPEAKER_07]: This town sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, that's my first FU.
[SPEAKER_07]: My second FU goes to two things that happened in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's the Folsom Street Fair, which happened today.
[SPEAKER_07]: That happened today in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the Castro Street Fair, which happens next Sunday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why does this shit happen on a Sunday?
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't go if you have this stuff on a Sunday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have it on a Saturday.
[SPEAKER_07]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: And your town is dirty.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I know a lot of people live in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like our number one market, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: The town is dirty.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure it's not you guys that listen to Horizons Radio to make it dirty.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the other million people living there.
[SPEAKER_07]: We can't pick up their trash.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's gross.
[SPEAKER_07]: Frisco's a gross city.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god, do a million people really live in San Francisco?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's actually 700,000, but I'm counting the surrounding area a little bit too.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's why I'm glad I don't live there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Screw you, San Francisco, and your stupid planning.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rest of the room's turn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's start with Puppy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Puppy.
[SPEAKER_31]: Whoa, I almost did not catch the microphone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are we having like a porn DVD slideshow on the camera or something?
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn, FUs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, um, fuck you to class starting because it's class and that's just the way it is.
[SPEAKER_31]: And, um, fuck you to my bike for like being really crappy.
[SPEAKER_31]: and fucking through the tree outside over the parking lot at my apartment complex because it made my car really fucking dirty with a whole bunch of sap and tree shit.
[SPEAKER_31]: and, um, um, hmm.
[SPEAKER_31]: Fuck Ikea, because of the press sawdust crap.
[SPEAKER_31]: And fuck Scandia for going to shit.
[SPEAKER_31]: And, yeah, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_31]: RKDN.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, okay, uh, fuck you to general stupidity, especially when it's my own, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, fuck you to stupid telemarketers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I gotta, I, cause I, on Tuesday, I got a call.
[SPEAKER_07]: I, I have to now, I have to pick up the phone, cause people might call me now.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, I might have to talk to people.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I pick up the phone, and it says, please, we have no available operators.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please wait for the next operator.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate that shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: So fucking stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I had to hang up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hung up before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Idiots.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, anything else to say fuck you to?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_30]: Fuck you for doing it right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I think I'm out of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I might think of something, so go ahead.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aaron.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't have a lot this week, actually, but, um, Fuck You goes to whoever broke the wheel on the initial D-machine at the MU Arcade.
[SPEAKER_10]: It, thanks to you, it no longer has the 270 degrees in either direction.
[SPEAKER_10]: It goes... Yes, it spins freely!
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just like RTA all over again.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think I know, I think it was one of those fat teenie bop, fat like high school teenie boppers I saw there on like Friday afternoon.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm not for sure.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was broken a couple days ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh no, it wasn't broken, trust me.
[SPEAKER_10]: It wasn't bro- was it?
[SPEAKER_22]: I was there on Friday morning.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I was there before that, I think.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Haku goes to Workload English 57 for being exactly like high school?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't like group work, I don't like the teacher, and I hate it, and I want to get out of there as fast as possible.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck you, those stupid neighbors who live outside me who are always either blasting the music or trying to be ghetto thugs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Be yourselves for once.
[SPEAKER_10]: Come on now.
[SPEAKER_10]: They are ghetto thugs.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're trying to act like ghetto thugs.
[SPEAKER_10]: And... I can't really think of any...
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, and fuck you to that stupid skillet that my parents gave me that doesn't actually work.
[SPEAKER_10]: It just happens to burn everything that you put in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because it's metal and it's not cast iron.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's move on and see what our chat room has to say, shall we?
[SPEAKER_07]: Brack2000 would like to say, F you to Overloaded, the Lesson 2 song, not being a real DDR Max 2 song, and only a stupid Lesson Mode song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh-oh, VHG needs to respond to something in the showroom.
[SPEAKER_10]: Someone asked why I'm in workload English.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's because I got cocky on my subject A, and I didn't put a thesis in my essay, so now I'm stuck there, and my friends are in workload English.
[SPEAKER_10]: Biohazard has a lot of these cheeses.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck me for missing Orange Lounge Radio for three weeks.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck Overloaded for being so owns-or.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck Chex Quest.
[SPEAKER_07]: These are coming from Biohazard.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck 2DX controllers being so expensive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck my CD burner for being broken.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck my QX949 for its bad mid-left front channel capacitor.
[SPEAKER_07]: Capacitor, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: I read that wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry!
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck my terrible C++ compiler.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck the guy who sold me a wireless PS2 controller and just cut the cord off a regular controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_22]: Did Loki, was that you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Biohazard also says, fuck my jelly bean tin having a finite supply on jelly bellies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck HAPP controllers for wanting $12.99 for a 2DX style button.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck peeps who talk like this.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is Asian writing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, ASEAN writing.
[SPEAKER_07]: And expect me to read it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck really negative people.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's funny, regardless of how old these people are, they still talk like they're in middle school.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just pay the money for the half controls button.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought like 16 of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get over it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: HK Holly, Aaron would like to read this one.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is mostly an inside joke from Calibimani, but fuck you, green vaginal ooze.
[SPEAKER_07]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_07]: Vaginal ooze is funny when it's green, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boy, oh boy.
[SPEAKER_07]: 23rd Magus would like to say, F you to Angel's fucked up work schedule.
[SPEAKER_07]: She misses the show again.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to forgetting to wake my dad up in time to get a ride to the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: You missed food.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am to suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: No comment.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to hatching a pouring egg, naming it, giving it a backpack, and then forgetting to feed it.
[SPEAKER_07]: 20k down the hole.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a Ragnarok reference.
[SPEAKER_07]: And once again, fuck the lamers on Ragnarok Online.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or PLZ.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's a PLZ?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you want me to heal the monster you're fighting?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have an F you.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know if you just said it because I was in the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_15]: A big fuck you goes to Botters on Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate you all.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I hope that your computers explode and you all catch Stars of the Ass.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chaos says F you to Heartburn.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Heartburn does suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: NoStylin says, my FU of the week is paying bills.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like you have bills and you pay them off and you have more of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you wonder where the hell they came from.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I go, huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: You pay bills and more come.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I find how once you get money, it's gone in a second.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, screw the government.
[SPEAKER_07]: Screw Gray Davis and this whole recall thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: And screw expensive schools that try to rip you off with name brand products which you don't have.
[SPEAKER_07]: Screw you to the recall.
[SPEAKER_07]: Governor and the recall?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: One or the other?
[SPEAKER_07]: Screw you to anything involving the recall.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just go away.
[SPEAKER_05]: It involves him.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tal would like to say F you to Final Fantasy Tactics Advance because I don't actually own the game or the Game Boy Advance so I have to borrow both.
[SPEAKER_07]: You moocher!
[SPEAKER_07]: You have my DDR Max and you have someone else's Tactics and Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mooch!
[SPEAKER_07]: And you have Jamie's Parappa.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Moochie the Moocher here on Orson Welles Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mooch.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's so bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's in Davis.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's where he's supposed to be from.
[SPEAKER_07]: Talon also likes to say, F you to initial D. I know you love me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because the music and the animation style sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the story is straight out of a bad samurai movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: and FU to my DVD drive for dying.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for playing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so I think we'll take another break.
[SPEAKER_07]: We exhausted all our new Max MP3s, so why don't we go back and visit Max USA 1?
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll go back and visit that.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to play some songs from Max 1 USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to get stabbed with a pitchfork.
[SPEAKER_07]: What am I getting stabbed with if I play Sandstorm?
[SPEAKER_07]: Chopsticks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we're going to start this break off with Sandstorm.
[SPEAKER_07]: And after that, we'll hear some other things from Max USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: Daughters die.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for sharing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Find it from my message board.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be back after this break.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_07]: How about Ask Orange Lounge when we come back?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure!
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, the chat room has some questions, so send your questions now for Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: And for the 5,000th time, we'll play Overloaded after the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've already played it tonight during the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm going to overload you in a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ask Orange Lounge
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, drop the bombs
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_28]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 62 in progress.
[SPEAKER_07]: As promised, we're going to do Ask Orange Lounge, so send your questions to us now in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anybody have any quick thoughts, any other Bimani related things they wanted to talk about before we get into Ask Orange Lounge?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any interesting Bimani stories?
[SPEAKER_15]: I have a question to ask the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_15]: Is it safe?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it safe?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you have to send your questions over private message or they aren't counted.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, real fast, just to plug some of our other programming on Orange Lodge Radio, bringing you live programming more throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tomorrow night is Vanilla Sky featuring myself and my cohorts in Crime Rice Princess and Lanky Style.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we just sit around and we talk about other video games and we kind of talk about other weird stuff too.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll talk about what's in the news and how it relates to our world and things that piss us off.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my God, you read the news.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Yahoo, yes, we read the news to our listeners because they aren't going to get it any other way.
[SPEAKER_07]: and we make fun of Yahoo and we do video game trivia to bad music and all sorts of fun things like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So tune in at 7 o'clock Monday night Pacific time.
[SPEAKER_07]: On Tuesday nights... Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was a peanut burp.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, Tuesday night is Pump Up the Volume.
[SPEAKER_15]: where I play your requests from our chat room.
[SPEAKER_15]: Except the thing is nobody requests anything, god damn it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's okay, more songs you get to play for yourself.
[SPEAKER_15]: So you get to, I'll basically partake in my really weird taste in music.
[SPEAKER_15]: I used to do a show called Ice for Five Minutes.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's it on the channel.
[SPEAKER_07]: This week on Orange Lounge Radio on Thursday, I will do a show called Ice...
[SPEAKER_07]: Pikachu Pikachu Pikachu Pikachu
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: No!
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously!
[SPEAKER_06]: A new show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't get the mic any closer.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're away.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, so, the new show.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's gonna be a game show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, a game show!
[SPEAKER_06]: My favorite!
[SPEAKER_07]: A new... Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: As long as there's nothing in the box.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, you can have the box.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, new game show, possibly, if I decide I don't want to do Livewire anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: It will be, there will actually be prizes, serious, like real prizes given away.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what kind of game show will this be?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do we know yet?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something crazy, very crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to call it like, attention... Why are the girls yelling for porn?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, it was either going to be called something like...
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_07]: Like the 10 second attention span show or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_15]: Porn!
[SPEAKER_15]: Back to my show, which I am still...
[SPEAKER_15]: It starts at 7 o'clock is the pre-show.
[SPEAKER_15]: At 7.30 the show begins to 10.30.
[SPEAKER_15]: And basically I just play a bunch of crap.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I've been saying that I'm going to do video game music trivia, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: People, send me songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I'll have my IRC open.
[SPEAKER_15]: My name is DarkSakuraSSF.
[SPEAKER_15]: So start sending me video game music if you want to play.
[SPEAKER_15]: If not, then you're a big stinky poopy head.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that's the bottom line, because DarkSakura said so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wednesday nights are open.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was following the example of our, you know, Baymani influence system SF.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wednesday nights are open right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: We do a bit of randomness on Wednesdays.
[SPEAKER_07]: This week, I've been asked to do Orange Lounge Presents Trivial Pursuit on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Which we might do, I don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know there's enough interest from the regulars on all the shows to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: If I was playing that, we'd have to break out the Genis edition.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm thinking we're going to do Trivial Pursuit on Wednesday, but stay tuned to our chatroom for details.
[SPEAKER_07]: So drop in our chatroom sometime during the week, and we'll have a Trivial Pursuit this Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're not in the chatroom, you're not cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, if you're not in our chatroom 24 hours a day, you're not cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: When I visit, like, maybe once a week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if you're not there 24 hours a day, you're not cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you're there 24-hour days, you don't have a life.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then you're not cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a paradox.
[SPEAKER_07]: What a fun thought.
[SPEAKER_14]: Either way, you're a loser.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thursday night, Snowden's Lounge Radio is hiatus right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: We might be doing some repeats of Livewire.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I get brave, I might do a new mix, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, there might be another potential.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did one mega mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: It played after Vanilla Sky one week.
[SPEAKER_15]: There might be another potential goodie, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm, a goodie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, yes, we have another show that may be coming up soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, maybe not this Thursday, but soon.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which, you know, I think that we need to introduce one of our newer listeners as another foreign correspondent.
[SPEAKER_15]: Even though he probably can't make it up here.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's probably not listening.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think he's listening.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's not in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_15]: Make sure he's here next week.
[SPEAKER_15]: He doesn't get foreign correspondent status.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll give him a proper introduction next week if he shows up.
[SPEAKER_07]: In the meantime, we've only got 20 minutes left of show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, no, 25 because we started late tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have plenty of questions that have already been submitted.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not too late if you want to join in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go into www.callybomani.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Break out the earplugs because Rob's going to sing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Click on Orange Lounge and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you can submit a question for Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have to listen to Rob sing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a good question.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob's going to sing all week this week on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie needs to stop playing with a fucking ferret.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or I'm going to get Loki to shove it up her ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Biohazard has about seven questions.
[SPEAKER_13]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Biohazard has about seven questions to ask tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Has about seven questions to ask.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: He's turning red in the face.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm starting off with questions from Biohazard.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob!
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob!
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why doesn't Jimmy crack carrots or potatoes or something?
[SPEAKER_07]: Corn is so boring.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why doesn't Jimmy just do crack?
[SPEAKER_07]: Good, I like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Biohazard also wants to know, how long will I have to wait for Overloaded to be available on Bomani Style or acquire it some other way?
[SPEAKER_07]: Excuse me, are we Bomani Style?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, are we Bomani Style?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's already a sim file up and it sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't get it.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're not the Monty style.
[SPEAKER_15]: Go ask them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, go ask them.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you were a member of our Orange Lounge Radio Live Journal community, you would have already gotten a link to that file.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki posted it earlier this week, didn't he?
[SPEAKER_07]: Who cares about the step file?
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make your own damn step file.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, and why he cracks corn so you don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's so boring, you don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, we missed you on the first part.
[SPEAKER_15]: People got a lot of free time if they're coming up with questions like, why does Jimmy crack corn and not potatoes?
[SPEAKER_15]: You can't crack potatoes anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll read one more from Biohazard, then I'm going to somebody else.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll come back to the rest of his questions.
[SPEAKER_07]: Biohazard wants to know, how would I write a script for Sis Reset to display a random line from a TXT file every time exclamation bad joke is pulled?
[SPEAKER_15]: Do what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Is that like a chatbot?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's some nerdy chatbot thing, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, you're not in our chatroom because we don't allow chatbots.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, you know, you can go... I don't know, blow a gorilla.
[SPEAKER_32]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who was that anyway?
[SPEAKER_07]: Biohazard, again.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't use the chatbots.
[SPEAKER_15]: We will kick you if you do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Biohazard also wants to know, because Aaron really wants to answer this, so I'll do one more.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why get mad when you can get glad?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you know, I don't really know, but what I say is, why get mad when you can just use that energy and put it into sex?
[SPEAKER_13]: Why get mad?
[SPEAKER_13]: Get horny!
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't get mad, get violent!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, it's Violent Horny Girl here on Orange Lounge Radio, VHG.
[SPEAKER_07]: Special guest, Violent Horny Girl.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: PPGL1.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn it, I'm not original.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I was the first to call you Violent Hyper Gangbang, was I not?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Violent Horny Gangbang.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, Violent Horny Gangbang.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Variation.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about Velvet Horny Gangbang?
[SPEAKER_15]: Violence is more fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: 23rd Magus would like to know, how's the food... Ah, who cares?
[SPEAKER_07]: Be nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: How's the food over there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because we all ate tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, no one's dead yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: The food was good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, hairball.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the food's gone, so it was eaten.
[SPEAKER_10]: At best, it was at least tolerable if it's all gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Jamie makes a sad face.
[SPEAKER_07]: The eel was interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've never really had eel in that mass quantity before.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if I necessarily like the fiber, but it was good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't even notice really it was eel, because I ate it with chicken, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, see, I had just straight up eel.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a little weird for me, but it was good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well, maybe that's why.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was good, though, and I appreciate Jamie's effort to cook for us because, you know, we're single and don't cook.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least I don't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to make sure you guys have proper nutrition.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're eating instant rice and, like, super bacon.
[SPEAKER_15]: You are going to... I haven't had super bacon in a good two weeks.
[SPEAKER_15]: And still, I've seen what's in your fridge, and there's hardly anything in there.
[SPEAKER_15]: What do you guys live off of?
[SPEAKER_15]: Pop-Tarts?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: For one week, I challenge you.
[SPEAKER_15]: You need to eat the same things that I do for a week.
[SPEAKER_32]: Oh, give me a break.
[SPEAKER_15]: What I eat is very, very easy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Very easy.
[SPEAKER_15]: You have to have a bowl of oatmeal in the morning.
Ew.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let me lick mud.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki said, let me lick mud.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maple, maples, the brown sugar and maple instant oatmeal is really good.
[SPEAKER_15]: and Yoplait Yogurt is really good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, no, it's for old people.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, no, it's for people who like to shit.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, you like to shit?
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's TMI Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's why old people eat it, but it's good for like your... It's fiber.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fiber's good for you.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then for lunch, you need to have like a microwave dinner because they're really good.
[SPEAKER_15]: and veggie burgers for dinner every night.
[SPEAKER_32]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Veggie cheeseburger.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have veggie burgers for lunch.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, that's good.
[SPEAKER_15]: But see, one week.
[SPEAKER_15]: One week.
[SPEAKER_15]: No Pop-Tarts.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually, I don't eat Pop-Tarts, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't like Pop-Tarts.
[SPEAKER_07]: I usually have either a Nutri-Grain bar in the morning or, like, I won't eat breakfast until when I get to work on a bag of pretzels.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's not good for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I try Nutri-Grain bars, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's usually what I eat.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have my super hot chocolate when I get to work.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's three bags of hot chocolate concentrated and then I put a little bit of hot water in there so it's like super frothy.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all I eat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everything is super with you.
[SPEAKER_07]: 23rd Magazine would also like to know.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: The thing I used to have when I worked at this stupid temp agency that no longer exists in my universe.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would have half a cup of super strong coffee and then pour the rest of it in hot chocolate and then throw in like five packs of sugar.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that was what I would drink every morning.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's healthy.
[SPEAKER_15]: See, I don't drink that crap anymore.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've been off of my soda now for a week, so I'm happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: 23rd Magus would like to also know Sky, that's me, could you give me my jokes back please?
[SPEAKER_15]: What, all three of them?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you wish you could be as cool as me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, he has negative jokes now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Campbell Soup, one of our new chatters, unless it's somebody who changed their name, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Campbell Soup would like to know, what's up with the foam on beer?
[SPEAKER_07]: Good question.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's what makes you fart.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki has a comment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why is beer better than women?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because no matter how you pour it, you always have good head.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did a magasism.
[SPEAKER_07]: He doesn't tell R-rated jokes, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why is there foam on beer?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just the way God made it, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: But all I have to say is don't drink beer, drink Guinness.
[SPEAKER_15]: Beard tastes like... pee smells.
[SPEAKER_07]: Foam is there to remind you that you're wasting your time, and if you want to get fucked up, just drink some hard liquor.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go straight for the 151, or the Schlager, or Everclear.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, alcohol recipe of the week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Apple pie.
[SPEAKER_07]: The foam is there to remind you that you're a pussy, you're drinking beer.
[SPEAKER_15]: You get a big glass gallon jug of apple juice.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then you pour it all out in another container.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then you pour in about half a bottle of Everclear and let cinnamon sticks dissolve in it.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then you pour in the apple juice and let it sit for like a couple days.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you have apple pie.
[SPEAKER_07]: 23rd Magus says beer goes down easy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'd like to know, is that the beer or the beer bottle in your case?
[SPEAKER_15]: Beer is nasty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I'm mean.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so mean.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yours does smell nasty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pip would like to know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, this is a good one.
[SPEAKER_07]: And another new chatter, or at least a name I don't recognize.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pip would like to know, how did the ferret get into the show?
[SPEAKER_15]: Ferret's been here since day one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, we've been throwing it around and having the ferrets rape each other.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mad ferret sex.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, ferret number one was a birthday gift to me from my old stalker.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I just, I have all these stuffed animals.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you shut the goddamn thing up for one minute while I tell the story?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's the ferret story, he's contributing.
[SPEAKER_07]: We used to have, or I still do, I have all my stuffed animals on top of the computer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I know you can't really see it on the webcam, but there's all these stuffed animals that sit on top of the computer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, Carmen, oh, Bradley's turning the thing over so you can see the stuffed animals.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have like Cartman, and Pikachu, and like a little stuffed devil.
[SPEAKER_07]: My happy birthday bear that Jamie got me, and all this stuff here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, it just went up to the cam, so there you go, you guys can look.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the ferret used to sit there, and one day Jamie pulled it down and started pushing the button and learned that it'd make noises.
[SPEAKER_07]: And behold, the show got worse.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Loki found a second ferret at some random store and he brought it over to some show a while back.
[SPEAKER_15]: They sell them at Walgreens so everyone can have a ferret of their own.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: HK Holly would like to know Can vegetarians eat animal crackers?
[SPEAKER_15]: As long as they're not made out of animal parts.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's an interesting question.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would say yes, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I know some vegetarians who do eat animal crackers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially, you know what's good are those animal crackers with the frosting on them and the little balls.
[SPEAKER_07]: The mother's crackers, you know what I'm talking about?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yes, the mother's cookies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mother's animal cookies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Those are the best.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes they are.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wouldn't care if I was vegan, I'd still eat them.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're so fattening though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just reminded of an old question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do vegans swallow?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Too much.
[SPEAKER_07]: I used to date a vegan.
[SPEAKER_13]: Whale.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Tal says, as a vegetarian, he would just like to say, yes, he can eat animal cookies.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's your question.
[SPEAKER_07]: You learn something new on Orange Lounge Radio every day.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're still accepting questions for Ask Orange Lounge, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just send them over private message to Sky in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, we still have a few left.
[SPEAKER_07]: Biohazard sent me plenty to get us through a whole other show.
[SPEAKER_07]: www.caliabomani.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Click on Orange Lounge and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nostylan, oh god.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually a good question.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: How come you guys don't play more Eurobeat?
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess my theory would be because to a lot of people who don't know Eurobeat, it all sounds exactly the same.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nostylan also says there should be a Bomani Eurobeat hour.
[SPEAKER_10]: No!
[SPEAKER_10]: God, no!
[SPEAKER_10]: What the hell is wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_07]: What was the question?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why doesn't Orange Lounge Radio play more Eurobeat?
[SPEAKER_07]: We can play more Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie's done Eurobeat pre-shows.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've done, like, hours of Eurobeat on my show, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Tune into Jamie's show, because she's the biggest Eurobeat fan.
[SPEAKER_15]: I did, like, a two-hour marathon of Eurobeat a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: If you don't think we play enough Eurobeat, you're listening to the wrong shows.
[SPEAKER_07]: Listen to Tuesday night's Pump Up the Volume.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am not vegan.
[SPEAKER_07]: God no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like I have that kind of discipline.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of my exes is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: He made this really good eggplant stuff at a party at my house.
[SPEAKER_15]: And nobody ate it but you and I. Well, I ate, like, lots of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_07]: John Fields would like to know, what do you call a river that's too big for its bridges?
[SPEAKER_15]: You need to shut up right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was the worst pun ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a pun straight out of 23rd Magus' book.
[SPEAKER_07]: You owe Magus a quarter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give him a quarter for stealing the bill.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pay them royalties and we'll stick the RIA on you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take it now.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll stick the RIA on you if you don't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nostylan has another question.
[SPEAKER_07]: God.
[SPEAKER_07]: What came first, the egg or the chicken?
[SPEAKER_07]: Depends on your religion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, in that sentence, the egg came first in your sentence, so... Yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get a mic.
[SPEAKER_07]: The chicken and egg rhetorical question is the dumbest thing ever because it's not actually a rhetorical question.
[SPEAKER_07]: They did not specify what type of an egg it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: Therefore, dinosaurs predated chickens.
[SPEAKER_07]: Therefore, the egg came first.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was deep.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was deep like a puddle.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was so deep.
[SPEAKER_07]: Going back to Biohazard's questions, because that's all the questions we have left, unless people send more over private messages to Sky.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think that it's safe?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're listening to the show, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_07]: The chatroom's talking about their vegetarian stints.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have actually had a vegetarian stint.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was vegetarian for about a month.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to bet doing it.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is like, as of April, made two years that I've gone without beef or pork on a regular basis.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've, you know, had a nibble now and then, but I've stayed off of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would like to say I have not drank regular soda in about six months.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I need to cut back on diet, though, because I do drink diet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Diet is worse for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't smoked a cigarette in four years.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I haven't smoked a cigarette in five and a half years.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't smoked a cigarette in a week.
[SPEAKER_15]: You are so square.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, aren't I?
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Biohazard would also like to know, why haven't I heard any ferrets yet?
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you burn them?
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously we have not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Those fucking ferrets won't go away.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks, thanks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's a somewhat serious question from Biohazard.
[SPEAKER_07]: Biohazard would like to know, why can't we vote for Holic?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because we said so, and we are the authority.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I have the real answer to the question.
[SPEAKER_07]: Holic is already in rotation on the station.
[SPEAKER_07]: Therefore, if you vote for it, you're voting a song into rotation that's already in rotation.
[SPEAKER_07]: You rhymed, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't need to vote for Holic.
[SPEAKER_10]: You rhymed, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: I rhymed.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm great.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rotation on the station.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rotation on the station on Orzhov Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like a Eurobeat song.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now you sound like you're spitting on the microphone.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just that calendar song.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is the meaning of... Oh, Biohazard also wants to know, what is the meaning of life expressed through interpretive dance in front of the webcam?
[SPEAKER_13]: Forty-two.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: In about ten seconds, I'm going to show you.
[SPEAKER_05]: The next webcam image, I will be showing you the meaning of life.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I will be getting help from the others, showing you the meaning of life.
[SPEAKER_05]: There it goes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Four...
[SPEAKER_05]: The meaning of life is up there on our cam for you to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got your meaning of life.
[SPEAKER_10]: His last question is, why do I ask so many questions?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because you suck.
[SPEAKER_10]: No way, he answered his own questions.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is the meaning of life.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, wait, wait, he answered his own question, never mind.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was what I was going to say too, except I've been to more Volker.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it skipped the picture.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, bummer.
[SPEAKER_07]: 23rd Magus, I'd like to know, will you people stop fucking stealing my jokes?
[SPEAKER_07]: Puns are my department, bitches.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Where's the meaning of life?
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you write the information for Max 2?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you write the information screens for that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Therefore, you suck at puns.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nurse Stylin would like to know, how many sounds does the ferret have?
[SPEAKER_07]: About seven.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we don't need to hear them all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at the webcam right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: John Fields would like to know, any interest in any of the games that are being shown at Tokyo Game Show?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um... Well, DDR Party Edition, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Otherwise, I don't really give a shit, I find.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see them when we see them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who cares if they're coming out in Tokyo?
[SPEAKER_07]: We need them out here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because say this really great role-playing game comes out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't read it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, but if they put out another Grandia, I'll import it.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Biohazard would also like to know, am I infamous for my bad questions yet?
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: You just kind of act stupid to us.
[SPEAKER_07]: You sure are famous.
[SPEAKER_07]: 23rd Magus would like to know, is it true that Jason Enos asked for my help in writing the info screens?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, you made that up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's close up the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you everybody for playing Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what we haven't looked at in a long time, Rob?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: Our actual mail.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now we're done with Ask Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We hope you learned something tonight on Ask Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, guess what next week?
[SPEAKER_07]: The ferrets won't be here because I'm going to go outside and run them over with my car.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see if... I'm just hoping the batteries fucking die someday.
[SPEAKER_07]: As are half our listeners, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: The show would not be the same without the ferret.
[SPEAKER_15]: The ferret is our mascot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we're actually checking our actual email address at orangeloungeradio, all one word, at yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we have two new messages, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's spam.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yahoo Education.
[SPEAKER_07]: Advance your learning goals.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yahoo Education introduces courses and degrees.
[SPEAKER_07]: SBC Yahoo DSL.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, only $29.95 a month for fast internet access.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't it about time?
[SPEAKER_07]: Then we have something in our bulk message, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, we have a message that says, Would you like to submit something to our SubmitWW.com service?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, because not enough people listen to Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess this bitch knows that.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, so that's all we have in our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you'd like to fill up our mailbag, orangeloungeradioatyahoo.com All right, we have some more Ask Orange Lounge questions.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm taking these last three, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're finishing this bit, and we're ending the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's some fair to ask for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Biohazard wants to know, what was the date of the first Orange Lounge radio show?
[SPEAKER_07]: The date of the first live show was June 23, 2002.
[SPEAKER_07]: The station first went on air, I think, May 18th of that year.
[SPEAKER_07]: May 18th or 22nd, somewhere in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first live show was June 23rd, 2002.
[SPEAKER_07]: 23rd Magus didn't have a question, he just had a comment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nostylan wants to know, when will there be another Pimpin' Hoes party?
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess he's referring to my birthday party, which he wasn't at, so I don't know how he knows this, but I think someone he talks to a lot was part of the brains behind that party.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe for someone else's birthday, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe for my next birthday, I'd love to have another Pimpin' Hoes party.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Dirac.
[SPEAKER_07]: A Pimino's party, it was my birthday, and some folks came over here on a Sunday morning and surprised me.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they all dressed like hoes and pimps.
[SPEAKER_07]: They brought over cake.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it was kind of like a Hawaiian Pimps and Hoes party, actually, because they were wearing Hawaiian coconut boobs and little lays, colored rainbow lays and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it was fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we had chicken and waffles.
[SPEAKER_07]: We had Eggos and Popeye's chicken.
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, live on the webcam, the ferret eats Loki's head.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright guys, guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's time to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank God this week's show went okay, unlike last week's show, which we're writing off and forgetting about forever.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's time for me to go around and collect the final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's start with Bradley.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does he have a microphone over there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you ever really looked at your toes?
[SPEAKER_08]: They look weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they do.
[SPEAKER_08]: They do look weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not Asian, and I don't know how to use chopsticks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you, Puppy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Erin.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, thanks to me, Puppy has now learned how to pick up Mike and Ike candies with his chopsticks.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm still not Asian.
[SPEAKER_10]: We realize that, but now you're one step closer to being Asian!
[SPEAKER_10]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_13]: I actually like that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: I solder.
[SPEAKER_07]: Great.
[SPEAKER_07]: My final thought is I hope I don't decide to flake on the show next week because the Castro Street Fair does sound tempting.
[SPEAKER_07]: What, on Sunday?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm thinking about flaking on the show, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't worry, I'll fill in your part.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can... We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can fill in all your parts on the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whoa!
[SPEAKER_07]: No!
[SPEAKER_07]: All your voice parts, you retard!
[SPEAKER_07]: Freaking... I don't need that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the other Matt that wants to fill those parts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whoa!
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, Holly says, puppy needs to do a hula dance.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ice Princess.
[SPEAKER_10]: I say no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm having way too much fun with the webcam.
[SPEAKER_07]: The final word of the show, I'm going to give it to Bradley because he never talks and I want him to give the final word tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Terraforming.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: We expect you a nice play again.
[SPEAKER_07]: And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pardon me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now it begins.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who all here is evil?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sound off!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm evil.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm evil!
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you are not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I am too!
[SPEAKER_04]: You're as harmless as a baby's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Zorak?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, he is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not a baby's butt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brack, I'm going to have to go with Zorak on this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: You simply don't have the mental capacity to be evil.
[SPEAKER_02]: See?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You see, Brack, you have to be able to come up with, oh, say, plots against the universe.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to hatch evil plans to conquer planets and be just plain mean most of the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're just too nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forget how to be mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: That radiation half-lobotomized me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, I've got an idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let Zorak teach you how to be mean.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do I have to?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, you have to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Bragg.
[SPEAKER_04]: Repeat after me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Space ghost.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will destroy you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will destroy you, if you don't mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, I'll get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will destroy you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will destroy you.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, I will destroy you.
[SPEAKER_03]: You and your little dog, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: You and your little dog.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I like this dog.
[SPEAKER_03]: Francine is a good puppy.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was just a prank.
[SPEAKER_03]: You want to hurt Francine?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're a big, bad, green, um, thingy guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bug.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bug, I don't want you to hurt Francine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Spacecoach, shoot that thingy thing on your arm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Destructo Ray.
[SPEAKER_03]: Destructo Ray so he doesn't hurt Francine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gladly, Brack.
[SPEAKER_02]: My dear old chum.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_02]: What'd you do that for?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was for Francine!
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, wait, I don't have a dog.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell me about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're in the Orange Launch Radio after birth.
[SPEAKER_07]: As promised, we won't make you wait any longer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here it is one more time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Overloaded.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lesson two.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, we're going to be adding that song into a rotation, by the way, on Orange Lounge Radio's Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you like that and can't get enough of it, don't worry, you'll get to hear more very soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Welcome to the Orange Lounge Radio Afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_07]: You are a scary woman, Miss Erin, with your whip.
[SPEAKER_07]: When's going to be another tournament where you can beat me up?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, there hasn't...
[SPEAKER_32]: Well, if you have to choose any time soon, she'll probably end up being there, so I'll try her there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, probably.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, see, the thing is, there haven't been any real good NorCal tournaments coming out.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, after the last year barrage of tournaments, it was kind of tired out, and now it's just, well... I'm kind of sad that I heard about the tournament in Nickel City today.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were having a Puzzle Fire tournament, and only one person showed up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played him today and beat him.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, did you go?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I played, you know, what's his name that was going to be there?
[SPEAKER_07]: I forget his name.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyways, yeah, so we played him and I won.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because he made a mistake.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it was, I don't know, I think it would have been cool to have a Puzzle Fighter tournament.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I know people in the Bay Area are pretty hardcore in that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I don't know how a DDR tournament is going to work out too well there.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else we want to share on the afterbirth?
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, have anything?
[SPEAKER_07]: Go to www.fanamatrix.net.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a pretty cool...
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, go to BitTorrent.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have BitTorrent links.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, they have BitTorrent links for the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a 10-minute or about 10-minute fan film that's done by professional actors, professional stuntmen, special effects and whatnot, cinematography.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's kind of like a practice movie for them.
[SPEAKER_07]: and no fan movie and it's basically a bunch of New Zealand actors you know doing this kind of prequel to The Matrix and it's pretty sweet so you should go check that out they're talking about doing sequels and stuff later on but it's the first movie is called Phantom Matrix and it's called Run Program and it's pretty cool so that's www.phantomatrix.net and yeah
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I think that's going to wrap up the afterbirth, unless anyone else has something they want to say?
[SPEAKER_07]: I will destroy you!
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, come in.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've got lint in my eye and it hurts.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, until next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks, you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: As I promised way in the beginning of the show, we're going to do the Night Style soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just a random order, you guys, so hopefully the song you want will come up soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good night, you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for supporting Orange Lounge Radio as always.
[SPEAKER_07]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'd be nothing without you.
Thanks for watching!
Come on baby, move it up, now you're home to get your magic shot.
I gotta give it to you tonight
Listen to my heartbeat
I'm leading a new evolution.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_20]: Thanks for watching!