Toto, I have a feeling we're not in Kansas anymore.
You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, the Lonnie Togg and then some.
Uh, mostly the and then some part of that.
Orange Lounge Radio is created by a bunch of potty-mouthed adults.
Orange Lounge may contain sexual, perverted, and mildly retarded content.
You probably shouldn't let your children listen to Orange Lounge radio.
Yes, I will spank your child.
If you're not going to do your job, goddammit, I will.
Well, here's my big opening.
A sphincter says what?
I'm super thanks for asking.
Oh, you little bitch troll from hell.
What am I doing here?
Oh no!
Dodge this.
This is a tasty burger.
Look, you stupid bastard, you've got no arms left!
It's a house? Look!
It's a flesh wound.
Searching for a boy in high school is useless.
It's searching for meaning in a polished order.
Oh yeah? Well, I hope your babies look like monkeys.
Dark Sakura.
I've had a sniff.
Skye.
But I'm playing it for the bartender, so suffer.
I hate you!
Orange Lounge Radio
We're live! This is episode 60 for September 14th, 2003.
You're tuned into the Bimani scene's most late show of all things Bimani.
My name is Loki, and well, Rob's not here because he's a slacker.
He is a slacker.
We're on time, where is he?
We're gonna, you know, let's start with the fuckies of the week.
Dear Rob, no.
Okay, and in this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Dark Sakura.
Hi, I have a sandwich.
It's tasty.
I have cookies, too, and I'm going to maul anyone who touches them.
Cool.
And in this corner, we have Rob.
Hi, I'm Rob. I'm not here right now.
Please take a message.
BEEP BEEP
you see me? And also, um, been away for a while, our, um, correspondent from the People's
Republic of Davis, Puppy. Oh, and speaking of tardiness himself, here comes, uh oh, this,
who's this poking in the door? Oh my god! I thought you said you weren't gonna be here
p0k3smot42o
burger king at like noon so in fact we were gonna get food we didn't have time
to stop that you have cookies cookies what kind of cookies not yours by the
way everybody well you guys already met but Jamie hasn't met Jamie this is Joey
Joey Jamie listeners this is Joey hey how's it going
Joey listeners okay so um we should take a break yes we should I think we should
We should take that opening break that we usually do right about now.
We're going to start off with this break with the first few MP3s I find.
So we've got, looks like...
Wait, here, here, here.
Hey! Oh, you got it?
Yeah.
This is going to be pretty much random stuff, so yeah.
Anyways, um, yeah, enjoy.
But love's pain, he's got an opportunity to not try again
But when she caught his eye, ain't no man to fight for peace
He knew he had something left for him
But no, he was in the mood for talking
So he began to play the game
Before he knew it, he had told her how much he'd been learning
Though he was hoping she was not the same
Could it be the kind of way that I'm thinking after all of this time?
Could you please fill up?
She says, boy, you don't have to look no more
I'll give the love you need to your father and the guarantee
I'd like to know, boy, I'm a blind lady
Counting out for things so good I am the killer
And when you wake up late thinking it's a dream
So touch me, boy, you know you can count on me
Baby, a kind lady that will never leave you lonely
Hello everybody and welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 60 in progress
person. I'm a little late. I was a couple minutes late. Sorry guys. My bad. Blame traffic.
You know what? The traffic in, nobody can hear you anyway and that's a good thing. The
traffic in, where the hell was that? Where 680 meets, Fairfield. Fairfield was horrible
because one guy crashes on the side of the road and everybody has to turn their head
and see if they can look at a dead body, never fails.
Ooh, I think I see an arm! Exactly, exactly.
It looks kind of severed. I'm very proud of you guys getting things
going anyway, though. I mean, not that Jamie hasn't done it before, certainly, because
I remember we took off for L.A. for a couple of times.
And although Loki picked... And everyone decided to abandon me to go downstairs
and watch the biography of Ron Jeremy. And even though Loki picked the chicken dance
first break music. I forgive him anyway. It was cute. It was a nice deviation. Yeah,
it was a good deviation from a seven-minute version of Kind Lady. I mean, don't get me
wrong, I love Kind Lady, but shit, there's only so much of that song I can take. You
just feel the disco groove or something. So, I know we have a lot to talk about in
this segment tonight. We could fill up a good hour a show in this right here. So I think
we need to play How Was Your Day, How Was Your Week, because, my God, there's a lot
to talk about today. I haven't even seen Jamie since, like, last Sunday maybe? Have I seriously
not seen you since last Sunday? Yes. That's the first. Isn't that weird? Yeah. That's
kind of weird. Usually Jamie and I hang out. My week was very retarded. Well then let's
start with you, Jamie. How was your day and how was your week? Very retarded. How so?
My week was really dull at work and I was on antibiotics all week which had me not able
to eat anything and then my inhaler that made me all shaky and this other stuff that's like
sorting sorting snorting like fire tastes like burning it sucked it's like
it's like snorting vomit flavored jelly bellies like the Harry Potter ones ew I
think we still have some no puppy oh let's try it well there's a dinner for a
month and a half for God's sake we need to get those off of there
But anyway, it was basically dull.
I came home feeling too tired, too sick to do much of anything.
And then to top all that off, my car starts behaving very badly, as in stopping every
time I stop.
I'm going to be getting into my car later.
I kind of remember that because I remember when we were driving places, it was doing
that vroom, vroom thing that my old car used to do.
But it was really doing it very badly.
Finally, it does it at every stop.
I decided Friday...
I was going to take it in Saturday anyway to have it looked at, but I just did it Friday
afternoon because I was so tired of it.
I went in on Saturday to go check it out, and apparently the compression's all messed
up.
The one side's good.
The other side is good.
The middle is sunken on my engine, like at an incline, sunken.
All right, here's the total cost of what I've spent on my car.
I have had little tiny things replaced.
I spent nearly $800 having the brakes fixed, catalytic converter put in, a new front axle,
and then, not to mention, the oxygen sensor I had replaced much earlier.
And now they're saying it's going to cost $1,800 to fix my car.
And they likely need a new engine and a back end rebuild.
Who'd you take it to?
I went to Meinecke. Normally Meinecke is really good. The guy there, he'll at least tell me
what's up and offer to let me go take it somewhere else. Now, he worked a couple of hours on
my car, which was supposed to be $65 an hour. He only charged me $65 for the diagnostic
and that was it. That's cool. And I think he tweaked the engine because I had only stalled
once on the way home. You know, you should see, because remember
Loki's story, I don't know if this was last week, but you had the brake issue going on
Oh, that was this one.
My bad.
I don't want to ruin this.
What we're going to do is we're just going to do a patch job on the engine and make it
drivable.
But in the meantime, Julie's offered to let me use her car.
Oh, what a sweetheart.
Well, her old car, which went fine.
But we tried to take off the dash last night to put in a fan switch because her old fan
switch doesn't work.
And we just gave up.
We're like, we're going to let the men's do it.
So Dan and them were supposed to go over it, but I couldn't get ahold of her all day.
Okay, normally when I hear, oh, you fucker, I look over and go, what?
Yeah, but it wasn't directed at you. No, I don't mean me. I was meaning what goes out.
I'm just kidding. Okay, shut up. I'm just going to stare at you.
The last piece, piece number 47 of 47 of BeatMania Complete Mix 2 was 68% done. Now it's a 404
on the internet might add that each piece is 50 megs in size
dough dough anyway um so my saturday was composed of um lots of uh i went to meanie's cafe because
i've never eaten there before they were pretty good uh i bought a car battery go to sam's club
up there $47. I bought the fan switch. I bought a multi-tool. I think it's in my pocket still.
I have a multi-tool. I feel handy. Hold my multi-tool up. Put it on the camera for me.
Go up there. No, stay over there and put it on the camera. Geez, because I'm lazy and
or not. That's my multi-tool. It's really neat. It was $3, so that was the cheapest
thing I bought all day. Then we went to TGI Fridays last night. After Julie and I were
in the middle of the massive game of Phantasy Star, I'm like, give me that. Give me my knife.
I'm still into my Ride and Rock online, however, I am now back in the highly addictive world
of PS opium.
You chose to take your PSO break right when I started playing, and now that I'm done with
it-
I'm playing it on Xbox now.
I think you're avoiding me is what it is.
I'm not avoiding you, Rob.
I'm going to go in here.
No.
But that's basically it, and I haven't heard anything about getting the Centro today, so
I may have to take the Tercel out again, I'm very upset that the VIC Viper has finally
crashed and burned, but I'm thinking of getting, um, sort of looking at an Echo, a 2003 Echo,
they're blue, and if I get one it's going to be the Twinbee.
I'm a nerd.
And I haven't touched any Bimani all week.
Good for you.
No story.
Because you always have to ask, since technically we're supposed to be a Bimani show.
We worked some more on my message board today.
I'm going to give myself a shameless plug on this.
I was going to say, do you want to give yourself a shameless plug?
Roleplay.darksacra.com, sign up there if you want to run a free-form RPG on the message
board, sign up.
I will set it up for you and make you a moderator of your own forum.
And if you want to discuss any role plays, coming soon I'm going to be implementing in
the MO RPG forum on there for Phantasy Star Online, Ragnarok, and I may even put a stupid
little puzzle of pirates on there.
You know what though?
Jared's got a great puzzle pirates forum, so it's all right.
And I'm going to put one on for actual video games, and yes, we're going to have the Battle
Royal RPG discussion forum. We could do a message board style one while we're working
on the tabletop one too. I actually signed up for your message board
the other day finally. When you called and you wanted me to relay a message, it kind
of reminded me, oh I should go sign up for her board.
My boards are really awesome. Sign up for them, everybody master, I'll steal your soul
and feed it to my cat so she can poop it in her litter box.
What a lovely thought.
Thank you.
I'm done.
Okay.
Then let's go on to Bradley.
Hello, by the way.
How are you?
I'm okay.
How was your week?
How was your day?
Pretty uneventful.
I'm looking for a job.
That's basically everything I did this week.
And then I went to Cuzar yesterday, and we'll probably talk about it later with the group.
Yes.
Cuzar.
I don't know if I did anything else interesting at all, only played one game of DDR and that
was yesterday. Jamie you did that under my name, now I get
all the credit for that kick. I don't care, you are always nice when you
kick people? Or you say something silly? I'm just like, because you suck. Or die or something.
So they know it's me anyway. Anyway, okay. I'm sorry to so rudely interrupt
you. It's not much to interrupt if I'm not saying
much of anything right now. Was there any interesting things you did this
week? Any Bamani or accomplishments or anything? No.
No? It's all good. Okay, well, moving on then. Puppy?
I got a microphone again.
Yes.
Okay.
So what are we talking about again?
How was your week?
How was your day?
Oh, let's see.
For my week, I didn't work this week because I was busy spending every single day packing
all my stuff into large cardboard boxes so I can throw it in the back of a truck and
drive up to Davis and move into my new apartment, which is actually pretty good.
But hooray for not being in the dorms anymore, huh?
Yes.
moved out of the dorms in my own apartment, it was like, oh my god, life is great.
I know. I actually have my car now, too, so I can, you know, leave whenever I need to.
And that's good. And then I went to Scandia earlier today and tried to play 2DX, but the
damn figure on the right side has to be broken. The damn key keeps, like, freaking out or
something and then I played like one game of DDR and got too tired haha old I
know I'm getting old damn it must be it must be college dear God what happened
to your leg did you get that like camping huh you've got like are those
bites all of your leg oh no that's not bites oh I'm sorry I thought they were
bites they kind of look like it but they do they're not bites they're just it's
just been having skin issues. Oh, I'm sorry. I thought because you went camping two weeks
ago, and when I went camping once, I got bit by so many bugs my legs looked like that.
Well, I know better than to go out camping and not have hugs break. Listen! I don't want
to go there. I know what to do about camping, because I've been going camping at the same
place for like 12 years, so I know the place. Well, don't I feel like an ass? I'm sorry.
And now I'm watching Loki type something on the TV computer thing.
Any other exciting events you want to share about your week?
Pretty much before yesterday.
Oh, oh, I did get to go to Ikea for the first time.
Ikea is so studly.
I love going to Ikea.
It's fucking scary, okay?
Why do you think Ikea's scary?
IKEA is scary.
Big blue furniture Death Star.
That's what it is.
It's not a big blue furniture Death Star, it is, it is the cool.
I love IKEA.
Like, it's...
Can I have one of those?
Yes.
Okay, IKEA is beautiful, because it's just everything in a box.
You can get a chair in a box, a lamp in a box, recliner in a box, couch in a box, tea
in a box, whatever you want, you can get it in a box, take it home, put it together.
But that's the problem, you have to put the damn shit together.
It works like Legos.
Can't you read instructions?
I bought a desk and a dresser and a TV stand for my apartment and now I spent all of Saturday
putting that crap together.
There was not one word in the instructions.
It was some weird transgender-looking character pointing out things on the pictogram.
It's weird, it's like the Swedes are trying to take us over.
Those don't know the Swedish on IKEA.
I don't think they have IKEA outside of California, I could be wrong.
I thought there was IKEA outside of California.
Obviously in Sweden.
Is there?
There's actually one over in Schomburg, Illinois, outside of Chicago, and the only reason why
I know this is because I've got a couple of friends that live in Schomburg, and that IKEA
blows the one in Emerville out of the water.
It is like seven stories tall, and it's huge.
That IKEA place is so big.
Size is everything at IKEA.
I just like to say, seven stories.
That's nuts.
Wow, I'm having to fan myself to give out that.
OK, but they need to learn that particle board is not
the best material for furniture.
OK, I put my dresser together at the helm of my roommate,
and we tried to move it into my closet.
And as we're lifting it up, snap,
there goes a board on the front of the dresser.
I think you put it together right.
She built it like a Riri.
OK, Navi, who's on the show quite often, me and him,
we went to IKEA one day.
Me, him, and Pixie Dust, the Orange Lounge wench,
we all went, I'm sorry, she's the madam, not the wench, my bad.
We all went to IKEA one day.
We had a big trip.
We went to the Jelly Belly Factory and went to IKEA.
This was like three months ago, right?
And we bought a chair that Navi had seen there
like three months ago he really wanted.
So we bought it, and then we all took it back to his house
and put it together.
It was so much fun because you had
Okay, sex topic just went over my head. Rocking and little bits of salt falling over, or popping.
Don't rock this boat. But still, I mean, particle board does not
make good furniture, and they need to figure out a better way to put the damn thing together
with, I mean, they give you a bunch of little wooden pegs that you have to hammer into holes
to hold it together. That's it.
It's like Tinker Toys. I know, it is, and that's what's so fucking
IKEA is tinker toys for grown-ups.
My roommate said they're trying to lower the productivity of Americans so Swedish can take
over the country.
Why would Swedish people want this country?
I don't fucking know!
I don't know.
Oh, yeah, I got all this stuff put together.
It's all about the watches. Watches and clocks.
There was no... They're gonna drive us insane by putting clocks everywhere.
Okay, that did not look right. Did you ever see a hook?
Just like that.
That did not look right from this angle.
You're a sicko.
Yeah, too bad we're not on TV. Anyway...
Oh, we do have the cam. We have the cam, I forgot. And the cam updates even faster now.
Yeah, but it's not pointing in your direction.
Oh, I forgot to whore out our chat room. My bad.
Do it!
Did you guys already do it?
www.calibomani.com, click on Orange Lounge and click on chat.
While you're there, visit our forums, because no one posts in our forums.
That makes us sad.
And the LiveJournal Community username Orange Lounge.
And sooner or later you guys are going to update that site.
Right!?
We made a purchase last week, I should say, and we're planning to put that purchase to
you soon.
kind of purchase would this be? Swedish stock. Yeah, Swedish stock. A Swedish bank account.
Okay. We're going to the fjords. Jamie says we're going to the fjords. Okay. Other than
that, I went to meet up with a couple of you guys at Qsar last night. We'll talk about
Qsar in a minute. Yeah, okay. Because that's a whole topic of its own right there. And
I bet.
Is there anything you want to say about your week, Joey?
I'll probably cover most of it, but...
Yeah, you probably will.
Is there anything?
Well, I'll go back.
Okay, go back.
I'll go back.
Last week, I went to Bodega Bay, and there was about seven of us friends, and we took
a trip, it's a yearly trip that we always go to Bodega Bay, ran out of house out there,
and uh...
stave
four days three nights
really fun
houses right on the ocean
and uh... so we just take it there for
you know the four days
and uh...
drink up and
so that's what it's almost like that movie we saw
where they went to the cabin
partied party yes
you guys are a party animal we went and saw cabin fever yes we went and saw cabin fever
two days ago
Most disturbing film I think I've ever seen.
Very disturbing.
I will agree.
I don't get disturbed by movies.
I know.
I'm not going to talk too much about it, but...
What?
What's this?
Eh.
Second most disturbing film.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Second most disturbing film I've seen.
We'll be the first.
That Ichi the Killer that Loki was talking about last week.
I'm sorry.
That's too much.
I mean, if there's a line, that movie crossed it.
I don't know.
We saw 28 Days Later yesterday, and that was pretty disturbing, too.
I like 28 Days Later, though.
I'd already seen it.
By the way, we brought you a movie.
Thanks.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
The most disturbing movie ever is freaking Manos, The Hands of Fate.
You know what?
Even Suicide Circle, that's just bad.
That's just bad.
Not disturbing.
Suicide Circle, a little strange, but not disturbing.
It's creepy and thought provoking, but not really disturbing unless you happen to have
fixations about, you know, flesh!
Well, there's Captain Fear for you. A lot of flesh tearing.
Yeah, it was nasty. It was pretty brutal. Tim Curry in legend.
Disturbing. Yeah, I'll agree with that. But so great.
Anyway, sorry to interrupt. Anyway,
what else? So that was that. That was a cool trip. Came back, didn't want to go back
home, and
that's why I took a day
a vacation before my vacation, and a day vacation after my vacation, because I was told it was
time to go home.
That's right.
Nobody ever wants to go back to work after vacation.
So I took Monday off, and then I took two hours before Tuesday to go in, so I had a
six-hour day on Tuesday.
So anyway, it was good.
Worked all week.
That was hellish.
Does anybody here like their job?
Show of hands.
Like their job.
Well, I love my job.
You don't work.
Yes, you.
I know you work.
What the hell are you talking about, I don't work?
But you're back in school!
Well, I'm going to be working.
Where?
I don't know yet.
I still have to go out this weekend.
Like right now?
Right this second?
You're not working?
No.
But I am still on the payroll at Golfland.
Alright, my bad.
And then later on I'll deal with the whole thing.
And how you enjoy your job working at a golf land, I'll never know, especially after what
happened to you this summer, which I want to talk about later.
Yes, I will talk about it later, but it's not Roseville and there's not hundreds of
thousands of snotty shithead kids to deal with.
And no water slides.
To the love of God, do not bring up each of the killer mid-show.
Oh no, please don't.
All I need to...
Yeah.
So I'll have to say yes, I do love my job.
I mean, I've been there for over nine years now, and I don't see myself going anywhere
any time soon.
To be honest, I actually like my job a lot.
Like four months ago, before I was promoted, I'd be complaining about it a lot, but right
now, love it.
I really do.
Looking forward to a fat pay increase.
Mine's busy now that peak season's almost over.
All you college students just need to hurry up and get in school and stop calling.
I can't really say that because I've talked to so many neat and cool people.
Your typical college student is smarter than your typical mortgage person.
Typical homeowner.
Really?
Let's go there.
Typical.
I, for one, am a homeowner.
I used to work in mortgage customer service and you have no idea how many people I had
to explain how to read their loan documents.
It's not funny.
Well, it's, yeah.
I would say they are kind of complicated.
I see people who sign with an X. That's pretty bad. Signing with an X, that's
pretty bad. You know what's even better on your driver's
license? I had friends that had this too. They signed it and then they put a happy face
next to it. It's those people that are so pretty that they always sign everything with
a happy face. That's just being sixteen. If I ever worked retail, I would say, I'm sorry,
this doesn't match your driver's license you need to put a happy face they need to take
all the happy people and put them on an island 42 people at a time put these nice pretty
shiny colors on them and give them all a weapon and have them kill each other off in three
days electro shock oh no battle royale have you seen battle royale no i haven't no i have
not seen battle royale yet that's it next time are you going to de-virginize me i'm
I'm going to bring over the DVD and have you watch it sometime.
Japanese movie put out what, 99? 94, put out 94. Oh, I don't think it's that old, dear.
Is it? Well, whenever it was put out. It's 2000, okay. Well, regardless, it's not that
old is the point. So, it's not that old and they put a bunch of students on an island
and when we say students, we're talking like seventh and eighth grade kids, ninth grade
kids and it's some kind of government program where they basically say, you guys have to
kill each other, and the last one standing gets to go home. And it's really violent,
because, you know, it's not American movies, so they're not subject to all the, you know,
R rating stuff. What? It had a theatrical release in Europe. See, but the British don't
care. You can show tit on TV in Britain, and no one cares. But, basically, it's really
violent, and kids kill each other, and it's great, because kids get really annoying, especially
I
like picturing them as junior high school kids.
Don't ruin my fantasy!
You're sick!
You're a sick man.
Playing DDR as long as I have.
You get to hate kids real fast.
Anyway, hi.
I love those things.
Anything else?
Oh, don't encourage them.
Don't encourage them.
You know what?
I still love this thing.
Yeah, baby.
I think I would start bringing him all of a sudden.
Don't you have to take a nap?
Actually, I am quite tired.
I've been driving all goddamn day.
Rob, you're on a time-out.
Go in the room.
Uh-oh.
I have the microphone!
You are cool.
You like the ferrets.
He just sneezed.
I can't believe he just sneezed.
Rob is making the give me hand, trying to take the microphone away from me.
Oh, and look at the eye on the floor!
Jimmy's here!
She's pouting!
Look at that lip!
My goodness.
Rob's being cute, okay?
I have to give it back.
I win.
What is this, Ferret?
We got present with that Ferret, and that was funny.
That was a flying Ferret, though.
Those are... are... special.
Special!
No, this is special.
One of these was, like, long gone, and we couldn't find it, anyway.
It's right here.
a couple of years, so Joey was like, let's go today.
I'm like, OK.
So we went to the beach today.
We went over to Stinson Beach.
Stinson Beach over on Highway 1.
Which is right just north of San Francisco.
And you have to take the most windiest road to get there.
It's so fun to drive.
Luckily, I didn't have to drive.
Oh, I was having fun.
He was holding onto the goddamn door.
I was not holding onto the goddamn door.
Did you master the inertia drift while driving?
The INERTIA Drift.
Oh, I love racing games.
I love racing games.
I will bring Initial D over next Sunday then.
Cool.
I said it last week and I will say it this week.
F, Initial D, F0 is where it is at.
F0 is much better.
I know I would.
Okay, so, the windy roads, we went to the beach, and the beach was fun, we took about
a gazillion pictures, and there's, uh...
Yeah, we did take a lot of pictures, but...
Thank you for taking all sorts of, like, disgusting pictures of me trying to climb the rock, like,
bending over, trying to...
Oh, they were, you guys all love this!
I got some blackmail pictures!
I'm trying to climb these rocks, because I wanted a picture of me on top of the rock,
so I could take a picture and say, I rock.
Oh, and I just kept on snapping, as he was climbing, it was great!
And so he's making a movie out of it, he just keeps on snapping, filling up my camera.
I get it back, I'm like, who took 48 pictures?
I did.
Anyway, so we had fun at the beach, and I still have sand all over my feet though, and
the tides suck, I got sand on my pants and everything.
The water was 60 degrees, it was quite lovely.
But this is why we're late, then, you know, we kind of, we knew how long it would take
us to get home from the freeway, I think, but we didn't account for the slow-ass grandma
drivers on the curvy roads who actually take it at the speed limit and you can't pass them.
Like five miles the whole trip and I'm like, there's passing lanes, turnouts, use them.
So we got stuck behind them. Grandmas or grandpas listening out there,
you know, turnouts, use them. And not only did that slow us up, but then
when we got to Vacaville or whatever that was, not Vacaville, Fairfield, there was all
the traffic, and if it had not been for that accident, we would have been here on time.
So for all those of you that get in car accidents, stop it and learn how to drive.
You know what's actually interesting is that a lot of the time it's not rubberneck drivers
that cause the traffic to slow down. Really?
Often the Highway Patrol actually sends out units to create traffic breaks.
It happened a couple days ago when I was on my way back from IKEA.
They probably do that on major accidents, right?
Actually, no. As I was going down 580 heading home from IKEA, there was a minor two car accident on the right-hand shoulder right near a freeway entrance.
and then two highway patrolmen busted ahead of traffic and created a traffic break and
actually stopped, slowed down everyone to about 15 miles an hour as they passed the
accident site, then pulled off the road and let everyone go.
Which makes sense, so the cleanup crew and everything can take care of it.
I've seen that happen twice in Sacramento actually, same intersection, same time of
day. Like we were coming back from the club, on the highway, coming back from downtown,
same intersection, Fulton and Eighty, I've seen two huge wrecks there, and the policemen,
they drive across all the lanes of traffic, and they do it really slow to pace the rest
of the traffic, because you can't get by them, because you don't want to pass a cop anyway.
But he's driving across all the lanes of traffic. That would be a great racing game.
Pace car driver! Pace car driver!
Oh my god, that would be beautiful. Then you could do it to your own beat.
That's funny, VidPower is like speed limit, what's that?
Something that is posted on the highway that you're supposed to follow, but you notice
that on the highways it'll say maximum speed of 65 miles an hour.
But in the city it has just speed limit, 35, speed limit, 40.
So it's not the max.
You can go 65 out of 40, but it's just not the maximum speed limit, you know?
Have you ever told that to a cop?
Actually no.
What about where they have maximum and minimums?
I'd love for them to go after the people who are not going the minimum.
That would be beautiful.
They pull over people going 50 into 65, I mean, come on.
Joey and I were talking about this on the drive home today too.
We decided that there needs to be a lane just for special people like us.
Screw the special people.
Well, it should be Joey's lane.
Hello?
You know, I don't have to deal with these idiot morons that don't know how to drive.
You know what?
Or how about a lane that you have to pass an IQ test to be able to drive in?
Like, here's the test.
You know what?
The higher the IQ, the stupider they get.
I don't get it.
When you see an accident on the side of the road, do you A, stop to help, B, slow down
to look at dead bodies, C, drive faster?
If you ask for a C, you get to drive in the special lane.
Of course, you could just have flying cars because you don't have to deal with highways.
That would be so much simpler.
Thank you, George Jetson.
Being in the position that I am in, if I see something like that, I would have to actually call CHP to make sure somebody's on the way.
Aww, you're a good Samaritan.
I wouldn't stop and help.
Do it from your cell phone while you're driving.
I would have to call CHP.
That's just me.
I think that's all I want to say, because we'll talk about QSAR later.
I'm sure Loki might get into it or whatever.
We need to take a break before we talk about that, but Loki, do you want to talk about
your week, your day?
Sure, why not, you know, since I'm just sitting here.
This week wasn't all that important, you know, it wasn't like I had my birthday or anything,
and uh, yeah, I'm twenty-three.
No one died except for John Reeder.
I cleaned.
Oh my goodness.
Yeah, but I didn't kill Johnny Cash.
John Reeder, though, was me.
There you go.
Oh man.
Johnny Cash.
He had one foot in the grave anyway, I mean, when his wife died.
Hey, hey, I, you know, I was really depressed, and I normally don't get depressed for famous
people.
Don't get me wrong, Johnny Cash, great man, talented man, but his wife died four months
ago.
He's been having all sorts of problems anyway.
It was time.
Bless him for trying to keep going on, but the same thing happened with my grandma and
my grandpa.
It's just too hard.
His spouse goes, you're next.
You get sick often.
This is what happened with my aunt.
When her father died, her mother passed within six hours of him, and she was in perfect health.
I guess that, you know, I'm glad that they're all, you know, united again, but it was very
depressing.
Anyway, I'm sorry, happy birthday.
So, what you're saying is Johnny Cash was so distraught over the fact that John Ritter
died that he, too, showed up?
I don't know about that.
I don't know.
Anyways, so yeah, I didn't do too much this week.
I took two days off, so I had a four-day weekend, and Thursday I went and got my breaks done,
I took it over to the mechanic that happens to be just a few feet from our door, literally
right over the fence.
How convenient!
So I took it over there, and I found out that I got my brakes done, it didn't need to really
be done, but I went ahead and did the back brace because it was kind of a birthday gift
for my mom.
So I found out that Speedy Oil Change lied about my brakes needing to be done, they just
wanted more service from me.
You know what?
have that just speedy in general or any kind of those quickie loops don't go
that's all I have to say well and they broke my axle they see hello to my axle
so that I'd have to come back and have it replaced there too you know I can't
prove that they did break it but I think they broke it a little bit more because
right after I got my tune up there my car started you know grinding when I
I turned right, which is from my right front axle going out.
But that's not going to cost that much to replace,
so that's cool.
And they're working my pad some more.
I have them all framed now.
They're all pretty.
And yes, they're sitting on the patio.
And yesterday, or right now, Friday, I
went and bought a TV, a 27-inch TV
that I'll be using in my cabinet.
And let me just say that was the most entertaining thing
to watch for anyone else that was out there
in that parking lot, me trying to get that in my car.
It wouldn't fit in the back door.
It wouldn't fit in the trunk.
So I ended up having to break the box open,
cram the TV into the front seat, and pad it
with the phone that was inside there,
strap the seat belt around it, and hope to God
that when I turn corners that it doesn't crush me when it rolls.
So that was fun.
And then getting it in the door as the neighbors are standing there watching me going,
Ugh, it's so heavy!
And then, um, so I did that.
Right, that's a quick hint.
What else?
Oh, yeah, then yesterday we went and played Cheez-Art,
and I kicked ass and won every game, as usual.
And there's some guy there that called me fat, and I laughed at him.
That was so great.
Bokey's like, that guy called me fat.
And it was the guy that worked there.
He was just pissed off that I was beaten up on him.
But we ended up tying, and we shook hands at the end.
That's all it's about, you know, just talking.
What is this shit?
That's not what I do.
What are you talking about?
Q's are that's what you do.
You talk.
That's gay.
You talk shit.
You talk shit all the time.
And at the very end, you know, you just
thank them for a good game, because that's what it is.
Because the next game, they could be whooping up on you.
And the game after that, you could be whooping on them.
never know. It's just a different situation each time, so. What? I just don't talk to
anybody and then I sneak up on them and poke my gun in their back and then fire and run
away giggling. Well, then we started doing G stuff because the arena isn't built that
well so the red headquarters, they didn't paint it too well and so we were tagging the
headquarters from outside the headquarters because the plexiglass wasn't covered all
the way. Lame. Let me just say, being on the team that was defeated by you, lame. Oh, shit.
Oh, great.
Sheet.
We were bouncing shots off the windows and stuff like that.
I was actually on the other side of the arena, seeing the lights on the windows.
Great stuff.
So we did that.
We had fun.
Played some Cuzar, dropped some business cards off there, so hopefully someone picked them
up that was listening to the show tonight, even though I don't think so.
And that's it.
There was no hicks there.
I was surprised.
No hicks at all.
They knew we were coming and fled.
But there was some guy that just gave Ryan, not puppy Ryan, but zero Ryan a hug out of
nowhere.
Some guy was hugging him goodbye.
That's right.
Really?
The way it started...
He said it wasn't the same guy.
No, it wasn't the same guy.
But the way it started, he came up and said goodbye to everybody.
And then he wanted to ask some kind of questions.
I think he was like, I don't know, religious or something, wanting to talk about God.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. I missed all that. Anyways. Moving on. Oops. Yeah. Oh well. Anyway, so then
So then later on we left and then I came back here and I was exhausted and today I bought
everything to convert all of our game systems over to S-Video and I bought a bunch of...
I raped Radio Shack's little component cabinet and I took all their crimp connections for
nine pin serial things for my cabinet and all that stuff and I got some pretty nifty
stuff from the cabinet. But next week I'm going to be buying all the wood for the main
cabinet and we'll hopefully have it built in under a month. So, yay.
Okay, that was this week's edition of How Was Your Day, How Was Your Week. I want to
talk a little more about Q's are when we come back and buy...
Well, not now.
Because it's time for a break. We've been talking for like 40 minutes straight here,
so we're going to take a break.
Okay, fine.
I said so and I want to stretch so we will be you right back. You're listening Orange
launch radio thank you
Every night I look at the sky All you're leaving was blue
Every night, every night
Baby, if you want me to come back
Every time I lose my self-control
It feels like I can't let you go
I'm at the point of no return
Don't ever wanna come back down
I'm not slow high above the ground
You're stealing, I will always yell
Kicking away
I'm flying
I'm gonna head for paradise
Nothing to say
I'm climbing
And I wanna stay in my spirit tonight
Keeps you alive
In the barrio, you've gotta learn how to survive
Cause you never know when it's your turn to take a dive
So you go, you stay with your eyes in the back of your head
You'll never know if you'll be alive or beaten
That is one old savage who'll carry on midnight special
Never leave, but without it Always better with a midnight version
It's the dark of the street You never know who you're gonna be
You're gonna need no more faith, you gotta make that good show
Orange Lounge Radio, we put your thing down, flip it and reverse it.
Hey, we're back. Hi, everybody. Yay, I'm in the chair. I did it all by myself, I'm so
loud. And I have the ferret too. So what are we going to do? I don't know. Give us a mic
and rub. Well, I wonder, because somebody in the chat room was asking over break, what
What is Qsar? Actually, the place is Qsar with a Z and its laser tag, but the reason
why we've been calling it Qsar tonight is because on our little receipt yesterday when
we bought the games, it said Qsar. We were joking. Qsar is hee hee hee, you know, shit
like that. But, what? Well, British was Quasar, wasn't it?
Yeah. Isn't it called Quasar in Britain? Yeah. Jimmy's like, I'm not that big a dork,
Okay.
But I actually, you know what, I was talking about how much I suck at Qs are and Loki told
me I had to shut up because I actually did pretty good.
One game I came in second just behind Loki.
I was happy.
Yeah.
It was the solo game too, because I just stood by the headquarters and every time Loki would
shoot enough people that he could go for the headquarters, I'd be there to jump out and
shoot them.
I got the headquarters like three times, almost three times.
I got it twice, and then I got tagged by Ryan at the very end.
I was tagged, and the light was up, and because Black Lab was trying to shoot it, even...
What?
This chat needs to be scrolled down, sorry.
Oh, der.
Sorry to interrupt your story, keep going, my bad.
Alright, anyways, so yeah, I was going to tag it for the second time, but probably didn't understand, I guess, the concept of supercharged, where you have to tag five people without getting tagged, then your gun goes in the rapid fire, then you can tag the headquarters, that's the only way you can tag it.
So, he's standing there blocking me because I'm trying to, like, tag the headquarters, and here he's standing there, had I remembered that you can tag it from the outside, you know, that would have saved me a whole lot more time, but, you know.
So no, I had to kind of get tagged a few times, but then I won, I guess.
There was some tubby little kid there that was talking crap, and I beat him down.
Then I was playing DDR later on, and he was like,
Oh my God, you're good at QSR and DDR!
I heard him say that!
It was not there. That's funny. Yeah. Even I would have made fun of that. That's cool.
It wasn't as bad as Skater Cowboy. Oh my God. Skater Cowboy was awful. Skater Cowboy was
there last night. I would have laughed. We always think about Skater Cowboy when we think
of Vacaville. I wasn't even there. Seriously, every time I go to Vacaville, I look for Skater
Cowboy, but I don't think we'll ever meet him again.
He's just rolling in the wind.
With his cool custom-made DDR Freak skateboard that sucked.
Jamie, do you know if DDR Freak has any officially licensed skateboarding products?
Hell no.
Just checking.
I think the only official DDR Freak product there is are the shirts and then that's it.
I thought there were stickers too.
Maybe stickers, maybe.
When you're a freak, you're a freak.
the syringe?
You know, I just hadn't been to play in so long, it's just like I kind of forgot what
it was like, but those energizers kind of sucked for me, like I could never get my gun
to energize right, and I don't know if it was just that I would keep shaking my gun
in front of it when you had to hold it, but even when I held it, it wouldn't do anything.
It was stupid, I didn't like that.
I guess I'm very impatient.
But it sucks we have to go all the way to Vacaville to play QZAR, because Laser Force
is unacceptable.
That's not laser tag.
That's...
Yeah, well...
Yeah, believe it or not, we just drove by the damn, like, why is that place still open?
It smells like pee.
You have to understand, because they're the number one laser force place since QZAR left.
They were about to go under...
They're the only laser force...
Imagine...
Well, Laser X is a count, but imagine, imagine if you will...
Okay, Sun Splash is about on the same level as Laser Force, laser tag boy.
talking like you know laser force was in the you know the quicksand going under
no chance or survival whatsoever no chance to survive make your time yeah
then all of a sudden you know Q's are leaves and gasps for air in this like
barely alive and it comes back with a vengeance the only thing I like about
laser force is I love the two-story arena concept I love because you know I
love to play sniper so I love to sit there on the top and help help people at
the bottom. Yes, I'm a camper and I'm proud of it.
I wish we could go play Qsar in Ireland because their Irish rules rock.
Irish rules. Can you club people with a gun? Can you drink
and then play Qsar? Irish rules, there's no neck strap and there's
running. Their arenas are huge and it's like running around in a huge, it's pretty much
like playing paintball because it's just that, it's just crazy and it's the most tiring thing
ever. We played Irish Rules one time when I was there on Tuesday night at that Cuzar
in Vacaville and that was very dangerous. Whoa, what a liability. How did you get away
with doing Irish Rules there? Well, gee, because they don't have any waiver
cards. It doesn't matter anyways. That Cuzar runs so poorly. It's a joke. If anyone got
hurt at all, stubbed to toe or whatever, you could just go and sue that place and it wouldn't
matter.
Hey kids!
Wanna make money?
Seriously, there's no waiver forms at all, so, I mean, you could.
I should do that as a college student.
Puppies are going to pay off his college loans by suing Cuzar, that's really great.
My leg hurts today, maybe I should sue Cuzar.
Okay, um, the show just kind of came to a screeching halt, I have nothing else to say.
Sorry, I just saw that my, um, BeatMania Complete Mix 2 was done.
Oh, aren't you special.
You want to do the cage match now, Jamie?
Yeah, I want to do the cage match.
Alright, let me get over there and also set up a cage match.
Alright, here, Loki, talk.
So yeah, um, today, or actually not today, a few days ago they, um, finally released the, um, hard drive image of Beat Me at Complete Mix 2.
And that was pretty cool. Bad puppy. Bad puppy.
So anyways, yeah, I just downloaded it, all 47 parts of it, and, uh, now it's gonna unzip. Very slowly. It's gonna take a while.
to make this room complete, you need to transfer to the other room.
p0k3smot42o
a big announcement. Go to your local GameStop and reserve your season 3 Transformers box
set now so you can be cool like me. Cause I have mine reserved. Season 3 is the best
season ever. We all aspire to be as cool as Jamie, don't we? Everybody in the world needs
to be as cool as me. You know what, I just met Jamie and Jamie is the coolest chick I've
ever met so hey yeah I'm cool but I have a spirit I sent you a rawr file zero
pre-show dot rawr
because I was cool and decided to upload it so I didn't have to waste any more
I endorse Wind Rar, not Winds Up.
I have it! Here!
The way the cage match works, if you want to vote for a Hollick, that's the first rule.
Second rule, if you want to vote in the cage match, you have to get in our chat room, www.calibomani.com, click on Orange Lounge and click on chat, this is the way it works.
Each of the three lovely hosts of this program, including myself, Sarca, and Loki, bring one song to the table.
And you guys vote on your favorite song, and that song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio.
However, if a song wins for a month straight, it gets taken out.
and guess what I'm a little scared and last week's song that one is now
halfway there last week's winner was Loki song that he picked two weeks ago
but it's still winning and it's every little thing from the cyber trance album
with face the change and this is the above and beyond and dirt devils remix
so you only get a clip of it because it won last week but this song number one
You can vote for tonight every little thing with face the changes. Here you go
It's me and the kid who's in love
Every hour I eat a pizza
Gotta need a game, gotta get there
did it, or what it's called but it's from Raiden. This is one of the best shooting games
ever. I can fill you in on the rest of it because I'm going to read it right off of
the MP3 here. It's Galantry, nobility of spirit. That's what it says. And if you have never
played Raiden, go play Raiden DX because it's the best of the series. Thank you. Alright,
So here's Jamie's pick. It's Ryza with Raiden Gallantry. Enjoy!
kostjamrh And now we get to tear it apart or praise it lots.
whatever you want to do.
It was a really good remix, and the song that I initially picked had already been played,
because I didn't notice the tracklist, and I just went,
oh, this is from Wipeout, and put it in.
I didn't even listen to it.
So, this one, this one, I liked it.
It's a good remix, and it's a great game, you know.
Always been a big fan of the Raiden series,
and figured a lot of people don't appreciate it that much, so I threw it in,
so it gets an A to me.
So I'll give it that. And Raiden is an underrated shooter, so I'll give you that too.
But as a song itself, I love Raiden. I can't see giving it much more than that.
We had a machine at our round table at Rock.
As a song itself, I can't see giving it much more than like...
A 6.66!
A 5.723.
Okay, uh, Bradley?
pretty good but easy to know
yeah
i forgot to listen to it
somebody else taking my chair
look at this guy he's so stupid
stupid guy
what the hell
what are you doing
what am i like
I feel like a lobster from Dick Tracy or something with his cord wrapping around me.
He ain't going nowhere until you spill, spill.
Oh.
No, I think...
Okay.
Switching.
You dropped it.
Yeah, but you stepped on the cord when you threw it.
Hi, cage match.
Remember me?
Oh, yeah.
p0k3smot42o
I'd like to mention that the Racebase R6 MK3 is the most gay racing chair I have ever seen.
I can vouch for Loki, he does have ADHD.
Hi, I'd like to finish Cage Mansion here, thank you.
I haven't, it's you, but I've never took anything.
Alright.
That would explain it.
Take this.
My turn, my song's turn.
with picking this. So here we go. This is my pick.
Let me show you where I've been You and me, I'll be in the same
Let me tell you where I've been You and me, you and I
The ocean shines so bright
It shines so bright
I don't know what to say, I don't know what to say
Come into my dream
Come into my dream Let me show you where I've been
It's you and me I've seen Let me tell you what I mean
In the deep blue skies
There were rainbows in the night
Here we need to fly
And the ocean shines so bright
Hello, that was Froggy with Comin' to My Dream, Jamie.
It wasn't bad, but it sounded very, I guess, cookie-cutter, you know?
The little pauses where it did the little vroom-vroom noise were kind of cool before it set up again,
but it's not anything that I could really latch onto and concentrate on, so it gets to about a seven, yeah.
I've heard that song so many times, not even funny.
But it has Froggy in it, so I was expecting swimming music, and that's what it was.
Music had me swimming into boredom.
Now I was kind of tuning that one out too because I heard it so many times, but I was
I was busy, you know, with renaming zip files and stuff.
You and that massive porn book.
Yeah, but this isn't about the porn collection. This is about Beatmania.
No, it was okay. It was a pretty good song.
In fact, I think it's better than my song this week, which you should vote out because I have a better one for next week.
just vote for low-key sister
chicken dance
rule number one, can't vote for hollick
you can however vote for pixie dust hot Kylie Minogue brand underpants if you want
just a nice check that wasn't a music
chat room joke, sorry
it's a cool song, it's a little bit repetitive to me but aren't most songs like that repetitive
kostjamrh I was listening to that song and I kind of liked it. It was slow in the beginning but I haven't heard many songs like it. But I thought I liked it. So I will have to say a 7.
Alright, sounds good. Okay. Let's recap kids. Here you go. Send those votes now to sky
Oh several more comment on that song. Okay, and then where's the lyrics?
I'm so proud of you
Some days I want to beat you over the head with that ferret repeatedly
Let's recap, you can vote for one of these three songs.
Song number one, two weeks running now, every little thing, cybertrance, face the change
with coming to my dream
jamie remember the lyrics to this one
you
my here you go
position clinton
much better
right now i feel like sandstorm
did you do it
the
and in great bonds i tradition place votes now
yeah this is
Oh yeah, Bonzai got cancelled.
Did Bonzai get cancelled?
It had to have.
You know what?
I don't care.
That makes things better anyways.
I'm sorry, puppy, nobody can hear you.
Hey, is Takeshi's Castle still on?
What was it, Most Extreme Challenge?
Yes, Most Extreme Challenge is still on.
I think I can find original episodes, though, of Takeshi's Castle.
I want to see those.
This is from some of the clips that they take out for the Hacked Up show.
There must be some really incredibly stupid people on that show.
My favorite clip is the one time that one chick took the soccer ball to the face.
I like Japanese variety shows.
I have a tape somewhere in my house.
By the way, this is the first time I had ever seen any Dragon Ball Z.
It was taped off of TV in Japan.
I had Macross 7 on the tape.
giving you an indication of how old this tape is, they had this show on a called...
Actually, no, I didn't give you the indication.
I don't remember what it was called.
It was called like, Udi Nadi Land or something, but they had these interviews and stuff, and
then they had dog soccer, where they tried to get the dog into the net by leading it
with toys and things, and the dog got tired and took a shit on TV, and then they showed
a repeat of it, and then they had sit, replay.
I could totally make a Japanese TV, they just need to let me have no rules whatsoever, just
let me do it.
Calvin Ball the show, they need Calvin Ball the show.
Calvin Ball the show.
Calvin and Hobbes.
There is no rules.
They were trying to get a cow, so then they had a baby dressed up as a soccer ball.
It was wearing this little black and white checked outfit with a little hat that looked
like a soccer ball.
Can I take it?
And this baby's like...
The thing is, is that this baby was so cute, because the baby would just sit there, and
then people would wave something, and the baby would just laugh at him, and then go
try to wander out of bounds.
And then they were wiggling things, and the baby was going, ah, baby, and started calling
across.
It was pretty funny.
I'll try to find my tape.
And I've also got an interview with Jackie Chan on there, and then a made-for-TV movie
with him on it, so it's cool. Jackie Chan rocks.
And I have the best Godzilla movie ever because of the man with the CD player in his head.
Godzilla vs. Mecha Ghidorah. Because the man had a CD player in his head.
Wow. It's like, he's this android guy, and he's
the only one who speaks English in the whole movie. It's great. Everything he says is in
English. Of course, the freak with the CD player in
in his head is the only one who speaks English. He wasn't Japanese, but I bet all the machinery
in his head was. I bet it was Sony. It's like he pulls this thing out of his head and it's
this storage device that pulls CDs in and out and everything. It's like an 18-CD changer
in his head. It was really cool. He saw, I'm totally ignoring all this chaos.
I'm listening to Yanni. I saw something else on TV, by the way. This
was cool. You actually watched TV?
I watched TV. I was at Julie's house yesterday, and we just happened to watch, what were we
watching. We watched the Teen Titans on Cartoon Network. It was pretty funny because the intro
song was done by Puffy. The J-pop group, the girl Puffy. I think she got sued by him for
using the name. Fuck him. I know. There was some drama a while back, but the opening song
was done by puffy and it was all in japanese it was cute
you got a teen titans looks gay from the chat room
it was funny it was very it was very happy and gay
no the guy it's like it's done in the style of batman beyond but they do like cutesy manga
things like like beast boy was doing sweat drops and everything it was cute
it was really funny don't everybody talk at once
you guys want to hear who won the cage match no okay okay then we'll go to a break i guess
the winner tonight, and I thought we were going to have a tie, but we got one vote in
at the last minute that broke the tie. So tonight's winner, it was a low voting night,
you guys pissed me off, that's right. Tonight's winner, surprisingly enough, is Broggy with
Coming to My Dream. Jamie, you were that close, your song just
had one vote shy and low-key, you only got one vote, so people are sick of that song
finally.
Yeah, they got tired of still my words because it's a more Ghost 10th Planet mix.
And an honorable mention to Hollick.
Do you mean that Pixie Dust Underwear didn't get any votes?
Pixie Dust Underwear did not get any votes.
Oh my God, that's a sin.
I vote for you.
I didn't have any voting privileges, so I couldn't vote for the underwear.
I think we collectively as a non-voting group, because we're all here and only people in
the chat room can vote, we'll all collectively vote for Pixie Dust in her drawers.
All of us except you.
I vote for the ferret.
Let's go to break.
Sounds like a good idea.
Nope, we're happy.
it
we would tell you let's go to break
they're like a good idea
the
all right
this is great
not going to hurt in hurricane force winds
will be back
and after this break i'd actually have some pdr music
but i don't think i music video news
because we have home versions coming out very soon we got to talk about there's a
lot of news on the home versions this week
and a lot of
uh... making fun of them that we have to do when we come back
making fun of staff that's what we do that because that's what we do
uh...
jamie what's the song you would hear this break
what's on the island here yeah
i want to hear all the songs that everybody hates. I want to hear Cartoon Heroes so we're putting that in. Put Cartoon Heroes in, put Love That Feelin' in.
Oh God, I don't even know if I can find one of that feeling.
I'll see if I can...
Okay.
Is it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Go back.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I want...
Volume 4 in.
What?
Volume 4?
Okay.
That's enough.
That's 3.
Okay.
Alright.
We'll be right back after this break.
Stay tuned.
You're listening to Orange Launch Radio.
We are what we're supposed to be, illusions of a fantasy
All that I'd like to speak or say
What you do is what you wish to do
We are the god of symphony
We do the things you want to see
Brain by brain to do the extreme
Our friends are so unreasonable
They do the unpredictable
I'd also like to speak and say
What we do is what you wish to do
There's no time nor fish for a friend
Do it on the little bay
Brain by brain to do the extreme
We're just one by one, we're making it one
We are the stars, we're heroes of the world
We are the ones who are never over
We're singing by your back, raising minds
For the ones that are gonna be forever
Get your body back, and rock it for the end
We're gonna dream about a true star for it
We're gonna superman, and never, never, never
We're one, two, three, two, three, four!
I feel, I feel
I can feel it. You are the only one. Let me feel this way.
I can feel it. I can feel it. I can feel it.
When I come down, I come down right to the sun
Hands right down, then right down the bed
Round and round, scoot right close to the air
Took just a sec, that's what it's like to come down again
Keep an edge, nevertheless I'll be fresh to the bed
Get to the feeling
I'm taking the pose until nobody knows
When I'm on my way to get down to the head
Down, down
Hands right down the bed
Just one, two, three, four
Come on y'all, I've been on before
Can't write down, can't write down a shit
I'm rounding out, super close finger
Come down, check, speed for net
Get to the fever
I'm keeping the floor, I'm getting right down to the dirt
In the dark, I'm kicking to the floor
Come down, check, speed for net
Nothing but this, I'm a friend to the best
The
We're back, and we're here, and Rob's running around on fire, because he's so hot.
or be attacked by a giant metallic man ah yeah you know what I'm thinking that
because the chat room has demanded it we should bring back one of our favorite
segments match game but not immediately because someone has to write up the
things for my team so we need to do the FUs of the week that is a very important
thing
you know why don't you
conduct the interview so I can get him to be ready
interview?
or am I supposed to be interviewing?
Rob's going to
let Rob do it, Rob's going to come
hurry up Rob
let him count the money and you come over here
take that mic
do you need me to write match game or do you want to do it?
Where is this cord going? It's going under Loki's chair.
Stop moving your chair around. It's rolling over the cable.
Stop moving the microphone. You know what?
I'm going to walk circles around Loki while I do this.
So, Puppy had a summer job. Where was his summer job at?
I understand that last month you had a very interesting experience while you were working
there than at the night shift.
Yes.
A little thing that's called armed takeover robbery.
I know, it's sweet.
You know what I think is so great about this is that Puppy has such a great sense of humor
about getting robbed at gunpoint.
I know, it's kind of funny.
So what happened?
What happened?
It was Sunday night, we closed at 11, but there was this last group of people out on
the golf courses that was taking fucking forever, because they were trying to like, jump on
each other and beat each other up while they were golfing, so they left about 11.30, and
then we closed up the arcade, the other employee that was there left, so it was just me and
the assistant manager there.
I went out to clean the bathrooms about 11.40, and then apparently some black truck came
2 guys come in behind me and I'm like, YOU SHOOT THE FUCK UP RIGHT NOW!
They were like, okay, whatever. And they both have their guns, they're just kind of nonchalant.
Were you high off the cleaning fumes? Was that what it is?
No, it's not that kind of cleaning fumes. It's not those kind of cleaning fluids. I kind of wish it was, though.
They basically were just like, yeah, we don't want to hurt nobody. Where's the fucking money at? How do we get in? Who else is in there? Typical shit.
It was funny because the whole time I was just like, not even, I was pretty much ignoring
the fact that they had guns, because all three of them, they had, let's see, after the first
two guys came in...
Were they real guns?
They probably were real guns, but chances are they weren't even loaded.
And it was kind of funny because as I was sitting there standing there while the two
guys with the guns were asking me questions, I saw the third guy come up around the corner
the building. He comes running around like he's a fucking 007 or something.
Like he was a Qsar. Yeah, like running around the corner looking
around like they're trying to see if there's anybody around. Like he's trying to run in
and tackle somebody. So what happened? They rounded you all up.
They got me and the assistant manager. They took me around the back through the workroom
in the back into the manager's office where the assistant manager's in there counting
money or actually he had just finished counting up all the money for the night and he had
a bag of money that was sealed up to drop off at the bank so they had us both on the
floor and they duct taped our hands behind our backs and then dug through and made a
fucking mess out of everything. And then they took the money, and they took a bucket of
change that the assistant manager usually keeps with them to take to buy options.
Well, draw plan tokens. Actually, no. Surprisingly, they didn't take tokens, which was kind of
funny. What would you do if you stole tokens? That's so sad. I know. It'd be kind of funny
to see them all take tokens. Are you that hard up for DDR that you have to steal tokens
a gunpoint.
Well, they were black.
I don't think they played DDR.
I know some...
There were black teenagers with guns.
What the hell do you think?
Well, he didn't have a gun, and he wasn't a teenager.
Anyway...
Well, I don't know what you would do with it, Lenny.
If I was a black teenager with a gun, I'd be playing DDR whenever I want.
There wouldn't be no fucking line.
Not with a gun, anyway.
So they took his bucket of change and he had sets of keys in there. They threw out two
of his three sets of keys. One of the keys was actually the set of keys to all the doors
and all the games and stuff inside the arcade. They didn't take those. They accidentally
took his car keys. Now he can't get into his car and he has to walk home. By the time this
whole ordeal was done with the cops getting there and everything. It was like almost two
in the morning.
They made off with about $4,700.
That's it?
I don't seem like that much. That's all the golf I make? Shit.
It's Castro Valley, we're not fucking Milpitas or Roseville, can you imagine how much money
that place was making today?
But they have a security job.
Not that we would advocate robbing, maybe vandalism, no, we're not advocating those
Those things were a good, polite show, but if you want to trip some little kids while
you're there, feel free.
Just don't damage their property, because we don't advocate that, because we don't want
to get sued.
Trip a little kids all you want, though.
And then tell the kids to have their parents sue Golf Land.
Okay, so the funny part was, as they left, they called the cops.
If they were to actually try, if they would have undone that, and there was just one of
them in the room, I would have probably kicked the people, the really crap out of him.
Because, I mean, I could defend myself against one person, but not three, and it was.
And then there would have been, if also the gun that he had would have been loaded, then
I could, you know, just use that.
Okay.
And then that's the whole dream sequence thing.
Enter dream sequence, and I killed all the two guys, and I'm the hero, and yeah.
Lokey called him a loser.
I don't blame him.
So did you get anything from, um, Castro Valley Golf Club from getting robbed?
Was it like, you know, did you get at least a card?
You know, sorry to hear you were robbed at gunpoint.
Yeah, here's, no.
Why don't you take tomorrow off? Did you get anything like that?
I took, I intentionally took the next day off.
But then again, did you call in and emotionally scarred to work?
No, I would have.
Well actually it was more like I needed to go out of the DMV because the fuckers took
our driver's license.
They took out both of our wallets, go through them, and take out just the driver's license.
No cash, no credit cards, no anything else.
Just our driver's licenses.
I mean, because that would have done them a lot of good to have your driver's license
because you look just like a black teenager and all.
Yeah, I know.
I ended up spending three hours at the DMV the next day to get my new driver's license
and out of all of it I got a new picture of my driver's license and now my picture looks
much better and more like me instead of me at 10 a.m.
Yeah, and you know what pisses me off about this emulator? Is that, um, no, here's what the thing is. It's like, okay, I've got the hard drive image for the Japanese version of Complete Mix 2, yet I have the ROM for the US version of Complete Mix 2, and they don't work together.
Ooh, that's not good.
No, they do for, um, it's weird because they do for Complete Mix 1, but I don't know why it's not working for Complete Mix 2.
hip hop mania is the same thing is this a different rom same hard drive image
So, let's, um, we're gonna go to a break and then come back and do the FUs.
Let's do, okay, let's do the FUs now.
The chat room can submit them while we're doing ours.
Oh wait, no, she's gonna put the music up herself, okay.
No, it's just gonna take a second here.
So, if you want to submit an FU of the Week chat room, just send those over a private message to me right now.
You can send those in while we're doing ours.
Usually I give you guys a break, but people don't start sending them in anyway until they hear us doing ours.
So, I don't think it does it all good anyway, so forget it.
So, Jamie, what happens during the FUs of the Week?
It's when we bitch about stuff.
Well, here we go.
My first nephew of the week goes toward mixed auto sales in Roseville, and they're out of
business now the bitches.
I bought my car from them.
My car had a low idle, but he assured me, you know, it's fine, we can fix it.
Now my engine is dead!
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you!
I love my car, and now it's shit.
Fuck him a whole lot.
And I can't even begin to say how mad I am over this.
Who all has been in my car with me?
Who all knows how much I love my car?
Okay, I love my car, and now it's shit.
So, I hope he eats shit.
and then, and then poops it, and then has it
Well, he's obviously bankrupt
No, I want, I want him to eat shit, poop it, and then have it fed intravenously to him
Wow
And then, and then, I want all of the, the shit blood drained from him
and then given to him as a suppository
I want him to have a bloodshed enema, because I'm so mad.
This is such a tasteful show this evening, I'm so excited.
I am so pissed, no, no.
I don't even get started when I'm really pissed off.
When I am really, really, really pissed off,
I think of the most foul and horrible things that will happen to people,
and then imagine them.
So this is me at work Friday, thinking of all kinds of foul,
and I've had days to think of how I want this man to die.
I could come up with so many good tortures, but the thing is, is that just killing him wouldn't be enough.
Because when you're dead, you can't hurt a dead person anymore.
Unless you pull their soul from the bowels of hell.
But usually the bowels of hell are even worse than what any single person alive could imagine.
Just have a defibrillator handy so that when he actually dies, like you wait five minutes
then bring him back to life and kill him again.
And you can't do that much damage to somebody though.
And you'd have to like freeze them to death and then warm up and you know thaw them out
like a TV did or, ooh microwave.
But you know you could like stick his hand in the microwave and then trigger it to where
his hand would explode.
You'd live through that.
You'd have a little bit of radiation poisoning but you'd live.
know I'm mad I'm mad I'm very mad I'm mad that my antibiotics have done
nothing that make me sick all week but I took the last one today so I'm
officially healthy but I still have to take all the other crap and my nose is still
running so I didn't do crap for that
and then and yes I love my car I said I love my car I deal with it I love my
car. And then, fuck Nissan. Because I asked them if they would order me a Skyline and
they said no. I want one. They said no. They won't. The dealerships will not actually import
the cars. You have to go buy them yourself and ship it yourself. Which is fine because
I know a place I can get one for $60,000. If I had $60,000 more, I'd go to my bank.
Hey, give me $60,000.
I need to order me a car.
I'm going to be like, uh, no.
Sure, you can have it.
But here's a 20% interest rate while we
steal your firstborn, your liver, and your kidneys
and sell them in New Orleans on the market.
Well, yeah, it'd be great.
I'll say, you can have my firstborn,
and then I just won't breathe.
So I'm cool.
I'll speak our hate.
And then, you know, if I have my computer, it does this weird thing, and I don't know why,
where it will not save my image files as a JPEG or a GIF as they're uploaded on their site's house.
It will save it as a bitmap, un-titled bitmap, so I have to title everything.
And then I have to go through and get, I have tons of bitmaps on my computer now,
so it's taking up more space than it needs to, but then again I have
that 120 gig hard drive, so I'm fine.
And then, and then, you know, there's just really not a lot else.
I can't really think of anything else.
It's really my car and my car makes me cry.
And oh yeah, a big, big F-you to Phantasy Star Online for freezing when I was going
into the ruins.
And they were just like, okay, we've gone to TGI Fridays and left our games on idle
And I had the cord holding down my analog button on the menu
so they would keep scrolling through the menu and would log me off.
I'm smart, see? Xbox.
I have the GameCube on too.
Entering that. No.
You can't do GameCube to Xbox. It does.
That's a waste of money.
If I remember right, they have
different classes. GameCube has a class, a separate class of its own.
Xbox has a separate class of its own.
I have the same one.
Oh.
Well, then it sucks.
The Xbox one has more outfits.
Oh.
But at any rate, I came back and Julie got logged off.
I stayed on.
So our room was intact.
And then so she logs on and everything.
And then as we're going down to the planet, my game freezes.
And I can't catch all my equipped items, including my Devil Wing Mags and all my Alrappies and
my God battle and my cross guards and everything, but I lost my flight plan and I lost all of
my crap items. The thing is that I have max money, so it was kind of cool. It was just
aggravating having to go get all that stuff. I went up five levels that night. It was great.
Six levels. I went up six levels. Then we did Endless Nightmare and that was cool.
I have to give an F.U. to Pepsi for making a vanilla Pepsi that tastes so damn good because
I hate Pepsi.
Vanilla Pepsi is the best.
What did I say when vanilla Coke came out?
I said, can't wait for vanilla Pepsi.
Here it is.
that same cokey aftertaste so and another at you goes toward my lifestyle
adjustment because on the outside it looks successful but not when I stepped
on the scale so I'm using my gym membership now and fuck everybody who
will go to the gym with me I hate you
okay I don't hate you I was kidding I know but I hate the guy who's holding my
car. I don't want him dead. I need a basement. Oh my god, I need a basement. If I had a basement,
I could still set up the perfect torture chamber there. I can see Jamie there right now. It
puts the lotion on its skin and puts it in the basket. And, oh yeah, fuck CD Japan for
making the pre-order for battle royale 2, 80 bucks, what? You should see how much it
is on yesasia.com. Fuck that shit. I'm just going to see if anime jungle Osaka can order
it for me, because I'll at least get it for 60 there. Because Jamie actually collects
the real thing. I buy the real thing so I can watch it on my big TV with my DVD player
over and over and over again, and then I can copy the DVDs for my friends and get a nice transfer.
What an angel.
Okay, next.
Loki, your turn.
Mario Golf?
Mario Golf is cool!
Shut up, loser.
Anyways, first I'm going to start off with a big F2 speedy oil change because you suck,
The fact that you made me wait four hours to get my tune-up the first time, then I come to find out you ripped me off on the tune-up, then you break my car, speedy oil change.
They suck, so you know, a few of them.
I should have gotten a clue when I saw a bunch of teenagers working there.
Teenagers can't fix anything. They suck.
It's like auto-shop. That's what it was. It was just auto-shop.
They have taken my car to auto-shop and having them fix it.
Well, we replaced your engine for you.
I just wanted a tune-up.
I thought you wanted us to put a lawnmower engine in there.
kostjamrh Why do I hear Ultimate Cheeseburger?
That's unacceptable.
Oh, bloop!
F you too, stupid people who can't drive.
And normally those people that turn out in front of me and then go slow.
Oh, and another thing.
If you're driving a ricer, you should not be going slower than I am, okay?
You're in a souped up car, supposedly.
Remember, the typical rice car, rice mobile now, has like, you know, a stupid four banger in it, and a hole in the muffler to sound hot.
And then just like, just a plastic box.
Yeah, but they had already just did all the, like, body modifications to it.
Haven't quite painted it yet, but they've done all the body modifications for it.
And, um, they were going really slow, in the slow lane.
And I was trying to pass them, because I was trying to, you know, go home.
Have you ever tried doing that to somebody? It's a blast.
i hate, i hate that
After the radio check, because you suck, I bought S-Video cables to hook up the TV today.
First off, they don't sell anything larger than 12 feet for S-Video.
Sure, they have 100-foot regular AV cables, but no, we don't have S-Video cables that are larger than 12 feet.
So I had to buy two S-Video cables and a connector for the two of them.
That cost $45.
Holy crap!
My turn. F you to people that aren't willing to drive 10 miles over the speed limit on
windy roads because that's what they're built for is going fast. Word.
An F you as well to the fact that it's easy to climb up a rock. You handed the mic to
If you did the fact that it's easy to climb up a rock, but it's not easy to get down, jumping is not an option.
You know wasting all that time and energy humping the rock. You know that I did not have the rock
As you did that lady who made us while a stand guard while she took a pee behind the rock
I almost did I had to have a picture of her somewhere and then when you see what this woman looks like you'll understand
Why I did not want to get a picture of her pain
Behind the rock oh my god
the
kids run over
and that you also to uh... the back of the arcade stars because that the your
machine
dot this is why should not be getting this is an i could have been able to go
And I might add, the DDR is broken.
All of them.
Yeah, but all the arrows, like, suck on DDR now,
so I can't play doubles or anything.
But, like, the shooting gallery, so you're playing 2DX,
you know, it's all, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da.
What's that noise?
Oh, that was someone shooting at us.
Oh, you shot me.
That's the shooting range.
Like, all of a sudden, I'm playing sync, right?
I have a 200-something combo going.
And then all of a sudden, oh, you shot me!
And bam, combo broken.
It's playing slag work.
You hear, oh, you got me.
That's fucked up.
That's how it was.
I wish the timing was just that good.
A few people at Paramount that thought it was a good idea
to do yet another movie about Tupac.
Yes, they're making another Tupac movie.
Tupac Resurrection.
I'm sorry. That's cool. That's cool.
Dude, Tupac gets more sequels than Batman. We're all going to go opening day.
Tupac resurrection opening day. Hey, seriously.
It's going to be fulsome. Come on. Anyway.
So yeah, that sucks and I'm trying to think what oh, yeah f you too
Pretty much Oh f you the fat bitch
Oh the stupid kid that was actually
Asking begging for money while playing DDR and they kept getting louder and louder because I was ignoring him
What?
Do you have a dog as I can have no do you have any tokens I have? No, why is it through my chair again?
p0k3smot42o1
p0k3smot42o
p0k3smot42o i have satan
you will die your chair has been liberated from the microphone
cord f either john ritter dying
doesn't he know that he has entertainment he has to do
why does he have to go off heart problems now
it's because he wasn't eating enough bacon
he has to condition his heart for bad food
i blame him
actually i blame suzanne summers
it was all her fault
Suzanne Somers is the death of him.
John Ritter sucked anyway.
I grew up with the Reese Company, hello.
But it was Suzanne Somers.
When I read that he died, the only thing that I could think of was this movie that I saw on TV.
If you have to be stuck on an island,
fighting off Indians with either Suzanne Somers
or John Ritter, you will want John Ritter on your side.
Suzanne Somers would be scarier.
Am I right?
Yeah, but that's the whole point. All you have to do is start crying and talking about the starving children in China.
Oh, and the other thing, the FU segment left like ten minutes ago.
I got one more.
Okay, FU to J-Lo and Ben Affleck, because guess what, your marriage lasted as long as Geely did in the box office.
Bam!
You suck. They broke up.
Because he had second thoughts. He's like, dude, I don't know if I can marry her.
He's such a pansy.
Her ass comes alive at night.
No, I can't handle it.
I'm looking at a bunch of straight men talking about the wedding of Ben Affleck and Jennifer Lopez.
I can't believe they're now going to get married.
Gay.
Thank you for picking that.
The other ironic thing is that I could give less than a shit about them.
I don't fucking care. I don't care what the bitch is wearing.
I don't care where they're getting married. I don't care if they broke up. I don't care if they mate. I don't care. Let's watch some guns.
It's a good thing because they're not going to breed now.
And you know what's funny is NASA's crashing a 1.5 billion dollar satellite or whatever or probe into a house.
Into their house? No, into Jupiter because they're afraid that bacteria might infect the moon around Jupiter.
I hope there's an evolving civilization on Jupiter, and it crushes them all.
It would be in Jupiter, because Jupiter's a big gaseous mass.
Much like Suzanne Somers, okay.
Again, bam.
You're so punny.
Oh, is it my turn?
Room's turn.
I've got a couple of FUs, a couple of political FUs, actually.
F you to uh...
to uh... what's-her-name
that one chick who's not getting any votes for not getting any votes i i i
wish you would
uh...
the one who's got like five percent
and who needs more
yes ariana huffington i forgot her name she she needs she needs
she needs more votes i don't have intent is the greatest candidate in the
election and you should vote for because i am i don't care she's only getting a
little bit of a vote but she's great
and um... she supports everything i believe it
and you suck
i think i think i think i think we're going to have to be down
she actually needs more votes
for not getting up close
and i'll tell you i'm telling her body like the other candidate
well she's not going to go to your she's just getting uh... a bunch of phone
calls
anyway i'd also a f you to tom mcclintock for uh... being an ass
and uh...
on a side note i'd like to say f you to nomo ono and uh...
and uh... silent profit for twisting my fragile little mind
and uh...
all i have left to say is mazel tov
my turn to rant
uh...
okay uh...
how come there's no music
i can't hear it
well then you should turn up your hearing aid
WHAT?! SONNY?!
Okay, um...
For one, fuck traffic.
Cause I hate traffic, and it's a pain in the ass, especially on every freeway.
And all the people who were on the road today.
Yes, that dumb bitch that wouldn't get out of my fucking lane.
That woman, oh my god, that woman was stupid.
And did you see the big dent in the back of her van? Yeah, it was probably from somebody she cut off like that.
She deserved it, bitch.
She looks like Sloth from The Goonies.
I didn't get to see her, but I got to see you flip her off.
You were a sick bastard.
Fuck Disneyland for ruining Big Thunder Mountain Railroad by having somebody die on it.
Because I love that ride, and now it's a death trap.
I'm waiting for a bunch of people to dial and you know Mr. Toad's wild ride
Can we get thrown out of a car and land on the ground and get run over by a car on a track?
One of the animatronics runs over him
Or I bet he has someone to fall off of the balcony in the ghost house
In the haunted mansion
That'd be great
Then that supposed rising elevator will actually collapse
And then, uh, fuck skin allergies, because they suck.
And fuck every kind of medicine that I've been prescribed to fix it and has it worked.
Or made it worse, because it sucks.
And, uh, fuck not being able to figure out anything that I wanted to rant about when I actually get here.
Because I, this morning...
Have you got it all out in the car?
I might have, yes, but I always think of stuff like on the way, like before I come, even leave to come here, and now I'm like, okay, you can have the microphone when I'm done looking.
Okay, do you have a microphone now? But I'm not done yet.
Okay, uh, let's see.
Fuck the DDR machine at Tactical Express in Davis because it's shit now.
I mean, it was kinda, it was crap before, but it's shit now.
Fuck Fuzzy's Health Drinks, because those gave me really bad diarrhea the past few days.
They taste good, but it doesn't come out the other end very well.
Thank you for that information that we didn't need to know.
No, you need to know that, because it can save you from a diarrhea trip.
Who drinks anything like that?
Really?
It looks like they have diarrhea going in.
But it's fruity, and it's colorful, and it's healthy.
Diarrhea?
Please pass the microphone.
No!
I don't feel like passing the microphone yet.
I got one more real quick and it's quiet quiet quiet time quiet time okay f you to the neighbor
upstairs because she's a racist she she she claims okay now get this cake this is her
reasoning she told she warned me and my girlfriend about the evil mexicans around here that go
and steal tools and she says i can i quote yeah i was watching my allergies and i saw
The Mexicans, and they were looking at your tools.
How can you physically watch allergies?
There goes an allergy! Oh, I better stay away from that one.
So, she sees an evil racist. I told you she was crazy. I knew it. I knew it all.
She gets racist. What's that with that sign over there, that cord that says Negro Bar?
Mexicans stole my stereo. That's really the name of the bar. I hate to break it to you, but it really is called that.
it's because it's spanish for black bar
anyway
bradley
bradley's turn
alright uh... fuck you to running out of money cause I'm almost out now
and fuck you to the
crappy economy
me for taking so long to get to the crappy economy to find a
maybe a crappy job I have to go
just to stay out here
Well, I've been talking to him about it later.
It's something good.
It doesn't require too much talking to people, because I'll suck at that.
Yeah, that's good.
See, that's why I couldn't get Bradley a job at Health Net, because I...
Oh, shit, I just gave that away where I work, but...
He is over there. He was at Death Net.
He's at Death Net.
cuz most of the people there take calls, so, you know.
I don't ever hear you talk.
Yeah.
Okay, uh, let's see.
Fuck you to having my hair being too long, it's getting annoying.
Time to cut it.
Low money, I can't really go to the barber.
I've cut my hair like twice.
I've cut my hair like the last two times.
I wonder if anyone noticed because it probably looked crappy.
Well, it's grown out now.
And fuck you to perfume inserts and cologne inserts. I hate smelling that shit all the time.
It comes in the mail. It smells up the mailbox. It smells up everything.
It smells up your mail.
Fuck you to people who wear too much cologne and perfume.
You stunk before you put it on, and then you stunk after.
Even worse.
Yeah.
And...
I don't know.
In the general, fuck you to every other crappy thing in the world.
the
job for everyone jobs for the people
uh... there bring them down
puppies ask you about an arena tonight actually tomorrow's press tomorrow's
brad's birthday
and they're celebrating tonight
because they're actually come they're actually coming over for vanilla sky
tomorrow believe it or not
well there is this good
happy birthday bread
almost a lot of cold winter nights a lot of birthdays in september i noticed
did anyone notice that i had one?
i won't tell
see you keep it a secret how do you show this to no one in the news?
there's actually an entry in my live journal that will tell you which day it was because it's a clue
there's an entry there and then
Well, happy birthday whenever it is.
It was early in the month, very early.
It's when I went to the DMV, so you can figure it out from there.
I gotcha.
I had to renew my license that day.
And that was fun waiting three hours.
At least they didn't charge me for not updating my dress for two years.
Because I feel like updating your dress is a $100 fine.
That's fine, that's good.
Dragon Rock Online. There's got to be a faster way to level up my acolyte, dammit.
Early for your...oh, never mind. That was a private interview.
Jamie says she will take you to level up.
DarkTetsuya says, F you to the stupid hit driving the pickup truck full of crap on the way to my girlfriend's.
He must have been doing 20 miles an hour.
Pixie Dust says, F you to work cutting my hours down to 26.
F you to this ugly, bitchy girl that I want to smack so bad.
computer monitor.
Dolemek says, F you to not having two days off in a row, F you to not winning Mega Butts,
which I'm guessing is a lottery in his state.
Vidpawa says, F you to nothing in particular and everything in general.
Too vague.
Everybody in mind knows Stylin says,
I'm my F-you for not having a job and my car being dead.
Sucks.
All right, that's it.
That's all for the F-yous of the week.
Finally, we're gonna do a quick break.
We're gonna set up for match game
and then we're gonna come back and do the match game.
In the meantime, I'm gonna ask a question
and the first two people to message me
the answer to this question will get to play match game.
It's a memory retention question.
How well have you been listening to this show?
Here we go.
Not last week. Not last week. I'm going to ask question of this week.
I didn't mean to put it on the microphone.
It's an easy question. If you guys don't get it, you're retarded.
Okay, here we go.
What golf land does puppy work at over the summer?
That's the question.
First two people to private message me the answer get to play match game.
match game
and i realize all you're a different differing buffers and it's probably not
fair for me to ask a question over the radio but you know what kids
life's not fair
so i feel that
in the meantime a break
with uh... a keyboard mania song i want to hear will be back
with matching
That's right, Joe Strick, joint one Before there were words, communication was
done to beat Body language is controlled by rhythm
Music is a universal link
Feel this, feel these
Uh, uh
Think of this world without sound
Can't even feel a heart pound
Wasting time, wasting life, wasting self
Shrimp in your health
Show me your drum and I'll beat on it
Brace the guitar, I'll shred
Show me your soul, one move control
And the few deaths can't be committed
Yeah, that's right
Come on, I can't hear you
What, what?
I can't feel you. What? Come on. Go on now.
Get busy. Get busy. That's right. Here we go, y'all.
Make music. Give me your time and I'll spend it.
Tell me your game and I'll say it.
Where's the help? I'll blow it.
The last alumni. That's it.
Where's the mic? I'll rip it.
Show me the club. It's on.
Give me a line. I'll send it.
The last alumni. And I'm back.
Where you from? Where you at? Where you going?
Just follow the beat. Come on!
And bring the heat, yo!
Where you from?
Where you at?
Where you going?
Just follow the beat!
Just follow the beat.
Come on!
And bring the heat.
Where you from?
Where you at?
Where you going?
Just follow the beat.
Come on, yo!
Just follow the beat!
Come on!
And bring the heat.
Where you from?
Where you at?
Where you going?
Just follow the beat!
Just follow the beat
Come on
Every day
Just follow the beat
Come on
Every day
Let's go
Just follow the beat
Hey!
Easier to dance to, isn't it?
to dance to than that freaking catch-up song, Orange Lounge Radio.
Welcome back, boys and girls, to Orange Lounge Radio. We're going to play the match game
now. Let me explain how the match game works. Basically, we're going to ask a question,
and then there's a blank somewhere in that question. We're not really asking a question.
We're saying a sentence. We're telling a story, and there's a blank in there somewhere.
You get to fill it in. The contestants will have to fill it in, and
for every celebrity they match, they get a point. So, a lot of you meanies in the chat
room got a lot of people got the answer to the trivia question correct puppy
worked at Castor Valley Golf Land over the summer and man when I told you you
were too late you just you're an asshole no sex for you you suck I hate you and I
hate your show get over it anyways the two of us need to dedicate to all these
people yes yeah I have something else to dedicate a nice big laugh for me to you
with love all right but I'm actually glad because we have two contestants who
we have never had a plane match game before. So this should be interesting. Contestant
number one, the first person to submit correctly was DJ Tyrant. Yes, a SoCal man. Contestant
number two, and this should be interesting, this is going to be very interesting, no stylin',
this is contestant number two. So contestants, you're going to send your answers. When I
ask the question, you send your answers to me over private message in the chat room.
But she was still the third person anyway. She would have had a ride if she said CVGL.
But, anyway.
Well, you know what? But she gets to listen and know that she inspired this wonderful segment tonight.
Maybe we should have an honorable third party.
Maybe we're running out of time.
Okay.
Here we go.
As much as I love Mern.
Alright, here we go. Question number one.
One day Betty the Bamani addict
Joey those are the music games
Everybody by the way is playing tonight. Everybody is a celebrity here tonight
Betty the Bamani addict decided she was tired of playing Beatmania
Instead she decided to try the new Bamani game blank
Jamie wrote all of tonight's questions, by the way, so if you don't like a question blame me
Betty, the Bomani addict, decided she was tired of playing Beatmania.
Instead, she decided to try the new Bomani game, Blank.
The contestants are thinking.
I have one contestant locked in with their answer, and I think that's both contestants.
Let me just verify they did submit answers and not questions like, huh?
Yeah, there's one.
I got a huh.
Give me a sec.
I need another pen.
Okay.
Okay, I have both answers.
Are all the celebrities ready?
Okay, here we go. Alright, let's see what you guys put. You want to do the contestants
first, or let's do the contestants first? What do you mean just in case?
I don't care. I don't care. Tyrant says, instead she decided to try the
the new Bimani game, Marshall Beat. That's not a new Bimani game but that's what he said,
so there it is. Maybe it's new at the arcade, I don't know. NoStylin says, NoStylin says
Betty decided to try the Noobamani game. DDR beat their meat.
Okay, let's see. Loki, your answer was? He decided to try the Noobamani game. Marshall
beat off. Oh, so close! Do you think that's a, do you think that's a, you know what, cause
Tyrant put Marshall beat in all caps. Beat is in caps, so the emphasis was on the beat.
We want to give them both a point? Give them both a point. Okay, so they both get a point
for that, cause they're both kind of close. Okay. A point for Tyrant and a point for No
Sound. This is amazing! Most number of points scored in the game ever. My answer, my answer
was they decided to play SARS mania. Not a match, sorry. Now Joey, this should be fun
because Joey got to see DDR, well Joey actually got introduced to the whole DDR obsession
of ours this weekend, so he's still kind of catching up on all the inside jokes, so this
should be great. Yeah, well the answer that I picked was beat me down. Beat me down! That's
It's good.
It's like punch mania, kind of.
But not a match.
So it sucks to be a contestant.
Mine was monkey mania pooflinging edition.
Monkey mania pooflinging edition, no I'm sorry that is not a match.
Puppy.
I said spoon freaks.
Spoon freaks is not a match.
I said forehead smacking mania.
Forehead smacking mania, fun but no.
night I'd kick a baby mania baby mania wonderful however not a match so after
the first round it's all tied up one to one five questions to go you guys ready
here's question number two Sally the shopaholic was so excited the outlet
mall had a new store that sold nothing but blank Sally the shopaholic was so
excited. The outlet mall had a new store that sold nothing but blank. I'm just waiting on
the chat room or waiting on our contestants to answer this question. Sally the shopaholic
was so excited. The outlet mall had a new store that sold nothing but blank. I have
One contestant.
I'm just waiting on the other one.
I'm ready.
Okay.
Okay, I got both the answers.
All right, here we go, let's read the, all the celebrities are done, right?
Yes, okay.
Here we go.
1. Sally the Shopaholic was so excited, the outlet mall had a new store that sold nothing
but F0GX 2. Tyron had a new store that sold nothing
but F0GX. Okay. This isn't Rob, it was Sally, but close. Okay. We'll see though. We'll see.
You never know. Flickin Nick Dickey. I don't know. I was thinking about that one.
Somehow I don't think it's going to match. I don't know if it's going to match, but I
said Cuban immigrants. A store that sold nothing but Cuban immigrants. No, not a match, unfortunately.
I put, Sally the Shopaholic was so excited, there was a store that sold nothing but babies!
Babies, not a match, sorry.
Joey.
Panties?
Panties, although I think Flick-a-nick-dicky might be a term for panties, I'm not sure
and I can't look it up so you lose.
Good point.
No points.
Alright, going on.
Puppy.
Oh, I'm sorry, Jamie.
Propel!
There you go!
You know, I usually expect people to pick Propel when I'm playing.
Yeah, well.
And no, stupid.
We have new contestants tonight, give them a break.
Puppy.
I say, defective condoms.
Defective condoms.
Oh, nice.
I don't know how a store would stay open, so I'm not, but okay.
Bubby.
My answer is, detached eyeballs.
Detached eyeballs, lovely, no.
A punk night.
Alright, my answer was down syndrome porn. Down syndrome porn, oh. Wow. Wow, I'm so glad
we let him go last. Alright, so after two rounds it's still tied up but one apiece.
And those are pity points by the way. Here we go, next question. Yay. Alright, shut
up here we go. Miyako was so depressed. She had been drugged and pulled into an
island with her classmates to do battle royale. And, the weapon she was given was
a blank. All right. She'd been drugged and pulled to the island with her classmates
to do battle royale and the weapon she was given was a blank we're just
waiting for the contestants to answer and waiting for all the celebrities
locking their vote Miyako was so depressed she got drugged pulled to the
island with her classmates to battle royale and the weapon she was given was
a blank? Alright, well we have music going. Mid Palace has a cassette tape of old Orange
lounge episodes. It's kind of close to what I put though. Okay, here we go. Alright, we
have the contestants logged in. Starting off with Tyrant. Miyako was so depressed she got
drugged and pulled to the island with her classmates to do battle royale. The weapon
she was given was a, Tyrant says, a trout. Like IRC, get it, a trout. Ha ha ha. Okay,
that was a cute answer, I like that. Alright. No Styler says the weapon she was given was
There's a magic kicky Dicky and the Nicky.
Oh Nicky please, not so quicky.
Okay.
Wow.
Loki, your answer please.
Three words, Iraqi suicide babies.
Awesome, anybody that used to listen to this show would get that joke.
I said the weapon she was given was a bad joke book offered by 23rd Magus.
a match, sorry. No, she'd win. She'd win. I just, I'm going to get killed. Joey, a multi-purpose
magic banana. A multi-purpose magic banana. She'd probably be too preoccupied with that
and get caught in a danger zone and her collar would explode. Mine was a yoko on a CD and
a CD player. Oh, very nice. There's a lot of this theme of like hearing things. Well,
0blivixx,0blivixx,0blivixx,0blivixx.
A monkey launcher. A monkey launcher, lovely. Alright. Okay, so not a match for either contestant, sorry.
No, in the book, in the book they have different weapons than in the movie and someone got a sticky dart gun. No, got a dart board and darts as their weapon.
all right moving on here we go still want a piece
Francine the fanfic writer was getting impatient for the next Harry Potter book
so she decided to write it herself
but she couldn't think of a good name finally she decided to name it
Harry Potter and the Blank. Francine, the fanfic writer, was getting impatient for the
next Harry Potter book, so she decided to write it herself, but she couldn't think of
a good name. Finally, she decided to name it Harry Potter and the blank.
She decided to name it Harry Potter in the blank.
I'm just waiting for both contestants to lock in with an answer here.
Finally, she decided to name it Harry Potter in the blank.
I need an answer, too.
All right.
Okay.
Here we go.
Ready?
Are we all ready?
Yes.
Ding, ding.
Everybody's named.
All right.
No silence says.
She decided to call it Harry Potter gone wild with a bomb and a cannon.
Harry Potter gone wild with a bomb in a can of some sort
DJ Tyrant Harry Potter and the breast implant
Loki. Let's see if we get a match. Damn, I have like two. Well, since they're both not
matching anyways, Harry Potter and the Horny Catholic Priest, or Harry Potter and the Sex
Change. But I like Horny Catholic Priest better.
Would he be Harriet Potter?
The Horny Catholic Priest would be kind of close. That would be like a half point. But
Horny Catholic Priest was your first pick.
Would he be Harriet Potter?
I was kind of stretched for an answer, so I used a good classic inside joke.
I said Harry Potter and the Stars Infested Monkeys.
Joey.
Harry Potter and the Search for Sexual Release.
Nice.
Whale.
Jamie.
I said, and people who actually are fans of the book would get it, and it also fits in
with the show, Harry Potter and the Magical Bouncing Ferret.
Harry Potter and the Swedish Furniture Good answer, but not a match.
Harry Potter and the plus filled Acne of Doom Appropriate, but not a match.
night. Harry Potter and the pile of dead babies. Not a match, I'm so sorry. Alright, here
we go, two more questions to go. Will they break the tie of one to one? Probably not,
but let's keep playing anyway. Here we go. Perry the painter was working on his new masterpiece
and ran out of a few of his paints. He was almost done, so to replace the missing paints
he used blank. Perry the painter was working on his new masterpiece and he ran out of a
few of his paints. He was almost done, so to replace the missing paints he used blank.
The contestants are thinking about their answers.
The celebrities are thinking about their answers.
Here's the question one more time.
Perry the painter was working on his new masterpiece and ran out of a few of his paints.
He was almost done, so to replace the missing paints he used blank.
I'm waiting on both contestants.
Oh, looks like we might have one.
p0k3smot42o
Tyrant said, Perry the painter was working on his new masterpiece and ran out of a few
of his paints.
He was almost done, so to replace the missing paints he used pus from zits.
No stylin says.
To replace the paints he used the jizz and then afterwards decided to fap to some Orange
Lounge Radio.
Aw, how lovely.
Way to show your love.
Alright, uh, Loki.
Um, he used clubbed baby seals.
Nice, but not a match.
Uh, I said he ran out of paint, so he decided to use skin.
Not a match.
I'm just being morbid.
You know, I was gonna use jizz myself, but then I decided to just use blood.
So simple, not a match.
Jamie.
The brains of golf lads children used the dog rotting on his doorstep.
A bulimic person's vomit.
A bulimic person's vomit. Colorful, not a match. Wow.
Alright, here we go, last question. This is your last chance to get a point, otherwise
we're going to have a tie and nobody likes a tie.
Alright, here's a question.
Kelly was tired of staying at home all day
so she decided that she would leave. She hopped in her car and decided that she was
gonna go on a road trip to blank.
All questions this evening written by Dark Sacra.
Enjoy. Kelly was tired of staying at home all day so she decided that she would leave.
She hopped in her car
and decided that she was going to go on a road trip to blank.
We are waiting on the contestants to answer the question. You're listening to
orange lounge radios match game
Is the Twilight Zone with a mystery host
Thursday night is live wire with the one and only Loki live mixing of various money songs god dammit
No styling hurry up, or I'm putting in an answer for you
I'm gonna let somebody else for the show
Or I'll beat you as a ferret until you die
Yeah, no frowny face perhaps I need to read the question one more time
Kelly was tired of staying at home all day so she decided that she would leave
she hopped in her car and decided she was going on a road trip to blank I have
an answer all right beautiful we have an answer all right and let's let's hear
what no silence answer is Kelly hopped in the car and decided she was going on a
road trip to the famous SARS land that was provided by Baca being another one
our chat regulars trying to take a slam on bucket there lovely answer we'll see
if it's a match I DJ tyrant says she decided to take a road trip to Castro
Valley Golf Lands very nice let's see if we get a match Loki she took a trip to
the big Thunder Mountain to ride the big Thunder Mountain railroad I thought
I thought you were about to say the dark black forest, but I said she was going to take a
trip to the McFlicky Dick Nicky, and you know, I tried to toss you a bone and you didn't
take it, so you lose, sorry.
Julie?
I couldn't think of anything, but she took a trip to the old Penisville.
The Penisville!
How nice.
Jamie?
She took a trip to that hand basket going straight to hell to join the Orange Challenge crew on their way there.
Yay! We're going to hell!
Yay!
Puppy, your answer?
I said to ride the death traps at Disneyland.
The death traps at Disneyland? I see Disneyland would have got you two points right there.
Bradley?
She took a trip to her local whorehouse.
To her local whorehouse! Practical!
But not a match.
She took a trip to dig up grandpa.
She took a trip to dig up grandpa. Beautiful, but not a match.
Alright, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah.
So, the final score is DJ Tyrant. One point! No stylin'. One point!
So, who do we want to win? Who do we want to win?
Nobody. I win!
Yeah, that's right. You know what? When they tie, that means we win. So congratulations
Orange Lodge Radio. We'll beat the chat room because we're better. Just kidding. Just kidding.
Stay, stay. I forgot to mention for my birthday, well, this is probably something for the afterbirth,
but I got erotic magnets. Erotic poetry magnets. You can make...
Put them on the fridge. Because they're not on the fridge. Because
people need to be creative and put erotic phrases on the fridge.
I'm going to go do one right now!
Right, I have no time to take a break, so I need to wrap up what's the news I wanted to get to.
Bahmani News, here we go, last three minutes of the show, we have some Bahmani News.
More U.S. home version songs have been confirmed for Max 2, here they are.
Loki, you'll be surprised at some of these.
Feeling of Love.
Oh my God!
max unlimited
surprise more deep version 2.1
a good song
and xenon
in max 2
ddr ultramix
castles in the sky will be in ddr ultramix that's ian vandahl
colors by dj taka and sugaru
also in other news on uh... ddr freak right now they're having people suggest
uh... songs that you would like to see
in UltraMix is probably one of those packs you have to buy for songs, you know, and whatnot.
So, go there and do that.
Plus, DDR Max 2 is going to have an all-new updated system for the diet mode.
They're going to have, like, you know, workout courses you can do, like low impact, high impact,
I'm lazy, you know, that type of thing.
So, fun stuff like that.
And you're probably going to see max period at some point in there.
Kitten. That's a dumbass name for a freaking song I've ever seen.
You know what's interesting? I'm noticing more and more that Max 2 is basically a US
version of Xtreme. It really is. It's a US version of the Japanese Xtreme.
So that means it's going to suck?
No, I think it's actually going to be really good because we've already all played Xtreme.
You know what's interesting though? We played the demo. Loki and I played the demo for Max
2 USA. We have it. And we were playing D2R. The first thing I noticed is that D2R has
D2R has Xtreme's video. It doesn't have the D2R video for Max 2 because they're different.
If you think about it, yes they are. In Xtreme you had this, I recognize one of the videos,
it's like a matrix effect where you have the numbers changing while it's running down the
screen.
That wasn't Max 2.
No it wasn't, but it wasn't in the D2R video. I'm almost positive, I'm like 99% positive
that D2R has a new video in this. It has Xtreme's video, not Max 2's video.
Oh, it doesn't really matter, it's a background video.
Yeah, I know. Not that we really give a shit, but that makes me think that, oh, it's based
off Xtreme's engine, not Max 2.
Well, it didn't...
Whatever.
Well, I thought they said that, didn't they?
It's based off of Euromix 2.
Ew!
It's not an engine.
So there.
Euromix.
I had a point I wanted to make. Also in Xtreme, they've announced that most of the unlocks
from the arcade, I'm not gonna read the whole list, but pretty much anything that was unlocked
by a code in the arcade, songs such as Sink, Dance Dance Revolution, Paranoia Survivor,
etc. is a hidden track.
Your mama's on crack rock, you should be in DDR.
Pixie Dust is suggesting your mama's on crack rock should be in DDR Max 2.
You should go suggest that in the DDR.
That is the best suggestion ever to be in DDR.
Not my mama, my mama in rehab.
That song was the best.
I have, like, on a tape that I made when I was in middle school.
What a lovely thought.
I'm going to go download that tonight.
Okay, um, any other Bamani news anyone had to report?
I mean, we've got the game, the game is out in a week and a half, Max 2.
And, uh, Wednesday night, next, a week from Wednesday, we're going to do, um, what we
did for Max 1, we're going to play it, we're going to just bring home the copy and play
it on air.
Yay.
Although I believe it's actually being released on Tuesday, right?
The 24th.
The 24th is a Tuesday.
Wednesday.
Oh, it's Wednesday?
I don't know anymore.
I didn't know because I have to start classes on the 25th.
Oh.
It's Thursday.
Well, we'll see.
Plan on that Wednesday.
If you're not able to get your copy of Max 2, don't worry about it.
We're going to play it here and you can listen in.
We'd like to live stream your video instead of just like a webcam.
We'll see what we can do about that.
So stay tuned for that.
That'll be next Wednesday for sure.
This Wednesday we're going to have some surprise programming, who knows.
Now is the part of the show I believe it's time to go around and gather everyone's final
thoughts I think.
Unless anyone else has Bamani's?
No, they need to have the Oha Ska.
Oha.
That would be cool.
Okay.
Final thoughts time.
I guess we're there.
Anybody else have anything they want to bring up?
Good, we can end this train wreck of a show.
What?
Play endearing music.
My point.
What do you want?
Give me a final thought, Dammit.
Give me a final thought.
College rules.
Lovely.
Bradley, do you have a final thought?
Slam it, cram it, jam it, dammit.
Okay.
Punkknight, muzzletuff, I hate you.
Jamie, oh, uh, Joey, do you have a final thought? No, he has no final thought.
Uh, what, you wanna go last? My final thought is, um, yay.
Loki, I'm gonna have an arcade cabinet and you don't, I'm gonna have an arcade cabinet and you don't.
My final thought is go to your local game shop and pre-order Transformers Season 3 boxset and sign up for replay.darksakra.com
And right after the show at 10pm, be sure to tune in to Conan O'Brien's 10th anniversary special, 9.30, 9.30, right, right now, right now, why are you all listening?
Alright, so I guess that's a sign we need to end this show then. Final word of the show, I'll give it to Joey. He gets one word, you say one word and it's the final word of the show, so what is the final word of the show?
P.A.C.E.
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Dark Sakura, Sky and Loki.
We expect you a nice play again.
And now, here's your porch and cookie message of the day.
We must be strong and brave, our home, we've got to save If we don't in just one year,
Mother Earth will disappear!
Fighting with the Gavilons, we won't stop until we've won.
Then we'll return, and when we arrive,
The Earth will survive with our Star Blazers!
Thanks for listening, and we'll see you next week.