This week it's getting cold outside but the news is heating up the next streaming game
service will be better than a local experience and the new PlayStation is named as unsurprisingly
as it possibly could be these are headlines you already know about stay tuned for plenty
more you may not starting right now on the show where every gamer has a voice orange lounge radio
hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where
every gamer has a voice it is orange lounge radio live tonight episode number 796 for this
October the 13th of 2019 my name is Rob Roberts joining you here as always with my co-hosts say
hello to DarkSakura or Jamie Summers why hello there and welcome back I hope you're feeling
better mostly okay all right well I got a weird pillow a weird a weird pillow yeah I've been
having you know I've had some damage to my cervical spine over time yeah and so I picked up this like
weird memory foam cervical pillow and it's like got these grooves on the side I can put my arms
over my head it's just really weird but I've had the first good nights of sleep I have in the
longest time well sleep is amazing yes it is it's nice not waking up in the middle of the night
and also say hello to tech master Loki hello how are you Loki I'm fine great have a good week yeah
it's all right all right we'll talk about games that you played and all that good stuff a little
later but for now I want to jump right into our kickoff topic tonight because it's been quite the
week in the gaming news world hasn't it give it a name what the name of the week or the name of
the story or what the name of the whole thing fuckery I'm honestly not a bad word for it
shenanigans I I don't know what to say it's it's been a weird week um okay so here's the deal I
know many of you that subscribe to gaming podcasts and the like and and watch streams on Twitch
probably stay somewhat afloat on gaming news so I don't like to think that I'm reporting the news
here at orange launch radio but we definitely want to discuss it with those of you guys in chat
because of course we do tape live every Sunday night at the voice of geeks Network twitch TV
slash vog network that's VOG Network six o'clock Pacific nine o'clock Eastern every Sunday night
right after the Bobby Black Wolf show so I'm sure a lot of you have heard about this already you've
heard one thing or another if you didn't hear it in the gaming blogs or social media or what have
you you probably heard about it maybe in some mainstream news because that is how big this
story has gotten this story had senators from the United States commenting on it it's that big a
deal what am I talking about of course I'm talking about this situation with Blizzard and the player
that they banned so Blizzard of course as you probably know suspended one of their competitive
players after a hearthstone competition the name of the player blitz chung is kind of the online
handle of the player and he was in a grandmasters Asia-pacific post-match interview and as he was
kind of wrapping up the interview and said goodnight goodbye that type of thing he said
liberate Hong Kong revolution of our age now if you don't know what's going on in the world at
large there's a lot of protests going on in Hong Kong Hong Kong was under British rule for quite
some time up until you're wrong but it was about 10 15 years ago and I'm sorry I don't know the
year off it was I think more recent than that I think definitely within the last decade well see
here's here's what comes to mind so you guys I'd say you guys here in studio not you guys out there
but you guys remember my ex was from Hong Kong right so he a big reason why I think his family
kind of relocated was because of that handoff that was coming up so it handed off from British rule
to Chinese rule long story short and I am greatly simplifying things 97 so my bad okay so it was
about 20 years and so I'm greatly simplifying things so I apologize but I do you know I do
want to get through the show tonight the people in Hong Kong don't necessarily want to be under
Chinese rule anymore so the people of Hong Kong are kind of speaking up and they would like to
kind of be their own you know country basically I'm really really simplifying a lot of things so
I again please don't feel the need to call me out because I'm openly admitting I'm taking some some
shortcuts here but that has people voicing you know obviously their opposition to wanting to
stay a part of China and wanting to be liberated as you can imagine this is very controversial
within China if you want to go back 20 years now I don't know about you guys or our folks that are
listening but I remember do you guys remember when they were having those free Tibet concerts
to bet and freedom stuff that was kind of an issue where Tibet also under Chinese really it was almost
like kind of a similar ish and again I'm greatly simplifying type of thing there so you know China
has controversy China doesn't have things like the First Amendment for example right we have the
freedom of speech and if I want to sit here and say Donald Trump sucks donkey dick I can say that
because of the First Amendment would protect me because I can openly criticize the president and
I may or may not have done that a few times on this very program right China you don't have such
freedoms right and we kind of know that the internet is locked down a lot in China as well
right there's a lot of websites and a lot of things you can access in China I'd imagine twitch is
probably one of those websites I don't know that for a fact but I can only imagine because twitch
has open speech running rampantly it's likely a website that they probably don't care for in
China so anyway that's a little bit of the oversimplified history lesson as to why why
would somebody want to say this on a live stream why would somebody want to go here and why is this
such a hot-button button political issue because there are many individuals in Hong Kong who don't
want to be under Chinese rule anymore China feels very differently about the issue okay so what
happened after this the stream went to an ad break very quickly and there was some harsh punishments
dealt by Blizzard Blizzard mentioned that Blizz chung violated such section 6.1 of the competition
rules which say that players cannot engage in any act that quote brings you into public disrepute
offends a portion or group of the public or otherwise damages Blizzard image and so what
was the punishment removal from the grandmasters surrendering of the prize money all of it and the
two presenters even though they quickly kind of did this whole like they want to cover their faces
like they they know what he just said is like oh shit they're like and they cut quickly to a
commercial Blizzard immediately ceased working with both of those casters as well and this left
a lot of people going wow does the punishment fit the crime I don't know about that and a lot of
people were left very confused and very angry because there's a lot of people out there who
also say if the people of Hong Kong want to be free then they ought to have a conversation
about being free that's the way many many many people feel out there now here's the thing from
and now I'm starting to interject some of my personal opinions here I can understand if
Blizzard wants their competitors to not say controversial political statements about anything
because they don't want to drag their game into you know politics it's really hard when you're
competing in a worldwide market because not every country functions the same way I get that as part
of follow-up to this you might have heard Riot Games basically has begged their professional
players please do not bring up politics Riot Games is also owned by Tencent a Chinese company
but I digress okay they they have asked their players please do not bring up these controversial
political issues on stream so I can understand if you sign a contract as a player whether it's
fair or not if you sign a contract as a player that says you will not talk about controversial
political statements and you do then okay I understand why Blizzard felt the need to
retaliate a little bit but I ask again does the punishment fit the crime because I'm not sure it
did and I think that's where a lot of people were left I really don't understand how the casters are
responsible for that when they're just giving the interview and that's a regular thing though in
news old-school communist governments I mean really it is a standard demo yeah so where are
we at now so I mean again I'm sure a lot of you are sitting there going but Blizzard has put out
to say yes so after several days and this is the part a lot of money lost I'm sure yeah oh yeah
this is the part that blew my mind it took them this happened on Monday right it took them five
days Friday 530 Pacific or 830 Eastern like that's the time when the throwaway news comes
out Friday at 530 Blizzard releases a statement and Blizzard says we're listening this this
decision was not influenced by China and our relationships oh shit because many people out
there were accusing Blizzard of you are up China's ass so much and you don't want to lose their
business that you threw the baby out with the bathwater with not only this player but the two
broadcasters and I gotta admit for me the two broadcasters with a part where I was like give
me a fucking break they did not deserve that punishment that's still though mo for countries
like China exactly and I think that's why many of us here in America because we have a different
view on things because of you know we we have the Bill of Rights and our Constitution and so forth
we're kind of seeing they're going this is not indicative of what our country would do and while
you might argue well but it's a worldwide market this is an Asia term Blizzard still an American
company right so I think that's why there's a lot of people that feel very strongly still about this
so after what four or five long days and I couldn't believe it took this long Blizzard puts out the
statement it's not China's thing we're gonna give the prize money back because under as a follow-up
consideration it was determined that he didn't cheat he won the competition fair and square so
why take away the prize money duh this is the thing we should have we asked you to that your
player base kind of expected you to know at the beginning you took away the money why and we're
gonna reduce the suspension to six months but then they they went so far as to still say it
was the broadcasters responsibility to not let this conversation turn into politics and get
political whatever they are says they are still suspended for six months it's still garbage it's
horrible this is still I think a lot of I my theory as to why it took so long is that they
were speaking with whoever their handlers were in in China to make sure that they could do something
in a way that wouldn't damage their business dealings in China um I'm gonna sort of say yes
to that I think it was legal departments that took it this long and all the legal hurdles namely
Activision's legal hurdle this shit wouldn't happen under Mike Morhaime I said it this shit
would not have happened under Mike Morhaime and it wouldn't happened when Activision wasn't in
the picture and it's so frustrating as somebody who's been like such an advocate of Blizzard
games in the past and so forth because it's like the Blizzard I know and love this is the harsh
reality like you've kind of like seen it coming for a long time like the Activision bought Blizzard
and then it's like Call of Duty was in the launcher and all this other stuff and but it's like the
harsh reality is Blizzard is not that like on your side as the player they are not that we are just
like you guys don't want a game and all this stuff if last year's Blizzcon didn't make that
very apparent this whole scenario did because it's Activision's legal department it's Tencent's legal
department that made this thing take so goddamn long so what do I think they should have done well
for one this suspension should not have been as harsh as it was I would have been okay if they
said you know what this blitzchung you signed a contract that said you would not get into
politics because it makes things very complicated we're trying to do things in a world market so
therefore we're gonna suspend you for three games and we're not doing any on-camera interviews with
you for six months I think that would have been more appropriate right I don't know what do you
guys think I mean because I can still understand Blizzard has to navigate tricky waters I get it
but like what they did was like way above and beyond I'd be honest I mean if it were up to me
personally like if I was the one who had to press the button I would have been like do nothing
honestly that's what should have been done in a protected world however you know if anything I
think Chinese politics is the biggest thing to blame that's it well for sure I don't mean to
ignore you guys in chat we just have a lot going on here quest buster and chat says the apologies
made to Western audiences into China were also very different from each other the one for China
promised to uphold national dignity yeah there was an interesting statement on a Chinese is it is
it why bow way bow I'm sorry I don't know the name off top my head but there's a Chinese social
network out there and it's way bow way bow thank you um a account that is supposedly blizzards
Chinese account made a very pro China statement I don't know how else to summarize it was very
like you know we're gonna make these decisions that uphold national dignity and because of course
they did it was it was kind of like it was really a fuck you to everything that was going on over
here with like the protests and people canceling their accounts I know many longtime Blizzard fans
that are like canceling their World of Warcraft accounts I'm including me I uninstalled World
Warcraft today after I unsubbed about two days ago you guys know I've been talking a lot about
World of Warcraft classic and I've been talking about World of Warcraft on this show I unsubbed
and I think a lot of it has to do with kind of that harsh reality that we're in that Blizzard
is now on the same level as EA and I feel sorry I just I'm processing a lot of information as I
think we all are because it's it's so weird like it's just a fucking game but I think for many
people World of Warcraft and in particular and especially you know other other certain things
like overwatch and Blizzcon stuff too Blizzard has historically done a very good job building
communities in these games like people with their World of Warcraft guilds like that is family to
some people right so it's so extraordinarily frustrating to watch that house that your family
is residing in slowly and slowly get turned into a Starbucks I don't know how else to describe even
Starbucks has more user friendly you know what I'm getting at though yeah it's the corporation
coming in and transforming that store being taken over by a Walmart that safe space is suddenly
transforming you know what I mean and I feel really bad for people that have spent a lot of
money to go to Blizzcon this year shit the girls on this network at girls gone wow they're over in
the UK they're going to Blizzcon for the first time this year and this shit has to go down that
is extraordinarily frustrating and I'm not gonna speak for them they have their own show and they
can talk about this or not talk about this whatever they choose to do but I can just look
at people like that and people that are you know out there and you know playing this and they want
to go to Blizzcon this event because it's to see their families and to see the people that they
play these games online with and to have all this happen is so frustrating and then I think about
the various people I've met over the years that work for Blizzard and I know several and I can't
speak for them either and I'm not even about to try but I can say y'all seen those pictures online
of the statue at Blizzard headquarters where it says every voice matters and it's covered up with
paper by the employees who did that and you can see the people standing around the statue the
employees because you got to be an employee to get in there with their umbrellas and what's the
umbrella a sign of that's a that's a symbol that goes with the yeah the liberate Hong Kong movement
so while I can't speak for the people I know I can let those pictures do the talking and so I'm
extraordinarily frustrated for them that this shit happens on an executive level it's it's horrible
what's happening you're watching this company that you knew and loved so much just fall apart and I
know other people out there that are like you know what this doesn't bother me I just want to play
the game I respect people's right to protest but I'm not saying people eating a chick-fil-a well
here's the thing and you know what you can choose what you do and you don't want to do and that is
absolutely fine to be honest but I think even somebody who's somebody in that position could
kind of recognize where it's very frustrating for a lot of us you know what I mean I can understand
you know if you bought overwatch you want to get your money's worth and keep playing it I get that
right I mean that's that seems reasonable to me but I didn't see a need to continue paying a
monthly fee for World of Warcraft anymore and if I was gonna get overwatch on the switch I don't
think I will now I'll reevaluate my thinking in six months since that's the time frame we've
decided to settle on that's where my head's at right now any comments from you guys before I go
to chat I'm probably not gonna re-up it all ever I had been considering it now I'm not although
right now I'm be honest I'm not really gonna re-up on any MMOs right now just because I don't have
the time for it but I had been floating it around in my head whether or not I wanted to and this
pretty much cinched it for me I went went in and uninstalled basically all my Blizzard games I
didn't install well because I was using the wow model viewer but actually now I'm gonna remove
that because I and I have to apologize to psychic for this but I'm not gonna continue with webcomic
using the well models again I'm not gonna do it I'm changing switching my directions because I
don't want to give them any advertising I don't want to support a company that's gonna behave this
way because just because they do it once and then think six months from now people are gonna forget
about it or oh we've changed this in six months they're gonna go back and do the same shit you
know there's already talks about protests at Blizzcon and all this stuff but I want to be
clear on something because this is this is a really weird thing that's happening because
there are people it's one of these weird or not when we live in such a divisive world where we
have you know folks on the left and folks on the right really going at each other right folks on
the left and folks on the right on Twitter kind of all seem to agree what Blizzard did shitty so
it's weird that there's this agreement going on there but some of those like shitty extreme
Twitter people are now getting involved with this whole thing and I just want to make very clear it
is not okay period to harass Blizzard employees to harass Blizzard fans to harass Blizzard content
creators who decide that because they need to still make money to pay their rent they're gonna
continue to create content it is not okay to harass those people period we've got that same
thing going on with the PG&E some some one of the PG&E workers got murdered over something that was
a decision over the company oh my god that's disgusting that's disgusting you know and it's
like this is it is not their fault so y'all I know our OLR listeners and viewers are good enough to
know better but I just need feel the need to say it like it's not okay to harass the employees okay
but it is okay to peacefully protest with signs so that you're seen it is okay to peacefully protest
with management it is okay to do those types of things and and you know if there's a peaceful
protest that's gonna go down at Blizzcon but let the attendees in because some of them came a long
way and have paid a lot of money to have this be the year the Blizzard shit on I will tell you one
thing that does sort of break the purpose of a protest is that civil disobedience in and of
itself is meant to inconvenience the population into paying attention to an adverse situation
that's the whole point of it that was why people you know here at pride while why the protesters
were making a sort of a stockade around the the event it's because you know why people block you
know the bridges in trying to protest for Black Lives Matter and many of the other charities out
there is the fact that you don't get the kind of attention and immediate action that happens as
you get when you make it a inconvenience for other people especially today we're way too
distracted by our modern conveniences how easy is it to say oh well the world is terrible right now
I'm gonna go play a game which is fine every so often but when you cut yourself off from
participating in things that even they don't affect your life immediately they're still going
to affect people that you know it still affects the world that you have to be a part of and just
pushing it away I say oh they can do this peacefully where no one can see them versus
no they're gonna be in your face they're gonna bring the attention to you the people that need
to be inconvenienced are the executives do you want Raven and EJ to not be able to go to bliss
con when they have waited years they can't go you know they're gonna the thing is is that to do it
legally they're they're not gonna be able to block any entrances and exits so that's not gonna be a
problem especially in a big places where this is gonna be I mean not a problem I mean even bringing
that up is like that that can't happen but the thing that I'm saying is that if you inconvenience
the people attending it directly inconveniences the people making money off of them because
there's gonna be complaints there's going to be letters written it's going to spawn more action
I kind of think the action is gonna really have to happen way before Blizzcon quite frankly like
and I think like if we were to put our finger on why are we upset like let's let's put our finger
clearly on that why are we mad at Blizzard what's the why here because for me it was the in bit well
obviously the original action was way too extreme that's part of it but for me like what really
broke the camel's back for me was how long it took them to respond to that it was straight-up
disrespectful in my opinion there are two statements here in chat that I agree with sure
I'm for SSJ 100 Matt says Blizzard is going to look at the week one sales of overwatch switch to
see if players really do care about the issue and then act-deaf says Blizzard will still exist it
won't go under anytime soon but what but what we do to support the free Hong Kong movement will speak
louder than any words or statement we make and that's a big thing actually that I'd really like
to see happen is that while people are taking their money away from Blizzard and hitting them
and in the pocketbook you know the big place that that counts we also need to be putting you know
for taking those resources from Blizzard why don't we put those resources into a charity that
supports the things that Blizzard seems to be trying to squash even if it's just indirectly
you know why don't we put that support in with with free Hong Kong why don't we help them with
protesting efforts why don't we help them with the materials that they need to continue to fight for
their freedom you know especially coming from people in America where that's pretty much we
were raised on being so completely religiously stupid that we have to oppress all other religions
and out of saying fuck you to other government powers so why can't we at least help them with
the fuck you part just saying I I would super agree that the most effective thing you can do
is to stop giving Blizzard money if you disagree you know cancel your wow accounts don't buy
overwatch on switch and those are the things that I plan to do for a little while while we wait and
see you know what Blizzard is gonna do is remember the physical version of overwatch on the switch
is actually just a download code so just you know but you get a box and there was a comment as to
the the week one commentary or you know the thing is is that the majority of people who are going
to get it will get it week one and that's where the bulk of the sales for any kind of game movie
entertainment comes out that's when it happens that and Black Friday or Cyber Monday you know
the big that's going to be the benchmark for if people do care about it because if it's something
that they care about why not why aren't they gonna get it day one it's digital why why you know why
wait if if they want it they're gonna get it and I think that we need to you know make sure that
people really do if they hate what Blizzard's doing they need to have some integrity and stick
to it you know and I know that we bring that we brought up other boycotts you know and some of
them are like oh well this is a minor thing it's not gonna really affect the the whole thing but
like in the case of I'm just use this as an example in chick-fil-a it was recently discovered
that they were funding missionaries who are going over and working with governments that are setting
up executions for gay people on file you know do you want to fund that kind of thing do you want to
contribute to this if the answer is no then you don't eat there anymore or you know with Blizzard
if you don't want to fund them you know just completely giving in to the dictates of China
then you don't support them anymore you don't support this activity you don't support these
business practices if you don't like but the joke let me if you don't support like for example what
GOP is doing you don't vote for them you don't support businesses that contribute to that you
know I'm saying that way you put your money where your integrity is but where do we draw the line
because I feel like you can have a reason to boycott everything I mean in this same bucket
people are talking about they're mad at Apple because Apple shut down an app where Hong Kong
protesters were using it to know where police were Tiffany and company had an advertisement
where it looked like a woman was covering her eye and the China folk China government found that
offensive so Tiffany and company had to pull that ad and there's more examples of this too
specifically with the China and Hong Kong issue so my point is like where do you draw the line
because I feel like for me with Blizzard specifically I think it's because you have this
very kind of like tangible punishment type of thing that happened and you have this big shift
in a company that you've supported for so long that's kind of happened and I think that's why
this one I feel like I really want to do something about this particular one I I think in cases like
for you know if it's something like an app you do have to do with international legalities there's
apps that we can't put out in the US for example for any service because they break federal law
you know I think that's a completely different story than going in for an active punishment of
a person for for using their voice that's a completely different scenario so you have to
kind of pick and choose for you not necessarily for me I have to look at the big picture you know
if you were dealing with you know say that you have X bad thing happen in one country but say
you have them doing different things in other places to offset it you know oh you know for
Blizzard this was a completely punitive action they took against a party that went above and
beyond what should have been what should have been done and the fact that they're defending
their actions is is also a completely different story too we have something more actively showing
the culture of the company in something like the app for example when you were also though
dealing with a company that that donates to companies that are not companies but organizations
that are going for international you know freedom attempts freedom of speech health care that's a
completely different story it doesn't mean that oh all things that China does are great it means
yeah our hand is tied on this one but we're doing other things to offset it you know for example if
you're dealing with you know a company that's out there actively trying to you know end an
entire group of people across the world yeah giving children books is gonna be very small
potatoes in regards to what could end up being seen very well as close to I'll put this way just
Nazi actions you know killing entire groups of people what we have going on in Syria right now
is absolutely horrendous and it's along those same lines it's an active punitive action that
is killing other people I'm to try to wrap this all up and move on to other topics from the week
because there has been other gaming news this week isn't it interesting how you know I think
there's been folks that's been critical of this program in the past you know you and me specifically
because gaming and politics should mix type of thing keep the political talk on the gaming
podcast but isn't it funny that here we are now where it's like we don't have a choice we have to
talk about it because it's impacting the industry like big time so it's kind of like you you you have
to be aware of this stuff and you know make your decisions and so forth it's just it's just
interesting to me that it's like because Blizzard deals in international markets and so forth I get
it they have to walk a fine line I do understand that but isn't it interesting that you know now
there's a lot of gamers that are talking about politics essentially in the fact that we sort of
feel that this punishment didn't fit the crime for just speaking out on how many people in the
country of Hong Kong feel so um anyhow I was looking for some other comments in chat so they're
talking let's see see a Tiberian chat is kind of talking about the you know boycotting a lot of
different things there's an episode of the show Adam ruins everything it's a show I've never seen
to be honest I love that show that talks about that for a little bit called Adam ruins a plate
of nachos which I think is the whole like you know every company that contributed to the nachos
is trash type of thing so there's there are some things on that show that that are factually
incorrect so I'm just gonna leave there you know how you ruin a plate of nachos you put olives in
it actually you've been rather quiet this little segment how are you doing well you don't really
play Blizzard games exactly I'm not affected by this I don't play any of these games so it's fine
no I I've overwatch I haven't played those for a few years so yeah I mean I don't know I I don't
have time for an MMO so that it's not like I would quit it for political reasons but I just
don't have time so I mean the fact that Activision Blizzard is doing something shitty well hello it's
a day of the week so I mean just remember Call of Duty's right around the corner you get your
whole whole nother fill of Activision Blizzard doing shitty stuff some other comments from chat
captain spike says Rob you're gay everything you do touches the political yeah fair and Bobby
Blackwell says surprisingly no talk about the gay guilds name band oh yeah thanks for reminding me
because that was the thing too that was honestly it was one of the things where it was like I was
already mad at this other thing is like when I heard about this gay guild name getting banned
type thing I was just like what else do we want to throw on the fire let's just you know and
another one why not let's just let's let's do the airing of the grievances shall we like it's just
but if you didn't hear I think it was in Wow classic there was a guild name called gay boys
so many people reported it that the name got stripped now in the essence of fairness it was
restored but it does go a long way in talking about why are these automated things why is it
automated why isn't it looked at by somebody because by doing an action like that it makes
it look like you endorse it whether you really do as a company or not etc etc etc quite honestly
again you're so mad about the one thing it's like that oh this just add that to the fire
unlike any other week I probably would have been like well that was a bad look but at least they
made it right and maybe they'll learn something in the future but this week it was like fuck them
it's it's hard it's difficult it's it sucks again to use the analogy that I use all of the time on
this program when we're talking about how can you love video games and love gaming companies yet be
so critical of them it's like Tyra Banks infamously did on that season of America's next pop model
where she yells be quiet Tiffany we were rooting for you we were all rooting for you how dare you
and that quite essentially sums up how I feel about this whole situation with Blizzard let's
see going to some other comments in chat over at twitch.tv slash vog network quest buster says
Blizzard just keeps throwing logs on that fire slidekick says let's start a guild in another
game called gay boys you know it's funny like I've gotten like two people sending me private
messages asking me like so how do I sign up for Final Fantasy 14 and I don't know if like Final
Fantasy 14 necessarily wants to just I mean it's hard it's hard to say like I I realize I'm saying
they don't want to get all this business because of what's happening with Blizzard I I but what
I'm trying to say is that I think Square Enix would quite frankly like to stay out of this
issue but the reality is Final Fantasy 14 a while have a lot in common so there's a lot of people
that are like well now's a good time to go looking for good time to go play port night oh wait well
it's funny because actually since you bring up epic epic was one of those companies it felt a
little bit opportunistic a little bit especially for a company that also has holdings intense or
held of them by Tencent but it was a little weird that they came out said well we wouldn't punish
players for what they believe in nobody asked you Tim Sweeney sit the fuck down have a seat
I made my own comment back God shut up I was like I was pretty much like let me know when you're
actually treating your employees better let me know when you have a shopping cart I think like
yeah go seriously go worry about your own shit no one asked you Tim no one asked anyway Bobby
Blackwell says Tim Sweeney opportunistic on Twitter say it ain't so yeah pretty much I
like st100 Matt says here's the moment Rob is talking about I love that it's bookmarked on
YouTube yes it should there there really there is there is definitely like a reality television
Bible that you should assemble on YouTube let's see we should definitely have that would be in
there there would be a whole book of New York where you would have the good morning good morning
good morning good morning not you you can choke let's see what else would be in the way there's
there's a lot of things that would be in there there'd be a whole book of Drag Race as well
absolutely my wife would like to add I'm not doing this with him today well what you want to
do isn't necessarily what you're gonna do oh yeah oh yes thank you there would be a whole
chapter 1 verse 1 of the book of Drag Race I never had a sugar daddy if I wanted a sugar daddy
yes I could go out and get one because I'm what bitch sickening you could never have a sugar daddy
because you are not that kind of girl anyway now I'm getting off topic but the reality is these
monologues they shift our thoughts and feelings oh yes thank you so I kick yes the the classic
Whitney kiss my ass yes the book of being Bobby Brown yes all right moving on I'm glad we could
end it on some laughs let's move on to a less serious topic our gaming weeks the types of video
games that we have been playing this week so let's talk about our gaming weeks dark soccer how was
your gaming week I'm still waiting for a Detroit to become human to come out on PC of course I'm
gonna be replacing my PC at the end of the year so I have to play it quick I thought it was on
the epic store no if I'd want the city of Detroit becoming human stop it the game's great I've been
playing pinball wizard on Apple arcade and it really annoyed me at first but now I actually
super like it I also started sayonara wild hearts which is so great I want the soundtrack for it
like so much like I love that rendition of Claire de lune from the first level it's on Spotify and
I imagine if it's there it's got to be on Apple music and all the other ones too yeah I was also
let me look at it again because I you know of course I was playing my I'm gonna be quitting
the Ragnarok game but I've been playing a lot of Animal Crossing because I just want Animal
Crossing to be out I also started hexaflip which is another interesting little puzzler I still
don't like various day life I gave it one more try and I still don't like it so that's pretty
much what I've been playing all right we'll move on to Loki how was your gaming week I played
Borderlands 3 so I played quite a bit of that and that's pretty much it is really just Borderlands
cuz I've been trying to finish it good enjoying it it's more Borderlands you know more more
Borderlands over again I have not started over because I haven't actually finished the first
time through I don't know where I'm at yeah I think I'm like 60% through the game but that's
good I mean it I think that they oversold the diversity of their because one of the things they
talked about was like oh yeah there's so many different planets and it's all very diverse and
stuff like I kind of remember all this stuff from Borderlands 2 this all looks very similar just now
it's on different planets and I don't know it's still good though I mean don't get me wrong I like
all the old characters coming back as well that's kind of a thing that they didn't Borderlands 2 as
well so yeah I'm digging it I actually sat through and because I haven't played through the pre sequel
or tales from Borderlands so I like some of the characters I didn't know who they were so I went
through YouTube and watched like kind of like here's all the things you need to know before
you play Borderlands 2 or 3 you know so I got caught up on what the pre sequel was and so I
didn't need to go back and play the pre sequel because that looks pretty good so there's that
and I worked on my game some I'm gonna work on a lot this week so it'll be good awesome my gaming
week I had kind of a busy gaming week I actually spent most of my gaming week on the cell phone
game I've talked a lot about on this show Ingress so you might see my shirt I'm wearing kind of an
interesting shirt today it says Umbra Sacramento epicenter of enlightenment so this was like our
team merchandise or swag supporting this weekend's anomaly event so Ingress which is the game of
course by the people who did Pokemon go it's where all of the pokey stops and all that come from
although not on our show world tonight but they replaced operation portal recon with a site called
Niantic Wayfarer which in many ways is great because now you can pick what submissions get
prioritized so forth but here's the thing about Wayfarer it's not Ingress art it's mixed art like
Pokemon goes in there too which you can infer they're going to open up OPR and that type of
stuff or now it's Wayfarer they're gonna open that up for Pokemon go players eventually so it'll be
interesting well good I can resubmit the stuff that I've sent because I haven't heard anything
since May and you should log in to Wayfarer because if you haven't heard anything it may
have actually been rejected or maybe it was even approved and you never got an email because you
can go back and look at all your old submissions now finally that's the thing you can do so yeah
you should check that out I'll have to do that now yeah I do that so anyway but I digress a
little bit the Ingress was the original kind of player versus player resistance versus enlightenment
game where a lot of that those landmarks came from so to try to make a long story short there
was a kind of a tournament a big event sort of like maybe like go fest in Chicago except to
remember that like Ingress probably has like 1% of the player base if that a Pokemon go but they
had that in Sacramento was the West Coast so there were three events in the Americas this
weekend at least unlike Pokemon go they do multiple cities so this weekend there were
events in Sacramento on the West Coast Brooklyn New York on the East Coast had also was yesterday
and in the middle was actually Guadalajara in Mexico so those were kind of the three sites
that went yesterday so what happened is that members from the resistance and members from
the light and all kind of converge and they do a live battle for three hours which consisted of
this time it was about who can control portals during certain measurements who can make the
longest link pathing between the portals at certain measurement times who could get the
most unique portal hacks and then there was a cypher game that's kind of like an escape room
type of thing that you like the decoder game that was worth bonus points so my team won yay
because I play on the enlightenment the green side and we did a great job and to give you an
idea about how many people I don't have any official numbers Niantic doesn't give official
numbers I don't know how many people were registered or whatever but people that were
watching the map and all the little like peak players that come up said it was about 300 players
on the green team 200 players on the blue team we're here so there are about 500 players actively
playing in the anomalies because that's a pretty that's a pretty decent turnout for something like
that and I know there was there was at least one girl on her team from Taiwan who was here and there
was a couple from like I think there's one from Sweden so we had some visitors that came a long
way to play so that was that was fun but there was a lot of prep that went into that as you can
imagine when it comes to things like strategy and how that's all gonna work work yeah a lot of my
week was focused on that so that was all yesterday and then today was kind of the cooldown mission
day all factions can do it together it's an individual thing type of thing apparently mine
still in queue oh I did withdraw the other one but it's still in queue and they have this upgrade
next thing so I went ahead and did that I don't know what that's gonna do yeah so all right um
let's see I was looking at some of the comments in chat act F said yeah there's talks about a pogo
event next year in Mexico considering they've done some already in ingress yeah so I and
Guadalajara is not the only city they've done in Mexico I mean that I think they've done one in
they had to have done one in Mexico City I think there was one last year and so on I mean these
events are all I missed an OLR last year because I went to one of these in Chicago so I've traveled
for these myself and they're fun but I walked 23,000 steps yesterday I was very sore and very
tired and I might be coming down with a cold as a result so I mean yeah there's a lot of that it
wasn't just Ingers though that I was playing this week I also played so you know the whole I've been
playing some how fancy 14 I was playing Wow Wow classic but with everything that happened I've
just decided you know what I've been talking about that I kind of need to play less MMOs and catch
up on my backlog anyway so I cancelled Wow we're talking about that but it finally made me get to
my backlog or actually I should say a new game I added to my backlog because it was on sale for
on PlayStation 4 for only $15 so I finally installed and started playing horizon zero
dawn the complete edition I have a copy of that that I'm borrowing you should check it out if you
haven't yet it's um it's okay the thing is I don't well see I know you are not the big fan of using
like controllers because your wrist and so forth and there is like stealthy stuff and so forth but
the game also one thing right off the bat you should know is that the game has five difficulty
levels or maybe it's six but I think it's five so normal it's kind of like the middle one so
I'm playing on easy mode which is one step lower well they have a bobby black wolf mode in the game
they have one that's called story where it's like you don't even have to worry about fighting at all
and that might be you know if you just want to experience the story and so forth that might be
a way to do it without worrying about you know the controllers and all that stuff I'm playing it
on easy just because I want to get a feel for the game mechanics but I just I want to get through
the story and experience the game and get to my next game in the backlog if I like it a lot then
I'll go back and do it on hard or what have you and I gotta say so far I mean I'm not that far in
the game I got through the tutorial stages and I'm in the a little bit after that you don't want
to say too much but I'm like level five so I'm very early on still but I'm really into it I will
say this right off the bat the game is fucking gorgeous it is a gorgeous fucking game like just
going through and I don't even have a 4k TV or an HDR capable TV and like if I had that stuff it
would probably be even more good-looking but I've just been going through on my cheap old 1080p TV
playing on my PlayStation 4 Pro and it looks great I didn't realize there was like an element of like
kind of like electronics so it's like you're out in this big beautiful world but you have this
little scanner device that makes like purple electronic lines type of stuff show up and you
can scan there's a lot of like Metroid prime esque type of scanning that goes on that can give you
some insight into story and things like that so and it looks really good like I thought the whole
game was like outdoors but no there's some areas where you go indoors it's kind of creepy and some
caves or bats fly out yes it's a really really good-looking game and so far this story is like
really yeah I'm into it so I may have yet again slept on a game I really should have started
playing about a year and a half ago but what else is new that happens sometimes right so excuse me
looking at some other comments in her chat over at twitch.tv slash vog network quest buster says
love that game alloy is the best yeah the the heroine of the story definitely they are molding
her to be a big character that would most assuredly be in the next Sony PlayStation all-stars if they
do a game like that that's for sure Captain Spike says OMG same Rob recent play so nice yeah pretty
cool Pele Hanumea says I hope horizon zero dawn 2 is a PlayStation 5 launch title I don't know
if it would be a launch title but I there's got to be a horizon zero dawn 2 in the making there
really has to be it seems like a lot of people who played this game are really into it and I do
I want to keep playing it it's um if you don't know like the type of game it is it's really like old
world or excuse me it's like exploration a lot of like you do the quest to go from one place to
another you may have to hunt monsters and you can do it stealthy and the game rewards you with more
XP if you like learn how to hide in the bush and like scan the enemy for the weak point and shoot
an arrow at it but there's skills that can help you like there's a skill that I bought that slows
down time and zooms in so it's really easy to get a shot on an eye or something like that and honestly
I imagine if you're playing in Bobby Black Wolf mode you don't even have to worry about the
stealth you just go in there with your spear and chop them up and it's way it'll be fine poke them
in the face exactly because that's like if I if I fail and I miss and the thing charges at me I
just swing wild with my spear and it usually ends up dead anyway so it works Bobby says you do still
have to do stealth yes you do still I mean in the tutorials you have to do stealth I don't know in
the game so far I imagine in some story elements there may be some forced stealth but I'm not so
sure if you were to play this game in its easiest mode the story mode it probably isn't gonna give
a shit you can probably just go in there and hack and slash mobs because they're not really gonna be
able to kill you quest buster brought up something I think I would enjoy what's that using trip wire
oh yeah I just got that I I went to the guy and got like a true so you set up a trip wire because
you scan and you can see the path that they take and you set up a trip wire so that way when it
comes and it hits the trip wire goes and it just collapses and you can shoot it in the face it's
great I know it's very rewarding it sounds like so fun dark soccer it's not just any trip wire
it's a shock trip wire so they trip and they get electrocuted can you also have it to wear like
shoots a spike into their face I'm oh there are other types I think there's like a flaming trip
wire and there's just you you got me a flaming trip wire robbed there's flaming arrows too you
got me at fire literally the first quest in the game is to make fire arrows you might have to
check it out yeah I think it's time to hook up ps4 again there you go or at least get the dust
off of it yeah quest buster says stealth is really simplistic in this one it's not on splinter cell
levels of tough no I I didn't think it was that bad I and I don't like stealth usually although
I'll be honest I have been getting my streaming setup together so I can play I love you Colonel
Sanders it's just I had to upgrade my operating system first to be able to do that six fucking
hours you know how long it took to upgrade my Mac 45 minutes yeah but then when you find out your
apps aren't compatible on Mac it takes you a little longer just so you know yes same thing
can happen on Windows well I haven't updated my MacBook Pro but my Mac's updated so all right
anyway um let's see I want to move on let's that was enough for our gaming week a little bit of
housekeeping we will not be here live next week I have a work trip that I need to do and work gets
number one preference sorry guys day job is the thing that pays me to be able to do this show
so we won't be here live on Sunday night however we're gonna try to record during the week but
we're trying our schedules are a little complicated so I can't promise it right now I'm gonna try to
record something for you guys I'll have an update on our Twitter over at twitter.com slash olr so
just a heads up there but if you're on the podcast but you don't see a new show come in next week we
weren't able to get around and record something so sorry about that but you can't always show up for
mr. Bobby Blackwell who is here live the voice he's network right before us on Sunday nights
all right uh anyhow let's move on let's get into some gaming news we've talked a lot about other
stuff let's get into what else has been going on the gaming industry this week so Loki let's talk
about this next Sony console that's is gonna be named PlayStation 5 you know what's funny
last week on the show remember we did that whole thing about Shawn Layden leaving and like yeah
mean and I sat here and I said well maybe they're gonna go in this radical new direction for the
Sony place never and they're not gonna call it the five it's gonna be the place to well can't
win them all I love that the very next day they gave him out and said no bitch it's PlayStation
5 all right so yeah so they basically put out they had an interview with wired and also put
out some stuff regarding the next console so it is gonna be the PlayStation 5 it's gonna be out
holiday 2020 not a big surprise there they said that the console will have a solid-state drive
and they said games released on it would be 100 gigabyte blu-ray discs it will have a 4k blu-ray
drive I hope that means 4k video as well because if you remember the current PlayStation 4 pros
thinking Sony's gonna get that right I mean I don't know but you know what Sony probably
also wants to talk about digital because I would think they want to talk less about the
discs and more about the digital but I don't want to I can't mind read Sony anymore I don't want to
download a 20 gigabyte video file no no thanks they said that the games will need to be installed
from the disc I mean it makes sense because you're talking like huge games they're talking a little
bit about how that the new PlayStation 5 controller is gonna be similar to the PlayStation 4 controller
but they're gonna be improving things like haptics in there as well and they have this adaptive
triggers so what that means is that there'll be variable resistance on the trigger when you're
pulling it down so you may have like different things for example it's like kind of like if you
remember like the old driving games in arcades and stuff like that where they had some you know
resistance on the steering wheel some games have that it's like that but with the triggers so your
game can now fight back sort of yeah okay so the controller is not gonna punch you in the face but
it can make it a little harder to actually like pull the trigger so when like you're choking a
bitch in Grand Theft Auto 5 then you squeeze and eventually you'll feel the neck snap and it'll
just give away so just go on and then of course along with that you'll have the additional
haptics to feel all the bones breaking and so they said other things it sounds like the HD
rumble or whatever that they have I'm not really sure how they're gonna do additional haptics
aside from I guess changing the way they do the rumble all together kind of like how they did it
with the with the the switch joy cons but they said some things that you'll be able to like for
example check out they had a demo I guess of Astrobot rescue mission they said on ice it made
the thumbsticks feel like my character was gliding or jumping in a pool and they said there is some
resistance on the water on a wooden bridge a bouncy sensation so interesting and they said
the thumbsticks I guess there is resistance I wonder if they're talking about resistance on
those as well aside from the triggers interesting so then other stuff I don't know they've got some
new blue point games is gonna be working on some new games right now they said we're working on
a big one right now I'll let you figure out the rest and then they said that their primary
primary focus on the new controller is I guess their primary focus is that new controller there
was some other stuff that came out I don't know if we're gonna be talking about it necessarily no
so there is some other patents we may have talked about this last week of PlayStation VR stuff that
there may be a new version of PlayStation VR that's gonna be launching with the PlayStation 5 as
well so we'll have to check that out and see that's the thing so I mean what do you think of
this news I mean it sounds good I mean I'm interested to see what what what in that how
that translates in the gameplay because I mean honestly at this point like you can push graphics
you can push graphics you can push to graphics but not every game really needs those graphics
push I want to see what you're gonna do they improve the gameplay of these games and I'm
curious to see how this haptic stuff feeds into it cuz yeah I'd be pretty cool I mean just don't
make the controllers like $80 each but you know I I'm interested to see where they go with that
because some things worked some things didn't work like I don't know about the touchpad that's
on the PlayStation 4 controller maybe that was kind of a not really working out thing but some
other stuff I'm kind of with you it's like it sounds really neat now show me what it can do
I realize you know a random day in October 2019 is not really when they are gonna do the big
unveiling for the next console this is the type of thing I have to wait for the next c3 or probably
Sony's own event but that also gets me excited about like you know with additional haptics in
the DualShock controller what about additional haptics in a new VR controller and that might be
pretty cool too yeah like that like I like the haptic type of stuff like especially like on my
phone in gaming because the phones have the haptic stuff in it like you know the the little like
haptic stuff that happens like an ingress for example like when people are attacking near me
you actually feel a little like a little haptic like shake in your phone it's really cool like I
like it and when you're glipping you you can feel you know and obviously other games have it too like
you know the yeah so I'm I like that haptic stuff and I'm curious what it's gonna do more for the
console gaming yeah so but now it's just a matter of okay so what are the games that are gonna use
these features but you know and then one feature that is see when it's going away I guess that is
maybe not a big deal to some people because they may have not used it but the integration with
PlayStation 4 and Facebook is gonna be going away as well basically saying that we're working with
Facebook of course is working with Sony to finalize an updated contract designed to improve
the Facebook integration with PlayStation while these discussions are in progress Facebook
features will be not available on PlayStation 4 and it's already gone which is kind of surprising
like I don't know like I kind of like the Facebook integration which is weird because there's a lot
about Facebook I don't like but it did make it very easy to find my friends who are also on
PlayStation and very very easy to just be like oh I don't know this person by their username so we
can just exchange the real names and that or my my real name that was probably the only thing I
used with that but I know they were talking about other things like you know sharing screenshots
videos music trophy details and stuff like that yeah or links to gameplay broadcasts but I really
only use it for the friends stuff but yeah no you can do all the sharing just like you can share to
Twitter like the video is not stuff or I shared us I shared a screenshot from horizon zero dawn
like either earlier today or yesterday to Twitter I could have done that to Facebook yeah but I just
figured the people that follow me on Facebook don't really probably care about all my gaming
updates most of the people on Twitter probably don't either but too bad I don't know Twitter
feels like the easier place for those like shorter updates whereas things on Facebook get kind of
lost but I'm I don't know it's it's still a little weird to me that it went away I'd kind of like to
know more of the reasons why behind it like was there some type of agreement that fell through
does Sony plan to build their own type of social network like what but if that was the case well
then they would get rid of the Twitter functionality and that stuff too so I'm kind of not sure like
what's all going on my first thought was maybe Facebook made it harder maybe Facebook did
something to to this but no you could still have Facebook integration on the switch you can find
your hands on the digital switch through Facebook I don't know what's up I'll be honest I never used
any features like that so for me it's kind of a no-deal I guess some people like it I'm personally
trying to get myself off Facebook as often as as I can which is why there's been an increase in
me using Twitter lately so yeah slidekick and chat says did you talk about the biggest news
of the recent week which was Galarian Ponyta since I brought up Nintendo says says the one
who just changed their Facebook Twitter name yeah so we did not bring it up yet on the show
but I will take this opportunity to mention it does look cute as if I wasn't going to buy
Pokemon sword and or shield anyway I'm gonna keep thinking of Galarian's I was gonna get Pokemon
shield anyway with heads exploding now it's just doubly so that I'm gonna get Pokemon shield so
yeah it's like it says someone who had committed to shield months ago I couldn't be happier same
that's the same boat I'm in SSG 100 Matt I love this as 200 Matt and chat says tinfoil hat maybe
Facebook is going to have a deal with Microsoft but at the same oh no I here's why cuz they're
still in with Nintendo switch wouldn't into the switch have to get rid of it too I don't think
it's a deal maybe it's just that maybe so much has changed that it just doesn't integrate well
anymore with it or something yeah maybe I don't know well we'll probably never know the real reason
why as to what's going on but it's fun to speculate see that's why you always do your quote
fingers and go reason all right well let's talk a little more about some things going on at
Microsoft dark soccer oh yeah I don't know how to feel about this I'm sure people have some feelings
but Mikey Barra left Xbox after having been there for about 20 years he's very very high level as in
the corporate vice president of Xbox said he's a he's gone bye-bye and this is his direct quote
it's been a great ride at Xbox and the future is bright thanks to everyone at Team Xbox I'm
incredibly proud of what we've accomplished and I wish you the best more soon on what's next for me
super excited sounds like someone was given some opportunity you know an opportunity recently
opened up at Sony I'm just saying yeah I'm not saying but I'm saying but I mean we've also lost
you know other big figures with with Xbox you know like a Phil Spencer was one of the the big
departures you know so he he did we know Spencer still had of Xbox oh no they said they're goodbye
to Ibarra sorry I misread something okay I was like wait a minute still there I was like why
is that there no he's still there no it said that they they you know the big big goodbyes on
Facebook sorry on Twitter but but he did get those some yeah the other high-profile one was
Tim Longo who is the creative director for Halo Infinite but no no we'll see what happens I mean
I wish him the best but he was also the same person that defended anthem so I'm kinda like
later bitch he was doing his job to be fair yeah but I'm still a steaming pile of shit I know but
anyway I it's just one of those things was like it's a like all these corporate departures are
just kind of like what the fuck's going on what's in the water are they just trying to all get out
of politics like what no okay a bad joke but you know it's very what if Shawn Layden and him just
switch places okay I doubt it's that I love how everyone though is giving a oh crap I mean his
name is spelled differently yeah but I still think it's funny yeah it's funny all right yeah
I knew this other Jamie Summers she was a bionic woman apparently and spelled it different
differently yes you know as funny as it at work one of the the senior advisors in my team in a
completely different location by the way has my maiden name oh and so people get us confused all
the time because even though I'm still first level I was a senior advisor before and have
like that guess that same tone of voice oh yeah this person talked to you no they didn't they
taught to the other Jamie you know what's so funny it took me a minute to remember your maiden name
like I had to sit here and go oh yeah and by the way my last name ain't really summers it's just
a mind yeah mine's not really Roberts I think everybody knows that at this point and just names
not really his birth name isn't Loki I think most people know that and smooshy's stage name is
actually this mushy no his name really is mr. smoosh it is mr. smoosh and he's vocalizing actually
no because remember mr. smoosh was a rescue cat and when they read the chip it had his original
name on it but that's not actually his name he did have a legal name change yeah you do not
legally change your name to Rob Roberts no I did not really change my name to Rob Roberts so that's
what we have yeah so mr. smooshy's name is mr. smoosh and I call him the smooshy's because he's
the smooshiest cat he's so cute all right let's move on and talk a little bit about a game that's
causing a little bit of controversy out there or did I I think I skipped a story I'm sorry
there's a story missing from our little sidebar oops awkward Loki has something to talk about
first yes we're gonna talk about theft and valve and now this isn't anything valve is stealing it
is people stealing stuff from valve so apparently there was this 32 year old guy Sean the shop of
who burglarized I guess valve and stole a bunch of games and computers and accessories yay so he
apparently stole 48 PlayStation 4 and Xbox one games and about yeah they said $40,000 worth of
games and equipment from valve um he it's among other things that he stole from other stuff he
saw a FedEx truck I guess at one time he also you know stole stuff from public restaurants so yeah
so basically he gained access to valve I guess by through a public restaurant and then through
a non-functioning stairwell door and then he stole you know all those games from them wait
so like valve is a big building that probably has some type of cafe or public restaurant the
first floor this guy went into the cafe then like found a stair access in the cafe or yeah
they got him into the rest of the building yeah and so then that's your solid along with that
he also stole 15 to 20 laptops some Nintendo switch and steam machine consoles see machine
consoles aren't worth much and then he well it's it's video games dark soccer he can carry as much
as he wants he doesn't exceed the number of he still gave Newell's metal minigun looking thing
yes so did they recover it apparently yes he did get that they did recover that stuff so he'd been
he says he'd been throwing some random items into a rolling recycling bin which he used to store all
the stolen goods but yeah they show like his haul there and there's quite a bit of stuff he
sold a signed copy of heavy metal that's random yeah don't steal things folks even though it's
kind of like interesting and very video game plot like that he did it you know you probably shouldn't
steal it's generally a bad idea he didn't steal Half-Life 3 and that's really what he means yeah
that that was what he should have stolen was the source code for Half-Life 3 all right damn it
next time all right let's move on let's talk about this Kickstarter for a new game coming
out called enchanted portals but the thing is if you actually look at the game enchanted
portals I'm sorry I didn't have time to get b-roll tonight because I see bags that have been really
awesome I'm sorry but with enchanted portals you'll just have to google it and look it up
yourself there was a Kickstarter going on for this and the game really looks a lot like cuphead
like a lot like cuphead but it's not a real they're not cups because they're little witches
and it's not technically it's just a ripoff of the style and like genre yeah well I mean no one's
got a copyright on the 1930s no they don't and technically no my god does look a lot like it
though no one has a copyright on shooter like shooters either honestly like cuphead is dr.
pepper and this is dr. slice like that or what's the one they sell at Walmart called what's that
brand it's you know what I mean though it's it's the it's the lower quality version of the I play
a doctor on TV mr. P but a lot of folks went to Twitter to say basically like hey screw you you
guys are trying to make money and like totally ripping off cuphead like what's going on well
the two-man team behind this game am I saying this right she show xixo she show I guess would
be the way to say that she show has been commented has commented on the issue saying yes cuphead was
a huge inspiration for enchanted portals we're both avid fans we would make something similar
but always from a place of respect and admiration for the original we were prepared for some
backlash but the trailer definitely reached way more people than we could ever anticipate
and all the hate and negativity coming our way has definitely had a huge impact on us that being
said along with all those negative responses a lot of people have also reached out to us to say
they adore the game and would love to see it succeed so we're trying to turn our attention
more towards all those who are supporting us and sending their love for the game look I can respect
the angle of just cut out the haters and embrace the positivity versus the negativity but I also
do think it's important like look I get the whole like the art style can be flattering so forth but
there were like they were like showing some bosses that were really similar to bosses and cuphead
and things like that like do something a little bit different you know I mean like take something
you wish was better about cuphead and do that you know like there there is a way where you can kind
of take a take cuphead as a template and then like do your own thing on it it's not like there aren't
tons of video games out there that are derivative of each other and this goes all the way back to
fucking pac-man right like after pac-man came out how many fucking maze games came out what like
ladybug mousetrap and even crazy auto which eventually turned into miss pac-man yeah for
amadar there was like a million like pac-man clones right or things inspired but they they
all kind of did something a little bit different didn't they so you know that that's I think what
people would really appreciate about cuphead and I think excuse me about I can't even get the name
of the game right enchanted portals and here's the thing that makes it dicey when you go to
kickstarter and ask for money when it's one of these things where it's like I would like to make
these dolls and I would like to put out my pack a chump dolls here and here's my prototype pack a
chump doll that I'm going to be selling and for those team pokemon that for those of you that are
watching the podcast feed I'm holding up a certain yellow creature that may look very familiar to one
that you know from a go game on your mobile phone or a sword and shield game coming on your switch
but my pack a chump uh is uh it's it's just inspired by pokemon I would never just directly
steal so what you have to do is you have to put a little mustache on it and glasses
and make it your own put a beard on him then he's evil package you
uh slidekick in chat says pack a chunk is the obese pikachu oh hey wait a minute just stop
pikachu is not a skinny little rat mind you thank you slidekick also doing the real work
that we need to know here saying walmart is apparently dr thunder thank you that's what
I was trying to think of dr thunder all right anyway that's always still sounds like a porn
name uh and then dr thunder in chat this is also very important because I talked about the name
of the company shisho act theft was asking is he related to shusha no I don't think so and
act after is asking does anyone know who the fuck shusha yes I do and of course I'm going to give
you my keys that was how she would end the show and give an extra lipsticky kiss on the cheek
to some kid yes now she's wanted for police several years later I want to make a game based
on shusha I'm gonna see where she is now yeah where is shusha please don't say dead I feel like
the answer is going to be dead
in prison no not in prison shusha american tv program okay 1993 my god
and it was based on shu de shusha which was the original show it looks like
all right her name is shusha mening meningale dijaroma s is saying thank god she's not dead
brazilian tv host film actress blah blah blah she's the queen of the short ones
but is she is the bitch alive yes okay good uh see a tiberian chat that should be a website is
the bitch alive and then you have a drop down and it's just a bunch of different celebrities
she is right now among brazil's most prominent celebrities and is worth over 400 million us
she's one of the highest net worth of any woman entertainer in brazil
metal mayhem in chat says shusha sells seashells by the seashore
that's actually pretty funny metal mayhem all right uh see a tiberian chat says someone should
make a video game about wing and she was on dancing brazil which is a brazilian version of
dancing with stars really and she is a big social uh activist as well working with brazil's poorest
communities oh so yeah she turns out shusha is a pretty pretty good and she had an affair with
pele oh back in the day when she was 16 scandalous i i just now i now i really want that website is
the bitch alive or is the bit excuse me is the bitch dead yes well hey and it's got the number
the default search has to be very wide and for people who want to look up shusha it's xu xa
and honestly the show is so on drugs that it's worth watching a little bit of it
because all the children programming we loved and adore especially in the 80s was probably derived
from cocaine oh speaking of things that were probably derived from cocaine pleased because
this was linked in the vog network discord and i probably wouldn't have seen it otherwise but
we do have our own discord server at vog network.com vognetwork.com slash discord
somebody she's on instagram what hold on somebody linked this uh saturday night live sketch that was
a parody of the joker movie trailer but it was for oscar the grouch and first off it was starring
david harbor yes you know david harbor was in the trailer becoming oscar the grouch but what killed
me was that they had all these real life interpretations of all these characters from
sesame street and like the count was counting his pills as he was taking them yes fucking like ernie
got stabbed by somebody and burt's crying over it it's really funny and i haven't said that about
saturday night live in a long time but that was a really funny trailer so thank you for sharing
that yeah the grouch trailer so there it is all right moving on let's get to another story uh
this is uh edutainment possible edutainment title right yeah um and actually it was the link was
provided to me by uh our dear ronma um but it's and now i'm really loath to say anything positive
about kickstarter right now but the union organizers and um have been saying please
continue to support it because it's how a lot of people get their money so i did actually back this
one for the sake of supporting their creators i am still however speaking out against their
practices and wanting to hold of course the corporate people responsible so um like i said
we gotta pick our battles right um shujinko is a game coming out that's supposed to teach you
japanese um it's going to have a release on switch and ps4 and um it's basically set in
a world where the japanese language is being erased by demons and you have to save it so it's
sort of a roleplay slash metroidvania style game and you have to react to different situations on
screen and it familiarizes you with the language as you go um and i'll put it this way it sounded
like a really good concept especially for someone like me who's trying to eventually pass the glpt
so i backed it it sounds like a neat concept especially you know for somebody that might
want to learn a little japanese um lord knows i could use it so well and i said that i was going
to teach me how to read like say it pronounce it i had well i hope so but i you know i personally
said that i wasn't gonna back anything until i found something worth backing because i do want
to support the content creator it's just i am still also you know visibly protesting the actions
of the corporation are you able to just reach out to the content creator directly and say hey can i
have your paypal you know that i didn't find out i should do that but yeah but you know the amount
that i pledged gets me my copy of the game so i should see if they have any other way to do that
and then i can withdraw my pledge yeah so i'll do that because i'd feel better about that than doing
it any other way um but that's cool i i think that's uh pretty awesome that uh you know it's
like an edutainment game but it's something a little more mainstream sounding so best of luck
to them on that i think that's uh cool i would love it would be fun yeah hopefully if the game's
you know kind of fun i'd love to learn japanese that way anyway let's move on loki all right um
so this is pretty exciting so steam is af um adding a new service soon that's called remote
play together and what that is is basically allows you to play any couch co-op games
online with other players so you'll be able to do uh launch up to four players in a specific game
and you'll play with other people that aren't in the room with you so so it's playstation 4 share
play sort of yeah exactly um so i'm down with this because if i release a game on steam i don't know
how to fucking code your code online gameplay this will make it much easier for me so um
i think it's pretty awesome and so they're gonna offer that it's gonna be something that they're
implementing very soon and it's just gonna be built into any game that's on steam i think they
have a few yeah it's in beta right now so they're launching around october 21st and they said it
includes split screen and local co-op play but and apparently it's all done through the steam
overlay you can accept invitations from friends to join and block people if you don't want them
to come in and there's other limitations you can set like um blocking certain inputs on a shared
keyboard and mouse and stuff like that they see can't just hit alt f4 on somebody else's keyboard
something like that and draw delete those types of things yeah so um i think this is very exciting
it'd be cool to see how you know we can use this but neat i i'm always for more um accessibility
for people to play over the internet friends yeah it's kind of neat i mean the playstation
4 share play is probably one of those features is like really underutilized and i think people
forget it's there so uh yeah it'd be really cool uh bonds 006 says i have some co-workers that
would be into couch play on steam yeah i think there'd be especially the the ability to like
kind of like try a game because share play is also only limited yeah that was the other thing
yeah this one is it's you don't have to own a copy of the game to be able to do that too
uh to play with somebody else if they have a copy of the game then you can play it and it'll stream
it to you so um pretty cool how about yeah that's kind of neat i like that all right well let's um
move on and let's talk about uh some things that are going on with the new atari vcs that is uh
maybe coming out i don't know uh because the reason why i say i don't know which is interesting
we just last week had that story about how ant stream was going to have like an atari
exclusive edition right well the atari vcs the architect of the system quit that's right uh not
only did he quit but he quit saying he hasn't been paid in six months oh no yikes uh rob wyatt is the
system architect uh he's the architect behind the system he was also one of the founding team
members behind the xbox should be pointing out and in an interview he told the register as of
friday october 4th i've officially resigned as the architect of atari vcs atari haven't paid
invoices going back over six months to the consultant firm that he runs tin giant as a
small company we've been lucky to survive this long um all they had so far was a prototype
motherboard last month and the team was in the middle of debugging said uh motherboard before
he decided to quit uh now it will probably fall to a different organization surface inc
uh which atari contracted with to complete the console but who knows how long that is going to
take yikes and it sounds this just sounds to me a lot like the whole um calico debacle that was
out there except a little a little different story because with the clica one it was i think
it was the clica where they had like fake hardware they were trying to like fake that the hardware
was actually done whereas this sounds like that he's actually been working on hardware they're
just not paying him so but still not a good sign uh dj rama s says what happened to that kickstarter
money uh-oh for those backers well to be continued i suppose anyhow now we're going to take a trip
down memory lane to better times to better games i'm literally tripping and falling over my feet
so we're going to uh get to our classic soundtrack of the month because once a month dark soccer goes
in the gaming vault and not only says here's the game you should check out but she's actually says
here's a soundtrack that we don't talk about enough although i don't know about this one we
talk about this one a lot so it was worth mentioning yeah and remember i'm trying to avoid
like the rpg ones and the ones like that but yeah this one just couldn't go without a mention you
really can't do this segment especially if you're gonna highlight 8-bit games and not talk about
this one uh for those i am putting the 16-bit thing on hiatus uh-huh and i'll go ahead and
make the announcement now next year we are doing classic pinball of the month all right
which is basically going to be 90 percent you know uh tables you own no because we have some
ones i don't like like i hate judge dread and we own that i hate creature from the black lagoon
we own that so is there a halo pinball table i'd hate that if it existed but it's not going to be
any of the current stern ones it's going to be everything like prior to the whole pinball 2000
thing so i'm using that as my marker for what constitutes classic pinball fair enough okay
for those watching on twitch because i i had all gonna be john papadook and steve richie games
there was a lot of stuff that i did before tonight's show with the system and trying to
upgrade some things that didn't work um so it's gonna go blank on twitch for just a minute because
i forgot to load the b-roll in advance oopsie daisy um but for the podcast folks you can listen
to jamie start to talk about this game so what did you pick for the classic game or excuse me
the classic soundtrack of the month ducktales ooh ducktales because of the moon it's all about the
moon i mean the whole game has an epic soundtrack um the uh the ducktail soundtrack was composed by
tonomura um hiroshige and it was actually one of the first soundtracks he ever worked on can you
believe this is early work from this guy actually oh i did fix things where i can turn this up and
down on demand here we go so now we all know the beauty that is this particular soundtrack
um it was um he also did compose um uh some of the various uh you know background tracks
in the game he also rearranged the ducktail scene for this so um and he took moments to get the
theme kind of incorporated back into some of the other tracks so at least that same feel of the
themes um it also has different uh little fanfares and jingles that were played off of the ducktail
like you know when you die or when you finish a stage or something um and all of these songs were
completely of course remastered for ducktales remastered um it was coded in uh 6502 assembly
and using a sound driver created by um uh sakaguchi uh yoshihiro a yoshihiro sorry so it's
really um you know some other things i'd like to highlight what the um composer has done he also
did um legendary wings for nes he did um some baseball games destiny of the emperor for nes
he did the ninja kids he did uh bust a move for uh in 1994 as nah he didn't do all that
and uh he no he was the sound producer for bust a move and he also was uh the sound director for
raystorm one of the you know best shooters out there um so he he's really you know i wouldn't
say he had like a very long list of things but he's done some very good things um and of course
the music is one of the things that people completely know this game for i mean apart
from it just being a really solid game um they also did um different versions of the music he
there was a transylvania stage that didn't make it into the final one um a slower version of the
moon stage and um you know just a bunch of different things that you can find there's a
beta version out there that has some of these things in it that you can listen to um and of
course uh as the game was uh ported over to game boy the uh the same music went along with it so
it was all all his work so we really you know again this is one of those games that the moment
you bring up oh yeah i really like playing duck tales people go oh my god but the music
right so that's that's our game is duck tales so anyone have some good memories of music
i remember i don't think you know i can't remember if i owned duck tales or rented it a lot but i
remember playing a lot of duck tales how many games did we have that we just rented it a lot
that it felt like we owned them or maybe i borrowed it so that's back when like we had
swapped games with friends in the neighborhood and stuff like that and so i just i do remember
playing this quite a bit maybe i did own it yeah it's a really good game i mean it's one of the
ones that when dan and i were rebuilding our nest collection we we had to have this one and i don't
know if it's just because it's like a capcom game or something like that but a lot of this music
reminds me of megan well you know who was the um the uh hold on let me pull up the list yeah the
one of the main uh artists um of the game was uh you know june so i mean he didn't really do much
else in the game but he was uh one of the main artists in this game so there you go that's who
we need to get in a marvel versus capcom game scrooge mcduck yeah he'd just poke off of people
scrooge for smash and he'd uh he'd smack gems at them hell yes and then but after you smack them
then he would run around the screen and go go save it because that's the kind of duck he is
i was reading actually a few other things about that beta version of um duck tales like um gizmo
ducks uh name from the japanese version uh was in a lot of it is robo duck it's funny i was
actually looking at the name um the original name of the game and it's called uh one paku
uh one paku daku yume boken which is naughty ducks dream adventures i just like the name
naughty ducks it it denotes like some unruly ducks it's the porn parody hockey team either
that or they like it's like the precursor to the untitled goose game bobby blackwolf in our chat
points out duck tales was the only nes game i could be as a kid without a game genie it's still
the only nes game i can be without a game yeah there there's a lot of games that i don't remember
really i mean i'm kidding i'm kidding i mean i'm just like i'm thinking back to beating the
guardian legend as a kid oh you know something else yes i did beat that you know something else
i played this week in a completely random tangent i forgot about it because it was earlier the week
it was like monday that you remember that mashup of uh zelda and metroid that they put out the
randomizer yeah the one they do for the speedrun z1 m1 or something like that um i i downloaded
that and i started playing that that's neat i like that i said the problem with it is then i tried to
figure out how do i run that program that automatically plots the map and i couldn't
figure that part out and i got frustrated i couldn't figure out the mapping software so i
stopped somebody's gotta hold my hand and walk me through it on discord if i can figure it out if
people look up the old gdq streams though there's a lot of really good um the other things that i
like are like the game bingos i would love for us to put together like um a run what's a game bingo
game bingo so you've got your bingo card set with different objectives to do in the game
and either you have to do like a particular line of them like you pick which ones you can do
different tasks along the way but when you hit your straight line of everything then it's bingo
there are some who do blackout bingo okay that's kind of fun yeah um there's there's a few on the
gdq twitch channel you can find some really good bingo streams as well um for the last uh
gdq thing that they did they did an ocarina of time uh bingo i want to like live stream some of
that stuff i think i know when we get into like emulators and stuff things get a little dicey
but here's the thing i legally own a copy of zelda i legally own a copy of metroid i don't think i'm
in the wrong like several copies of all this shit i think we all do at this point because we've all
had to rebuy i have a snest class it gets fine i'm covered for all super nintendo games now well
i wouldn't say all super no it's all of them all right anyway uh bobby buckle says yeah they did
a super mario sunshine bingo at the last gdq that was the one i was thinking of yeah um but i know
that they've done an ocarina one so good times all right well let's move on and talk a little bit
about some rapid fire news quickly um some things going on in the uh gaming industry so uh loki uh
doom eternal has been delayed to march that's unfortunate the delay the march 20th 2020
and it's because they have to add some polish so they can live up to their standards of speed
and i guess polish so please understand um take the time to get it right it's cool i'm down with
that you know that's fine uh let's see what else and then um they have a new cross sorry i have to
say that act deaf to chat says bethesda's delaying a game to fix it why it's id software just because
they're owned by bethesda doesn't mean they necessarily operate in the same standards but
i see um anyways there is a new crossover coming to rocket league for halloween and it is stranger
things so yeah stranger thing is going to have a crossover and they've got some displays the theme
song on loop while you play i wish i would that'd be worth it right there so apparently in that you
can earn uh candy corn to spend on treats uh during this event including you can pick up uh
wheels with the star court mall logo hold on hold on because i've done a scientific survey amongst
my friends and as it turns out i'm the only person on planet earth that likes candy corn oh candy
corn oh shit i have candy corn in my car for you yeah finish all this shit and i'll go get your
candy corn wow can you grant me two other wishes while you're at it
anyways um so then you can also get uh apparently dustin's um camp nowhere hat as a hat in the game
because you know the cars wear hats in that so that's something and they also have a demigorgon
player banner and it's scoops ahoy themed avatar border of course and this is gonna run from
october 14th through november 11th all right uh bonds 006 and chat says soulless monsters
all of you for liking candy and they also have a farmstead arena which has like an upside down
type vibe with like it looks like the mind flare in the background stuff you ready for me to say
something really controversial okay like wait wait for it guys because you're gonna just you're
gonna gasp okay so you think i'm weird for liking candy corn you know you know what else i like you
know what else i like really like black licorice good and plenty good stuff like that's actually
like one of my preferred movie snacks is good and plenty i love black licorice fight me
or give it to me like if you don't like it give it to me
all right anyway let's move on i'm just waiting for the chat reactions do you know did you dark
soccer did you happen to have any uh black licorice out there because
oh are they pumpkin they're pumpkin candy corn i gotta try this okay pumpkin and apple pie okay
after i do this story then i'm gonna eat this is space i like candy corn for the record although
i made candy corn cookies and i learned that if you were gonna bake candy corn into a cookie you
have to seal the shit out of those cookies or you get that glass candy thing all over the place
dj rama s and chat says why would you say something so controversial yet so brave
love it i loathe licorice i i think it it's i love it give it to me i think that it's the shit that
shit shits it's not that bad i also don't like jagermeister i don't like uzo i don't like any
of the annie's licorice flavored things now you know okay i have to say i'm sorry i have to say
this is now we've opened this pandora's box and i can't stop it's not you know it's even better
than like the good and plenty's and like the actual black licorice and the rare circumstance
you can find it um not that jelly belly black licorice shit like the buttered popcorn jelly
belly is pretty good but the actual like jelly beans not jelly bellies fuck those the actual
black jelly beans like those family easter basket jelly no all right but you and dan are the people
that i will buy licorice for when i find good quote good you know like high quality you and
dan are the only people i will buy it for you're the only two people i like enough to buy black
licorice for uh down up destiny and chat says black licorice is good thank you uh so our oatmeal
landfill i'm not gonna i'm not gonna fight about oatmeal cookies i love oatmeal cookies i hate
raisins though yeah the thing is is that you just need to clearly label like i'm fine with oatmeal
raisin cookies as long as they are clearly labeled oatmeal raisins raisins are deceptive
little assholes i'm fine with oatmeal raisin but like if i eat that thinking oh that's a chocolate
chip cookie and then i bite into it and i surprise it's a raisin i'm gonna be dissatisfied but as long
as you tell me up front yo it's an oatmeal cookie then we're fine if i be prepared i will not make
oatmeal raisin cookies but i will make oatmeal craisin cookies you made those ones they were
really good they're really good craisins are great okay anyway but i am doing strawberry
cookies next and i'm gonna put rose chocolate chips in it back to rapid fire news
apple has added five new arcade games to apple arcade including inmost uh which is uh by the
makers of uh stardew valley and war groove i didn't know that from uh hidden lair games
is a very different type of game they're neat uh the publisher was those other games uh shock rods
uh is another game that has been added it's kind of like a racing game uh stella is another
game that's been released as well as decoherence and mind symphony uh i believe those of you that
started your free trial it's going to be running out soon so just a heads up on that if you are
on your free month trial and you do or do not whatever wish to keep it but it's five bucks and
you can share it with your whole family through family sharing so i mean it's like one of the
cheapest subs you'll ever have out there for that much and there's a lot more games coming out i'm
really excited i haven't got it yet just because i don't want to add to my gaming backlog but once
i make some progress in my gaming backlog i'll probably do it it's a lot of the things on there
there were things that you can play in bursts so if you're out and about it's really easy to do
it's fair except i'm usually just playing ingress pokemon go harry potter all at once oh you owe me
all right uh oh and one other thing to mention here from me uh there is a very scary halloween
mask that's been spotted out there it is a is a sonic the hedgehog movie mask that's right even
though the sonic the hedgehog movie got delayed until next year you know it didn't get delayed
licensing agreements so if you want to be the scariest person on the whole block you can get
the sonic the hedgehog mask you gotta buy one and wear it on the show are we gonna have a dress-up
night here at olr for halloween now that we're video my co-workers want to do 80s and that's
kind of lame but i don't know i think i just need an eyesad shirt with a popped collar when you're
good i'm going back and forth between two things i'm pretty set on one though but i don't want to
ruin it so you just have to wait you need to get like the mullet hair and do jed nelson from um
breakfast club that's it anyway can i do my story yeah of course you can do your stories okay
because i want to eat these candy corns let me know how they are because i like candy corn too
um so they are doing retro style ghosts and goblins figures in japan or as it was called their
makamura um and they are selling them through uh the uh e-capcom online store and hot toys um in
japan but they have two three packs in a single pack and the three packs include um you know uh
the big monster the little monster and arthur and then there's another one with arthur in his
underwear and there's a single one that's arthur in the gold armor so cool i already started
looking on how to buy those and i don't think i can yet and then mega man or ruckman as we're
uh maybe knowing him as they're getting a six album vinyl collection um that has uh the uh
soundtracks as their various compilations but mega man one through 11 the collection
has 152 tracks 30 years of uh mega man music and um onto uh six discs of both of
rockman's major colors the light blue and the darker blue and each of the sleeves has uh artwork
on it and they're in what's called a luxury ridged board slip case and so each uh and they've got all
the oh god i'm actually looking at this and it's really really pretty artwork um yeah i i want this
except i don't have a working record player time to get one but you can time to go thrift store
shopping in the uk you can get it for 90 pounds what once october is over and i'm past halloween
like my weekends are going to free up immensely so we need to have a uh thrift store shopping
bitch i'll do some thrifting november it'll be fun but i'm not i'm not free until november
i wish i was you know what i'm usually working every saturday so don't oh well we can work
around it all right anyhow um let's move on god what's this on party city i think they're still
talking about the um sonic thing oh no see it to be very lengthy of rupaul wigline thing that's at
party city because now people are taking like in so much information from drag race they're
dressing up like drag queens and stuff and rupaul has his own line of wigs you know what
this wig is cheap shit and i expect better rupaul all right moving on that's right as
200 matt says rob is also coming to new york next month i am so technically i oh my god though this
queen is actually using rupaul's wig and it actually looks really good the way that she's
dressed it up but that ain't no lace front though all right can we get to the release dates no
because i like wigs all right fine while you read about wigs while you untuck back in the gold bar
loki is going to go over some world release dates yes we have a game called disco Elysium that's
coming out on pc this week earth defense force iron rain coming out on pc uh grandia hd remaster
on pc overwatch legendary edition on nintendo switch uh steins gate elites on ios and the
witcher 3 wild hunt completed edition on nintendo switch by the witcher instead of overwatch
seriously uh little town hero on nintendo switch uh monkey king the hero is back on pc and
playstation 4 uh travis strikes again no more heroes complete edition on pc and playstation 4
and to jaman stories cyber sleuth complete edition on pc and nintendo switch ice aid
scratch nutty adventure on pc nintendo switch playstation 4 and xbox one plants versus zombies
battle for the neighborville on pc playstation 4 and xbox one and last but not least you too can
get the we fit or it was the the nintendo switch uh strap-on with ring fit adventure
coming out array the nintendo strap-on and ring yes i can't wait actually i'll check it out i
probably will check that out yes that's this week that's this week so fast i know they like
just announced that thing all right anyway um moving on talking about what's happening in japan
and looking at the release dates over there let's see uh coming out on october 17th in japan on the
playstation 4 we have travis strikes again no more heroes complete edition monkey king hero is back
is out in japan as well saryanto vr is out in japan and that is all on the 17th traveling to
the nintendo switch to see what they have on the same day uh story of seasons friends of mineral
town is out as well as digimon story cyber sleuth complete edition oh and the witcher 3 wild hunt
gets its japanese uh switch release even though we've had it for a little bit uh it's getting its
japanese release this week pretty cool how about the uk dark sakura pardon me uh this no the site's
kind of changed some of their stuff up so i had to go some hunting but on the 13th we have grid for
pc now i know this isn't a game but i'm saying that because the name is hilarious anyway
pop games but stallion but stallion but stuff but stallion um north guard comes out on the 14th for
playstation overwatch for switch don't buy it please zombie land double tap comes out on the
big three um daisy comes up also on the 14th uh the witcher 3 wild hunt complete edition for switch
and um i think i have hit through no i haven't because on the 16th goodness it's a long week
uh 16th is the fisherman fishing planet um which i'm sorry i'm not gonna play it if i can't use the
rod controller so monkey king hero is back um ring fit adventure on october 17th crazy machines
a hat in time that looks cute um plants versus zombies battle for neighborville raging loop
um planetscape baldur's gate one and two enhances there's a lot of stuff on the 17th
an ice age scratch nutty adventure okay i don't want to know about nuts all right that's it what
do you see what you get those nuts out of my face what's your verdict um believe it or not the apple
pie ones are really good like the pumpkin ones are good of course but like the flavor is a little
more subtle but the apple pie ones look really good all right well let's hear from the dollar
store i can't throw it at you okay my stomach's upset all right well let's move on uh to the mail
bag question oh there's nothing in the mail bag this week bummer you guys should get on that
participate at orange lounge rita.com although i'm understanding we may have somehow lost some
emails i don't so it's weird to me that we keep not having emails so i will look into like what
the bleep is going on um but this is also part of the reason why i'm kind of like maybe we need
to have something besides emails for people to interact with us but i don't know i don't know
how to do that yet i i kind of want to have a text message thing or like an app or something
i don't know i'm gonna look into that you guys i'm not saying mail is going away so please send your
mails participate at orange laundry.com but i'm getting to that point where i'm like maybe we can
do this better so anyway for now though doing things better that's what new consoles are
supposed to do or or console less consoles right and i'm sure that they're totally not
promising things that they can't deliver on but google stadia claims that they're gonna be um
it's gonna get faster and uh more responsive than local gaming hardware they say they're going to do
this with some sort of um trickery that they're saying is like negative latency so they're
basically going to use predictive technology to figure out what you're going to press before you
actually press it that doesn't sound like that's going to work but that they say in a year or two
that's what's going to happen it's going to make music games super easy exactly they predict i'm
going to hit it right every time perfect so people were worried about the latency making music games
possible on a game like on a console like google stadia but you're gonna get perfect every time
now exactly uh call me skeptical but i don't think that's gonna work out and also a year or two into
the console life i don't know i mean well to be fair this just reminds me of the console launches
like next month right yeah early adopters with the chrome cast and that whole thing but this like
this just totally screams the console we all know like was it the playstation 3 when they were
saying oh yeah it's gonna be you know 10 ap on everything or like i think they were even saying
like higher than 10 ep like and 120 frames per second on like a lot of the games or whatever
i just i'm skeptical that this will be a thing but i guess anything they could do to reduce latency
would be nice but i'm just anything negative latency i'm sorry that's just kind of ridiculous
ssj100 matt in chat says this story is nonsense bobby blackwolf in chat says believe it or not
loki and i agree on this topic
i i feel like you're not oh my goding at that revelation even though i was
what we did get an email oh we did you just missed it like four minutes ago okay hold on
we'll backtrack you can't you can't interrupt now all right uh bobby blackwolf continues on and says
negative latent latency equals blast processing it's a buzzword i would i would agree that this
is the blast processing of the year 2019 because they could try to predict what you're gonna press
but like it's not a guarantee so that's just gonna throw all sorts of problems into the mix
so i don't know i just don't see it happening it's it's a weird comment that's really all i have to
say all right let's backtrack we can go to the email it's really short okay that's fine all
right so this comes from ryan and it's all in caps never do that to me 2020 is quickly approaching
there are just over two months left in this decade what are your favorite games of the 2010s
oh god this we could do a whole episode on this topic um let's table that one to do a whole
episode on that topic do me a favor save that for a taped show next week okay okay if we do that
mass effect all the things my list is probably pretty similar but to hold that thought because
i want to have a longer discussion on that now i need time to think about it because i need to
think like what came out in 2009 and what came out in 2010 okay because i need to kind of plan that
out a little bit so all right anyway bobby blackwolf says is this the first time we've
used the backward headline button on air uh no you think this is the first time i fucked up that's
cute no we never fuck up all the time on purpose fuckery and and backing up doesn't have the smooth
animation you've seen it all tonight you got to see the backup you got to see me insert a headline
live on air last week i changed a headline live on air because it said classic soundtrack of the
month when we had to change that out at the last minute but no it doesn't do an animation when
you backtrack but that's okay all right anyway that was fun playing with the sidebar especially
for those on the podcast they can't see what we're doing um but you just have to check out the
archives over at twitch tv slash vog network but we can move on to our next story which has to do
with uh moral combat 11 and you know the way a lot of these uh characters from world combat 11
have been leaked is through data mining so people will go in the files and that's how they found
that oh things characters like ash and spawn and nightwolf and the terminator are going to be
inside mortal combat terminator is fucking hilarious by the way yeah it's it's interesting
it's like uh it's looks very arnoldy and all that but anyway um apparently what they've done for
data miners is they've trolled a little bit with a combat pack two in one of the outros for the
terminator yes you get a first person view where you see kind of the red scan style and then some
text comes up on the screen really quickly and one of the things that comes up is data mine in
progress and it shows melina rain lee may serena meat and mocap now some of those are actually
characters that people would like to see added like melina and rain but other ones like they're
not going to do meat give me a break that would be ridiculous mocap i i think would break the game so
but it's it's it's a cute little thing that they what's mocap mocap was the character um it was
just really overpowered i think what could do everything keep something like that oh of course
my hubby that is mortal combat obsessive instantly knows the answer to this who is hi alan how are
you okay uh speak into the mic and tell us you can grab loki's mic here yes have a seat with a
pack of chonk uh who is mocap i don't know what game he was from but he was a gag
character and it's a guy in a morph suit like a green morph suit with the little ping pong balls
on him like a mocap like they do the mocap for the character fighting it's just that guy so all
right dumb well it's like an easter egg on my head but like as far as like oh iconic punder
money is a dlc that's like a deep cut character that's like a fan favorite no he isn't like if
mocap comes to the game before melina people are going to be really mad yeah it's like
guys come on who do they need to add to mortal kombat 11
i they still play mortal kombat 11 no not i haven't in ages no you've been playing doom i've
watched because it's halloween it's how spooky season doom is your spooky game yeah okay i can
play doom i can't play outlast shut it down i can manage with doom okay yeah all right but you also
mod the shit out of doom like i look at your computer it doesn't even look like you're playing
doom it looks like oh it's disgusting like there's like killing blows they're like glory kills like
a doom 2016 where you're like ripping the sprites in half and there's like intestine sprites you'd
love it yeah no i'll stick with my everyone look up project brutality 3.0 and that's my advice to
you real quick before i let you go unpack groceries or whatever you were trying to do
in one sentence tell me your thoughts on blizzard this week
if it stinks real bad and you keep hearing seagulls you're probably standing in garbage
and it's been smelling real bad and the seagulls have been chirping for
decades now and you look down and it's like oh i'm in garbage
thank you alan yes all right enjoy your night all right let's move on
and uh we'll get to our next story which has to do with a classic series coming back
anyway bubble bubble yay bubble bubble for friends is going to have the 1986 version
a bubble bobble like so many classic versions have um but apparently it's going to have some
other stuff floating around in it so that seems like it could be pretty good it's going to come
out on switch in europe on november 19th and then um we'll be out in north america early
um next year so yeah we're getting this one a little bit late um but i mean it it's bubble
bobble i like bubble bobble um but it's going to also be out by in games as in the end that you
dine at i and then in the games there you go hopefully the boss on level 30 works yeah but
this isn't like a completely redone version no i know this this will be fine uh but i yeah i i'm
all for revisiting bubble bobble it's a fun series but i liked i i liked parasol stars and all the
rainbow or yeah it's parasol rainbow rainbow islands yeah parasol stars was the one where
they jump up and down on no that was rainbow islands yeah the one where they jump up and
they're human again parasol stars was a weird game uh cuz you know in chat says they need to
add blood effects to bubble bobble maybe uh dartitsia says i'm disappointed they haven't
done a new title compilation like i know they've done some of the arcade archive ones but i don't
think bubble bobble has been done yet uh true i you know it's funny i think i have it sitting
right over there on the original xbox there was a title compilation it was pretty good but you're
right they haven't really done one in a while which is kind of surprising i think there's a
mini cab like if you go to an electronics store and look in that section where the nes classic
and the snes classic used to be where everybody's ripping it off now like especially fries oh my
god if you have a fries in your town i know they're not everywhere but if you have a fries
electronics like look for that part of fries electronics it's gigantic with all these like
mini consoles and things like that it's crazy fries though has been looking like an empty ass
warehouse lately yes i i really i fear that fries is gonna go under there yeah i went to their game
section the other day and i was like there's nothing here yeah it's it's uh you know they're
getting killed with online stuff i hope they're able to turn it around because i love fries
all right anyway let's move on and uh talk uh to loki about something uh that i think is on
they're saying in chat is is going something's going on with this right now yes it's so season
10 of fortnight uh just ended which it basically ended in a singularity so there was this event
that happens kind of at the end of each season um there's different like kind of almost like a cut
scene event that happens so this one they launched the rocket which then ended up um going through
one of the rifts and eventually you saw a bunch of rockets come back and then the meteor ended up
all kind of just hitting the planet at once everything got sucked into a big black hole
including the entire map everything just like got sucked in and that's it the game is over for now
but it's funny though is even if you um try to play now you can't play in fact if you go to the
lobby screen to go load into it all of the lobby menu and everything gets sucked into this big
void and everything is gone all of the social media stuff for fortnight and everything all
gone all of the you know their bug fix pages all gone all of the their social media and everything
is just now this this black hole basically but there's of course that's a hell of a way to take
your game down for maintenance for a day let me just say yes but there is this um there's a lot
of stuff going along with it so right now um they've been they have a live stream that's going
on with this just little portal thing so if you want something to do in the meantime which is
kind of cool they do have a konami code built into um the game if you actually go into the actual
launcher and play the game um there's that but there's been these numbers that have been flashing
on the screen stuff and people have decoded the message so the message right now is i was not
alone others were outside the loop this was not calculated that nothing is now inevitable and so
the thought is that they're going to do like a fortnight chapter two by tuesday and it's going
to launch with a whole new map and they're going to have like different content in there as well
interesting but they people were worried well now am i going to lose all the progress they
had everything and uh playstation put out a thing saying don't worry all your v bucks and everything
are still fine all your inventory is still fine just it's like an event thing that's going on
right now so but right now you cannot play fortnite it's the most clever pull your game
down for maintenance thing i've ever seen but think about all that lost money you know they're
not making money if they have the they have to shut it down to do this update anyways this is
the way to do you know and they've gotten the focus onto fortnite for the time being so yeah
all right well we'll see what develops i'm sure we'll know by tuesday if not sooner in fact
actually they're seeing right now like this was uh one of the comments you know on the stream 4.5
million plus on youtube 1.5 million on twitch 1 million on twitter um just the amount of people
watching 50 fucking people on twitch there's 1.5 million watching a black fucking hole yeah
anyway all right it's interesting i i watched the video of like what happened and even like
i think it was a couple seasons ago with the giant mechs and stuff was pretty awesome
um i don't know it's interesting all right let's move on and talk a little bit about uh a new
silent hill game that's right we're going to talk about a brand new silent hill that was just
announced but it's not really a playstation game or an xbox game or even a freaking cell phone game
nope it's a brand new game that was announced at the global gaming expo in las vegas you know what
that means it's a slot machine that's right silent hill escape is one of those slot machines that
kind of has different sides to it so that three people can play it at the same time and it's a
slot experience and it's talking about uh it's one of the first on konami's new video slot cabinet
which is a 49 inch j curve 4k uhd display so it looks really pretty basically uh let's see it's
a first glimpse of great things to come from konami that according to the executive vice
president of konami as we all know and i think we've talked about before on the show konami is
no stranger to the gambling industry if you ever go to a casino um in your neck of the woods i mean
i don't know what gambling laws are like in your state but we have a lot of um uh native american
like land here where they have casinos and uh if you ever look at the machines a lot of them are
by konami and have a konami logo on but i'm just surprised like this is doesn't seem like the
property that you would want to make out of a slot machine like i just don't like i would think of
anything like more of like the music based stuff like is a lot more flashier and stuff i think
would draw more attention than silent hill which honestly the demographic i think for a lot of like
gamblers is a little bit older like i don't think they're going to know what that is keep in mind
there's a certain generation that kind of grew up with those games you know yeah but i don't think
these machines are just for they're not just for the u.s obviously there's a lot of gambling in
asia in um places like makao and places like that so i don't see like i already yelled over this so
you already had your scream and your cry no i i yeah i pretty much did my usual tell off konami
on twitter but i mean honestly it's at this point that we we can count konami is no longer a
a friend of gamers well i don't know because like i mean obviously they've gone lost a lot
either their contour game is really shitty oh i haven't played the country yeah it's really bad
oh that's too bad that's too bad to hear because the castlevania those collections turned out
pretty good the bomber man games people seem to be really well received and they supported it
will really well after the fact so it's a bummer if that contour game didn't turn out that great
but i haven't played it myself it's not yeah it's like a game that is not contra that they threw
the contra name on uh captain spike in our chat hi captain spike and welcome back to our pals
at gameboy.org i noticed they've had two new episodes which means they must be back on a
regular schedule uh so it's good to have you guys back captain spike says been to japan parlors are
trending younger the ip has value so that's that's what it is you know it's just different stuff
whereas like if you go to japan you're probably not going to see dolly parton machines
unfortunately because those machines are the ones i play every time i'm going through the vegas
airport um but anyway let's open up uh the discord for your calls and then also the chat room if you
have anything you want to talk about you can do that now via our discord server and uh our chat
room if you would like to give us a call um let's get to we do have somebody waiting in discord so
we will get to that now hopefully it will work i'm gonna welcome them on the air oh i tried to
bring them on air and they left let me try that one more time and say hello you're on orange
lounge radio who's this and they left if no if i drag you in the on the air room you don't want
to leave you want to stay in here let me try that one more time all right hi you're on orange lounge
radio who's this okay they left i guess they don't really want to be on psych at least say psych
do you have any last minute stories you want to talk about um yeah so we can talk a little bit
about uh let's see here i know i had something on here so call of duty moral warfare i know that's
coming out in just like a couple weeks here if you want it on pc it's 175 gigabytes to install
that game that's ridiculous that's like the size of an entire hard drive almost no thank you i
will not be installing that i don't even know if i'm gonna get that game honestly i do like single
players uh call of duty stuff but i don't know all right we have another person waiting in the
green room so let's see if we can get them on the air hi you're on orange lounge radio who's this
hey everybody it is ron hey ron it's good to hear from you and it's nice to know that discord works
what's on your mind tonight not too much given i'm surviving from my crash this weekend but i'll live
i'm sorry i that didn't come through i didn't have you loud enough what'd you say
i'm doing well given the crash i survived this weekend crash like an actual leader my system
crash i lost everything oh god i thought he meant car crash or something i was like what
okay yeah i yeah i lost everything i'm hoping to be able to take care of a disaster recovery over
next couple days so either one well good luck i i know losing a bunch of stuff like that is a pain
in the you know what so yeah and i've already mentally prepared for effective i have to start
all over with everything so be it well what's on your mind tonight horizon zero dawn oh yeah
what's that horizon zero dawn that game is so gorgeous oh my god that game is so good yeah
how long ago did you play through it i haven't finished but i bought the game like the weekend
i got my ps4 um games i've had it for like 10 bucks so i shimmied my way over there so i was
like let's see how this is 10 minutes into the game i'm like why didn't i get up here sooner for
this game it's it's amazing yeah it's kind of where i'm at where i'm like wow i really should
have got on this train sooner even though people were telling me to do that but it's just like no
i want to keep playing mmos and you know but sometimes the nice i was just saying the nice
thing about getting to the game late is that now all the expansions and everything are already
included and the thing is when somebody says something is so good and like your entire squad
is all over the game i'm the type of person i'm like nope i don't want it i will wait i will jump
onto the game order series in my own time you know so how far did you get oh god it's been a
while since i played because i i have gamers add um i think i'm still on the path some path or
something like that i just know i'll be able to pick up right where i left them i honestly don't
remember god well i'm really gonna try to be in on this game for the long haul i want to try to
get really far in it maybe even beat it um i and i guess there's a whole expansion there's this
frozen wilds expansion i don't know how that plays into things yet i guess i'll find out when i get
far enough in the game uh but yeah i definitely want to play through the game definitely oh and
one more thing before i go um did you get the thing that was sent to you
oh you mean this thing right here
yes yes yes i did thank you very much uh for those that can't see of course because i'm uh
i'm holding something up it is uh some postcards from that golden girls show a puppet parody and
um i'm sorry i didn't text you yesterday but when this arrived yesterday rama that was during the
ingress event so i wasn't even home until like 11 o'clock last night okay cool but so tell us
about the golden girls puppet parody show okay so it was about an hour hour ten they talked about
um dorothy not believing into superstitions uh blanche wanting to get liposuction and sofia dying
did they actually take episodes of the show and do it that way or what
i don't think they took from the show but they just took like some of the major plot points
and rolled it together with the tropes and just and it just played out so well that's fun that
would be a thing i want to see if it's still going in new york when i'm there because i'm
going to be in new york in like three weeks four weeks i know but they just finished up out of new
york and i've been following that i am hoping to hit the west coast but they're mostly doing
the midwest and east coast at the moment um yeah uh and i'm already seeing some big shows and i'm
in new york so i guess not that bad because i'm going to be seeing the um the first few days of
the jagged little pill broadway musical which i'm so excited about uh and then we're seeing
moulin rouge on broadway i'm screaming i'm so excited to see it oh fancy yeah fancy so
all right well my friend um i'm gonna let you go so we can try to squeeze in another call before we
get out for the night but thank you and i'll see you in a few weeks oh you got it and you know
mako chan's hyped as well yay i just got to figure out when and where to meet olr people but we'll
figure it out we'll figure it out because you know she wants to add you to her collection
yay i'm looking forward to seeing y'all next year too oh yeah we got to plan that we got to plan
that and do it do it awesome i'm still trying to decide if i want to pick a character from
a different game and android them hey if that works we we can do it let's do it i need some
help coming up with cosplay because none of my costumes fit anymore i'm kind of starting to know
what that feels all right take care rama have a good one you too all right we're gonna so yeah
i'm apparently making it to derpy con next year after working on the book for six years you should
go it'd be fun all right hi you're on orange launch radio who's this hey this is act deaf
hey act deaf it's good to hear from you what's up well i kind of wanted to talk about the blizzard
thing but it well most of what you said everyone has said already has been said so it's like kind
of redundant so fair enough i want to talk about something uh that don't know if you talked about
last week but uh pokemon go and the the ticket they're gonna sell for for an event i don't know
if you talked about uh that already no not really i may have touched on it but i didn't really super
get into it and can i just also say about pokemon go i couldn't do trap inch day because the ingress
thing was at the same time now both those games are niantic and a lot of people that play ingress
play pokemon go why the hell did they schedule those two things at the same time it's so
irritating i tried to do some trap inch catching with my bluetooth but i didn't get any shinies
boo hoo um well i know isn't that bad garbage mon anyway so i don't even like the evolutions
so whatever all right anyway the shiny does look great but okay uh tell us uh from your perspective
so so if i'm not mistaking that nothing official has been announced this is all through data mining
which i think is important to note because that means subject to change but apparently they're
looking at doing potentially a raid for a generation five legendary pokemon that may be
something that you have to pay for a virtual ticket to do so it would be like oh you can do like a go
fest wherever you are in the world which we know they have the capability of doing because when
they had all those issues at go fest was it last year the year before you had the ability to do a
makeup day wherever you were in the world and those those mobs would spawn where you're at
so they're talking about you know through the data mining doing something like that where you'd buy a
ticket to a virtual festival and you might be able to catch a special gen 5 legendary with this
virtual ticket yeah basically the gist of it is there on the 15 at least uh it seems that they're
gonna launch this ticket a colossal can i remember the the exact name but it's colossal ticket or
something like that and the thing is yeah most people are thinking about this is gonna be a
ticket uh uh kind of rate a ticket for uh dredgy gigas which is one of the legendary pokemon from
the four generation and probably probably but it's not necessarily confirmed uh there's gonna be
tied to a go fest safari zone type event that if you buy the ticket you will get like a special
uh research task like with yurashi mu celiby and all that all those more pokemon
uh you're gonna get something like that and that like uh when you complete all the tasks you will
get uh probably the chance to uh to get ready gigas it's not necessarily confirmed and again
like you said it's all that data mining but uh i was gonna ask you because this uh something
kind of similar happened with ingress you already talked about this i think but what's your opinion
on on something like this like another paid event from niantic this time with pokemon go which is
kind of more popular well they have to make money right niantic's got to pay for their employees
they got to keep the lights on right so we can't expect that everything is going to be 100 free in
these games and i get that but sometimes and where i've taken issue with niantic especially in ingress
is the way that they tell people you know people plan for months to do these things like anomalies
or you know pokemon go fest or whatever the case is and so uh the thing i got really agitated with
niantic about was that they announced a month before the anomaly 30 days before that oh by the
way if you want to get a badge that proved you participated in the anomaly you're gonna have to
pay for it which they've never done before never ever and there's people that will be here on the
ground playing in sacramento or wherever the anomaly is there's also lots of people helping
in other places around the world because somebody's got to be like like looking at the
bird's eye view telling people where to go and what they see because you can only see so much
around you on the ground you can see more stuff from the air and there's other ways people can
support remotely as well and niantic wanted to charge those people too and look i understand they
got to make money okay fine so they want to charge a fee to you know do these things but give tell
people give them better notice give them proper more advanced notice about it and we have this
whole issue with the 1.0 scanner was just it's gone the 1.0 scanner or redacted is gone it's
only prime now so this anomaly we did yesterday was all in ingress prime i kind of think the
people that hate ingress prime aren't giving it enough of a chance or are looking through redacted
a little bit too much with rose colored glasses because let me tell you especially on ios redacted
had a shit ton of issues too like i have not been able to upload stats to agent stats until they
finally got it in prime because redacted you couldn't do it it had so many issues um but
anyway i digress um i also understand a lot of people want to use this just as their reason to
quit ingress when they need a reason to get off the game and that's fine too you know whatever
whatever the case is back to the issue of uh paying for particular raid monsters or whatever
in pokemon go i think a lot of it is in the way they announcement announce it if they do this
announcement where they go it's coming out tomorrow and you got to pay 10 bucks to do it
that's going to be really shitty and i'm going to be kind of upset but if they announce it's going
to be happening on november 15th or something like that let's say they announced it this week
and they say it's going to happen on november 15th and you can purchase it with in-game currency
i think that's all right because that gives you plenty of time to start saving up those gym coins
and you can buy a ticket that way if you like um or if you're just lazy or a casual player then
fine maybe you'll pony up the 10 bucks and participate that way but at least you'll have
a little more choice and you'll have time to decide what you want to do to make that choice
um but that would be the way i would prefer to see them do it is via in-game gold which you can
technically earn for free it's just that it would be kind of shitty if they don't give you an
opportunity to start saving that's all and and yeah that's one of the things that the other thing
that kind of bothers me is that we don't know exactly what is going to be the event
it may be just a rate pass and if it's a eight dollar eight rate pass for a pokemon that's
probably not going to be that great either that's the thing that's worrying a lot because
because the ticket is going to be like on sale for like at least two weeks and the event is
scheduled to be on the second on november 2nd so that gives people time that that's okay
but the thing for me at least the the thing that worries me is how they're gonna do the event what
the event is going to be because if it's only like okay you're gonna get a special access for access
to to regigigas and again that pokemon isn't that great either it's not something that you're
probably gonna use even on raids or other like in even pvp so it's like it's useless but mostly
it's useless it's gonna be it's gonna look great but it's gonna be useless yeah so again if it if
it's tied to a go fest safari zone type event i think that's gonna be like really really great
especially for people like in rural areas that which still with the spawn changes that have
happened in the past in the past few weeks they still have problems and they and people like
would really actually like i i would actually be glad to pay the the eight dollars or how
how much uh it's gonna be in mexico for for this even if i have to pay up money up front or with
uh in-game currency it's gonna be okay on my part uh if it's done like that but if it's just like
that rate pass like a normal rate pass for this pokemon in particular yeah i'm just gonna skip on
it because it's not gonna be that worth it right i kind of think you know again this is kind of the
problem with data mining in some ways is that you know you see the beginning point you see the end
point and we're left to fill in the gaps with either our fantasies or based on what we think
they've done before they're going to do again i mean there's a million different ways you connect
point a to point b but we don't really know until niantic says something so i'm going to give them
the benefit of the doubt and not make too many decisions about it until we hear the bottom line
and niantic says this is what it is this is what we're selling it's a virtual festival
that you know climaxes with this pokemon or whatever i i just need to hear the details and
then i can really kind of make a fair assessment but um i think it's a fair question to ask you
know how does niantic continue to make money especially when ingress is having a lot of
issues right now a lot of the player base seems to not be into it and you know they're they're
having problems having that game make money harry potter well i think it's doing okay it's not at
nearly at the same level pokemon go is not by a mile so who knows maybe there'll be more games
in the future i'm sure i'm sure that's inevitable there's gonna be even more niantic games in the
future but we'll see and that's the thing pokemon go is already making tons of money so it's like
do they really need more but yeah they do well and to be fair technically harry potter is not
really niantic's game yes niantic has a stake in it that's really that's really warner brothers
game portkey you know that's you know that's why their logos show up in the beginning of the game
too niantic's just providing that location database and maybe you know helped him out
with some of the map coding and things like that but ultimately that game really kind of
wrestled warner brothers so anyway uh i'm gonna let you go my friend so we can wrap up but thanks
so much for the call appreciate it hey thanks for having me like always you're welcome take care
buddy all right well i think that's gonna do it for calls tonight um sorry if you didn't get
through you can always tweet us or you can email us mailbag at orange lounge radio dot com um but
before we wrap up and uh call it a night do we have any last minute stories um this isn't really
much of anything but it's the producer of simpsons hit and run so he's up for a remake of the game so
we'll see if they ever get the license to do that um that's about it okay fair enough
then i think we'll uh go around and start to wrap up for the night and get folks final thoughts uh
thank you of course as always for listening to orange launch radio either uh watching us live
on twitch on sunday night or uh listening to us via our podcast feed uh however you decided to
watch or listen to the show we really appreciate it uh if you enjoyed what you saw or watched or
listened to uh be sure to tell a friend or two about the show help us spread the word because
we are the show where every gamer has a voice but if the voices aren't here to put out on the air
what are we left to do so i really would appreciate that so tell a friend about the show
hosting on twitch goes a long way even if you don't stream a lot yourself putting us on your
auto host list super appreciate that and many of you do and i really just want to say thanks for
that um if you're doing that uh otherwise we will be back live in two weeks hoping we'll have
something for you next week stay tuned to twitter for all of the updates because now i want to
tackle that question we got in our mailbag earlier so all right um that's gonna do it though so uh
dark soccer your final thought tonight check out afro punk podcast um stuff you missed in history
stuff mom never told you all really good podcasts um and uh i was gonna say something else and my
brain just went oh yeah be kind but don't be complicit um my final thought is i really hope
i'm not getting sick because i'm supposed to be working the next three days out of town and in a
class and like if i'm getting sick it's gonna be really awkward because i just started this job
like not even four weeks ago so please don't let me get sick gods above goddesses above
i don't need that right now loki your final thought uh my final thoughts i'm gonna be
working a lot on um my game this week and i may be streaming tomorrow night i think i may i've
been holding off on streaming what the golf so i may do that we'll see all right well that's gonna
do it for another week here at orange lounge radio thank you guys so much for watching uh or
listening and uh we will see you next time happy gaming enjoy whatever it is you're playing right
now have fun and uh don't be mean bye you've been listening to orange lounge radio orange lounge
radio is a production of olr studios to join us for a live show tune into vog network.com sunday
nights at 6 p.m pacific 9 p.m eastern the views and opinions expressed in this program do not
necessarily reflect those of the staff of orange lounge radio or vog network but you know they were
all still true see you next week
you