[SPEAKER_04]: Tonight, October 3rd, 2010, NBA Jam goes solo on the 360 and PS3, Sonic 4 gets a release date, and if big titles this year save the PC gaming industry?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello everybody, this is episode, what are we on again? 283.
[SPEAKER_00]: 283 of Orange Lounge Radio I'm sorry, 384 I totally threw out a random number there That's kind of funny, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, 283 We went back in time Rob's gone and the show has become the TARDIS And we have run back in time You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio I got two of the numbers right, though They were just out of order
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, an OLRG, yes, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob is on a plane.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dead.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or dead.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then this is Loki, our tech master.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you do any tech stuff lately with us?
[SPEAKER_00]: I stole a cord the other day out of the box because I need it for something new in the home, but other than that, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mar and Marvel Video Games
[SPEAKER_09]: So, why don't we go ahead and start with you for how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_07]: My gaming week was alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played a lot of WoW.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've gotten back into World of Warcraft after not playing for a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: And other than that, pretty uneventful.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played some, I like the music games like the Lips and the Beatles rock band, so I did some of those.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I've been trying to play Final Fantasy IV The After Years, which came out around this time last year on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I had started playing it and I just like dropped off the face of the earth and so I started playing it again and now I'm at a point where I'm seriously underleveled for the area I'm at so I'm going to have to go do my least favorite thing which is grinding and leveling up.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was always the thing that I could not stand in World of Warcraft just because it seemed really monotonous to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah there is that too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tiara, Mar and Marvel
[SPEAKER_07]: Sky, and Loki, and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll make you famous.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_07]: This is all sounding very dirty.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have ways to make you famous.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now we've got you outnumbered.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's estrogen time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, dun-da-dun!
[SPEAKER_00]: It was always estrogen time here with Robs.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's gonna go back and edit this and go, what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Although it's the truth.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, well then, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I didn't play a whole lot, but I did play some stuff on the iPod and
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know, a lot of it was just disappointing because I go on these binges where I buy a lot of junk.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, not even necessarily buy a lot of junk, but I download a lot of apps and that includes a lot of games, especially stuff that's on sale.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I went ahead and I downloaded, because it was free, Duke Nukem 3D for the iPod or iPhone or whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: The only problem is I deleted it almost immediately because the controls in it really suck.
[SPEAKER_00]: Otherwise, it's Duke Nukem 3D and it's pretty awesome, but it's just the controls really suck, so what's the point?
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, more Plants vs. Zombies.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: I also played a little bit of the newly released Bit.Trip beat on the iPod, and...
[SPEAKER_00]: The only thing I don't like about that game, and it was kind of the same way when it was on the Wii, where everything, you had to kind of tilt the controller to move your paddle up and down.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you had to tilt the iPod to move your paddle up and down, and I really think it would have been a lot better if you could just use the touchscreen to move your finger up and down the screen.
[SPEAKER_00]: It would be a lot more accurate, and it can ramp up the difficulty or something like that, because...
[SPEAKER_00]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_00]: I gotta admit, that game was actually kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it kind of reminds me of the old iToyPlay games.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you may be thinking, oh, iToyPlay, that's going to be crap.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, actually, what's kind of cool about it is the fact that with the camera now and the motion controllers, you can actually do a lot of the augmented reality stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, for example, most of the games actually in that use augmented reality controls.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you'll have your...
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: They had a little, I guess, round in the game where it kind of switches up games really quick, kind of like WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it was actually quite fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I might actually check out the full version of that if, you know, it would be a good party game or something.
[SPEAKER_00]: That and, of course, more sports champions.
[SPEAKER_00]: Play a little bit of that demo as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because I still haven't actually gone out to buy any full version move games yet because I just don't...
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_00]: Dead Rising 2, Halo Reach
[SPEAKER_00]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ow, that hurt!
[SPEAKER_09]: There's this one part right before you go to fight, was it Ridley or one of the... Craig.
[SPEAKER_09]: Craig, sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: Craig.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was thinking of school.
[SPEAKER_00]: Craig.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, Craig.
[SPEAKER_00]: Craig, that's the wrong game.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's in Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, which we did play.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know, I know it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which we did play.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'll get to that next.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there's this one part where this person's like dead and covered in bugs and the bugs fly off and Rob's like, LOL, you're dead.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which I thought was funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then Rob left and we played Turtles in Time on the SNES and we beat the game because Dan and I are an awesome team.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Shredder did not dine on turtle soup?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, but he kept talking about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, dude, don't you have any original lines or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: And so, yesterday I went to play, just because we had to go ahead and go buy this really crappy arcade, I stopped to play Parapara Paradise, which is the first Mix Plus.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually remembered how to do three of them off the top of my head and did a decent job and
[SPEAKER_09]: of course I had four songs to play so I just redid Night of Fire because Night of Fire is fun and then came home and I've played some Sims and mostly it's just been little bits of gaming except for Tuesday night because I've had school work and other stuff to do so that's been my gaming week more eventful than usual but not as not really all that busy my gaming week will be busier soon once Fable 3 comes out because I totally pre-ordered that this weekend ooh
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you going to yell at the dog?
[SPEAKER_00]: Already for Dance Masters when it comes out since you've been playing some Parapara.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's all that game really is anyways.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or not Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it is Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dance Masters, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because there's Dance Central as the other one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wonder if there's going to be actual Parapara in it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It is.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's what the moves are.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're Parapara.
[SPEAKER_00]: They had Night of Fire on there and it's the exact same thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm totally getting this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dan, we're getting this.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's over at my desk.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have to get the Kinect, though, and that's expensive.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I am getting that.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I actually probably will pick up this game just for fun, because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dan's over there saying that he's sure that we'll have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So as for some general housekeeping, like we've been mentioning, Rob is on a giant cylinder defying the laws of gravity, although he is making good use of the laws of propulsion and aerodynamics.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, way to go, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's probably up there asleep or playing his Game Boy or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: That being said, Rob will probably not be here the entire episode.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or if he's here, it will be towards the end.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm not making any promises.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also... Which is why we're going to do this episode really quick so that it doesn't happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we do have the lovely Tiara with us tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who is always welcome to be on the show if she ever gets in town again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I gotta save up some vacation time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that being said, why don't we hop right into the news headfirst and get ready for some decontamination afterwards.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: So the big news this week, of course, Nintendo had their own little press conference not to be outdone by Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, of course, everything Nintendo was covered by.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bitch, we're Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_00]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_00]: They can do what they want.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're not coming to your conference.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have our own conference.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you can't come.
[SPEAKER_00]: So they talked, of course, the 3DS, because that's going to be the big release for them next year.
[SPEAKER_00]: Lots of details coming out about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, it is going to be coming out in February for a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_00]: Unfortunately, I don't think it's going to exactly be that expensive when it comes out over here.
[SPEAKER_00]: But over there, it is quite expensive.
[SPEAKER_00]: 25,000 yen, which is the equivalent of about 300 USD.
[SPEAKER_00]: and it'll be out in aqua blue and cosmos black so that's interesting February 26, 2011 is the actual date they're saying that the estimates in the other regions it's supposed to come out around before the end of the first quarter so probably during their fiscal year
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, so anyways, so that's, uh, coming out then, and some other details, of course, um, came out about it as well, since, you know, they covered everything Uh, what it'll actually come with when you buy it, it's gonna have, of course, uh, the AC adapter, but what's kinda neat, though, is it has a charging stand Um, so you don't have to buy one of those third-party things, you just slap it right in there
[SPEAKER_00]: And by the way, when it's sitting in the charging stand, it kind of looks like a little puppy.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that's kind of weird with the two cameras on there.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a cute little puppy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, that is cute.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, the touch pen and a 2GB SD card, as well as six augmented reality cards, as well as instruction booklets and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I guess...
[SPEAKER_00]: There's actually going to be a built-in augmented reality game that you can play using the 3DS cameras.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that'll be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_00]: I wonder if PictoChat's still in there, because that'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: And of course, other fun stuff that's going to be available.
[SPEAKER_00]: You will be able to, of course, download games to the console as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're going to have the ability to import games that you've downloaded from your DSi or DSi XL into the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: also they're going to have a brand new virtual console that's going to cover Game Boy and Game Boy Color games so that'll be out there at some point and other fun things of course they're going to be having a web browser that actually works this time it's not just some cheap ass web browser that they're going to
[SPEAKER_00]: Tackon later on.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's actually going to have flash support in it, I believe.
[SPEAKER_00]: And they're going to also have kind of a tag mode as well where you can walk around and it'll automatically exchange data with other machines and you won't have to just manually turn it on.
[SPEAKER_00]: And some other things that they're talking about with that is possibly doing firmware updates using that tag mode.
[SPEAKER_00]: So kind of a way to
[SPEAKER_00]: Make sure everybody's not pirating.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was reading about that, but it also seems to me that all it would take would be one simple hardware hack.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you could just also turn it off.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's really worked well for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, well, they don't have any sort of tag mode with the PSP, but you can always turn that stuff off.
[SPEAKER_00]: You might want to turn it off, say, if you're playing at home, because that's going to use up a lot of your battery just with the Wi-Fi on all the time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um...
[SPEAKER_00]: So yeah, so that's what's coming out at least for the 3DS stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sure a big list of games that they were talking about.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, everything that you can imagine.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think they even had video of a bunch of different things.
[SPEAKER_00]: The new Zelda remakes, Mario Kart looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: A lot more games we'll be talking about a little bit later, but very exciting stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, now you were saying earlier when Bobby called us that you expected to have a lower price point.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, so we'll just have to wait and see when more information comes out about that stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: And once we get closer to the launch, it'll be here before you know it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Reckon so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Tiara, do you have any news for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially if you like blue hedgehogs, because... They're crunchy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sonic the Hedgehog 4 Episode 1 is coming out this month.
[SPEAKER_07]: and there are going to be a lot of different release dates for different platforms.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's coming out on October 7th for iPhone and iPod Touch through the iTunes App Store.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can also get it through the Wii Shop channel on October 11th for 1500 Wii Points.
[SPEAKER_07]: Xbox Live Arcade, it'll be available October 13th for 1200 Microsoft Points or $15.00.
[SPEAKER_07]: And on October 12th, you can get it on the PlayStation Network for about 13 euros or 10 pounds, which I believe is something like a million dollars US or 15.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's 14.99 actually, but our exchange rate kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's putting it mildly.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was actually watching a video of Sonic 4 in action, and it looks like it's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like the updated look to it, but still the cool 2D style play.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: I gotta be honest.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have this.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've played it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_00]: No way!
[SPEAKER_00]: So, that might be a good thing for people that like Sonic.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's more of the same, but I thought it was terrible.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, that's my opinion, but this is coming from someone that doesn't really care for Sonic the Hedgehog.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, one thing, now, I did watch someone play through the minecart level, and it looks incredibly annoying.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, I do like the little air dashes in there, where you can target the enemies and dash at them.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was my favorite thing in Sonic Adventure.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I'm glad that's in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, that seems to me like it's enough of an innovation.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see what it is when it comes out for those of us who don't already have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I think the appeal of stuff like this is definitely that it's like the old Sonic games.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it's still 2D and it's still, I mean, the graphics are a bit shinier, but it's got that
[SPEAKER_07]: Big nostalgia factor for people who are like, like, I remember playing Sonic the Hedgehog as a kid.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's like, oh, wow, Sonic, I want to play this just to kind of relive those memories.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a lot of it here with me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, if they don't, you know, don't change what's not broken, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, in other news, oh, Bungie, they've done it again.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have banned 15,000 Halo Reach cheaters and are still looking for more to ban.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not technically cheating.
[SPEAKER_00]: They just found a glitch in the game and exploited it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, my story, dude.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: What they did, it was called network manipulation.
[SPEAKER_09]: They...
[SPEAKER_09]: were going in, they found an exploit in the challenge, in one of the challenge levels where you could complete it 20 and more times and then keep disconnecting yourself.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or I like as the bungee rep said, intentional network manipulation to make it sound like it was something other than pulling out the cord.
[SPEAKER_09]: so they were able to find every one of these so they've just gone and done a blanket ban and what happened with the ban itself is that they've actually banned them for 24 hours and removed all of the credits that they earned and so they won't be able to get any more TigerClaw in chat points out that it's still cheating if you exploit a glitch which I think is true I agree
[SPEAKER_07]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_00]: HaloMakers, patch your damn game and fix it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, they are.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it wasn't really anything I don't think that affected a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was just credits to buy crap for your characters.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't even see what the big deal is.
[SPEAKER_09]: it's getting free credits to get free stuff in the end but then again, I can see it both ways they're especially trying to maintain some level of fairness in the game and definitely replayability the more you play it, the more you have to earn the points the proper way but one thing I would like to point out is that Halo Reach earned $200 million in its first 24 hours so that's the biggest Xbox game ever
[SPEAKER_09]: StarCraft
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because Bungie's not the only people banning.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, Blizzard's doing it too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Blizzard hit up 5,000 StarCraft II cheaters.
[SPEAKER_09]: They actually, for people who hacked and modded their game, they were, they've been permanently banned.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think they're still on the hunt for more people, but for right now, nope, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: You cheat, you lose, bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, thanks, bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Flush.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're getting serious on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Literally only a week away of its release, NBA Elite 11, the reboot, if you will, of the NBA Live franchise, has been delayed to 2011.
[SPEAKER_00]: With it, of course, was the opportunity to get a free copy of NBA Jam, which was only going to be available originally through the purchase of NBA Elite 11, at least if you wanted it on PS3 or Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_00]: of course they haven't announced when they're going to ship it yet but apparently they're going to be shipping NBA Jam as a standalone product on Xbox 360 and Playstation 3 in time for the holidays and they haven't said exactly when
[SPEAKER_00]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's kind of funny because that just makes NBA 2K11 the only choice for basketball, at least in October.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can go outside and play some real basketball.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would work too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, but then they'll fall and skin their knees.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm actually kind of good at basketball, but I'm very klutzy, so I always am jamming a finger or getting hit in the face with a basketball or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, the video game versions are very much safer than actual real life sports.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're not NBA jamming your finger?
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I dig NBA Jam.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think that's probably a game I'd be interested in at least versus NBA Elite.
[SPEAKER_00]: But you got to ask yourself, Elite 11 must have been really fucked up if they got to delay it to next year.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, was there some serious problems with that game?
[SPEAKER_00]: Obviously, no one seems to be really kind of asking them, so why was the game delayed anyways?
[SPEAKER_09]: Licensed NBA star here wanted more money for said likeness.
[SPEAKER_00]: There is a rumor, though, that it was done because there was somebody, I guess, that was selling a disc on eBay for the PlayStation 3 version.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not sure if that was a demo disc or what.
[SPEAKER_00]: But at least there was some sort of disc pressed for NBA Elite 11.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: No pun intended For the record mine was fully intended
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: But yeah, looking forward to NBA Jam.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hope there's lots of presidents in there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hope Clinton's in there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, Obama.
[SPEAKER_00]: That'd be funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it'd be cool if you could play as Sarah, what's her face?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sarah Palin?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd usually try to put her out of my head.
[SPEAKER_09]: But like, I'm just picturing now like specialized quotes for different political figures.
[SPEAKER_09]: It would be funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like hers would be, Hey, I can see Russia from up there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can see Russia from the court.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyways, moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: Since Loki was talking about the 3DS release details, that wasn't all that was talked about during this whole Nintendo conference.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mistwalker's last story was actually given a release date, and it's going to be out on January 27th.
[SPEAKER_07]: But not only that, there's going to be a couple of Wii sequels that they announced at the Nintendo conference.
[SPEAKER_07]: And one is for the Game Boy Advance slash DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's Rhythm Heaven.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I actually did not like that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played the first Rhythm Heaven, and yeah, I thought it kind of sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: It did.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I don't know why that's exciting news, but it's there, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: and the other one is a sequel to the Zero series which is known here as Fatal Frame.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, Fatal Frame is awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's kind of a cool game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's more exciting than Rhythm Heaven, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: The creep factor is definitely with that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Are you... Am I going to pick up Fatal Frame?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I am.
[SPEAKER_00]: They already had a Fatal Frame game over here.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just... I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still need to buy Cho Aniki.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which has nothing to do with Fatal Frame.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know if you need to buy that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's probably not that good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's muscle-bound men flying around shooting things.
[SPEAKER_00]: My mistake.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess that must be awesome then.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's laughable and awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, now, moving on to another front, PC gaming.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's been speculated that the PC gaming market is on a serious decline.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, yeah, we've seen a lot of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some of the major franchises just haven't been there or have been turning towards the consoles.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: StarCraft2
[SPEAKER_09]: These are actually pulling in a lot more of the money.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now other titles that are contributing to this too is definitely The Sims 3 because they keep bringing out more and more expansions to that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think Steam has the right idea with bringing out more and more PC games.
[SPEAKER_09]: But as far as those in particular, they are exclusively PC developed.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're ones that are definitely trying to keep that whole element of gaming alive.
[SPEAKER_09]: And do you think that they're going to be enough to keep it going?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't even know if PC gaming is really dead.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's just... Well, it didn't say dead, just on the decline.
[SPEAKER_00]: On the decline?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't even know if that's true.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_00]: If anything, I know digital distribution seems to work the best on PC.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think... I mean, it's definitely easier sometimes on consoles because you don't have to worry about having the specs to play a game.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just, you know, it works or it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know if I agree with the statement that it's... I mean, I'm sure it helped because they're big selling games, but...
[SPEAKER_00]: There will always be something else that comes out that will be a big selling game in the PC world.
[SPEAKER_09]: Civ V got a 91 on Metacritic, which is pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: and Starcraft 2 was a 3 million 3 million copies have been sold already so that's pretty crazy and it got a 93 on Metacritic so I don't know I don't
[SPEAKER_09]: I think in some respects, if you look at it in a financial sense, as far as games that come out that just aren't selling very well, then I think that that's where the decline can be seen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not necessarily in the people that enjoy the gaming themselves, but just in the games that have come out and how well they sell.
[SPEAKER_09]: But these two have clearly turned that around, if that was the case.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, of course, we've got our MMOs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Always going to be addicts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right, Tara?
[SPEAKER_07]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_07]: For me, there are some MMOs that I can't play because I am on a Mac.
[SPEAKER_07]: Star Trek Online is completely out for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: My friend who also owns a Mac has StarCraft II and he has incredible problems with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not as stable.
[SPEAKER_07]: For me, it's harder to play quote-unquote PC games because I don't own a PC, I own a Mac.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, now, Steam, though, does have a Mac client now with a good number of games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is true, and I actually have downloaded a couple of games through Steam.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so, actually, you know, that has opened up the door to me to buy more games, but it's just a lot more difficult, especially if you don't, you know, if you want to go out and you just want to play a game right away and it's not available, it's like, well, I guess I'll just get the console version then.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ranma is suggesting desktop parallels.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't like Windows and I don't want to put Boot Camp or anything else on my Mac to run Windows in order to play games.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's about what it's going to be like when I have my full Linux box.
[SPEAKER_09]: One cool thing about Linux though is that it will run multiple environments fairly smoothly if you have the computer with the processing power for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that Linux users probably have the best of all those worlds.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would agree with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Linux is a good OS and it's
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty stable, and it's better than Windows.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all I can say about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Linux Mint now is in its final production version, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: But this isn't Linux Chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Orange Foodio, where I'm enjoying a delicious taco salad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nom nom nom.
[SPEAKER_09]: So now that we've had our mention of food and Linux, how about some release dates?
[SPEAKER_00]: I feel sick since we were talking about food and Linux, mainly just about Linux.
[SPEAKER_00]: I got a sandwich and I thought it would be good, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_00]: Apparently this local grocery store over here, Rayleigh's, they have these mega subs now and they have like you can put two different meats and stuff on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Normally I just get like a turkey and cheese and stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I figured, hey, two different meats, so I better pick two different meats.
[SPEAKER_00]: Two different cheeses, I guess I better pick two different cheeses.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I have like a turkey, cheddar, provolone, and salami sandwich.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not as good as I would have hoped.
[SPEAKER_00]: The salami's too sweet.
[SPEAKER_00]: My mic is steady.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, you were cutting out just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you give me the crappy mic?
[SPEAKER_00]: I thought I didn't give you the crappy mic.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Lots of stuff coming out this week, of course.
[SPEAKER_00]: The delay of FIFA Soccer 2011 on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: It came out a week later than the rest, so poor, poor Wii people had to wait an additional week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pokemon Ranger Guardian Signs on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yay, Pokemon!
[SPEAKER_09]: Pokemans, let us show you them.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hollywood Squares on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, because those games never get old.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Sports Collection from Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_00]: Could we get a more generic name for that?
[SPEAKER_00]: Seriously, that's just some sports games, I guess, on the DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: Who wants to be a millionaire on the Wii and DS?
[SPEAKER_00]: I hope Regis is still in that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Enslaved Odyssey to the West coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's supposed to be a pretty awesome action RPG.
[SPEAKER_00]: Lilith's Pet Shop.
[SPEAKER_00]: Got lots of games for that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Lilith's Pet Shop, Biggest Stars Blue, Biggest Stars Pink, and Biggest Stars Purple.
[SPEAKER_00]: And... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Gotta purchase all three, I guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because they're that awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait till you start buying blues clues and all the kid titles for your little boy when he's older.
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: For one, they don't make those on DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's really just Dora or Go Diego Go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or, uh, Niha, uh, Kylan.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, no, I will not be buying that crap.
[SPEAKER_00]: He will have more sophisticated tastes than that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's like, you know, I want the Dora to explore a game.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, you want some Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here you go, you shoot the hooker.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, I can mod a game of Grand Theft Auto that's not as violent.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have that ability.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ben 10 Ultimate Alien.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii, DS, and PSP this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Def Jam Rapstar coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also with the version with the microphone.
[SPEAKER_00]: It is the, I guess, karaoke revolution of the rap world.
[SPEAKER_00]: and it must be hardcore because it's got Def Jam in front of it.
[SPEAKER_00]: NBA 2K11, now the only NBA game coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, the only...
[SPEAKER_00]: Simulation NBA game coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, more kids games as you were mentioning before.
[SPEAKER_00]: Stuff I could purchase for my son later on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Freddy Fish ABC Under the Sea.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's definitely for little kids.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pets Fantasy Sunshine Magic and Moonlight Magic.
[SPEAKER_00]: Those are on DS as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Castlevania Lords of Shadow.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Castlevania game that's not really Castlevania but has Castlevania in the title just to sell more copies.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that is coming out on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 this week as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ah, the epic award-winning I Love Puppies for Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's neither of those two.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just another puppy game where you raise puppies and do stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But don't you love puppies, Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: Puppies are great!
[SPEAKER_00]: Puppies are fine, but I'm not going to buy another game with puppies in it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I learned the first time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_00]: Vampire Moon, The Mystery of the Hidden Sun.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a vampire adventure game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_00]: It was probably one of those hidden picture games, and I guess that's fine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Rapala Pro Bass Fishing 2010, the bundles version of that, with your wireless fishing rod, so you can...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Live out your white trash fantasies?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Way of the... That's a re-release.
[SPEAKER_00]: If I ever saw one, Way of the Samurai 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's already been out.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not going to even mention that again.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um...
[SPEAKER_00]: Final Fantasy The Four Heroes of Light on Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's actually a pretty good release.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I agree with Ranma.
[SPEAKER_09]: He says fuck all these puppy games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want a kitty game, damn it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, listen.
[SPEAKER_00]: They are going to have kitty games coming out.
[SPEAKER_00]: In fact, I know there's one coming out.
[SPEAKER_00]: But you're going to have to live with the puppy game for right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about a monkey game?
[SPEAKER_00]: They've already had a monkey game.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's been a ferret game too.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's been a Pets Monkeys game.
[SPEAKER_00]: In fact, there's two Pets Monkeys games and they were terrible.
[SPEAKER_00]: You dressed up monkeys in little outfits and stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_00]: That sounds like the most amazing thing ever.
[SPEAKER_00]: I only remember what
[SPEAKER_00]: there was some TV show where there's these people that couldn't have children or something they're really old people and they ended up dressing up monkeys like children and would take them out in like baby carriages and stuff like that it's very very disturbing and you can still get that game so that you know alright Tiara we need to go get pets monkeys
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I agree with that statement.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dress up our monkeys.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: John Daly's Pro Stroke Golf on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pro Stroke.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pro Stroke, yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's not just an amateur stroke.
[SPEAKER_00]: He can stroke it like a pro.
[SPEAKER_00]: That is coming out on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: It does support the PlayStation Move for one-to-one stroking.
[SPEAKER_00]: and then this is I think a leftover from last week because oops prank party still still hasn't come out yet thank you Hudson for delaying that another week so I have to mention it for you free advertising there
[SPEAKER_09]: More Bomberman, Hudson, do you hear me?
[SPEAKER_09]: More Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a new Bomberman game coming to the Xbox Live Arcade at some point.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've seen it with my own eyes.
[SPEAKER_00]: From Coco Interactive, it's another casual game, Jewel Master Cradle of Athena.
[SPEAKER_00]: Who gives a crap what it's about?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just a jewel game that you match three.
[SPEAKER_00]: NBA Jam coming out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right, you get it before the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 versions because it was actually supposed to come out standalone on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: None of this fancy stuff because your game sucks so you have to delay it and that kind of fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that would be it for this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know, disappointing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not a lot of pets games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it needs more monkeys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Definitely more monkeys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sadly, there are no monkeys being released in Japan this week either.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there is Enslaved Odyssey to the West on both the Xbox 360 and the PlayStation 3, as well as F1 2010 on both of those consoles.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Red Dead Redemption and Tom Clancy's Hawks 2 are both out on the 360 and the PSP as well this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And on the PS3, but not on the Xbox 360, we have Geki Joban Macross F, Itsuwarino Utahime Hybrid Pack.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, that's a mouthful.
[SPEAKER_09]: I heard Macross.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Macross F, to be precise.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's from the new anime, Frontier.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Kento Mahou Togakugen Mono 3 is also coming out for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Coming out on the Sony PSP this week, we've got Boku wa Koku Kanseikan, Airport Hero Haneda.
[SPEAKER_07]: That should be something with an airport in it, I assume.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kana Imoto is coming out, as well as the limited edition version.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ken to Mahou to Gakugen 3, or Mono 3, is also coming out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: And lastly, for Japanese releases on the Nintendo DS, we've got Kingdom Hearts Recoded.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_07]: We also have Tenkaichi Sengoku Lovers and Maru Gogaku Shikaku Dashu Hanbashi Kente Shiken 2Q3Q That's too many QQs.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: On the 5th, we have Left 4 Dead, The Sacrifice for PC and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: And on the 5th, we also have Phantasy Star Portable 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: On the 8th is a whole crap ton of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Castlevania Lords of Shadow, Enslaved, Odyssey to the West, Final Fantasy, The Four Heroes of Light, Front Mission Evolved...
[SPEAKER_09]: John Daly's Pro Stroke Golf, because he likes to stroke it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Around the world.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like a pro in England.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh dear.
[SPEAKER_09]: PES 2011, WeParty, and WRC on a bunch of systems.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that would be it for the UK.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, one game that's not coming out this week, or even when it was intentionally going to come out back in April of 2011, Gears of War 3 has been delayed to the fourth quarter.
[SPEAKER_00]: No reason why.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sure it's just to add extra polish, or because Microsoft realized, hey, we don't have a good fourth quarter game, so...
[SPEAKER_00]: it will not be coming out when it's intended but you know what there's plenty of games coming out in April and hell I wouldn't want to take any more time away from Marvel vs. Capcom 3 so I'm fine with that delay I definitely I think I could just totally ignore any Gears of War for Marvel vs. Capcom 3 because that game is full of the awesome intensive characters I want to play
[SPEAKER_07]: yeah uh MVC3 yes Gears of War 3 uh probably not because I haven't played Gears of War 1 or 2 just saying yeah I don't know I think I I'm most excited for playing as uh X-23 and Deadpool oh I don't know about Deadpool but well yeah Deadpool in video games is kind of cool because he like he's aware that he's a video game character and he has all the
[SPEAKER_07]: Deadpool is self-aware now
[SPEAKER_07]: is Beyond Good and Evil.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you guys remember that game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a good game and it's actually getting an HD re-release.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Ubisoft is going to be re-releasing the game in high definition and they haven't said when but sometime in 2011.
[SPEAKER_09]: That sounds like it will be a treat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes indeed.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm very excited about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really loved that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a good game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well now it's time...
[SPEAKER_09]: For the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And because I do this, it's kind of weird for me to have to manipulate the music and everything at the same time.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm actually just going to stop that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I don't have Rob's mad skills to do them all at the same time.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I will instead start off with a little bit of music, and I'd like to see how many people can guess what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just by the opening.
[SPEAKER_09]: Presented by Sega.
[SPEAKER_09]: That should be clue enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, the game of the week is Samba de Amigo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_07]: Party!
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a special love of Samba de Amigo.
[SPEAKER_09]: This music is just so perky.
[SPEAKER_09]: I feel like shaking my butt or some maracas or maybe the microphone like a maraca.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or all three of those.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will do them all at the same time, which makes it really bad for radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: At any rate, as we've been talking about maracas, yes, you use maracas as your controllers, and they have these little sensors on the bottom.
[SPEAKER_09]: And what you do is you have to hit these little...
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: And then the Sticky Man, Stickly Man comes up on the screen, which we all know Stickly Man from his next job working for Homestar Runner.
[SPEAKER_09]: But he poses, and you have to match that pose by holding each maraca at the right position as indicated on the screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, in the Japanese version, it's called Ichi ni Sanba, which is a funny pun in Japanese, because it's one, two, three, but san, ba, yeah, anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, there's party mode and battle, where you can play versus couples game, there's a couples game version, which in Japan is called Love Love, where you play through the song to see how compatible you are.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, um, in, uh,
[SPEAKER_09]: Later versions, in version 2000, there's different things to play in there, like hustle mode, where you have to follow the dots and shake the maracas the right way, but you have to do things in these really weird poses, and you're actually moving the full 360 rotation around, so it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's also different versions out that have extra songs in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Version 2000, Amiga, Tambourine
[SPEAKER_09]: Different Sega games, like for downloadables you had the theme from Afterburners, you had Burning Hearts from Burning Rangers, which I love You also have the Rent-A-Hero theme, which is incredibly funny, stuff from Nights, stuff from Sonic Adventure, Jet Set Radio, Daytona USA, Outrun, Fantasy Zone, the Opa Opa theme is in there
[SPEAKER_09]: Sonic CD, the Japanese opening song is in there, Super Sonic Racing from Sonic R, and just a bunch of cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: But as far as the songs in the game, definitely some people might recognize Mambo No.
[SPEAKER_09]: 5 and Mexican Flyer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, anyone who played Space Channel 5 and watched Swing Girls should know that song anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oyakumova by Santana, Papa Loves Mambo is in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, also SOS The Tiger Took My Family by Dr. Bombay is in there, which has nothing to do with Latin music.
[SPEAKER_09]: And yet is still awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, um, one of my favorite things to play in there was, um, actually, uh, The Cup of Life is in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the stupid catch-up song is in there, which I always avoided.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Highway to Hell is in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: In the Wii version, anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: That has a lot to do with Latin music.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to play the combination of Highway to Hell and...
[SPEAKER_09]: Tub Thumping, which is also in all of the versions.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's really fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, the Wii version did come out, but it didn't get very, very good ratings.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has some extra stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has Are You Gonna Be My Girl by Jet and Mambo Mambo and I Want Candy.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's got other characters in there, such as Sonic and Ulala.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you can, it will use your little me's and put some right by your score.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it changes the different expressions that are used based on your performance in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was a successor out that not many people know about.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've actually played it.
[SPEAKER_09]: that's called Shakuto Tambourine which is played just like Samba de Amigo except you use a tambourine controller and it's all J-pop music.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there was a version of Samba de Amigo kinda that was the eye toy version for Sega Superstars where it used the eye toy to hold where your hands were instead of the sensors like the maracas used.
[SPEAKER_09]: And by the way, Shakuto Tambourine is actually really fun and very hard.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very hard.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you've only got one tambourine, and you have to do these little swiping moves over your head and shake the tambourine at the same time, and it's kind of a pain in the butt.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, you've got characters.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have Amigo, who we've mentioned is a monkey, and Amiga, who is also a monkey.
[SPEAKER_09]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_09]: And we have Linda, who is the samba school dancer that wears the butterfly costume.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Bingo and Bongo, they're bears that play the bongos.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rio is a cat person who's like a cat and a jaguar.
[SPEAKER_09]: he carries a rose and a horn there's Chumba and Wamba who play the mandolin and the conga drums and they're named after Chumba Wamba and Mr. Pose who is also known as Stickly Man and that is the game that is Samba de Amigo which I personally think the Dreamcast ones are the best but that would be me so anybody else enjoy Samba de Amigo
[SPEAKER_07]: Somebody Amigo is awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: The way that you describe the characters just now, it makes me think of old Disney cartoons like DuckTales and Tailspin, where it's a town full of weird animals doing stuff that people usually do.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sounds like Somebody Amigo belongs in the Disney kind of world.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, maybe they've got their own, like, Amigaville, where they all hang out and drink Nescafe.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a good, I used to play Samba de Amigo a lot, like,
[SPEAKER_07]: A million years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a good game, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it's like my old New Year's parties that we used to have over here were always... I mean, rock bands pretty much replaced just about everything music-related, but would always break out DDR and Samba de Amigo and pretty soon would just be drunk in Samba de Amigo, surrounded by lots of beer, and people would fall over, and I would tell them not to break my maracas.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still have my maracas and I still I should dust them off and play them soon you should well we are now though sadly at the end of part A but this means we get to go into part B yay so everyone stay tuned we are going to go to a little break and we will hear you when we we will talk to you when we get back you will hear us when we get back I can't hear them
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Welcome back to part B of episode 4384.
[SPEAKER_09]: 384 episode yes of Orange Lounge Radio I am DarkSakura this is Loki and joining us is Mar and Marvel also known as or known in real life as Tiara I just told them your secret identity oh no it's like you unmasked me in front of millions and millions of people now I'm going to have to make a deal with the devil and have my entire history changed so that nobody knows who I am
[SPEAKER_09]: Except really the Illuminati's behind it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So welcome back.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's another reference to perhaps a different podcast that Tara and I do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_09]: With another friend of ours.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who is also an Orange Lounge listener.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, welcome back to the show, as I said.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have got some rapid fire news coming up and tweeter topics, because they're tweety and gooden.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you're all good, then Tara might do it in a porn voice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_00]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mayhaps?
[SPEAKER_09]: Mayhaps.
[SPEAKER_09]: We may have a porn voice tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: So why don't you get us started, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Finally, we've been begging and pleading for Capcom to listen, and they have Mega Man Legends 3 has been announced.
[SPEAKER_00]: Coming to the 3DS, of course, right now, it's just Project, or Mega Man Legends 3 Project.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a work in progress, I guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: And we'll be coming out at some point, I'm guessing probably next year.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that'll be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then of course, this week, like every other week, Rock Band download content.
[SPEAKER_00]: Got lots of it.
[SPEAKER_00]: This week we've got REM.
[SPEAKER_00]: They have a pack there, including Driver 8.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the end of the world as we know it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Living Well is the best revenge.
[SPEAKER_00]: Radio Free Europe, Stand...
[SPEAKER_00]: Superman, These Days, and What's the Frequency, Kenneth.
[SPEAKER_00]: Those are each available for $2 or the equivalent in fake points.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or you can get the pack for $13.49 or $10.80 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry, it's not available for a pack on the WiiWare store.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, the T-Rex pack featuring three songs from them.
[SPEAKER_00]: Children of the Revolution, Cosmic Dancer, and Jeepster.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, those available for $2 each or $5.49 for the whole pack.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, that'll be coming this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, unfortunately, no standalone songs.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess it's just those two packs.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I mean, you can purchase a song standalone in there, but nothing additional.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then finally, there's been some new information coming out about my game of the year next year, Earth Defense Force Insect Armageddon.
[SPEAKER_00]: Some gameplay video looked absolutely awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, they had some details regarding the gameplay in case anyone had concerns.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: and 150 weapons also I believe you can earn different points to increase abilities on your player as well as the weapons that you have there will also be an equivalent to the genocide gun in the game which for those who haven't played Earth Defense Force 2017 the genocide gun is a gun that fires a really big laser blast that blows up a lot of stuff the title itself will also run very smoothly as opposed to the last game that came out
[SPEAKER_00]: The Legendary Infernal Mode
[SPEAKER_00]: and they're also going to have a 6 player horde mode which apparently you will be pitted against endless waves of enemies that will attack you relentlessly also a remix mode where random enemies will spawn instead of the normal enemies that appear during the campaign and if you're very interested in checking it out there's some gameplay video on Destructoid and oh my god it looks awesome I was kind of worried though with the developer being the one that did the
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: and um apparently they are pretty good and they'll actually help you out through the game otherwise you can get people to help you out and uh definitely looking forward to this gonna probably pick up about three copies of it so make sure I have one for uh each person to play at my work so yeah check it out and we got any more news Tiara yes we do
[SPEAKER_07]: Those of you who have pre-ordered your keyboard bundle for Rock Band 3 on the PS3 may have noticed that it has disappeared from US retail sites.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's because there is a contract problem where Harmonix cannot sell the PS3 keyboard bundle.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you will have to buy your keyboard for $10 extra.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you can still buy the bundle on the Xbox 360 and Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, because...
[SPEAKER_07]: I have the Xbox 360 and also Konami is releasing an awesome awesome awesome new 3D racing arcade game called Road Fighters and it's got like a cabinet with a steering wheel and it has drop down 3D glasses so that's kind of awesome and you can switch between 2D and 3D by pushing a button and I don't know it seems cool I love arcade games like this I suck at racing games but
[SPEAKER_07]: It just looks cool, and 3D is the whole new fad of TV movies and gaming, so it should be interesting, and it does look really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: The glasses look ridiculous, I have to say, but it should be fun, and 3D really, I think, is an excellent element for a racing game, since you are right in there with all the cars and all the excitement.
[SPEAKER_09]: The glasses look 80s-tastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: They do.
[SPEAKER_07]: They really do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's part of the reason it's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: And lastly, with Marvel vs. Capcom 3 coming out and Street Fighter 4 released lately and things like that, what about Darkstalkers?
[SPEAKER_07]: I would like to see another game having something to do with Darkstalkers, wouldn't you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, Capcom producer Yoshinori Ono told Eurogamer that making another game in the series would be his ultimate dream, and it can only happen if fans demand it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he said that it's all up to the readers to get Inafune-san interested in doing the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And according to Ono, it would take one million requests before Inafune says yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: unfortunately there haven't been that many requests for the game there have been about 5,000 so only 995,000 more requests for a Darkstalkers game before they will consider making one get on it peeps I'm not going to put my name in there
[SPEAKER_00]: Darkstalkers is awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but I think that they should know that the interest is out there, and if they made the game, that people would buy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, for them to be like, oh no, you have to ask us for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, just make the freaking game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not like you're going to be losing money on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll ask for it with our dollars.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or our yen.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, to put it bluntly, it's like saying, okay, listen, you gotta suck my cock, but you're going to have to beg for it first.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, that's...
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the way they're putting it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it's insulting.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, if you want to put out a game, put out a good fighting game because people are going to buy any fighting game that you put out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't make people beg for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We own the recipe for these fantastic lollipops, but a million of you must say that you want our lollipops.
[SPEAKER_00]: And by lollipops, we mean cock.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was trying to do something that every... Who does not like a good lollipop?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: Parasite Eve was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not bad for a game based off of a book.
[SPEAKER_09]: So they're basically just going to be bringing it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: They just have to tweak it so that it will be playable.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's not just Parasite Eve.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Parasite Eve 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you ever see the live action movie?
[SPEAKER_09]: I have it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't watched it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been trying to look for the translated version of the book.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think I have it on VCD somewhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got a VCD of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, my copy's on a VCD as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just sort of, oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, look what else we've got.
[SPEAKER_09]: Final Fuck X. Because I think I got them both at the same time.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was also based off a book.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_09]: and moving forward how about Scott Pilgrim the new download content is going to have for Scott Pilgrim I said Spock Pilgrim Spock Pilgrim I would buy Spock Pilgrim because it is Spocktober you know
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: For Scott Pilgrim vs. The World, The Game, there is going to be new download content to go along with the film's release on DVD and Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_09]: It will have a new playable character, Knives Chow, along with two other modes.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's an arena battle with weapons, kind of a light version of Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: it's described as, and dodgeball.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it will be $1.99 on PlayStation Network or 160 Microsoft points on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_09]: and they also are going to fix some of the difficulty balancing to make it the average Joe level more forgiving and get rid of some bugs and do drop in drop out co-op it's only though for offline play only and they're not going to incorporate the online MMO into it so none of that yet
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, speaking of Spock, Star Trek Infinite Space is to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a free-to-play browser version of the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So Mac people can play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_09]: And it will be out in summer of 2011.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be published by Gameforge and developed by Keen, who also did What's Cooking with Jamie Oliver.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_09]: And now this is the part that makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's set during Deep Space Nine.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: I thought you were going to say Jamie Oliver's in the game, so... No.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's exciting.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's not special.
[SPEAKER_09]: The only cooking I want is the Klingon chef who plays the violin.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And sings opera.
[SPEAKER_09]: Klingon opera is the best.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: And serves half-dead gach.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course you will...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_07]: And, uh...
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it's not STO, but I like that it's set in the Deep Space Nine universe.
[SPEAKER_09]: That makes me particularly happy, because Deep Space Nine was my favorite.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's, you know, I mean, TNG was going on at the same time as Deep Space Nine, so it's probably going to be more focused towards the war, I'm guessing, with the Jem'Hadar.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that'll be pretty awesome, because that was really a great arc.
[SPEAKER_09]: I agree, and it certainly opened up lots of fantastic characterization for all kinds of people in the series, so I thought it was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, moving forward, we've had another visitor come into the room who was not supposed to be in the room.
[SPEAKER_09]: You need to go find your mommy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please shut the door.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you, Pumpkin.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: She didn't shut the door.
[SPEAKER_09]: Off with her head!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that was Sophie.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is my cousin-in-law's daughter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, we have lots of children over right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: She was excited about Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you blame her?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: She came in wearing my Indiana Jones hat when we were talking about Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, where were we?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yes, we were over to Twitter Topics, weren't we?
[SPEAKER_09]: What do we use for Twitter Topics again?
[SPEAKER_09]: Journey to Wonderland?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we're using it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Twitter Topic time.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't have any Twitter topics so we forgot to tell them to send Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did not forget.
[SPEAKER_07]: I told them during the break.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we told them in the chat room to send the Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we do have some Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_07]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: TigerClaw305 sent us a story about ex-Nintendo sales chief to lead Kidzania's creation of kid-sized cities.
[SPEAKER_07]: So let's see what this is about.
[SPEAKER_07]: I found the right music. ...
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, that sounds more like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now you can continue.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kidzania is creating places for kids to learn about real life jobs and entertain themselves in mini cities with shopping malls.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I don't know, it sounds kind of like some kind of second life type thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Second life equals no life.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: and TigerClaw305 also sent that the Just Cause film has been optioned and the movie script will be written by Michael Ross and it will be produced by Adrian Ask Korea and that should be kind of cool or probably crappy because video game movies kind of suck.
[SPEAKER_00]: And when asked why they decided to make the movie, they said Just Cause.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: We're gonna make it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the reason, yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And for the record, Shadowrunner says Fallout Children.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see, Jay Jugo says, Hey guys, I like this new way to present a co-host on the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a must-keep, in caps, NEVER FORGET, in hashtag.
[SPEAKER_08]: Never forget.
[SPEAKER_07]: Never.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, and Spazinator says, in my porn voice,
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, there's a crap ton of new free vids on the PSN store right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I assume that they're also available on XBL, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what do you think about that?
[SPEAKER_09]: That sounds hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tiger Claw Sentence is another story, but we already talked about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blizzard banning StarCraft II cheaters.
[SPEAKER_07]: And...
[SPEAKER_07]: Dark Kisuke says, wait, what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sexual innuendos in Orange Lounge?
[SPEAKER_07]: No way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lollipops.
[SPEAKER_00]: Way way.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Matt Ostro... Okay, yeah, I can't say that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Matt Ostrovsky, sorry if I said that wrong, Matt, sent us a story.
[SPEAKER_07]: He says, his story sounds too good.
[SPEAKER_07]: It might be a Skrull.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh no!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yuji Naka wants to work on the Dreamcast 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can dream, we can dream.
[SPEAKER_00]: That is wrong.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's never going to happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can dream about the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: Poor Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think one more person sent a Twitter topic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, AlphaKananagram sent us a topic about the Katamari Damacy director and his wife starting a new company called Uvula.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uvula.
[SPEAKER_07]: with a Loki website.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then rather than focusing solely on game development, the company's About Us page details a focus on music and video games, adding that we want to widen our limit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Widen the limit.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what could they do to top Noby Noby Boy?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you know, I actually still play Noby Noby Boy on my iPhone.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not surprised by this actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's going to eventually meet girl.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just like I have no brain capacity to think of anything to do so I'm going to play with my little warm person.
[SPEAKER_09]: It works.
[SPEAKER_09]: DDRDollarBill says no Dreamcast 2 ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alas.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sadness.
[SPEAKER_09]: MesaSuma Shenmue 3 on Dreamcast 2 fall of 20 never ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, that will do it for our Twitter topics this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you want to have your Twitter topics read by Rob when he is back next week, then send your Twitter topics to Rob at OLR on Twitter and he will read them, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe we can get Rob, instead of doing a porn voice, he can invite Mr. Spanky.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob can do one of his voices, which always sound like Rob with kind of a high-pitched voice.
[SPEAKER_09]: So how about we find a few more topics to discuss?
[SPEAKER_00]: I suppose we could.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: Apparently, of course, it's not unexpected, Sony is going after anything that's possibly going to mod the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, they went after the PS Jailbreak before, and now that that's kind of gone, because there's free versions out there, they're now going after other things, including the PS Groove, the kind of open source...
[SPEAKER_00]: PS Freedom, and OpenPS Jailbreak They are aiming for takedowns.
[SPEAKER_00]: Apparently the website PSX Scene has found some different things that they've marked out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Exhibits and they are trying to basically erase the existence of these, not necessarily the devices, but of these programs because the devices themselves can be practically anything nowadays because they've been adopting the PS Groove to
[SPEAKER_00]: Practically everything.
[SPEAKER_00]: Everything from an iPod to a TI-84 to some old ass MP3 players, USB development, cards, just everything.
[SPEAKER_00]: Unfortunately not PSP because they were unable to port it over to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: But your phone, iPhone, Droid, you name it, it can hack the PS3 now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your mom can hack a PS3.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to start hack-storing brains because people are always going to think of a way to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I mean, you can try to stop people from doing that stuff, but where there's a will, there's a way.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if they want to hack it, they will.
[SPEAKER_00]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of hack-storing brains, during the Tokyo Game Show event, Q Entertainment head Tetsuya Mizu
[SPEAKER_07]: and Mizuguchi unveiled the new component of his upcoming rail shooter, Child of Eden.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he wants participation from us.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's for part of the game he calls The Journey Project.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he's seeking to build a collection of player-submitted pictures for inclusion on the last level of the Child of Eden game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mizuguchi says, In this game, the player's mission is to purify everything, even data.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is the final stage of the game, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need the beauty of memories.
[SPEAKER_07]: So with collected memories of family, friends, and beautiful landscapes, you can get that kind of memory with music.
[SPEAKER_07]: It must be real.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mizuguchi also added, I want to put everybody's credit at the end of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Ubisoft clarified that images can be submitted to the official Child of Eden website through November 20th and any approved photos will be used in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't even imagine what's going to be submitted by random people.
[SPEAKER_09]: No butts in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to get a lot of ganguro.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which would be kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_00]: What the hell is going on out there?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like I said, the cousins are over and they're having a fun time in the front room.
[SPEAKER_00]: Happy fun time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Watching YouTube videos of the guys singing all of the John Williams themes with his own lyrics.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually all about Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, some YouTube thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, well, we do have a little bit of other news, at least I do, about Medal of Honor, which for anyone who tuned into Bobby's show earlier, they know this, or if they can read, but they have decided to change the name of the multiplayer faction Taliban to Opposing Force.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, they're doing it, as I said, out of respect for those in the military and for those who have lost family members in the war.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they're trying not to show any disrespect.
[SPEAKER_09]: I sort of have the opinion that they already had this in mind.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this was a ploy to get a little more publicity.
[SPEAKER_09]: But...
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, if they're doing this... I mean, the name Opposing Force is kind of unimaginative.
[SPEAKER_00]: Generic, much?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, very generic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, I mean, wouldn't Opposing Force all be relative to what force you are opposing?
[SPEAKER_07]: They could just call it Bad Guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: They should just... Bad Guys...
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh no, the bad guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then it's offensive to people who are bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh no!
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_09]: They should just call it Red Team?
[SPEAKER_09]: Dudes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dudes?
[SPEAKER_09]: Chicks.
[SPEAKER_00]: But see, then that's just sexist right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_07]: I call everyone dudes, so that's not sexist.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, but if you have chicks to find out in there as well, you just can't do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It should be dudes and blokes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blokes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It works.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh no, I thought we were us.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm me.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's me versus everybody.
[SPEAKER_09]: Die!
[SPEAKER_09]: No, anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Misty says woot blokes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_00]: and also location tests I guess for XG2 are going to be starting soon as well as Guitar Freak's Drum Mania V7 that's way too many damn games that'll be starting very soon and
[SPEAKER_00]: They haven't really said exactly when those location tests are actually going to start.
[SPEAKER_00]: Same with GB Ripples.
[SPEAKER_00]: That location test, sometime next year, but the only one announced so far is XG2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why is it called Knit?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why does Konami name anything like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I want a knitting game.
[SPEAKER_07]: But not really.
[SPEAKER_00]: I believe there's Crafting Mama, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: I want Crochet Master Master of Crochet You could call it Check My Hook To a guy who says Fancy Nancy Fancy Nancy Knit for Fancy Nancy Oh dear In other news Yes please Well we all know how
[SPEAKER_07]: Weird and perverted the internets can be.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so since the internets is full of weirdos and perverts, you have to take some measures to make sure that LEGO Universe can still be child-friendly.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so NetDevil has recently outlined a couple of measures that they are implementing to help protect the MMO's younger players, since it is targeted towards kids.
[SPEAKER_07]: and basically it includes content moderation which is no surprise to anyone really so you will have to get anything that you make the name will have to be approved before it will go out into the LEGO Universe world and the other part is a LEGO Universe ID which is kind of it actually sounds a lot like Nintendo's friend code system to where you give your LEGO Universe ID to other people outside of the game
[SPEAKER_07]: And then they can see your creations that you've made even before they're approved.
[SPEAKER_07]: Protecting the innocent childrens from the weirdos of the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_09]: And later on they will become the weirdos of the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Indeed, but on their own, not without the perversion of other people.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh no, no, we can't have that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Think of the children.
[SPEAKER_09]: Think of the children and how crunchy they are.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it's time for another special segment of the show that this time I will actually use the correct music for.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's time for the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I've got the rubber gloves on.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's bending its stinky self over and I'm opening the bag and...
[SPEAKER_09]: This is kind of... Because Rob hasn't cleaned out the spam filter like he does for me, so there's all kinds of... Read the spam!
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, read the spam, because I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's spam in there about Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_09]: I should have left it in there for Rob, but I won't.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's so Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob loves Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have started appreciating Lady Gaga a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lady Gaga is stalking me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ever since I sang Lady Gaga for karaoke...
[SPEAKER_07]: One time, now she's following me everywhere and she's like in my head.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now when you start, you know, busting out the asymmetrical wigs and, you know, dresses of meat.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't look enough like Marilyn Manson to pull off any of Lady Gaga's looks.
[SPEAKER_09]: She was so much prettier before she went, anyway, I'm not going to get into that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Greetings, OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: I come to Loki with a non-gaming question that I think he'll have a good answer for.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, I'm a contractor and my cell phone contract is up.
[SPEAKER_09]: What would you recommend for me?
[SPEAKER_09]: All I want is a family plan with no text, no data, and 1,500 plus minutes of phone a month.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've looked at the big four.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't know if there's some weird hacker service that I'm unaware of.
[SPEAKER_09]: At the moment, I'm leaning with T-Mobile because of price.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, can you help a desperate turtle?
[SPEAKER_09]: Your loyal turtle in Philly, Serious Turtle.
[SPEAKER_09]: And disclaimer, Orange Jones Radio is not paid by any of the companies that might be mentioned and we should be even if they wanted to pay us.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Honestly, I have a crap plan that didn't have any of that stuff, and it's actually more expensive than plans to have all that stuff, so go fig there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just have to really kind of shop it.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's websites and stuff that you can actually put what you need for your plan, and it will kind of shop everybody and tell you what the most affordable plan for you is.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can't think of the life of me what that website's called, but I know it's out there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's not Google, it's something else.
[SPEAKER_00]: But you can do that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm planning on getting a phone through Virgin Mobile just because they're $25 a month for 300 minutes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because I honestly use like 12 minutes a month, if I'm lucky, on my phone.
[SPEAKER_00]: So anything cheaper than that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was actually looking at a prepaid phone.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I think $25 a month with no contract would not be that bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: And plus I can browse the internet on that if I really want to.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry I texted you earlier.
[SPEAKER_09]: I should give you a dollar.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we've got some suggestions from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: Spazinator says to quote Monty Python, I hate spam.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's, I don't like spam!
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100 Matt says T-Mobile sucks and suggests Verizon and Ranma suggests go with Sprint, great coverage, dirt cheap Virgin also because they're piggybacking on the Sprint network Spazinator uses Cricket I use AT&T because I have an iPhone
[SPEAKER_09]: and I basically use everything except the phone to call people I do not call people only if it's necessary because I hate talking on the phone I did it way too long for my job the only people I like talking to on the phone is like my mom because she's funny and frustrating at the same time I'm pretty happy with Verizon myself they're a little bit more expensive though but I get better coverage from them I have no reception for AT&T or Sprint within my house
[SPEAKER_07]: And I deal with Verizon, so, you know, can't go wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I noticed that I didn't get as good reception in your house when I visited.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep, it's AT&T and Sprint both have really crappy reception inside of my house.
[SPEAKER_09]: AT&T's pretty good out, at least in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_09]: So the next email comes up from Kamitsuyo.
[SPEAKER_09]: It says, Hi everyone at OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's time to revisit how Rob is doing on his quest to finish three games this summer.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't heard any talk of it lately.
[SPEAKER_00]: Considering the summer's over, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: He failed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, what I'm writing about is an episode at the beginning of the summer when Rob talked about how he never finishes games and was dedicating himself to finish three games this summer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Haven't heard any progress on this or on the show lately.
[SPEAKER_09]: He has kind of inspired me to play several games to completion, which I have done several.
[SPEAKER_09]: Red Dead Redemption, Final Fantasy XIII, Darksiders, Alan Wake, and currently working on God of War series on PS3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just finished the first, along with a slew of 360 arcade games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Love the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep them coming.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look forward to the big 10-year anniversary marathon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stay black.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kamitsuyo.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, yeah, one of the games that Rob was supposed to finish was Final Fantasy XIII, which is currently sitting in my living room because I'm playing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, I'm also playing the... I'm sitting down with that Avatar game finally, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we'll just have to make RobFest up next week, won't we?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And last email.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is from DarkKisuke.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just had to note, whatever that Japanese game you brought up on Twitter, I swear it was a fucking hentai.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go back and listen for yourself and be the judge, XD.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hail the FSM, DarkKisuke.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's it for email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, if you have any emails you want to send us, it's mailbag at OrangeLodgeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Send it!
[SPEAKER_00]: A couple more final stories here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I think you have something that we need to do first.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on, someone just said that the stream went down.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although I don't think that it did, did it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you hear us, internets?
[SPEAKER_09]: It says the server's down.
[SPEAKER_09]: Crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's back online.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shoutcast is saying that it's not.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Who crosses streams?
[SPEAKER_00]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we'll just let him... Winamp froze, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Winamp froze.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ah, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tara, can you let the chatroom know?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_00]: You probably want to make sure that Part B saves.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe save it now and we'll continue on with Part 3, if you will.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need to mark this down.
36, 45.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shit, where's my pen?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_09]: Are they hearing us now or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I just like Loki's comment.
[SPEAKER_06]: End scene.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm actually closing down Winamp.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to reload it.
Sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: All Games Radio is now broadcasting live from Sacramento, California.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, we are.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got to fix this to the right settings.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: MP3 encoder.
[SPEAKER_09]: What the hell was it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_03]: 44 kilobyte.
96k.
[SPEAKER_09]: and we should be back are we back can you hear us internets internets are you there oh crap I forgot we can't hear them all right let us know in the chat room if you can hear us we had a little bit of an issue which should be resolved now and thankfully it only went down during mailbag so and I gotta admit it is your fault chat room it really is it really is we we know
[SPEAKER_09]: And DDRDollarBill says, I thought the Daleks were next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, from what I understand, it went down during mailbag, so we'll make Rob edit it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, so shall we move forward with our little podcast?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, rescue us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, you can't rescue us right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know why?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's at the use of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just in time for the stream to go down.
[SPEAKER_00]: Timing is impeccable.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: My FU of the week goes to the stream for going down while I was busy paying attention to other things and for Rob going to Club 33 without me!
Bitch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Heart, heart, heart, heart, heart.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you did my headache that I've had for two days now, and it just won't go away.
[SPEAKER_00]: Lack of sleep, really, but I've been trying to get sleep and just can't.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have a small person.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's not even, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a little bit him.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, it's all him.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, yeah, it's been very tiring to say the least.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, yeah, so that's, after that, after the crappy drivers, I literally saw somebody pass somebody on the right within the same lane on my way here.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I was just like, really?
[SPEAKER_00]: Really?
[SPEAKER_00]: You just did that?
[SPEAKER_00]: You're in that much of a hurry that you need to pass somebody in the same lane on the wrong side?
[SPEAKER_00]: Awesome, thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: And Effie the Scammers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which, by the way, brings us to our favorite, well, my new favorite topic, which is shoutouts to people on AOL Instant Messenger.
[SPEAKER_00]: In fact, we have somebody that you probably should give a shoutout to and let them know that they should really do the right thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that person would be...
[SPEAKER_00]: Pimpin Tyler 146 on AOL Instant Messenger.
[SPEAKER_00]: I will be posting his name in the chat room and Twitter.
[SPEAKER_00]: Be sure to give him a nice little hi because he is a douchebag that didn't come through on his end of the transactions.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sure he'd love to hear from all of you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to my work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because not only am I working my normal shift, which is 9 to 6.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm also now working these extra days where I'm working until midnight or 1am.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's really messing up my sleep schedule.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they don't want to pay me overtime.
[SPEAKER_07]: And on next Sunday, I get to work from 2pm to 2am.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that really, really sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I did not sign on for this.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so F you my work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't they have to pay you overtime if you work more than a certain amount of hours?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, because I'm salary.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they don't want to give me any incentives either.
[SPEAKER_07]: They just want to do this stuff, and it's like, this is not part of my job description, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's very upsetting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope there's some improvement soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, now that the FUs are over and we're full of angst that we have now released onto the unsuspecting internet, Loki, do you have another story for us?
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course I do.
[SPEAKER_00]: and it's funny since you mentioned release there is going to be a brand new peripheral coming to the Nintendo Wii Remote unfortunately it is not something that is say approved by Nintendo or even something that you would say use with a Nintendo game we've covered this yes but they finally actually were going to be releasing them now fun
[SPEAKER_00]: But these are Nintendo Wii remote accessories that are kind of...
[SPEAKER_00]: They're for dildonics, basically.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's two different peripherals to use.
[SPEAKER_00]: And what the main function of this, obviously, is it's actually for chatting over the web.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're using the Wii remotes as kind of a Bluetooth adapter so that these things can vibrate and you can remotely vibrate them across the web using, I guess, different programs.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the Mojo Weejo is what it's actually called, the company.
[SPEAKER_00]: and I believe that they said they're going to be supporting a bunch of different chat applications and I'm sure their own chat application as well but it's in the beta stage right now but it'll be available for purchase in time for holiday season 2010 so God I would not want to be part of that beta test
[SPEAKER_09]: I had to link a copy of that image in the chat room, but I think it's funny that there's like a whole YouTube video describing how it's supposed to be used.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's intensely hilarious.
[SPEAKER_09]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Intensely hilarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, even the name is just too ridiculous for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mojo Weejo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mojo Weejo.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, even porn voice doesn't make Mojo Weejo sound good.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: And your porn voice is excellent.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on, away from the porns.
[SPEAKER_07]: Former Sega man Yuji Naka is working on an action game for the Xbox 360 and PS3 with Prope.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he hasn't revealed what the game is yet, but he will soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, according to Naka...
[SPEAKER_07]: They are doing a few quite big action game projects at Prope, but he didn't tell us anything about them.
[SPEAKER_07]: He did say that a very original action game based in the sky will be revealed within this month.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's something to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope it has airships.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, airships!
[SPEAKER_09]: I wonder if it's going to be Skies of Arcadia.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, maybe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Could be.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's based in the sky, and it involves airships.
[SPEAKER_07]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we will know soon, according to Nakasan, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Within this month, they are going to tell us about his project.
[SPEAKER_09]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_09]: if we can get it to work so I'm going to go ahead and make this disclaimer right now because we do have Tiara in through Skype I'm going to try to get these to work as a conference call so we don't have to disconnect on her so I'm going to go ahead and open up the Skype line now and go ahead and make your calls I'm not going to play any music call
[SPEAKER_00]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is about we do the waiting game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, Dan.
[SPEAKER_00]: Riveting.
[SPEAKER_00]: It is riveting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, we got a call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, we got a call.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to answer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, you're talking to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_12]: This is DJ Blaziken.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, DJ Blaziken.
[SPEAKER_09]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm doing fine, and I just found...
[SPEAKER_12]: a solution for all DSI owners that might be listening in I found this out through the internet and through the grace of it because I don't know if any of you guys have had this problem but I have and I'm sure there might be a few of you that might have had this the L and R buttons becoming not able to be fixed when hit and you'd have to end up Kung Fu mashing them in
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, the thing is, the little gap that lets it go down is basically letting dust in.
[SPEAKER_12]: Basically, best bet, take a little mini vac or whatever you have to suck the dirt out and do exactly that.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's supposed to... Actually, it's made my DS work again.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fully functional again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, thank you for sharing the tip with us.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm glad it's worked for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure other people have had similar issues.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, and, um, other than that, my original DS, well, the second DS light I've ever owned, started to completely fail on me, and ended up spending, well, going broke, really, on a new DS light, and it was actually the last one in the batch.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it was well worth it, with Pokemon HeartGold, which is kind of a, I don't know, basically just HeartGold with the crystal
[SPEAKER_12]: and yellow features sort of slapped into it with new DS graphics.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'll tell you what, we're getting other calls in, so I need to go ahead and let you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for calling.
[SPEAKER_12]: Otherwise, I do give it a 10 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, thank you for calling.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that was DS Master.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I am super professional.
[SPEAKER_09]: Osfer says I'm super professional.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's make sure that we haven't... I'm going to see if I can't get Marin off of... Are you there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, so this is what we're going to do now for future calls.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want people to... I'm going to add the conference.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aha!
[SPEAKER_09]: It worked.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, who are we talking to?
[SPEAKER_10]: Clark.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, hello you across the ocean.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, Aki Ripper, how are you?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm doing just fine on this Monday morning.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we do have Tara on the line still too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Monday morning?
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you from the future?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I just live in this place called Sweden.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the future in Sweden.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm like, well, what is it?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm eight hours ahead of you.
[SPEAKER_09]: That means you are from the future.
[SPEAKER_07]: You are from the future.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's the future like?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it beautiful?
[SPEAKER_07]: Are there flying cars?
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell us, I must know.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, nothing of that yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_07]: But since you're in Sweden, you have awesome chocolate, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're thinking of like Switzerland or Switzerland.
[SPEAKER_07]: What does Sweden have that's awesome?
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell us about Sweden.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do we have that's awesome?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we... Oh, that's like... We have... What do we have?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well... Damn!
[SPEAKER_00]: Prostitution?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cotton hookers!
[SPEAKER_03]: We have prostitution in Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's Amsterdam, sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyways, what's on your mind, dude?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, well, what did I call?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, well, something of some sort.
[SPEAKER_10]: Crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: You forgot to talk about something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dragon Age Ultimate Edition is coming soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, somewhere around December or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: and, well, the funny thing is that I've just been reminded I did buy Dragon Age on launch day and I haven't played it.
[SPEAKER_10]: The reason I've just been reminded is that I play it on a PC and, funny story is that my computer that I play it on, you can unlock it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can unlock all the four cores since two of them is disabled by default of sorts and that makes Dragon Age load up pretty fast
[SPEAKER_10]: but then the two cores was really faulty so I had to disable them and then I was like I don't want to play this slow loading game so I'm going to play it when I have a quad core and I still don't have a quad core so I'm just going to wait even more.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you should just suck it up and play the game, because Dragon Age Origins is an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the best game ever, and you're really missing out.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, you have Dragon Age Origins in Sweden.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what you have, but you are neglecting it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, to be honest, I'm playing that thing called Sims 3, and I'm eagerly waiting Nightlife.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm probably going to get it well after everybody else has had it.
[SPEAKER_09]: The chat room also would like to inform us that Sweden has IKEA.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but where I live, where I live in Sweden, we don't.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have it, but I have to go like, well, what is it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Two
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, because I'm like one of those, in some way, uneducated bastards that lives in a cave of sorts.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's okay, you're like the rest of us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where we live in our caves called our computer rooms and don't come out except when we need to eat and go to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's like one up on this one, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I have a challenge for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a challenge for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the end of the month, you must start Dragon Age Origins.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, well...
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's... That's not... Well, that... Because of the thing, though, in one way, actually, I've been reminded.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have played it, it's just that... It's just that I want to play the... Well, I have, like, played a few of the origin stories, and then afterwards I just get bored by some strange reason.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you have gamer ADD.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, well, and I actually have a real ADD too, so That would contribute.
[SPEAKER_10]: If we are to go be that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would contribute.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Aki Ripper, I appreciate the call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are we doing okay without Rob?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you're doing just fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, well, in some way I would say more of this in the future, please, even though it's like
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, Rob, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, yeah, that's the way, yeah, something, I don't know, I'm just this worthless foreigner of whatever, I'll just, oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, you are not a worthless foreigner, we adore you.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we need to go ahead and let you go, we've got another call coming in, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, later.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, caller.
[SPEAKER_09]: You are on Orange Jones Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who be thee?
[SPEAKER_01]: I be DDR Dollar Bill.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, DDR Dollar Bill.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, nothing much.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just want to give an update about the PlayStation 3 that I got a couple weeks back.
[SPEAKER_01]: I finally purchased it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I said congrats.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, thanks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a lot better to watch DVDs on there, I'll give you that much.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the move, I didn't like it at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: I found out that you asked for me, I actually have to be about six feet away from the TV, and unfortunately I don't have that much room in my apartment.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, so, I mean, I went forward, and it stopped detecting, and I was only, like, maybe four feet away from the screen, and I said, uh, no, this is not gonna work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there any way that you could wall mount, like, a receptor or something?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd have, well... I think you should mount it onto your ceiling.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's at least six feet away, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd have to lay down on the floor to do that, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd be laying on the floor waving my stick.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, that doesn't look right at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well then.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but I just wanted to say that, and I've gotten a lot of enjoyment out of it for one big reason.
[SPEAKER_01]: No fucking batteries on the controllers.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was such a joy just to actually plug in the controllers, get it going.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, we got multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's always a plus.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, so... So let's... Hold on a second.
[SPEAKER_01]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm hearing myself repeat myself.
[SPEAKER_09]: You had to do what to yourself?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I was hearing my voice coming in an echo.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was like, why?
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe you've got your... You're too close to your speakers or something to that effect?
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to be at least six feet away.
[SPEAKER_01]: You must be at least six feet away to enjoy this podcast.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, so the biggest hits so far in the household is LittleBigPlanet and ModNation Racers.
[SPEAKER_09]: How do you like ModNation Racers?
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been meaning to play that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, before I go into it, I'm going to say this again.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is the sole disclaimer.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought Super Mario Kart on the SNES was the biggest piece of shit that ever existed.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought the controls sucked horribly and the perspective just...
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know.
[SPEAKER_01]: And especially when they can't just design their own characters and cars and even tracks.
[SPEAKER_01]: When they start doing the tracks, that's going to be a lot more fun because we can just recreate anything we want.
[SPEAKER_01]: Especially around New York, we got no shortage of tracks to replicate.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I need to ask you something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: As a dude, I have to ask you this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is it about being able to customize your characters?
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't that a lot like Barbie dolls for dudes?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: When we have all these wrestling games and my husband would like try to, you know, make the wrestlers look all cool and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, dude, it's like you're playing dress up.
[SPEAKER_07]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_01]: In essence, you're halfway right.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is kind of like doing Barbie, but... But it's manly Barbie.
[SPEAKER_09]: And wrestling is like soap opera for dudes.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, no disagreements.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, he got her drunk and they got married!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh no!
[SPEAKER_09]: Triple H. Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Look, I'm coming back from the dead again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, now it's the underbiker.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, he's back to Undertaker, like the dead guy again.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was a biker for a while though.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right, but the underbiker was.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now we're on wrestling, sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's alright, he lost tonight anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh really?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's been that long, I'm like, I don't know who any of these people are anymore.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's terrible that they wrote that into the script, that he would lose.
[SPEAKER_01]: He lost by getting hit with the urn.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: They wrote that all back in there, they're going way back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: They went backwards.
[SPEAKER_09]: Given that I remember playing Wrestlemania in the arcade and you could choose The Undertaker when I was a kid Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: The underbiker needs to retire.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're not the only one who's saying that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, anyway, so now, thank you for clearing this up for me, because I've always wondered if it's just the same sort of little giddy joy in making them look pretty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, pretty, pretty ponies.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just to add to it, in the wrestling games, it's also a joy now where you can actually create your own finishers, so now it's not just, ooh, they look pretty, like, ooh, I can kick your ass pretty!
[SPEAKER_09]: That's... I've never heard someone say, I can kick your ass pretty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ha ha!
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, just going with the thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you ever play WrestleMania 2000 on Nintendo 64?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: I played that, and I made this guy who was part of D-Generation X, and we would just put him on watch mode, and he beat everybody.
[SPEAKER_09]: He won every belt, including the women's belt.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, gosh.
[SPEAKER_01]: When the AI was actually that
[SPEAKER_01]: easily manipulative.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, this isn't wrestling chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is Orange Ons Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Video games, but... Are you sure about that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sometimes.
[SPEAKER_09]: We talked about food in Part A. We did already get our food out of our system.
[SPEAKER_09]: That sounds bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's more like what we do during the break is get our food out of our system.
[SPEAKER_01]: Speaking of which, I got my pizza here to eat too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why don't we let you get to your pizza?
[SPEAKER_09]: What kind of pizza do you have?
[SPEAKER_01]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_09]: alright, you too bye pizza and wrestling so reminds me of my early years with my husband how romantic well, you know how we got engaged was watching UHF and drinking Manischewitz wine, which should have set a precedence there yep so, do we have any other callers?
[SPEAKER_09]: because if you don't, I'm closing the line and you're all SOL
[SPEAKER_09]: 5, 4... Misty is supposed to call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Call, Misty!
[SPEAKER_09]: Misty, call!
[SPEAKER_09]: You must call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or we'll call you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Conferencing you in in just about a minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you on?
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, she's sneaky.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do not see her in the list of people who are on the lines.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, there we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope, I do not see a Misty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Call us!
[SPEAKER_09]: Call us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, we got another one in, but it's not Misty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see who this is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, you're on Orange Jones Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who are you whoring yourself out today?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm whoring myself to whoever has the highest amount of money for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh baby, oh baby.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi Ranma.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi Ranchan.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ranchan, oh hi.
[SPEAKER_09]: We see what you did there.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I do try.
[SPEAKER_09]: How are you doing today?
[SPEAKER_11]: I am doing good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Would you believe I just finished editing my podcast to get it and it's... Huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Did we lose him?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hit the mute button by accident.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember, don't hit the mute button.
[SPEAKER_09]: Never hit the mute button, because then you'll end up sounding like this while you're trying to talk.
[SPEAKER_11]: And right, we can't have that now.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just finished editing our podcast, and it just went upline, and I'm looking at all the emails of all the gaming demos that's going on at New York Anime Festival slash Comic Con this weekend.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, do tell.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, first email I got is from the people behind DC Universe.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh!
[SPEAKER_11]: Which is also interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Marvel Super Hero MMO will be playable as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm looking at a graphic of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's pretty much the Marvel Super Hero Squad online game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aw, that's cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: That should be adorable.
[SPEAKER_11]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I also got an email from Sega, so they'll be showing off the new Thor game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I am curious about DC Online, because this will be the second time I've ever played a PS3 in my entire life.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, first time I played it was at some gaming con, and I played it on Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_11]: Only thing that annoyed me was the load time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I much prefer that on Xbox.
[SPEAKER_11]: As do I. It's funny though, I only bought Street Fighter 4 only because I know the person that does the voice of Ryu in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who is it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, what other stuff has he done that I would recognize?
[SPEAKER_11]: His name is Kyle Hebert, and did you ever watch the dub Dragon Ball Z?
[SPEAKER_09]: I tried not to, but I have it sometimes.
[SPEAKER_11]: He did the voice of Adult Gohan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: He was actually one of the ones that wasn't annoying.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of the very few that were not annoying, he was one of them.
[SPEAKER_11]: He wasn't the older adult Gohan when Viz and Pioneer dubbed it.
[SPEAKER_11]: He was part of the Funimation cast when they redubbed the series.
[SPEAKER_09]: I pieced it together when you said it because I remembered Ryu's English voice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, and that and I don't remember how many episodes they dubbed before Funimation took over.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just like a giant blur to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dragon Ball Z is a giant blur to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, with Dragon Ball Kai, which is supposed to be more of the manga-based version, or I like to call it Dragon Ball Z Kai, less filler reps, still tastes great.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the battle with Cell only takes like five episodes instead of 73 episodes?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously, when I had my fan subs of the Cell episodes, they were seriously over four VHS tapes at whatever the long play was.
[SPEAKER_09]: SLP.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's way too much.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: I remember the first time I watched the Phantom of Dragon Ball Z. Me and my cousin were at his grandmother's house watching it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it was third or fourth generation VHS tape because as we're watching it, the video quality was so bad that it would just flip to a blue screen like every three minutes.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we're just sitting there glued to the TV watching every single minute of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That sounds like my first experience is watching Ranma 1.5.
[SPEAKER_09]: My first copies were fansubs from the Ranma Project, about four or five generations old.
[SPEAKER_11]: I remember there was this comic book shop I used to periodically hang out at, and they actually had the fansub copies.
[SPEAKER_11]: But the thing is, I didn't like the price he was offering.
[SPEAKER_11]: He was like, two episodes for like 20 bucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm like, no, that can stay on the shelf.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember the old days when he traded fansubs.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ah, memories.
[SPEAKER_11]: I still have all my fansubs in storage.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now we download them off the internet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shh, shh, don't say that.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're not supposed to.
[SPEAKER_09]: How else am I going to get my Digimon fix?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, did you know they actually... I'm watching the new series of Digimon.
[SPEAKER_11]: ...refansubbed on Digimon?
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, don't... Don't get me started.
[SPEAKER_09]: So how about more video games?
[SPEAKER_11]: I do like Butterfly, the opening theme.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about more video games?
[SPEAKER_09]: What else is going to be up there?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's basically it.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all the information I have here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, there's another company called Game Tech that's supposed to be there.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're probably doing these little flash-based games or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's my assumption.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're not saying too much about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to be the Kentia Hall of your convention.
[SPEAKER_11]: To be perfectly honest, the Kensha Hall of Comic Con is like the little room in the back where it's open gaming and then people try to get up on stage and make fools of themselves.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's always the best part of cons is people making fools of themselves in costume.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll definitely be in costume.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of in costume, I am looking for pieces for a River Song cosplay from
[SPEAKER_07]: The end of the last Doctor Who series, so if you know somebody who can help me out with finding some pieces for that, I would be much appreciative.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm probably the minority in my group that does not watch Doctor Who, only because I have so much stuff on my plate to watch I have no time for it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tsk, tsk, tsk.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, if it helps, I watched some of the original stuff from the 60s and the 70s.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I grew up on.
[SPEAKER_11]: on public access.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fourth Doctor with Sarah Jane.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, if Ron-chan can't help me, somebody on the interwebs that is hearing this, the tens of people who listen to this show, there are a lot, so if you would like to help me out with some River Song cosplay so that I can go to the Laguna Beach Comic Con, is that the one?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm going to Long Beach Comic Con at the end of this month, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: In the old home of Anime Expo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I remember that place.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I remember walking all over that section of Long Beach in four-inch platform heels.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not smart.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, but I was cosplaying.
[SPEAKER_09]: For the record, I was cosplaying Mad Hatter from Angel Sanctuary.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hence the boots and walking around in wings in a crowded dealer's room.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not smart.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't do it again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well Tiara, I can't say this much.
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually do know a couple of people out in the Vegas area that are cosplayers, so I may be able to cash in a favor or two.
[SPEAKER_07]: If one of them is somebody that I think it is, that might be a creepy person from high school that I went to high school with, so maybe not.
[SPEAKER_11]: Male or female?
[SPEAKER_07]: Male.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're in luck, they're all females.
[SPEAKER_11]: Most of the cosplayers I know and commissioners are female, so you're good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got you, I got you.
[SPEAKER_07]: No creeps for you today.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, one day creep free.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except when DS Master called in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I missed that call, so.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right, you were on hold.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Ranchan, thank you for your call, and you need to get your ass back out here soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: As soon as I get some cash monies, me and Joe, Daya, and Missy will come out there and invade for a weekend or two or three.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or everybody compile and get me out there, because I don't want to be in California.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I want to go to New York.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, we need to make the Send Jamie and Tiara to New York fund.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and DDR Dollar Bill said I should ship myself there, but I don't know how many air holes I would need, so I'm not sure if that would work.
32.
[SPEAKER_07]: 32?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not to mention that they put you in one of those non-compressed compartments and you'll freeze to death, so that's not good.
[SPEAKER_00]: That would kind of suck.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, hey, Loki, when did you show up?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I've been here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's been looking at porn and playing the magical unicorn fart game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been doing either of those, but yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would explain why the stream went out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bad Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it went out from spam overload from the email.
[SPEAKER_11]: Eep.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, do you have anything else for us?
[SPEAKER_09]: Give us more.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well we are going to let you go reluctantly, reluctantly.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, take care and thank you for calling in.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anytime.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fantabulous.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I think that we're about called out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to leave room for one more call and if not, then we'll go ahead and ask for any last minute stories and wrap the show up in ribbons and bows and call it pretty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay, so pretty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shadowrunner says someone should cosplay Billy Mitchell.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what, all that makes me do is when I hear the scout doing the Slap Chop commercial.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on, somebody fill time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Time, fill, woo!
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Misty's birthday.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should say happy birthday to Misty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy birthday, Misty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy birthday to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy birthday, dear Misty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_09]: Now send us cake.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fresh, fresh cake.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, cake.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or cupcakes.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love cupcakes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ranma's telling everyone to tell GFDia to call in and do coffee talk.
[SPEAKER_09]: Coffee talk with Jamie and Tiara.
[SPEAKER_09]: Give us a call.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll talk.
[SPEAKER_09]: No big whoop.
[SPEAKER_09]: That Madonna is such a skank.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was my favorite coffee talk.
[SPEAKER_09]: With Madonna and Roseanne Barr.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then Barbara showed up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because she's like, butter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I'm still trying to find this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't find it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where is it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Shadowrunner says, the cake is a lie, but pie is constant.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is true.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pie is constant.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can't spell today Well, last minute stories I guess Yes please Retailers are apparently listing Duke Nukem Forever for February 1st I can tell you right now that's just an estimate Because they haven't really given out the exact release date yet I'm assuming it's February though Because we have it listed in February as well But not the 1st Because that would be wrong Well, here I've loaded this up Oh, we've got another call coming in, hold on
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me add them to our call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, you're calling in Orange Lodge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is Gio Vidal.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_09]: You've called.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now we can talk.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can talk, so we can have... We can discuss.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can be done.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can has-hasing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, so how are you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Why did your nose hurt?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, I pierced my symptom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fun!
[SPEAKER_09]: That sounds about as fun as putting a hole in your face.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why did you go and do a silly thing like this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: I had the time and I had the money.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you've got the time and money, you should just come out here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's less painful.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I was on a weekend vacation at a barbecue competition thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was at the beach, so I did it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I just, it's a weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not being able to go out to California.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, if everybody else put holes in their noses with you too, oh, I guess you did.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what's going on on your gaming front?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually trying to play through the Lego games again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, which one are you playing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I went through.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to play through Batman now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lego Batman is so much fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It absolutely is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm having so much fun with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's just, it's absolutely ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fantastic, innocent fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think Lego Indiana Jones is still my favorite though, but I have a soft spot for Indy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even though he's old and walking around with a cane.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I have that for the DS, and I like the dumb DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have Batman for the DS too, and I played that like crazy, so now I'm just trying to get through everything on the 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you play through Arkham Asylum?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do not have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to wait for it to come down in price and find it down at price.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I can find it cheap, I will send you a copy.
$39.99.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I can find it cheap at you somewhere, I will find you a copy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's really worthwhile.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, I think I saw it at one of our local used music and game stores for like $20.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll work out something after the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can PayPal me.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: That sounds good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even though I still have to send a soundboard to Tiara.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still have stuff to mail you too, so it's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you only sound vaguely Atlantean.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: so well I totally I totally suggest the Arkham Asylum game it's pretty fun and you can also just go around and the best thing to do in that game is to get up on the gargoyle heads in some of these areas and then drop down behind people upside down all crazy like and you pick them up and beat the crap out of them and drop them down it's just awesome Batman it's so fun I know see that's the kind of stuff that I do in Metal Gear I just go up behind people and just like strangle them and snap their necks it's
[SPEAKER_09]: See, now in my head I've got Rob's voice going, LOL, you're dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the kind of crap that I do in video games, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: You like the ninja.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that makes me a little violent, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's nothing wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have to blow off steam somehow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I do it on video games and kill people and knife them to death.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because we know the difference between gaming and reality.
[SPEAKER_09]: And as much as we imagine doing it to people in real life, we do not actually do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we just wish that the video games were real sometimes.
[SPEAKER_09]: DDRDollarBill says, remind me not to piss her off ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: And doesn't want to have this next snap silently.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, let's not do that for reals.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or what was the line in Silence Good, but let's play Metal Gear for real.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, do you have anything else that you wish to discuss with us?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just calling in to say hi, basically.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, hello.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're glad that you called.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, indeed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Batman!
[SPEAKER_09]: He's Batman.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm Batman.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you take care, and we will end it on Batman.
[SPEAKER_02]: Batman!
[SPEAKER_09]: Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na phone call!
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, that's it for Skype.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to go ahead and go on the Do Not Disturb because I will not answer any more of your insolence questions.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do not disturb.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will no longer respond to your insolence.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you have any more last minute stories for us, Loki?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tiara, do you have any last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_05]: I do not.
[SPEAKER_09]: So how about last minute thoughts?
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, last thoughts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, any final?
[SPEAKER_00]: My head hurts.
[SPEAKER_00]: Baby's sleeping right now and that means he's going to be up at night.
[SPEAKER_00]: My head hurts even more knowing that I have to get up at probably 3 in the morning this time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Time to break out the Vicodin.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can't swallow pills so that doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll put it on your pizza.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Tiara, for you, any last minute thoughts?
[SPEAKER_09]: Happy Spocktober, everyone!
[SPEAKER_09]: That makes me all warm and fuzzy and logical.
[SPEAKER_09]: And my final thought is... Taco Salad defeated!
[SPEAKER_09]: Dun-dun-dun!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright everybody, well that's been this episode of Orange Lounge Radio sans Rob who never did make an appearance.
[SPEAKER_09]: How dare he not make an appearance.
[SPEAKER_09]: Goodnight everybody!
[SPEAKER_04]: See you next week!