[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, October 24th, 2010, two Capcom worlds collide in an upcoming 3DS game, fans of Sonic the Hedgehog up the ante in a new HD version, and in one country, Grand Theft Auto 4 is ordered off the shelves.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are that radio video game talk show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do tape live every Sunday night, 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern at All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: www.allgames.com right after the Bobby Blackwolf Show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining you over the next few hours are myself, Rob Roberts, and my awesome co-host.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello to the one and only Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Storms, LOL
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything is so dried out from a long summer that it just screws everything up.
[SPEAKER_05]: and the oil floats all up to the top of the streets and it becomes a big slick and no one knows how to drive in the rain.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's been raining for almost, it feels like a day straight.
[SPEAKER_05]: It rained yesterday almost all day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the rain.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I've been sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I like rain when I'm sick because then it makes all the warm food I'm eating so much better.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, say hello, of course, to Tech Master Loki, also joining us tonight, as he always does.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: And complete with what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we on quadruple bacon pizza now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't want to scare them with the thought of putting four times the amount of bacon on a pizza.
[SPEAKER_05]: They'd have to make you sign a medical disclaimer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd eat them into that, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: How have things been for you?
[SPEAKER_02]: How's the baby doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Baby is fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was with mom going to her parents' house.
[SPEAKER_02]: And where's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that in the bay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Folsom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is he pooping fine?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, he's pooping just fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I remember the poop scare.
[SPEAKER_04]: Inquiring minds want to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining us in studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, in studio, not on Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: We love having guests actually come down to the studio and hang with us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello to our pal, The Seg.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Seg.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, OLR!
[SPEAKER_04]: Wonderful to be here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wonderful to have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you so much for coming out here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't really had a chance to say it to you before we've gone live because it's just been go, go, go, go, because I was running in the door late tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I did get a new mic cord for Dark Sakura, so it wasn't all for naught.
[SPEAKER_04]: So just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully it works tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not having to hold it in.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what she said.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, but Seg, you drove all the way here from the Bay Area, which is a good... Well, usually it's probably about an hour and a half, but I'm going to guess because of the rain, it probably took like two and a half hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it was exactly an hour and a half.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I am from Detroit, so I actually know how to drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Ford family here, so... Well, regardless, no matter how long it took you to get here, it is quite a bit of a tank of gas, so I do really appreciate you coming out and hanging here in studio with us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not quite as glamorous as it sounds on the radio, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't have to pull back the curtain for everyone out there on the internets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I meant, of course, our microphones are all gold-plated.
[SPEAKER_04]: This couch is absolutely wonderful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give me more grapes, servants.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Sag, you are here, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course you have ulterior motives for being here tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that we mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: We appreciate a reason to have you here in-house.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you're here to promote a little something-something that's going on, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a little something.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you might have heard of it because, you know, gosh, we've only mentioned it on the show about 50 gazillion times.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's okay because it's a charity thing and we'll say it a gazillion more times for charity.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is up?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the big event that you are co-hosting?
[SPEAKER_03]: Umlaut, a rock band night for child's play charity.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a performance-based rock band night, and I really stress it as performance.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not a competition.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't give a care about your score whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all about rocking out for child's play charity.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, no one, as the old saying on the internet goes, no one cur if you have a crappy score on a song or what have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to get the most props if you're really into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the outfits and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the stuff I saw last year, outstanding.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Lego Rock Band people were great.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was lots of dress-ups, bands, good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we started it last year under the wake of Fundrauser which went away but it was Chris Kohler of Wired.com game life blog Joe Marquette of Game Helper and myself and we put on San Francisco's Child's Play charity event community fundraiser for Child's Play and last year we did it
[SPEAKER_03]: all soup to nuts within eight weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's also incorporated as our own nonprofit to be all nice and legal.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I guess I should talk about the band packages because that's really where we're leading into.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're all over the map, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why it's a three-hour show.
[SPEAKER_03]: We can never stay on one track.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take all the time you need.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's not... We don't do the just go up and play at a bar.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like if you go to a bar or anything...
[SPEAKER_03]: to play rock band.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's usually one screen and everyone is looking at the screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: What we do is have the performers turn around and face the audience and perform out to the audience.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's monitors on the stage floor, but they look like speaker monitors to the audience because it's next to the speaker monitors.
[SPEAKER_03]: And
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they have one song that they pick that no one else will play on their main stage.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, like, if I claim a song, and I say, like, Gaga is mine tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am Gaga.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then nobody else can pick that same Gaga song.
[SPEAKER_03]: First come, first serve.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, yes, once it's locked in, it's yours.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one else will play it on the main stage.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that really sucks at, like, karaoke sometimes, and you've got, like, four people in a row, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we belong together now
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, oh god, shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: They all get progressively worse.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are 2,000 songs in Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be hard to duplicate.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that even counting the network stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think their 2,000 count counts the network stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But still, that's a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the thing is that we don't know what's going to happen with these bands when they show up, especially last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: We didn't know if people were going to get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, we didn't know if people were just going to like, oh, I'm playing rock band or like, no, this is my rock concert.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there were people that got it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The one band that to me really got it was Ironhead.
[SPEAKER_03]: as in the Brutal Legend game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's pictures of that girl all over the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I should plug the website.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you go to umloud.org, now that's U-M-L-O-U-D, umloud.org, and you'll see the little flicker button there too, and that will give you all the pictures, and you'll see Ophelia there.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's pretty hard to miss because she...
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, spent a couple of hours before, you know, that day being dressed up in blue makeup, head to toe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, and I didn't know that they, I mean, I knew they were named Ironhead.
[SPEAKER_03]: I knew they were doing, uh, uh, um, I'm totally blanking on the song name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever song they did, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, Hellion Electric Eye.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when they hit the stage, you know, I saw her there dressed up and like, oh, that's one of my bands.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then when they performed it was absolutely amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They got it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this year we hope to have more that get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The ante is being upped now that people are seeing the pictures from last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, how can we just even take it a step further?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know there's going to be people that are like, we gotta outdo.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we want to facilitate that at Oomloud.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is why we're doing something additional to the event.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, the
[SPEAKER_03]: The Ultimate Band Package.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the band package that we did last year and then we're still doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those go on sale November 1st.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we decided we wanted to do one really special package that we're calling the Headliner Band.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this package is, there's only one of them because it's the Headliner.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's auctioned off and it's actually going on right now through eBay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they get a two song set.
[SPEAKER_03]: And as long as they don't dilly dally, they get first choice for the night to reserve those two songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're the headliners, so obviously they're on the flyers, they're on the posters, they're on the video that we make.
[SPEAKER_03]: We actually have Area 5, which is a video production company that will be making the commercials and, assuming schedules gel well, will be...
[SPEAKER_03]: Doing the video for us with the headliner band And you get your own place at DNA Lounge, which is the venue that we're in With drink and food service all provided to you So you can have people feed you grapes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes Alright, awesome I'm liking this so far And that's going on now, and that auction actually ends Thursday at 4pm-ish
[SPEAKER_03]: and we really hope we get a lot of people bidding on that thing because the donation all goes to Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to stress, this money is not going to SAG.
[SPEAKER_04]: This money is not going to DNA Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: This money is going to charity.
[SPEAKER_03]: All of it, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to Child's Play charity which provides video games, toys, and other financial support to children's hospitals around the globe.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it's kind of known as the Penny Arcade charity, but even Penny Arcade wants to stress that it's not like, oh, this is directly all Penny Arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: They want to stress that this is, yes, they house the offices and the staff,
[SPEAKER_03]: for it, but... They planted the seed, but it's grown into its own thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And especially with all of the community fundraisers that happen, like Goom Lab, but also Desert Bus for Hope and the Mario Marathon and all the others.
[SPEAKER_03]: These are people... Child's Play itself just is the direct servicer.
[SPEAKER_03]: They take the money and...
[SPEAKER_03]: Directly deal with the child's life services or equivalent of the children's hospitals in their network.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they get the toys there.
[SPEAKER_03]: They make what toys are needed and all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what's given is exactly what the hospital needs.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what the community fundraisers do is help in very creative, unique ways to raise money for this charity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every year for Child's Play has beaten its high score the previous year, including the past two years when that shouldn't have happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: Economic downturn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Child's Play was one of the very, very few charities that increased their giving.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's everything to do with these community fundraisers across the globe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you guys have a fundraising goal set for Umlaut this year?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or is that one of those, you know, I don't want to talk about it type of things?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it kind of is.
[SPEAKER_03]: We always want to do more.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we just focus that energy on making the best event possible.
[SPEAKER_03]: without making much cost of how to put on the event.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we have a lot of partners that help us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me ask this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I ask how much we raised last year?
[SPEAKER_03]: Last year, I wrote the check out and mailed it in for $7,000 to Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was eight weeks of putting everything together.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was kind of last moment.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this year, we hope to improve on the situation.
[SPEAKER_04]: and also a lot... Umlaut is... Just for the record, I would have never known that it only took eight weeks to do if you hadn't told me.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys did a really good job last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know how we did it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm not just saying that because you're a friend.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really was a smooth operation.
[SPEAKER_03]: We also have good partners.
[SPEAKER_03]: DNA Lounge...
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie Zawinski, the owner, and Barry and all of them over there are just absolutely wonderful to us.
[SPEAKER_03]: We definitely make sure they're in the loop.
[SPEAKER_03]: We definitely respect them as the venue.
[SPEAKER_03]: Harmonix is on this too, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_03]: I should say, we will have
[SPEAKER_03]: Every song playable in Rock Band 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: We actually have two stages.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I know I've been stressing the main stage and the performances there, which is the show in itself.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's a lot of other things that we have there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have in the lounge room, the second room, free play rock band show up.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have the donation bin out there to kind of guilt you, but it's free play, we don't care, just walk up, that's your traditional bar, rock band setting, and that's free play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last year was like the Beatles room, because that was the big game last year, and this year is just kind of whatever is clever?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we don't know what we're going to have special yet for...
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't know what we have special yet for this year, but last year we debuted before it came out the Rubber Soul album from Beatles Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is the best and it's sitting in my closet right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's somewhere in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, am I going to get Jamie to go with me this year?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe she can belt out a tune or two.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the beast, I will make you go on the main stage.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, let me ask this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry to take this wheel in another direction, but this question has been kind of like lingering on my mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I'm not a person that wants to get up in front of the crowd.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to help the charity, but singing in front of people is not my thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: What fun things can I expect to have at Umlaut?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, first of all, it's the performances.
[SPEAKER_03]: As I said, they are performances.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you search YouTube for Umlaut, you'll see what I mean.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, yes, the cell phone cameras, but you'll see the kind of performances.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that alone is worth the $10 door, but we don't stop there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We will have...
[SPEAKER_03]: What's been called the nerd yard sale.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we clean out the closets of various game studios and developers and publishers and news outlets and all that to clean out all the swag they've collected for the year and just put it out on the table.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you pay for the door, you pick one thing from the table.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you at least walk out with something.
[SPEAKER_03]: but in addition we're going to have a raffle and some pretty good prizes if I do say so myself we'll be announcing those a lot of right now our attention is all on the bands because we're trying to get this auction that you know finished on you know it ends Thursday and then the following Monday is when we get the ultimate band so we're kind of geared towards that and then we make the push of please show up
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I wanted you to get that out there, that there was that going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we do, believe it or not, there are a few friends of our show that work at various developers and things.
[SPEAKER_04]: And even though I know they don't email us or talk to us all the time because they don't want to talk about their projects, if you happen to work for a developer or some type of game studio and you have some extra stuff sitting in a storage room that maybe some fans might want, Umlaut would be a great charity to kind of give those to, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we actually are looking for sponsors, both financial as well as gifts and all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are our own nonprofit, so we are our own 501c3 in case people are a little weary of not giving directly to Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_03]: First of all, yes, it's going to Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: and donating to us directly is also legal in the state of California and the United States as a non-profit so please if you want to give us stuff or be a financial partner with us please please please go to umlaut.org there's that sponsor link there and we would love to talk to you
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm trying to think what else to kind of get out here before we move on with the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll ask you more maybe later on the show, Part B, kind of about what goes into the actual planning of the event.
[SPEAKER_04]: But as far as the event itself, anything else we need to know about what's coming up December 9th?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Thursday, December 9th.
[SPEAKER_03]: I stress the Thursday because last year was on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_03]: We leveled up to Thursday.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if we get more people, we may be able to level up for weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's really important for people to show up.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you're anywhere remotely near the Bay Area, please come on down.
[SPEAKER_03]: And tickets, if tickets are on sale right now, you can click on tickets on the website if you know you're not going to be in a band, but do want to show up.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's really helpful for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: I should also note that if you are in a band package, you're on the guest list, you get in, you're good.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you have any inkling of showing up, please show up.
[SPEAKER_04]: You will not regret it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for those of our listeners, because, you know, we are, believe it or not, an international show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have folks that listen to the show in Mexico, in Sweden, and all these places.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I just, as much as we really want them to come, they're probably not going to be able to swing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there are ways they can still participate if they're very far away, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have the donation button right on every single page at Inland.org.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is, if you, Child's Play uses PayPal for direct donations.
[SPEAKER_03]: We use Google Checkout.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I want to stress that we're not trying to take money or have this bidding war between who donates to Child's Play and who donates to Umlaut because it's going to the same place anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you feel more comfortable with Google Checkout, the donation button's there for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to go straight to Child's Play, awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's ChildsPlayCharity.org.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that just goes such a long way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I have a good feeling you're going to beat that $7,000 this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a really good feeling.
[SPEAKER_04]: I sure bloody hope so.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, best of luck, Seg.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, you're going to be sitting in on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: So feel free to chime in on anything gaming related.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'll have opinions.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I bet you will.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially there might be stories about a particular developer that might be of interest to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't put into words what a big freaking deal that is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to put out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because everybody but me thinks I can sing.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura is actually a pretty good singer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we extend that maybe through the next week for our podcasties who maybe aren't listening live tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: If we get 150 tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay, you're throwing down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: If we don't get 150 tonight, if we get 250 by next weekend... She's throwing all these random numbers out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, seriously, because there's a method to my madness.
[SPEAKER_03]: If we don't hit 150 tonight, and they have a way of saying donate in the name of... If they go through the Umlaut donation button, I can't, I have obviously no access to the Child's Play one, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, there should be some sort of note, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been a...
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll figure out the logistics.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you do donate, if there isn't some place to put it in, obviously, can people email... Let's have them email the receipt number.
[SPEAKER_05]: Email your receipt to mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com Perfect.
[SPEAKER_03]: That works.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you can't put it on there, make sure you say For Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you happen to buy a million copies of Eye of Judgment tonight, then... How about if we can raise... How much money can we raise to get Loki to go to the show in a Tingle outfit?
[SPEAKER_05]: How about if we can raise $1,000 by the night of the... No, I'm not going.
[SPEAKER_04]: We gotta watch it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, if we can raise $1,000, but then I'll dress as freaking Tingle shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: She said it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: If we can raise $1,000 by the night of Unwild, I will go as a Parapara girl.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blonde wig and all.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, regardless of how much... I'll wear some costume.
[SPEAKER_04]: Regardless of how much is raised tonight or until the night, you're at least going to go to the show, I hope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got school that night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cut class.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll think about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell the teacher it's for charity.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what kind of video games have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: What else did I play?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Bayonetta, because she is a sexy bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what else did I play?
[SPEAKER_05]: I played some Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_05]: I tried to play some Star Trek Online, but I'm pissed off at the Borg right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very, very pissed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, if somebody knows how to pass a stupid Borg mission, let me know, because I am pissed off at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just says, defeat Borg, steal data.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's 50 of them in there!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a viniculum!
[SPEAKER_04]: and he said, oh, that's my rogue.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, that's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it made me think of you because it's all Star Trek nerds.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why isn't he playing Star Trek Online?
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Must be on a Mac.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not that there's anything wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have several friends who actually can't play Star Trek Online anymore because they don't have it for Mac.
[SPEAKER_05]: hurry up, get out oh yeah, and I also played a lot of Plants vs. Zombies because I'm addicted, addicted, addicted to jackpot mode in Plants vs. Zombies and zombie bowling and I played a bunch of other stuff too I've given up on Narbacular Drop I'm done with it, given up oh, and I played some Portal
[SPEAKER_04]: Portal, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't really been playing that much this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, the only iOS game I think I've really been playing a lot of recently is... How about Unicorn Attack?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, actually not that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did play some last week, though, on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I've been actually addicted to Cartoon Wars 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a tower defense game with stick figures, except they have heavy artillery and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have everything from, like, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: Medieval weapons, swords, spears, bow and arrows and stuff to giant mechs and bazookas and all that fun stuff So it's pretty fun, I'm just grinding along right now And then I played a little bit of DJ Hero 2 and I'm totally digging the new songs in there
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the old 90s rap stuff that's in there is alright, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just think they need more variety in some of the songs because I can only hear so many remixes of California before I just get sick of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or OPP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's too bad you can't get the booty mashups or that kind of level because they have to actually get the licensing for the music.
[SPEAKER_05]: More gorillas!
[SPEAKER_03]: They have the stylo mix with itself, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: But I like kind of just playing it more relaxed instead of just trying to mash buttons like crazy in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And even on medium, it's mashing buttons like crazy with a lot of the songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like the Firestarter remix with itself, it was just insanely... It was more difficult than I anticipated for a song like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's why you chose poorly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't load the soundboard before.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, do they have where you can play as your home character?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know, Sony's really innovative with all their home features, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you really asking that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to play it with my me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me answer that with a sound.
[SPEAKER_04]: Delayed radio, boys and girls, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I used the toilet today during the other podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: During that other show?
[SPEAKER_05]: Which I have to say something about soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we'll get to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're hopefully going to have some DJ Hero music during the break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, smart me forgot to bring my stupid VGA cable for my 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I'm trying this really, you know, I guess MacGyver way of getting it to work by hooking up my video capture card through my PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't like the fact that it's on two different networks, so I have to plug it into the router.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the router's cords are so short that I can't pull it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't pull it out?
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't pull the router out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want us to start disconnecting random cords.
[SPEAKER_02]: As if the storms weren't causing enough problems with the internet out.
[SPEAKER_04]: The last thing we need is Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I can pull the gray cord.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cut the red wire.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're running long tonight anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: The gray one is actually the main.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll just take a look at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And free cookies!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, cookies!
[SPEAKER_04]: Make it all better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seg, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been so busy, but I know you were going to ask me this question, so I really made it a point to actually play games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been playing Costume Quest, which just came out on Xbox and PlayStation 3's downloadable service.
[SPEAKER_03]: and this is Double Fine's first let's not make a game once every five years game and it's really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: They set out to make a nice, I'll say light RPG game
[SPEAKER_03]: And the concept is, you either play, I'll say the two main characters are twins, a guy and a girl, and there's literally the point in the intro cutscene where you pick which gender you're going to be, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the one you didn't pick gets kidnapped by monsters who...
[SPEAKER_03]: are trying to collect candy, but the adults think that they're just big kids dressed up so they don't believe the kids that there are real monsters out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: This sounds like Saw for children.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make your choice.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you're wearing costumes because it's Halloween, but when you go into battle mode, the costumes that are like cardboard and tape, they turn into...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd totally be down for a G-rated Saw movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: What would be the point?
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've also been playing Game Dev Story on the iPhone because, you know, I can't get enough of game development.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's a nice little game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It feels like it was a cell phone game, like your, you know, before the iPhone, you know, the days of before, before, before.
[SPEAKER_03]: But...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a really nice little game that I can play a little bit and put it to a side.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I got something else as I pull out my Rock Band keyboard.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I've been playing Rock Band 3 over the weekend for research for Room Loud.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because there's no fun to be had.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: cannot stop the rock so are you going to have up to seven people because yeah awesome uh you know obviously if if it's a rock band one song well you know it's a rock band one song but um if the song supports it yeah though for harmonies though
[SPEAKER_03]: We have all three mics, and they're actually plugged into the sound system before they're plugged into the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we just have the mics on all the time, and people can just do harmonies or whatever anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: So even if you have a Rock Band 1 song, if you want to have backup singers anyway, no harm, no foul.
[SPEAKER_04]: No harm, no foul.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's not about the score anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: It gives the sound engineer actual control with the voice to make you sound good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I know you haven't been able to spend a lot of quality time with Rock Band 3, but what do you think of First Impressions?
[SPEAKER_03]: A worthy upgrade?
[SPEAKER_03]: It is definitely Harmonix finally putting into practice the years of research and all the things they've done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not that they haven't, but it's just they now, they got it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, like, they're able to put it together, and that's...
[SPEAKER_03]: and it really shows.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like how career mode is sort of always on in the sense that even when you're just doing quick play, it's still contributing to... That's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is career...
[SPEAKER_03]: activities, like very structured career activities of like, okay, here's two songs and a set of five go and an achievement is associated with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But just in general and in broad is just play.
[SPEAKER_03]: the game and it's just always it's ranking up it's more of raking up the personal your personal account so it's really stressing more of bringing your profile putting it on your USB stick when you go to your friends and then you're raking up when you're at your friends place oh cool and doing that profile well that sounds really interesting yeah they're doing that so you don't have to make all these separate bands anymore that's kind of cool that's very interesting so let me ask this real quick what was the first song you had to play
[SPEAKER_03]: What was the first song?
[SPEAKER_03]: I should have recorded that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I thought there might have been one.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I started doing Career Path and I'm totally blanking on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the first keyboard song, Rock Lobster.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, the correct answer should have been Bohemian Rhapsody.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, Sag, you lose.
[SPEAKER_04]: That button's never going to get old.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's my favorite button.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm saving that for when I play with friends of mine.
[SPEAKER_03]: That you need a band for because it was just me playing alone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fair counterpoint.
[SPEAKER_03]: All by myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw the trailer for Pro Mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was pretty crazy with the new guitars.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the pro guitars, damn.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the MIDI Stratocaster that they're working on?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, actually, the MIDI stuff, like the Rock Band 3 keyboard itself is MIDI out ready.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a MIDI keyboard.
[SPEAKER_03]: and on November 28th they'll have a breakout box for real professional MIDI instruments and just to plug it in directly into the console itself.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't tell you how excited I am for Pro Mode keyboards.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, and that's beauty because you can do Pro Mode with the Rock Band keyboard.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only thing that you out and out need new equipment for is guitar in regards to Pro Mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: Drums, you do need the add-on for the extra cymbals.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm talking about the new ones because the old ones kind of suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they're not doing a new, new rock band drum set.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they fixed the cymbals a bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the cymbals, the add-on pack is new, but there's no rock band 3 drum bass, you know, the bass of the drum kit.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no new rock band 3 one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just they're now packaging it with the new cymbals.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't have a promo for singing in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, well, what is promo mode?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you get harmonies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Promo mode's oom loud.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice, like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, and honestly, if you go into whatever the hard mode is, it's pretty hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm a Beatles rock band.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, these are songs that I grew up with that I wasn't hitting perfectly, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also do want John Drake will thank me for this Pro mode is great when you want to go to pro mode but don't feel that you're losing the essence of rock band if that just doesn't attract you
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, I've actually, uh, we're actually discussing taking, uh, guitar, pro guitar off the table for Umlaut just because it's too new, it's an instrument switch, and we want to focus on performance, you know, people performing and not just going on this technical prowess.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you, you would be fair to say, you know what, it's too much of a pain in the butt to swap out the guitars every time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now all you have to say is those guitars are too damn expensive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Done.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're all sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_04]: We sold the guitar and gave the money to kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anything else for your gaming week you want to share with us?
[SPEAKER_03]: A little bit of a Scott Pilgrim, trying to finish that out, but then Costume Quest came out, so there's that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Since I'm going to get crap from Bobby Blackoff if I don't try to get you for info on this at some point, because since you haven't brought it up your day job, you do work for a certain developer out there that makes a lot of amazing adventure games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is Back to the Future as awesome as it sounds?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because if you go to TelltaleGames.com and go to the blog tab, it's on game trailers.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Telltale just posted a quick little interview with the voice of Marty McFly.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is in Michael J. Fox, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: He did give likeness rights and all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to...
[SPEAKER_02]: He sounds very close to Michael J. Fox.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and let's not forget Michael J. Fox is about twice as old as he was when the movie first came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I still have to say, he didn't give his likeness rights for the pinball table, so this is kind of big.
[SPEAKER_03]: AJ LaRosso, I'm probably mispronouncing his last name and I apologize, but all I'm just going to say, go to the video and you'll hear how good it sounds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, did you get Biff?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, AJ is doing a great job with sticking on target.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do also have Christopher Lloyd as doc.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's voicing and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to seriously get him to say every word in the dictionary because that guy is not getting it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get him while you can.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, get the fiend on the table on him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'm not going to pry too much on the day job because I respect that you're a friend and we don't want to see you get fired for saying too much on the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, talk about my game like Puzzle Agent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about what's out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Puzzle Agent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, Puzzle Agent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is actually...
[SPEAKER_03]: Artstyle of Graham Annabelle who does the dank or dunk, depending on what mood he's in, comics on the TelltaleGames.com website and also has a lot of video shorts and we made a game with really his artstyle but new characters of Nelson Tethers, Puzzle Agent the single agent of the FBI Department of Puzzle Research They have that?
Yeah
[SPEAKER_03]: They do now!
[SPEAKER_03]: but uh no it's it's a it's it's a puzzle game with a plot and we try to do made the make the puzzles at least the the critical path ones uh relevant to the plot enough uh you know obviously there's a suspension of disbelief but try to not do something like I I can tell you this key important thing you need to know about the plot but first here's a puzzle of matchsticks uh but um
[SPEAKER_03]: We're having cat drama
[SPEAKER_03]: But no, it's a nice little fun game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's out on platforms.
[SPEAKER_03]: iPhone and PC, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: iPhone, PC, and Mac.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Mac, yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can't forget them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I've plugged enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's no problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: We appreciate you being here.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can plug whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to  I don't even know what you're working on now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You probably couldn't talk about it anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: But best of luck with all the upcoming projects over there at Telltale and keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and just saying, there really, really should be an Elvira adventure game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we need Elvira.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you haven't heard last week's show, we're just thinking, you know, speaking of celebrities you want to get before they're too old, Elvira really needs a good game treatment.
[SPEAKER_04]: So just something to think about for next Halloween, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just throwing that out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was trying to think what that was.
[SPEAKER_02]: I knew there was a game we were trying to pitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Was it Golden Girls?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that too, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be a little hard to do now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not going to really be able to get Bea Arthur, but you might be able to get the drag queens that play the Golden Girls in San Francisco around the Thanksgiving season.
[SPEAKER_04]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: My gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was all excited this week because Alan actually bought me a game, and you'll appreciate this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alan actually bought me a copy of Poker Night.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, bless his heart.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, he bought me a copy of Poker Night because Steam was having an awesome little pre-order thing on it, and he's like, Oh, Rob, I bought you a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's play the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then it's like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the game's not out yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're selling it on Steam.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'll be ready to go day one.
[SPEAKER_04]: So thanks for that, Seg.
[SPEAKER_04]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to rash on that at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, obviously, it's going to be cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I'll plug Poker Night, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not looking for anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: My expectations going into this game are not like, my world is going to be rocked.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just going to be like... It's going to be a cute poker game with funny characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right?
[SPEAKER_03]: We've been telling people... Yes, it's Texas Hold'em Poker with Tycho, the Heavy from TF2, Max of Salmon Max, and Strong Bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: And...
[SPEAKER_03]: it has more dialogue than any single episode of a Telltale game so it's not going to be five lines repeated for every single play all the time there's going to be some variety to it and it's five bucks I was selling those hotcakes at PAX actually because we also threw in a poster with it I've tried for three days to buy it
[SPEAKER_03]: How does that work?
[SPEAKER_05]: My PayPal hasn't ever gone through.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now, whose fault is that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not mine.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Valve's problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Steam or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Poker Night is coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: They haven't even told me.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's really cool to know there's all that dialogue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, my expectations going in, I was thinking this is going to be like an Xbox Live Arcade style poker game with characters I recognize.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope there's a lot of trash talking.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds like it could be a part of it with all that dialogue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Things are said.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ha ha!
[SPEAKER_04]: Words come out of mouths.
[SPEAKER_04]: There may or may not be playing cards in the game in some shape or fashion in Poker Night.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All that stuff aside.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I have that to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will say a game I did buy on Steam that is out and has been out for a month that I played this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: The listeners should be very proud of me because I don't think WoW was the game I played the most this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shock and awe.
[SPEAKER_04]: But World of Warcraft was probably actually down there on the ladder this week because...
[SPEAKER_04]: I finally got Civilization V on Steam and I've been playing the heck out of Civilization V because it's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't decided if I like it more than 4 yet because I haven't truly got to the end of a game yet because it is so long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's way better than 2 or 3 in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Way, way better than 3, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Hex tile thing is actually one of the things I noticed the least.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a very fluid transition for the series and a very kind of like logical next step.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really like a lot of the subtle changes they made.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the fact you can't stack armies on top of each other and just build like super army.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the fact that only one unit can defend a city, so you can't have these uber cities.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes you have to think a different way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that they have talent trees that they call social policies.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of a neat addition.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's all these cool little things they've added.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very customizable games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of difficulty levels, lots of sizes.
[SPEAKER_04]: The city states thing is really neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't think I would like it at first.
[SPEAKER_04]: A city state is basically a whole new civilization that is only ever one city.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't aspire to grow.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't aspire to do anything but exist in their little city state.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Not only did I get the French to surrender, but the French gave me Pittsburgh Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: How they had that, or no, sorry, Philadelphia How they had Philadelphia, I don't know, but I got it now All of those sandwiches are so French Maybe the bread It's now a Greek city in my game, because of course I'm playing as Alexander the Great
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Philadelphism is a big word Okay, I'm just saying you said the French gave it to you when you were in Greece
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of interesting how that worked out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I totally forgot what I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, the thing about Civ is you can always save, but it's always that one more turn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, yes, oh god, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what makes it fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't go to bed until 1am the other night because of one more turn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just one more turn.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Paris will be mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: So just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spazinator said a junk ferret running around Paris will get France to surrender.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, I do want to also acknowledge our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been such a bad boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't acknowledged chat all night long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.OrangeLawnTrader.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please join.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've actually been a little bit quiet tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat room.
[SPEAKER_01]: Memorized by my voice.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob needs a spanking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they're... Yes, maybe they just are...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, of course, sadly, we don't have a whole lot of people from the Bay Area, so I think we've got a lot of people that are kind of like, oh, sounds cool, but, you know, plane tickets cost a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we do have, I know, a lot of podcastees in the Bay, so hopefully we'll see a lot of them at the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know I'm going to go come hell or high water, so I'll be there for sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, also, actually, you know, for the... I don't know about...
[SPEAKER_03]: Other local physical events happening at 4 Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's also Desert Bus for Hope, the Loading Ready Run guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're starting...
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to say them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, no, I got it on the calendar.
[SPEAKER_03]: But these are the folks that play Desert Bus as a marathon run for Child's Play Charity.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they start November 19th, unless things changed around a bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they'll do the live stream and all that on the 19th.
[SPEAKER_03]: which is definitely interesting to watch because yes they're playing Desert Bus but they're also a comedy troupe so they really make it a telethon show with it awesome I've tuned into a little bit of it before it's funny, it's good times what a crap game to be playing
[SPEAKER_04]: What a crap game to be playing for so long.
[SPEAKER_04]: But hey, make some money.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, Umlaut will be streamed live.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forgot about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So starting at 7pm California time, go to timeanddate.com to figure out what that means for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: The event will be streamed live, so you can actually watch the performances.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Umlaut website will change over to that mode when it's actually happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: And last year, weren't you the most streamed event in the lounge's history?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, no, we killed their internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: We didn't kill it, but we were the one event that used the internet the most.
[SPEAKER_03]: This being from a venue that is currently owned by one of the co-founders of Netscape.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're very proud of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They actually increased wireless capacity after that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to say it's because of us, but feather in our cap.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congratulations on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more game that I played this week I want to talk about is DJ Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though Loki kind of already talked about that a little bit, I just want to give my spin on it, pun intended.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't going to buy the game originally because I was like, oh, yeah, $60.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, boy!
[SPEAKER_04]: Over and over again with the button.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the way they're doing the freestyling now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so much better.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the freestyle crossfades are great.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the scratching zones are really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So many more ways to freestyle and really ruin such great songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do appreciate all that they've thrown in the interface.
[SPEAKER_04]: The head-to-head modes are more interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the interface as a whole.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though the black and white look is a little bit too plain, I just kind of like the construction of the game a lot more than I did the first mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's a worthy upgrade in the interface and what it brings to the table.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rihanna's Rude Boy Rihanna's Rude Boy
[SPEAKER_02]: There was some weird ones that I didn't recognize the song.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was one with a Tiesto song that was like an R&B song or something mixed with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was surprisingly good, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will hopefully play those during the break.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm attempting... This is like disarming a bomb over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it doesn't work out, it doesn't work out.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got the stuff to make it work.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't understand, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not going to stop and ask for directions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: One more bit of housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Contest!
[SPEAKER_04]: I was threatened with domestic repercussions by my significant other if I played any song that had Soulja Boy in it one more time.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura has a contest
[SPEAKER_05]: This is our contest, and the prize is going to be a code for Xbox Live to play Castlevania Symphony of the Night, which is a fun game, one of my favorites.
[SPEAKER_05]: The question is really easy, and we are going to be taking an emailer at a random number, which we will decide by literally rolling a die.
[SPEAKER_05]: on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is in relation to Comic Insanity, which is the other podcast that I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we broadcast every... We're actually up on InfamousNFAMOUS.net on Mondays is when the new podcast is up.
[SPEAKER_05]: The question you have to answer is what is the name of he who shall not be named on Comic Insanity?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll give you a clue.
[SPEAKER_05]: We hate him.
[SPEAKER_03]: That so narrows it down.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: That could be anybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can send your emails to... Go ahead and... I guess go ahead and send it to the mailbag here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll check it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at orangezonesradio.com I will sift through it and we will roll a number at random and I'll pick a name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now the other contest.
[SPEAKER_04]: More!
[SPEAKER_05]: Which isn't us, but a lot of people would be interested in this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also at Infamous.net, there is a contest to win a bunch of Blizzard goodies from BlizzCon.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you missed it, there's stuff for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are free pets, um, cataclysm, uh, stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's also a, uh,
[SPEAKER_05]: A demo of StarCraft 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a few StarCraft 2 lithos and some goodies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of goodies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do I have to do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just send in a name?
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to go to Infamous.net and click on the contest link.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's, again, N-F-A-M-O-U-S dot net.
[SPEAKER_05]: And click on the Blizzard contest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Follow the directions.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just basically have to fill out your information and let them know what you're looking most forward to for Cataclysm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which, you know what my response was?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Except maybe Plants vs. Zombies, but I don't play World of Warcraft, so... You've been tempted to go back a couple times, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have been.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't make me go find the timescales.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because Tiara told me that leveling is faster now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is.
[SPEAKER_04]: And in Cataclysm it's going to be even better.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hated leveling in freaking World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just messing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Star Trek Online is much more fun because I can kill Borg and play with Klingons.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's that working out for you?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, this might be a new record, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're an hour into the show and we have yet to touch gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's alright, so we're going to kind of quickly move through some gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_04]: Some gaming news, if you can get away from the MacGyver stuff for a moment.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got the work, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm awesome like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox.com has gotten a makeover to kind of update everything with the new dashboard updates coming soon and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've added avatar editors on the actual website, so now you don't have to wait until you get to your console to make your avatar look neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, apparently, they're going to add some multiplayer web games, which...
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if it's going to be some more stuff that you can...
[SPEAKER_02]: If it's going to tie in with different games, like how they did with Crackdown and Facebook games and stuff, perhaps.
[SPEAKER_02]: But right now they're saying that they're going to be able to play web games with your Xbox Live friends on the web or on Windows Phone 7.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm sure those will be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is all, of course, this already came out this week, so go check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are any of those free games available yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: The web stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: They were just teasing them.
[SPEAKER_02]: They haven't really made them available yet, but the Avatar editor's there, so you can check that out at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll be coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm glad that they actually updated the website because there's a lot of stuff that's broken on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, links to games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're like, okay, I want to look up stuff about Crackdown 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, that page doesn't exist.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, when was the last time they changed the look of the page?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was even before the new Xbox experience.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was before the Xbox 360 launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I want to say they did change it with the 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it seems that they're doing this... This was more in line with the Windows phone and all that, and they're trying to integrate... Yeah, they're really pushing this Windows phone.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're really pushing the phone because, you know, let's face it, they're a competitor.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: well and let's also not forget that there's some stories this week about how AT&T is really starting to get behind these phones because the rumors are starting to snowball a little more that they are going Verizon with the iPhone in 2011 and so AT&T is actually going to start pushing a lot more of the Windows phone I mean not to say they're not going to sell the iPhone anymore but they're going to also be pushing the Windows phones diversify the portfolio exactly exactly
[SPEAKER_04]: So it'll be interesting to see if there's any truth to these so-called rumors.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will say about this with the Xbox.com site that I wish Sony would do is when you hear about a game that's available as a downloadable service...
[SPEAKER_03]: At least with Xbox, if you're at work and you hear about it, you can buy it on the site and you don't have to be at your Xbox and you can make that purchase or say, okay, I want the demo.
[SPEAKER_03]: So then when you get back to your Xbox, it'll be downloaded waiting for you and remind you that you wanted to look at the thing and play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's also just a lot more content on the Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's always at least a couple games coming out each week versus Sony.
[SPEAKER_02]: There may be a game coming out that week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not consistent.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless you count their old PlayStation 1 classics that they're putting out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really, for the both of them, Xbox needs to make their indie game service or whatever community games they're calling it now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Showcased
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, exactly, because with the App Store, it's easy to spend money like crazy on that thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if they made it more like that and had like, okay, hey, look, this feature now has weather updates, and this app does this and this, I think that would be beneficial for them, especially since they don't have a web browser.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, I will say, though, one thing about the website, one thing I tried to look up was the Game Room website.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to do a search for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something not pretty is going on with Game Room, I'm sorry to say, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just to kind of follow up a little bit from last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Diablo 3 Diablo 3 Diablo 3
[SPEAKER_04]: Diablo 3's latest class, the Demon Hunter, is revealed.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that is supposedly the last class that's going to be in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, PvP battle arenas.
[SPEAKER_04]: That does sound kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is also coming to Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are some of the big announcements.
[SPEAKER_04]: One thing that was missing, though, was when.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not even a hint of a quarter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cataclysm is coming out on December 7th
[SPEAKER_04]: Addicts!
[SPEAKER_04]: I love them, but they're addicts and suckers
[SPEAKER_04]: StarCraft 2 is going to be getting some scenarios for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of them is a Defense of the Ancients scenario.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Bejeweled and Left 4 Dead, some other interesting little versions of those in StarCraft 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I find the Defense of the Ancients one the most interesting because Valve, of course, has their Defense of the Ancients game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They actually got the people who originally did the mod now work at Valve, but yet Blizzard is now going to make their own...
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're going to have StarCraft or what they're calling Blizzard Defense of the Ancients is going to be coming to StarCraft 2 soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, no date there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yep, folks went to BlizzCon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some guy broke his leg while dancing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tenacious D played.
[SPEAKER_04]: People spent $150.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hope you guys found it worth it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really don't have any interest.
[SPEAKER_04]: As much as I'm an addict and war program, I have no interest in BlizzCon.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also $150.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that, Seg?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ultimate Band Package for Oomloud on sale November 1st.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I tell you, that's probably more exciting than... That's probably a better deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's what I'm... Honestly, you guys... Maybe you can't say this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you guys doing the swag bag again for the Ultimate Bands this year?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, we don't know what's going to be in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we're going to do a bag.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're probably going to get better shit in those bags than you do in the BlizzCon bags.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the BlizzCon bags... I can say that, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll get better stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did they even get a pet this year in the BlizzCon?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they got another... It was another Murloc, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a Deathwing Murloc, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's so many.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was that correct?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's part of the giveaway.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's so many.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then go win one off Infamous Gamers and don't spend $150 to get a swag bag.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually looked at the live blog for it and I was like, so they announced a new class for Diablo and that was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: That...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: By simple math, we have deduced that it is December 7th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: So anyhow, yeah, that's what went on at BlizzCon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, you had angry gamers asking questions and raging in the microphone at BlizzDevelopers because everybody's so mature.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, so that's all the stuff you missed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tried to get people on Twitter to, if they were, I'm like, if you're gonna rage question, then at least rage question about real ID.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do something that actually affects your real life instead of like, stop nerfing my paladin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will say, if I may, since I am a Warcraft player and I'm teasing myself here a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: You may.
[SPEAKER_04]: That new patch that Blizzard did, although I really like some of the features and some of the changes they did, boy, did they screw some things up.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have this bug in there right now where an icon turning into a certain shape will crash the entire game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called the Cogwheel bug.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what's great about it is that for the Halloween event, in order to summon the Halloween boss...
[SPEAKER_04]: You gotta click the cogwheel on the headless horseman thing, the pumpkin So pretty much everybody crashes out They've been able to fix it with a third party fix that's available on Curse But yeah, Blizzard's too busy throwing their party to really be on top of that right now Maybe I won't go back and play it
[SPEAKER_04]: This new patch needed a little more testing, but Blizzard really wanted that game out this year, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least it's not as much of a hot mess as another certain MMO that came out and they had to extend the trial period of the game because it was so terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyhow, I'm not going to go there again for another week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, if you don't understand, Rob, it still is the trial part of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will be the trial part of the game for the next few years.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll stick with Final Fantasy XI
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XIV, that's right, that's the game that sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XIV is fucking terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't hold it in anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: It blows.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a brand new game.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have the same races, but we named them something more ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it sucks worse.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although I do remember one MMO that I played that was in beta for like seven years.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ragnarok?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I played through the whole thing in several different languages.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they better not hear you talking smack on our show or we ban you!
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_04]: Permanently.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, this must be... My account can't be banned on Ragnarok, even though I don't play anymore on the IRO server.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who'd you blow?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I was a beta tester.
[SPEAKER_05]: All the beta accounts that played for the PvP testing got to keep their accounts.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's good to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: It must be a key to my personality, but the only MMO I've actually played with some length was Myst Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mist Online was kind of creepy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mist Online was a great idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, man, Zombie Game refused to die.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that game got relaunched about four times.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was great, it just needed...
[SPEAKER_03]: There were just things that hung it up on interface-wise.
[SPEAKER_03]: And narrative-based MMO, that's a huge beast to fill.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, going to our chatroom at chat.orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw says, talking about BlizzCon, one fan complained about the WoW characters looking like they came from Victoria's Secrets.
[SPEAKER_04]: The developer replied, what magazine do you want them to look like?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Penthouse Jeremy Todd 1 in our chat says all the WoW players moved on to a better game Hello Kitty Island Adventures you know what's funny is that we were at Target the other day and there was Final Fantasy 14 sitting on the shelf and Alan's like you should buy that he's like hey you should buy that you should buy that I'm like I will buy this before I buy that and I pointed at Hello Kitty online you know that Hello Kitty is getting her first Wii game coming in November no one cur alright what
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember me picking up a certain Bats Maru Hello Kitty game and Rob going, Oh girl, I want to play that!
[SPEAKER_05]: And me lending it to him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Says the person that has the Hello Kitty toaster.
[SPEAKER_04]: I deny these allegations, all of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a Hello Kitty TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, it was a Disney Princess TV for wine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's much better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gave it to a seven-year-old girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the Hello Kitty coffee maker is no more.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got a real coffee maker.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_05]: If you really want to be cool, you'll just get a French press.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob Blinks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on with more gaming news, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will see them in early 2011.
[SPEAKER_05]: And... The good thing about Space Channel 5 Part 2 is that we never got it in North America.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this means we get to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, there's really a whole bunch of Japanese in it to change.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean... Didn't we get... We got it on PlayStation 2 version, didn't we?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got the Japanese one.
[SPEAKER_05]: With that freaking hard one where it does all the stuff and you have to do it backwards.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, but it's a Mizuguchi game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Space Channel 5, really, really like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I love Space Channel 5 Part 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mainly because of the thriller dance.
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole section where they do just Michael Jackson dances.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Pudding is especially fierce in Part 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm Pudding!
[SPEAKER_04]: She's my favorite, just for the record.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pudding is my favorite character.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Shermie has left the studio.
[SPEAKER_05]: You notice she did not step on your laptop.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's good that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good kitty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, crushed his laptop.
[SPEAKER_05]: She is not that huge, and she knows better than to step on laptops because we got on door.
[SPEAKER_04]: She'll get a kitty spanking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: She likes it.
[SPEAKER_04]: More gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shermie does like spankings, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't need to know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Family show!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck family shows!
[SPEAKER_05]: If you pet her on her lower back, she'll stick her butt up in the air and start purring.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't need to know what your cat's into.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does your cat want a leather harness for Christmas?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, she's not into that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, your Hanukkah?
[SPEAKER_05]: My cat's not Jewish.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's agnostic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, Ubisoft is recalling Sean White's skateboarding on the PlayStation 3, which means I'm going to have a lot of fucking work to do tomorrow because they've already shipped them all to us so that we got them to our customers, so we're going to have to do a bunch of fucking returns on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But apparently, and this was coming from some big-name retailers, they're saying that there's issues with...
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for all the work, you fucking dumbasses.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we printed it wrong!
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now, Loki, mistakes happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was there some Arab song in this that someone got offended about, you know, playing the beta or something, like LittleBigPlanet?
[SPEAKER_02]: I did get one of those copies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really, it was stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I liked it better with the lyrics in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Sean White skateboarding isn't intentionally supposed to be that bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is this a big title?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: How many people buy this game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Most people are like, Sean White?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who the fuck's he?
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't that the snowboarder?
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that the guy that looks like Carrot Top?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it is the guy that looks like Carrot Top.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know who it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: He actually skateboards, but Tony Hawk has a game coming out, Tony Hawk Shred, and as far as I'm aware, Tony Hawk does not fucking snowboard.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's a poser.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, that game is terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not the Sean White game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sean White game's decent, but Tony Hawk's terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if Shaquille O'Neal can do everything, like, you know, he had that whole TV show about Shaquille O'Neal does this and that, then, you know, why can't Tony Hawk decide to... And they're doing comic-style art of him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shaquille O'Neal?
[SPEAKER_05]: And, because, with the new Celtics lineup.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can listen to Infamous.net's Comic Insanity for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plug, plug.
[SPEAKER_04]: Salacious Pop is bringing us some lols in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Has anyone actually seen Sean White?
[SPEAKER_04]: What he needs is a line of shampoo and hair care, not video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Salacious Pop mentioning Shermie was walking out and Salacious Pop was suggesting talk about the Sony move so she'll poop in the hall.
[SPEAKER_05]: She does that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every time we bring it up, she goes out in the hall and takes a big crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got something better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I noticed when I was in the Sony Marketplace this weekend that there is a preview download for... Is Shermie listening?
[SPEAKER_04]: Shermie, The Tester Season 2 has a preview trailer available.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do not get my cat to take a crap because guess who has to clean that shit up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Me!
[SPEAKER_05]: Literally.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Tester Season 2, Shermie.
[SPEAKER_05]: And again, disclaimer, my cat is old and fat and can't get to the bathroom easily.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's fat and sassy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about something else that's going to be very sassy, at least for fans of these series.
[SPEAKER_05]: As long as it doesn't involve cat shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it doesn't involve that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Professor Layton and Phoenix Wright are going to be colliding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Worlds are colliding in a new 3DS adventure.
[SPEAKER_04]: What I love about this is that these are like two very culty kind of games on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like either you play them and you love them or you're like, what is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So somehow, and of course I'm looking at this going...
[SPEAKER_04]: How does this even work?
[SPEAKER_04]: How do these two games even... Alright, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you watch the trailer?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no, the Japanese trailer is out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, there's actually a good high-res one out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, is there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I sat and watched the whole thing going, I can only understand half of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, and it's going to be on the 3DS, and that's kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the noise you hear in the background, by the way, is a little bit of the trailer, but that's like
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they biting a little bit from the other puzzle game?
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole FBI investigation.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is starting to sound a little familiar.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might want to look into exploring a lawsuit on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just starting crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm excited for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the kind of thing of like, this can go horribly, horribly wrong, but there's a chance that it can go horribly, horribly right.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it'll be in 3D!
[SPEAKER_03]: But seriously though, I wait in eager anticipation to what this turns out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't read up on it or anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think they even publish much to anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's probably in Japanese and I'm a gaijin.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the right word, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if you were in Japan, then yeah, you'd be gaijin.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: I love this way it's described here by Level 5 President Akihiro Hino.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quote, two TV shows getting together and making a movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's like Facts of Life meets Golden Girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's gotta be tons of cinematics from what they show.
[SPEAKER_05]: The trailer was long.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, really long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I bet that's gonna be pretty awesome, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what do you have for us before we get into release dates?
[SPEAKER_05]: Something that's even better than Sonic 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know how we feel about Sonic 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, aw.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are a group of Sonic fans, actually two people that brought out something called Sonic Fan Remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is actually absolutely gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played it before the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: And didn't you think it was...
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very pretty.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got different mechanics from different Sonic games thrown in, except for the dash thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really think that... Now, one thing that I did notice when reading up on this is that they actually brought in tons of elements from Sonic CD, which that's really how it felt to me, playing like it is playing Sonic CD.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, uh, they're doing so much of a better job than what Sega's doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Sega should just be like, hey, um, we like you.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the people that are doing it is Pelican13 and Mercury.
[SPEAKER_05]: The demo is out to download.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, you can go to, uh, Sonic Retro and find it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They also do have a direct, uh, let me get the link for it real quick, because there actually is a direct, uh,
[SPEAKER_04]: SONICFANREMIX.COM SONICFANREMIX.COM
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they'll file a lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, Rob, bring up the trailer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Play some of the music because the music is gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me bring that up here from the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: yeah my only you know I didn't I was just looking over your shoulder for it but definitely the backgrounds are sort of like too busy and it kind of illustrates how they're really going to 11 with the art like hey look what we're doing and gets a little too just on the edge of showboating with it yeah but not stupid it's noticeable but it's not stupid it's not completely deprimental to the game itself
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it'd be something to get used to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very pretty looking.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love some of the interactive backgrounds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though, yeah, the multi-layered background thing can get a little busy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it kind of detracts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really love some of what they did with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looks hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like it when it gets into my favorite part of this music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kudos.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, which was next.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that little shark thing that jumps out as he's running over the bridge.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like a big killer whale, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Little touches like that are awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it even knocks the blocks or all that same checkerboard pattern all around it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd have to say that this is an epic job and I hope it doesn't get shut down the way that the Chrono Trigger thing was because that was also awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Burr apparently has been following this pretty closely.
[SPEAKER_04]: He has a follow-up comment here in our chat room at chat.orange.radio.com The people on the forum about it say Sega won't do anything about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not sure why they're so confident.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, definitely worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grab it now until it becomes a problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my suggestion.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's go get some release dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Loki, I know there's a lot this week, but I just want to point out we're already at an hour and a half for Part A. In other words, if we cut out the Hello Kitty games, I think we'll be okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't worry, I won't read any Hello Kitty games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need more Hello Kitty!
[SPEAKER_02]: Sean White skateboarding actually came out today on Xbox 360 and we were disavowing any knowledge of the PS3 version because that's it's not yet ready the re-release of Dragon Age Origins the Ultimate Edition it's packed with all the download content including the expansion Awakenings and you can get that this week Family Party 90 Great Games Party Pack that is also a compilation of the last three Family Party games I'm sure 90 awesome games
[SPEAKER_02]: Art Academy
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nerf N-Strike.
[SPEAKER_02]: Man, it's just fucking bundles of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: The N-Strike Double Blast Bundle.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's with a gun in the two last Nerf N-Strike games.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cabela's Dangerous Hunt 11 with the wireless shotgun.
[SPEAKER_02]: The top shotgun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's on Xbox 360 and the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Wii has a gun shell that goes with it, but
[SPEAKER_02]: Same type of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also the game is available by itself on those three platforms as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: SBKX on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Smackdown vs. Raw 2011 on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii, DS, and PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Star Wars The Force Unleashed 2 on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii, DS, PSP, and PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pets Cats Playground on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dora the Explorer, Dora's Cooking Club, that's on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sims 3 Late Night Expansion Pack, now you can have your own emo vampires in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's on PC only.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do they sparkle?
[SPEAKER_02]: CSI Fail Conspiracy on PS3 and Xbox 360 I'm hurt
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we should try harder.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever played one?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't watch CSI.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, if it was Law and Order, it was Law and Order.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't worry, I got your back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tony Hawk Shred coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and we just don't buy it, seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one of those games that requires a stupid skateboard to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what that really should be?
[SPEAKER_02]: Skateboarding outside.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if you have to buy a skateboard to play a game, you should just skateboard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Halo... That'd be funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was Halo.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hasbro Family Game Night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Halo Family Game Night 3!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a Spartan good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Frag your friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: Frag Grandma.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Hasbro Family Game Night 3 coming out on the Wii, PlayStation 3, Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some more games with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, and I doubt that this is coming out on this date because why would you release this a good week early, but who knows.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fighters Uncaged, I believe that's supposed to be coming out in a couple weeks, but that's the fighting game for the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's of course on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Imagine Fashion Stylist, another game that you're probably not interested in, that's on DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Sims 3 that's coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and Wii this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: DS and PSP as well, I believe.
[SPEAKER_02]: DECA Sports 3 on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: and one of my favorite games, Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're releasing a complete edition with both Grand Theft Auto 4 and Episodes of Liberty City, all for $39.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: The fights lights out on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is the Move fighting game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's coming out on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rock Band 3 on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii, and DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I've heard of that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Monopoly Streets on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii on I believe DS and PSP, Pet's Nursery 2 on DS, and Lego Universe on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: That should be pretty big.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's the MMO, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that is the awesome MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't even heard a darn thing about that game, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of curious now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mama is doing everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now she's crafting.
[SPEAKER_03]: What kind of crafting?
[SPEAKER_03]: TF2 crafting?
[SPEAKER_02]: Arts and crafting.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is on Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: But don't worry, Wii fans.
[SPEAKER_02]: There will be babysitting in your future.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remington Super Slam Hunting North America on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: ZHP Unlosing Ranger vs. Dark Death Evilman.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's on PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has an awesome title.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blood Drive on Xbox 360 and Playstation 3 that's going to be kind of like a Twisted Metal type of game so definitely check that out I think it could be a sleeper hit Imagine Resort Owner, don't even bother Mercury Limited Edition why I keep re-releasing these games no one bought them in the first place that's on PSP and Yu-Gi-Oh 50's Tag Force 5 on PSP Fable 3 on Xbox 360 just a little game there
[SPEAKER_02]: What's with these tie-ins?
[SPEAKER_02]: Mega Bloks, Diego's Build and Rescue?
[SPEAKER_02]: What, you couldn't spring for the license for Legos?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and Power Geek's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not to be outdone by Rock Band, but it will be outdone by Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: That poor game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it is too damn expensive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Disney Channel All Stars Party on the Wii Intellivision Lives on the Nintendo DS and Chevrolet Camaro on the Wii It's lived like every year for the past 10 years in one way or another Really guys?
[SPEAKER_03]: Still alive?
[SPEAKER_04]: I like Intellivision at all, but it might be time for it to die.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I actually want to read some of the comments in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.OrganizationRadio.com Salacious Pop is giving us some dialogue that could be used in the Halo Family Party trailer, actually, here at Chat.OrganizationRadio.com Quote,
[SPEAKER_04]: How the hell does Grandma keep getting headshots?
[SPEAKER_04]: She has Parkinson's.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mom, Granddad teabagged me and called me that mean word for gays and now everyone on my headset is griefing me and laughing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming to a store near you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo Family Party.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm surprised they haven't gone there yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: They might.
[SPEAKER_04]: We like money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cha-ching.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to the Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Xbox 360, Fable 3 gets its Japanese release on the 28th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Radurgy Noah Massive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Radurgy Noah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know what this game is.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, yes I have.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a shooter game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rattergy is a shmup.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard of this before.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a version of it on DS too, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, Rattergy is finally coming out on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: So check that out on the 28th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, World Soccer Winning 11 2011 is coming out this week on the Xbox 360 as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to the PlayStation 3 and looking at some of the releases there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Usually they pretty much get ports of the same releases on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: which yes, World Soccer Winning 11 2011 Rubber Baby Buggy Bumper Edition is coming out this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also there is a slim console bundle in 160 and 320 gig models that contain the World Soccer Winning 11 2011 game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rubber Baby Buggy Bumper Edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: D.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: is out this week
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Sola Torobo, Sode Karakoda E is coming out this week on the DSi.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a regular and a collector's edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is like a DSi enhanced version.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's from the creators of the .hack series.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's an action, sci-fi, fantasy game.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a world ruled by dog people and cat people.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you play a hunter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you hunt the dog and cat people, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take this, dog people!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Alpo.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's super effective.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Sony PSP, God Eater Burst comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: That doesn't sound sacrilegious at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Phantom Brave Portable comes out on the PSP this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've eaten so much God, I'm just gonna burst now. ...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: In the UK, on the 26th, we have BlazBlueContinuumShift, DeathSpank, which is the best name ever, Splatterhouse, and the Sims... Are they just getting the... Oh, no, this is the new Sims 3 expansion.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the 27th is BloodyGoodTime, which I think is a fantastic name, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: The 28th is SuperScribblenauts, Fable 3, FIFA Manager 11, Football Manager 2011, which is real football and not what we call football over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: My Sim Sky Heroes, Rock Band 3, Sean White Skateboarding, Star Wars The Force Unleashed 2, The Lord of the Rings Erogrance Quest, Tony Hawk Shred, TV Superstars, We Sing, Robbie Williams, WWE Smackdown vs. Raw 2011, and on the 30th we have Sims 3 Late Night.
[SPEAKER_05]: And since we're not having a show next week, I'll go ahead and say on the 31st is Saw 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like Robbie Williams.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I know he's not a big deal here in the US, but he's pretty big everywhere else.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can see why he's getting his own karaoke game.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on to some more news.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the classic game of the week is just a few steps away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, so this is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, and I actually saw this on the news, which is kind of weird, but there was a lot of, or it was, I guess, brought up by the Wall Street Journal that there was a bunch of Facebook applications actually transmitting user IDs and other information, I guess, to third-party advertisers.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of those applications, I guess, some of them were created by Zynga, including FarmVille.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, the three of the top ten applications, FarmVille had been transmitting personal information about users' friends to outside companies.
[SPEAKER_04]: of course your user ID is publicly available and is by itself just a number however this data can be and as apparently the Wall Street Journal reports is being shared with other parties specifically wait wait a minute wait a minute you mean to tell me that Zynga the makers of that free Farmville game and all these other free games that they knocked off from other companies you mean Zynga the company that's been called pure evil by many people on the internet
[SPEAKER_04]: They've been raping my privacy this whole time.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who would have thought?
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're lying.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I understand it correctly, it wasn't that they're like, hey, here it is, but more of being able to access that data from other sites.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, the embedded ads.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't just like, here you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please!
[SPEAKER_03]: Take it!
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just playing those games made that stuff more accessible to be grabbed and they took advantage of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So wait, Amazon.com might know I'm gay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I've played Farmville once in my life?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you have terrible taste in games, apparently.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wondered why it keeps trying to sell me Will & Grace, even Season 7, and Funny Girl on Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just couldn't figure that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And because of this whole leak or whatever, of course, what's going to happen?
[SPEAKER_02]: Some lawyers are going to catch wind of this, and they're going to file a class action lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's what they did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently...
[SPEAKER_04]: because it's the American way.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to sue you about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, law firm Edelson McGuire filed a suit with San Francisco Federal Court, I guess by St.
[SPEAKER_02]: Paul, Minnesota resident Nancy Graff.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're seeking monetary relief for those whose data was wrongly shared and injunction relief to prevent continued privacy abuses.
[SPEAKER_02]: No specific amount was mentioned regarding the extent of aforementioned monetary relief, but seeing as how the announcement claims the leak has affected 218 million Facebook users, we're guessing the damages will be significant.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or sought will be significant, not necessarily what they get.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would say that's not too uncharacteristic for that company, but that sucks, I guess, if you're into Farmville.
[SPEAKER_02]: But honestly, with Facebook and stuff, a lot of your information is just kind of out there anyways, even if you're turning on your privacy settings and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just love though how, you know, this couldn't be timed any better because it always seems like, you know, that guy, that bro that runs Facebooks is like a billionaire, is always getting up on stage going, hey, you know, guys, we're really working on the privacy thing and, you know, we want your information to be secure and information and your security is our number one priority.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, you know, it comes out like literally the next day, like Farm Bill is selling your information to the devil.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Facebook creator is actually devil.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, yeah, so Didn't we already went through this debate with web browser cookies, which is essentially what's happening only it's a different avenue?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a super cookie It's a super cookie Delicious But it just seems like all it is is like, okay, we know this is a unique user, and yes, attached to Facebook, but it's not I'm not dismissing the issue, just trying to get more clarity on what the issue is
[SPEAKER_03]: It just seems like it's the same thing as the cookie of like, okay, unique user.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what knocked it up the next level is that this number, which was first just like, okay, plant there, this number we generate so it can keep a unique ID.
[SPEAKER_03]: This time it's more persistent because it's attached to your Facebook profile and et cetera, et cetera.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so anything you post on Facebook might be publicly accessible.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, lesson learned.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're going to use a site like Facebook, make sure, you know, if you don't want to get it out there, don't post it or lock it down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if you're locked down to private, like my Facebook is locked down so only friends of mine can see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And even then, there's some things I just don't post on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, Rob, there is a good use of Facebook.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like Umlaut on Facebook.com slash Umlaut.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_04]: You had all these plugs written down on a sheet of paper.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait till we get to Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like you're playing a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is at Umlaut.
[SPEAKER_04]: While we're at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, quickly here.
[SPEAKER_04]: You won't be able to find Rock Band on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, you loud fans.
[SPEAKER_04]: But one thing you will be able to find is a brand new Games for Windows Marketplace with lots of new stuff, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: November 15th is when the new Games for Windows Marketplace launches.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Right now, when you think about, how can I download PC games on my computer, you usually think about, I don't know, Steam is one of the big ones, or maybe Direct to Drive, or even maybe that good old game site that had that big old joke, ha ha, we're shutting down, no wait, we aren't, I think a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't usually think about, oh yeah, Games for Windows has their own marketplace.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Microsoft's not happy with that, and they'd like to change their perception there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they are going to be beefing up their online portal with some more stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all going to be branded with the whole Games for Windows Live, more competitive and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: They want to make it a store, really a destination for PC gamers.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's going to be stuff enabled through Live, all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're going to be revamping everything on November 15th.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: and they're saying you should show up on day one because we're going to have a great pre-order on a title you may care about the speculation is that it's Fable 3 for the PC foreshadowing you know what though if they can match some of those sales that Steam is having you know what competition is not necessarily a bad thing because you know if they're going to try to one up Steam they're going to have to do so with some of the prices so we'll see exactly how that goes over
[SPEAKER_04]: In the meantime, let's get to a segment we like to do here on the show where DarkSakura dips into the video game vault and says, Hey, you ungrateful kids with your desert bus events and your umlauts and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to know where these games came from.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get off my lawn and go play these games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And while you're at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: We like to explore gaming's past.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pull up your pants!
[SPEAKER_04]: Buy a belt!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're going to explore gaming's past by checking out the classic game of the week, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is the classic game of the week from the vault this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm angry with myself for having never reviewed this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sonic & Knuckles.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've done Knuckles Chaotix, I've done other Sonic games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have not done Sonic & Knuckles.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is wrong with me?
[SPEAKER_05]: So this is something that Sega has done right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Rob, we have to start off with the noise.
[SPEAKER_04]: We always have to start off with the noise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_05]: Best music ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sonic & Knuckles, it came out on the Genesis, also known as the Mega Drive overseas, and it was actually developed in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: at the Sega Technical Institute by members of Sonic Team.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it came out on October 18th, 1994, which was, guess what, the year I graduated high school!
[SPEAKER_05]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_04]: You're older than me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bite my butt, Robb.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm Vintage.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, this was a, uh, you could play it by itself, and it also locked on to Sonic 2 and Sonic 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game was actually developed with Sonic 2 and Sonic 3, so that's why it's got all the special little nummy goodies in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Almost as delicious as these peanut butter cookies.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you've got different stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: It actually picks up from the end of Sonic 3 after the Death Egg crashes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which, by the way, Rob, I was playing Bayonetta and I got that they were calling that dude Eggman.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that was Robotnik's name and the Japanese version was Eggman.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: And so you have to go get the Chaos Emeralds and the Super Emeralds and all the stuff and be super awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you get all of them, you turn into Super Sonic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can go to the Doomsday Zone.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then you can blow up the machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: And return the Master Emerald.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which leads right into Sonic Adventure!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the island crashes back down in Sonic Adventure.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Knuckles is pissed off at Sonic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then you've got Knuckles' story, which everyone just beats up on him, and he's like, well, crap, I'm tired of getting you, so I'm gonna go get all these emeralds too.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's the Knuckles' story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't you just love my paraphrasing?
[SPEAKER_05]: As far as the way it plays, well, you can't use Tails.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, if you lock it on to Sonic 3, then you can play Tails.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you just lock it on.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got different bonus stages.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got ones where you collect 20 rings by walking through these bumpers.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then you have the slot machines from Sonic 2, like in the Casino Night Zone.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's, of course, the labyrinth type thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then there's also the magnetic orbs that you can use to move upwards and pick up shields and rings and lives and fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does not have a save slot in it unless you combine it with Sonic 3 to make it Sonic 3 and Knuckles.
[SPEAKER_05]: so as far as other stuff in it again with Sonic 3 you can use Sonic 3 to play through as Knuckles lots of fun in Sonic 2 you can play Knuckles in Sonic 2 and you don't have to have as many rings for the little bonus zones and you can also if I remember right I think Knuckles has a lower ring no he can carry his rings over to the next stage instead of having to start over
[SPEAKER_05]: So that was a big thing with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was much easier to play through it with Knuckles.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I'm getting motion sickness just watching this bonus stage.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could not do the bonus stages because I would get very motion sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: And speaking of those little bonus stages now, if you tried to hook up...
[SPEAKER_05]: The Sonic and Knuckles to Sonic the Hedgehog, you would get a screen with all the cast going, no way, no way, no way.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, if you press a series of buttons, you can play the Blue Sphere game, a hundred different levels of it, and there's actually different levels depending on which game you do this with, because you can also do it with a bunch of other games.
[SPEAKER_05]: But keep in mind, you will not be able to play Knuckles in, you know, Bionic Commando or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That just wouldn't work.
[SPEAKER_05]: He'd fly everywhere and... That would be kind of awesome, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't it, they weren't able to do it in Sonic 1 because Sonic's blue was also coded to, like, the sky or something like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: And, like, if you, you know, they change the color on Sonic, you know, from blue to red, but then it's blood sky!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's funny that you say that.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's talking about hacks.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a game hack called Miles Tails Prower, which was, you know, Tails' name is Miles Prower, which I thought was always cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they did, the same group did one, it was a game basically to put Tails in Sonic the Hedgehog.
[SPEAKER_05]: They also did Knuckles the Echidna in Sonic the Hedgehog.
[SPEAKER_05]: So instead of changing the palettes, because you're right, it did change the sky color, they actually lifted different colors of red from another part in the game and changed the socks to blue so that he didn't have to change the palette.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that was pretty smart of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another thing too about Sonic 2 with Knuckles is that for the longest time, because of that patch that they used to make the games work together, you couldn't find a ROM of Sonic 2 that you could play Knuckles in for the longest time.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've since gotten around that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, as far as the releases, what was really great, and I remember this, because I was like, I want to do this!
[SPEAKER_05]: Blockbuster Video and MTV had a tournament where people could play pre-release with the final one being at Alcatraz.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if anyone else remembers that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was called MTV's Rock the Rock Warning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sadly, I think I do remember that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It came out on Virtual Console, and it got a 9 from IGN.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your classic game of the week, folks!
[SPEAKER_04]: Sonic and Knuckles.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't do this damn stage at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: The bonus stages are evil.
[SPEAKER_05]: I prefer... Oh, is he finally getting the Chaos Emerald?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: You got a Chaos Emerald.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: There it is, the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enjoy that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been a long time in the works.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sonic & Knuckles there on the Sega Genesis or the Mega Drive, whichever you prefer.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a good ending spot, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a good ending spot.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was as good of a transition as Seg has plugs for his Umlaut tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is all available at Umlaut.org, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: See what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we are going to take a break here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: But don't go anywhere because when we come back, there will be plenty more.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got a lot, a lot of news to get through.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to ask Seg a little more about charity-related things as well, kind of like how he started this whole charity thing in the first place.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to kind of get into that, especially for those of you out there that might be thinking, hmm, I want to do a fundraiser too and go on radio show podcasts and work in plugs everywhere I can.
[SPEAKER_04]: And be a mild internet celebrity.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So on the internet D-list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not even the celebrity D-list, and then there's the internet D-list.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Keyboard Cat would be on the B-list.
[SPEAKER_04]: OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: D- That means we can hang out with Kathy Griffin.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, she's on the celebrity D-list.
[SPEAKER_04]: We would get to hang out with... Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who would be on about the level of OLR?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to think of internet celebrities that would be on about our level.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking... See, even people like... Even like the kid in David Goes to the Dentist.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like the B-list or maybe even the A-list of the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could we hang out with a sassy gay friend?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sassy gay friend's probably up there, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe the what-what-in-the-butt guy, because that's been a few years.
[SPEAKER_04]: We might be on about that level.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been a few years since he was popular, so... Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're probably up there with Double Rainbow Guy, because he's kind of...
[SPEAKER_04]: All joking aside, I wanted to read this real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a comment in our chatroom from our pal Derek H, who is one of the hosts on Dead Pixel Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's there weekdays at All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: He hosts his own little shindig there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: sends us this link to a story on Slashdot about is Zynga trying to patent virtual currency since we were talking about Zynga and how some of their ethics may be questionable once in a while I thought this was kind of fascinating apparently a recent patent application was spotted by Zynga attempting to patent virtual currency purchased with real money for use in a gambling context
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm thinking, and this website's thinking as well, aren't there already plenty of ways that that exists?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I don't know, Xbox 360 money?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, I mean, just a lot of MMOs out there you can buy money for.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if they get the patent, then they have the patent.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if they get it denied because of prior art or whatever ruling, then they can say, if someone else tries to claim it, they'll go, oh, no, no, no, no, we did, and the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Patent Office said, oh, it can't be patented.
[SPEAKER_03]: So maybe it's a move to protect themselves in the long run?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you think filing all these patents and all this news is for?
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see what happens with that because, heaven forbid, they should be granted the patent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, we will be right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back right after this.
[SPEAKER_04]: And welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are live on this Sunday evening, October the 24th of 2010, for the 387th episode of our little podcast here.
[SPEAKER_04]: OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, we do tape live every Sunday night at AllGames.com, where you just heard during the break there, if you were listening live, we can't put it on the podcast because it's copyright music.
[SPEAKER_04]: We played some music from DJ Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of had the whole thing going live here in studio, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also live in studio tonight, joining us, The Seg.
[SPEAKER_04]: He is one of the co-founders of Umlaut, but he really hasn't talked a lot about it tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I've been coaxing him like, hey, if you show up to the show, you've got to try and drop a plug or two for what you're trying to sell.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's hard to get people to go to Umlaut.org and read all about our charity.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So just try to work in a couple more plugs if you could.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, say, I just would hate for you to have wasted that tank of gas to get here and then just not talk about your charity event.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really hard trying to get people even to follow our Twitter account, which is at umloud, U-M-L-O-U-D.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quickly, I want to ask you some more questions here since we have you here tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're so kind to be here live.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know one thing you've also been doing a lot of this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Besides the Telltale stuff, besides the Umlaut planning, another thing you've been doing quite a bit is you've been doing speaking events.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know you did PAX East because I saw your panel there when I went to PAX East earlier this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know you did  didn't you do a companion piece at PAX West?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of same song, different verse type of deal?
[SPEAKER_04]: Same song, different time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Different audience.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the panel all about that you were doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it was trying to
[SPEAKER_03]: So, we're trying to communicate, okay, there's a lot of people who obviously give to Child's Play, and there's definitely a lot of people who want to do more, and what I wanted to do with the panels is to establish and get the right general questions answered for people who want to start their own Child's Play community fundraiser.
[SPEAKER_03]: and what that means and just sort of the broad overview of where to get started and to take that next step of starting your own event whether it's a local event or an internet based event.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, I obviously, you know, we could, we could probably have you recap everything, but that would take an hour, like your panel.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't want to, I don't want to recap the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, but just trying to get some of the points out, like, what would you say for somebody who is trying to plan one of these events for themselves?
[SPEAKER_04]: And maybe you can speak from experience on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, what's one thing that people don't anticipate when they say, hey, I'm
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanna throw a rock band charity event at this, I don't know, the Masonic Lodge or wherever people are doing things.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, we wanna do like a little charity event.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what do you think is like one of the top things people don't foresee in the planning of these events that comes back to surprise them?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, oops, we should have thought about X. Well, uh...
[SPEAKER_03]: Besides the legal thing, which is a whole other conversation we'll touch on in a few moments, but the big thing that I stress is set up...
[SPEAKER_03]: What I call a list of products, if you're doing an event.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where, okay, these are the things that we're going to have as a quote-unquote product for the event.
[SPEAKER_03]: So to take Umlaut, for example, we have this ultimate band package product, we have this headliner band product, we have the ticket in the door product, we have the raffle ticket product.
[SPEAKER_03]: And by listing these down, you go, okay, how do we make this happen?
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's what's really sort of lost because people don't really know how to take the thing from soup to nuts.
[SPEAKER_03]: It may be a great idea, but you're actually at the event and you go, oh crap, how do I do this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, we have to do all this stuff and then fumble from there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's really take a step back with your team and go, start brainstorming, get all the ideas in the world, but then realize that it may be best to put some things off the table if you can't deliver on them because if you do too much and not account for it, it's all going to go to shambles.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's best to just
[SPEAKER_03]: Hold back and make sure you establish yourself and maybe next year you'll do that thing that you wanted to do or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to think of other things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think sometimes people maybe think too big when it comes to these things?
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: As people who have the best of intentions and believe me, I'm not discouraging it as someone who did a show in eight weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: But
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, first of all, for Umlaut, Umlaut wouldn't have happened if it wasn't for Foom Drawzer, which was an event that was actually founded by Joel Johnson, started in New York, and then grew to Denver with Brian Cassente of Kotaku doing the Denver event, and then Gizmodo did the San Francisco event, and I went to that event, showed up, and it was
[SPEAKER_03]: It was at Shine Bar on Leet Mission Street in San Francisco, 1337 Mission Street.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was a 200 capacity bar and it was just show up with rock band, you know, very simple, but packed the place.
[SPEAKER_03]: and that established, okay, there is, we can get enough people in here and that was just with Day of Advertising.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I always, I hadn't done charity work for a while and I wanted to get back into the swing of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And separately, I always wanted to do an event that incorporated rock band, guitar hero rock band, but focused on the performance aspect.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it was just this perfect storm so I threw my hat in and that's when I first got introduced to Chris Kohler who also helped out with the Fungrauser event in 08 and it was us planning this out actually throughout the year but with Joel and Joel had a lot of things going on so he couldn't
[SPEAKER_03]: continue on and so we were left with making our own event since we already had the deposit reserved for DNA and got things together and it really, it also, don't do this alone, I think is the other thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you can't get other people to do it
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't break yourself.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm not trying to discourage people.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not trying to knock them down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if you're a big control freak like me and you want to do everything, you just have to let some of it go because it's too much for one person.
[SPEAKER_03]: It goes down to if you can't get people to help you quite yet in working the event, how are you going to get people there?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a fair question.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say be realistic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But don't that outright discourage you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't let any of this scare you off from trying to do something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's important too.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just trying to be real here on OLR and say, if you're ready to take this dive, by all means dive.
[SPEAKER_04]: But here's some floaties.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some tips so that you don't drown.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let me get to a question from our chat room if I could here.
[SPEAKER_04]: At chat.orangefantasia.com, Salacious Pop is in chat and wants to know, Seg, how long did it take to get incorporated as a non-profit so that people could legally write off donations to you in their taxes?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are the fees steep?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you have to do it through an attorney to protect your own name and assets?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have the benefit of a wonderful father who does this...
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty professionally.
[SPEAKER_03]: I say that just like he doesn't actually have it as a job job.
[SPEAKER_03]: But as I alluded to, sort of the family business that wasn't really a business was charity events back home in Detroit, Dearborn.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we did Detroit Children's Hospital Festival of Trees.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: and our high school auction and all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So he already knows how to, you know, the tax end of things.
[SPEAKER_03]: The state of California was definitely new to us and oh, the state of California was definitely new to us for those filings.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's
[SPEAKER_03]: It's sort of a level thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: The official birth date, as far as the IRS and the state of California is concerned, for Umlaut is November 17th, and that was when the California URA business that happens to be non-profit was first minted, which is pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then, for all the stuff you want to do, like donation buttons, either PayPal or Google Checkout and all that,
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we got the TIN very easily, the text ID number for Umlaut, but then you have all this other stuff that has to go through.
[SPEAKER_03]: It takes a while for the IRS to process the paperwork, and you have to fill out the longer form and all this.
[SPEAKER_03]: So really, things did not get settled, settled, settled as far as establishing and getting our determination letter from the IRS until like...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: Put your paperwork in and know that we could revoke the status because something didn't clear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything was up to snuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just to back you up in our chat room, DefectiveCandy is in our chat at chat.orange.radio.com and says, From experience, the state of Michigan is way easier to do the non-profit than a place like Cali.
[SPEAKER_03]: California, actually, from what I've been told by others, is the most complicated in the union.
[SPEAKER_03]: I should also state that
[SPEAKER_03]: Every state has a different way, completely.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, the IRS is obviously consistent within the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: Outside of the U.S., I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_03]: But when I do these panels, I guide people to the general questions that they have to ask themselves, which is basically...
[SPEAKER_03]: Start by Googling up whatever entity in your state does business entities.
[SPEAKER_03]: Secretary of State usually, but not always.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes they have a separate department and all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that will start you down on the road of what you need to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: But don't let all this stuff freak you out either.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I should also say that there's sort of two general avenues of, at least for Child's Play community fundraisers.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Actual, local, physical event, which is what we do.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there's the internet-based fundraisers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, the internet-based ones, they haven't made as long as they're not stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, like, for example, Desert Bus, which is the online telethon for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: They use chip-in to point directly to the Child's Play PayPal account, meaning they never touch the money.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Period.
[SPEAKER_03]: The chip-in tracks the metrics of how much people clicking on their button went to Child's Play, but they never touch the money, so they don't have to do any of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: We touch the money at UMA because we have to pay for the venue, and we're taking in
[SPEAKER_03]: and donations ourselves in this physical event, so we have to go through the process.
[SPEAKER_03]: The big numbers, at least at the IRS level, is if you get more than $250 from any one individual or your total take is $5,000, you need a file.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've graduated up to, nope, you need to do it for reals.
[SPEAKER_04]: there's a great follow up from Defective Candy here in our chat room saying there are some great books on the matter I like Nolo's How to Form a Nonprofit Corporation and all states have info on how to do them on their official website you might have to do a tiny bit of digging let me throw this out there too one more kind of little thing here because I know this is one of the things I took away from the panel I was like oh yeah that's something I might not think about otherwise but say if somebody wants to do a Child's Play fundraiser you know before just throwing the name out there like hey we're going to do this Child's Play fundraiser
[SPEAKER_04]: There's probably people they should be getting in touch with, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Kristen Lindsay is... I'm sorry, Kristen, I'm totally forgetting your new title position.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not the official title, but she's the woman in charge of Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_03]: We will call her Goddess of Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Goddess of Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_03]: She has an official title, and I apologize for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's okay, it's live radio, you're on the spot.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's sort of... Child's Play's not going to give you too much help because, let's face it, it's a...
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not going to run the event for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's good to check in with her and sending an email to her saying, hey, we're doing this event.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she'll give some help, but you have to understand that everyone else is doing all this stuff, especially around this time when the season's ramping up again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: The process of giving them money is, if you're doing the chip-in thing, the internet-based thing, well, you don't have to do anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's already into their PayPal account.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for us, we mail a checkout made out to Child's Play Charity and mail it in to the mailing address that's on the Child's Play website, and there's that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, I don't want to spend too much more time talking about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to ruin your possible panels in 2011.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know if you're going to be doing it all over again, but it was, at least when I went and saw it at PAX East, I certainly learned a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know we've kind of dabbled in the idea of maybe doing an OLR charity something something at some point, so it was interesting to hear all that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, good deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and it's interesting there's been a little bit of back and forth between Interplay and Bethesda over the rights for Fallout and stuff and I believe at one point Interplay was demanding 50 million dollars for Fallout and apparently Bethesda said no so it'll be interesting to see and I'm sure that a Fallout MMO will be pretty interesting but we'll have to wait a couple years for that
[SPEAKER_02]: The ESRB is rated Twisted Metal for the PlayStation 1 Classics.
[SPEAKER_02]: So obviously that will be coming around pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe to tie in a little bit with the new Twisted Metal game maybe coming out next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll have to wait for that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at least you can expect that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then a racing game that is on the PlayStation 3 right now, Mod Nation Racers, is going to be getting a Stunt Pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and that is free for two weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's beginning October 26th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you do have that game or if you're thinking about picking up that game, you might want to download that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hurry, hurry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got some quick stuff for you guys too One of them is about Xbox Live The Xbox Live Silver account is no more It is gone, it is out of here But don't worry You didn't all get suddenly upgraded to gold Actually I don't think that's something anyone would worry about No, here's what really happened The Xbox Live Silver memberships are now just called Xbox Live Free Membership It is what it is Yeah, finally
[SPEAKER_04]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that is launched right along with the Xbox.com remake that went live this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they just basically say it's free.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're saying the features did not change.
[SPEAKER_04]: The name for the paid membership does not change.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just this little component of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just so you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's easier branding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus, I think especially when one of PlayStation's big things is selling the free PlayStation Network, I think for them to be able to say... Not quite anymore, but... Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now they're kind of on par there, so it works out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tron Evolution is getting some voice acting from the movie, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Olivia Wilde, who plays Korra in the upcoming Tron Legacy movie, is going to be doing some voices in Tron Evolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, the voice of the original Tron character, Bruce Boxleitner, is going to be in there, so that's
[SPEAKER_05]: From the Scarecrow and Mrs. King
[SPEAKER_04]: NBA Jam, as we've talked about for a couple weeks on this show, is getting spun off into its PS3 and 360 retail releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game is going to be $49.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: From downtown!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming out November 17th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, it should be noted that it is going to be online and all that, but not on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: That version is already out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Online will be available on the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 versions.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's going to be two-on-two online.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's going to be a title update in December that will have a remix jam party for up to four players and all sorts of that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: $49.99 if you want to check out NBA Jam on the 360 or the PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's on fire!
[SPEAKER_04]: Boom Shakalaka!