Orange Lounge Radio
Music Hosts
Dark Sakura
Sky and Loki
Tonight April 11th 2010
Konami announces a variety of new games
Warhammer overcharges customers in Arrow
and an old classic game is a Latin translation
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends and welcome to episode number 362 of Orange Lounge Radio
The video game talk show where every gamer has a voice
My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my co-hosts
The one and only Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers
For a moment it sounded like you were using a porn voice
A porn voice?
Yeah, a porn voice
What was porn-tastic about my voice?
You were doing that little dip in your voice
I was doing that wacky morning DJ
Let's go to Techmaster Loki with a check on traffic
No traffic in the house
Okay, let's go to Techmaster Loki with a check on the food
What's the food look like in the OLR studio today?
Awful and in a bag
Okay, for those who weren't listening to the wonderful Bobby Blackwolf
who tapes before us here at All Games Radio
www.allgames.com where of course we tape live every week
6pm Pacific, etc.
We were doing our little call that Bobby always does to us at the end of the show
and we got the realization that Loki brought to the show with him tonight
KFC, but he usually brings chicken to the show
that's no surprise
but he didn't just bring any old KFC tonight
oh no, he brought a Double Down to the show with him
For those who don't know what a Double Down is
Loki, please quickly define
What is the Double Down from KFC?
It's a new sandwich from KFC that just launched today I think
and it's basically instead of having some sort of bread holding a sandwich together
there is chicken strips holding bacon, cheese, and cheese sauce together
and it's supposed to be incredibly unhealthy
so that's why I tried it
because it would be funny
because it's like, oh my god, that's gross
yes, when you have that heart attack, it's gonna be hilarious
it smelled awful
it actually wasn't bad, but here's the problem
the cheese sauce is just awful
that's why I am not eating that
not because it's so unhealthy and full of bacon and grease and stuff like that
it's because that cheese sauce tastes like some blended
rotten mayonnaise, ranch, and cheese whiz together
and it's just, it's awful
so, if you do get Double Down, don't get it with the cheese sauce
otherwise it'll probably be good without it
I mean, seriously, the strips themselves
it's all white meat and so it's healthy for you
no, just kidding, it's not healthy
you can get it grilled though
that's gonna really help with all the cheese on it
I think though that if you got it grilled
well, it actually would be perfect for anyone doing a low carb diet though
I guess, but honestly, if I want to eat healthy, quote unquote, at KFC
I would probably get like a two piece meal
grilled with like mashed potatoes, no gravy, or something
I know, I was just being funny
or I probably wouldn't go to KFC at all
I would probably just eat a fruit salad
I just was going to see if they had the Double Down
they did, so I got it, and
I was sorely disappointed with that cheese sauce
I figured, okay, it's just gonna be something that tastes like cheese
but it's like a melted consistency
but no, they had to spice it up with like ranch or something
it's just gross, and it's overpowering the entire
it smelled really bad, or whatever it is
I could smell it from over here
so that's so unfortunate because I had high hopes for that
but, oh well
I actually have a challenge for everybody
for next month
what's that?
no fast food for a month
good luck
I've been
no, I've done it before
that wasn't the first fast food I've had in two weeks, so
it's not dinner that I have a problem with
that's really easy, it's lunch at work
is really hard, especially when I only have had a three minute lunch
but I'm starting a new job this coming week
which is exciting
I will tell you
day job
my BFF Becky
we have three days out of the week
we walk during lunch, and we bring our own lunch
and I have this huge mungus thermos thing
but the dollar store, Rob, is selling those cubes
those frozen cube things
that you can put in a thermal container
but no, it was something I was actually wanting to do
is do the one month fast food free challenge
and then
for, you know, average how many times you want
would normally go out for fast food
and then put the money that you normally would have spent
on a happy meal or something aside
and donate it to charity at the end of the month
questions from chat
Zappi says, does Subway count as fast food?
Yeah, what defines fast food?
That's tricky
because you can't say anything without a drive-thru
because I've seen subways with drive-thrus
and subways with drive-thrus?
God, that would be annoying
Okay, I'll make a list
Basically, okay, if it's a sandwich
you know, if it looks unhealthy, it probably is fast food
I would say the types like McDonald's and Sonic
I love Sonic
It's something like, we're getting way off topic
If they serve hamburgers or tacos
Or maybe if fast food is okay
if you can keep it 10 grams of fat or less
I don't know
Because at Subway it's really easy to do 10 grams of fat or less
Okay, this is the thing
Almost any of these
I'm talking about just like the
the really highly processed food, you know what I mean?
I include KFC in this too
because their chicken is just a gene bait
But seriously
I'm giving it a start in May
because I know for a lot of people it's a habit to change
Let's try to tie it in with some type of Wii Fit or DDR
That's what I was thinking
If you rub the food on a piece of paper
and it turns transparent
then it's probably fast food
The food or the paper
We gotta get back to
Listeners, help give us ideas
and we'll formulate a contest
But seriously though, this is the first soda
and first fast food I've had in two weeks
I ate my first soda today
That's only because I wanted to try to double down
So technically I ate very few calories
because I only had like two bites of that in a soda
So I'm doing good still
So what grade would you give the KFC double down here?
I would give it probably a D
just because the cheese sauce
If it was at the cheese sauce
I would have probably given it like a B
The double down gets a D here on Orange Lounge Mornings
on KAllGames
It needs like American cheese melted on there
instead of the cheese sauce and it might be good
Once in a while we talk about video games here on the program at Orange Lounge Radio
Hey if you wanna pull up a chair and join us in our chatroom
Or what they need to have instead of the cheese sauce
their gravy that they have
That would be perfect
Okay enough, enough, no more food talk
Let's talk about games, dark sakura
Please tell me you've played a video game this week
Rock band
A fuck ton of rock band last night for my party
What was the best beer at your beer potluck out of curiosity?
What was the best one?
The one that I brought of course
I'm just kidding
You know what Rob, I've actually saved that chocolate beer for an occasion
And Dan's like, they bring you, what's this? Peach? What?
It's good
I like the black currant one but I've had tons of their different ones before
I haven't tried the peach yet but I love the black currant
But the Young's is gonna be
I'm going to be having one every night when I get back from school
Nice
That's gonna be my I'm not in school beer
There's still so much beer in my fridge really
I wasn't really gonna drink any
It's totally my fault but we went from food to beer
And just totally dodged the game
Oh yeah, by the way, rock band, beer!
Totally my fault, I enabled it
I had a Guinness, a couple of new castles, about three fat tires
Clearly she was playing tapper
Two Killian's Red
Heather brought the Sierra Nevada but I really don't like Sierra Nevada at all
And then I was gonna go, I actually picked up the four pack
I was like, I'm gonna have, can't drink any more beer!
I had no voice, my throat still hurts today
And there was rock band?
There was lots of rock band, all day, rock band
We stopped long enough for Dan to play outrun
And then him and one of my co-workers that showed up
Played, it was either him, no I think it was my friend Gary anyway
They were playing Bad Dudes
Awesome, oh like on the Wii?
No the Xbox, was it Bad Dudes or Double Dragon?
It's Double Dragon, it's on the Xbox, not Bad Dudes
I was like, are you a bad enough dude to eat some carrot cake?
Just the topic of Bad Dudes has come up on this show before
There is still a lot of cake left
If anybody wants cake, I have lots
Will you FedEx slices of cake to our listeners?
I'm talking about people in this house
What kind of cake?
Chocolate and carrot
The carrot cake is actually really good
Chocolate and carrot cake or chocolate and carrot cake?
Separate
Oh the chocolate and carrot cake would be kind of rad
You could smoosh it together
I don't like carrot cake
God damn it with the food!
Would you like a piece of chocolate?
No, I shouldn't, so I'm not going to
You should have some chocolate cake
Take it with you
I can't take it with me, Laura
I could build a house out of cake
That sounds like a fun project
Should I just pitch the show for the Food Network?
I mean, should we leave all games and be on a more appropriate network?
No, I have tons of game stuff I could talk about
I'm just waiting
Add three cakes
One of them is gluten free though, so I will be taking some to work
So cake mania, taproom
I'm going to get cake right now
Loki
Here I thought this week's show would be better than the train wreck that was last week
But clearly, clearly I was underestimating the ability of this program
Well, Loki, before you do your gaming week
I already spoiled it and sent it to the listeners last week
But congratulations for you and Nellie are in order
Yes, thank you, thank you
She is, ironically enough today
She is as pregnant as she was when she had the twins
So she is a little nervous, but less nervous today
But yes, she's about 21 weeks and four days, I believe?
Three days? 21 weeks and three days
Yeah, so
One boy, we know that
So everything's cool so far
Anyways, so games
So let me first start off with a story
Because this is really odd, but awesome at the same time
So Friday, you know, it
I think it was Friday, anyways
Friday, not this Friday, but last Friday
I get this mysterious package in the mail
I'm like, what the hell is this?
Was it something I ordered off eBay and completely forgot about?
Inside was an Xbox 360
Apparently we have a listener who is staying anonymous
In the Austin, Texas area
And has sent me a 360 that was already J-tagged
To replace the 360 that I had stolen
I don't know who we have in Austin, Texas
I don't know either
That's not far from where Travis Donovan is, but
He doesn't really like this show
No, no, I don't know
Whoever it was, they posted like a small little message
It was kind of in broken English, so I don't know if it's
I don't know, anyways
So long story short, I'm very thankful for that
And thankfully I do have
Wait, how did they get your address?
I don't know
Isn't that, doesn't that, wait, wait
Doesn't that strike you as slightly creepy?
Like, I don't know if I would actually be excited about the Xbox
I would more be wondering, how did a listener get my home address?
No, it was sent to my work, so
Oh, have you said where you work on this program before?
I might have at one point
Weird
Maybe Namco sent it, they know where you work
Yes, that makes perfect sense
We learned that a couple of years ago
Fun times
No, but anyways, I'm incredibly thankful for that
And, you know, I've been messing with it for
Well, this last, you know, week or so
Okay, but seriously, ask before you send us strange packages in the mail
It's always a nice thing to do
Exactly, and I mean, definitely, I would
You know, that was incredible, and I
No, I mean, it's a very nice gesture
Exactly
There is a small part of me where I'm like, oh, that's awesome
Like, that's 90%, no, I was even like 95% awesome
But 5%, like, how did they get your address?
I wasn't even thinking about that, honestly
I was like, woohoo, yeah!
No, but, no, it's been cool
So, I've been playing a lot of games, obviously
One more thought, could it have been the guy that we sicced the O.L. Army on?
Maybe just
In Austin, Texas? Would he, like, leave the state?
Maybe?
I don't know
Alright, just cheers
Alright
So anyways, so, games
What did I play this week?
I played, actually, some Japanese shooters
I was at Espegluda 2, actually played that quite a bit
Went through kind of the
I figured I'd start off at the easy mode on there
And it's pretty fun, it's a little different
I haven't really played a lot of the Japanese shmup games
But, it's pretty fun, a lot of dodging bullets and whatnot
So, definitely worth checking out if they ever bring it over here
Tried a little bit of Otomedius Gorgeous
That game is a little weirder than I thought
But it definitely has that whole Gradius vibe to it, of course
But that's pretty fun
And, played through more Final Fantasy XIII
I'm now, well, I don't know if I should say Warmack
Because that's kind of a spoiler, I guess
But, I'm to the point in the game where it kind of opens up, like, you know
How many hours in are you?
16, but then again I'm cheating, remember, so
Oh, right, that's right
So, I'm on chapter 11, I believe
Okay, okay
And it opens up kind of like an overworld and stuff
And it's almost like in Wind Waker where you go, spoiler
You go under the ocean or whatever and you see Hyrule
And you're like, why couldn't the whole game have been like this, you know?
Why couldn't they have just done this instead?
Well, that's almost, to me, what this part of the game is for Final Fantasy XIII
For the people that are complaining, why isn't there an overworld in this?
You know, why couldn't they have done the whole game like this?
Because it's basically kind of like an overworld situation
But, at the same time there's all these side quests and stuff you can do
Which are kind of annoying, but they're relatively easy for me, I guess
And the narrative's kind of moving along a little bit, but I still don't know entirely what's going on
But I think I'm at the end, or close to the end
I just want to interject real quick, because the chatters were commenting on Loki's mic being all screwed up tonight
That's actually really my bad
I took Loki's mic to PAX East with me for the show that we did out there
And unfortunately he has our old spare mic, which is just an old mic we had lying around
And the audio settings were left on, every mic is different
And so, long story short, I've been having to adjust on the fly
So if Loki's audio is going up and down and changing around, that's me playing on the mixing board
So it should be all better now though, I think I found where it needs to be
Sorry, listeners, sorry, Loki
And then, so yeah, it's alright, it's kind of neat
And unfortunately those characters didn't seem like they were too much lesbians at this point in the game
Although there was an embrace part of the game which I was like, are they gonna kiss?
I wasn't trying to go there, I was trying to keep quiet on the spoilery stuff
But I do think there are lesbians in Final Fantasy 13
Yeah, they're close, we don't know how close, but they're close
I think they're very close, just saying
Cougar kitten thing going on there
There is definitely a cougar kitten thing going on
Anyway, no more spoilers
Alright, anyways, so yeah, it's pretty awesome
And then, and there's a loud commercial for Lysol power toilet cleaner
Anyways, I believe that was it as far as games though
Granted, you probably guys know what JTAG consoles are for
Nothing legit, Bobby would not approve, of course
Let me just say, there's a lot of Rock Band load content out there
Well, I'm hoping, Loki, you're only using it to do the import games and not the shady stuff
Import games are okay, I think
I say import games, they don't bother to release, they're a fair game
That's my stance on piracy
The only games I've ever really, really liked, just totally been hardcore pirating into would be the import stuff
Especially back in the PS1 days
Because I'm not gonna pay to import games if the publisher doesn't believe in the game here
I did install a 640GB hard drive though in the shell of an old 360 case
So now I can use that because JTAG consoles allow you to do that
But it's awesome, I like playing games from other regions
Alright, if that's it for your gaming week, then I'll talk quickly about my gaming week
I actually didn't play a lot of new games, just kind of a potpourri, a lot, a lot of old games this week
Especially on Xbox Live Arcade
I did play a little more Game Room, I guess I could say that, just a little more
I haven't really been working on the Yars Revenge duel with Bobby
Because actually, Bradley, Arkadian42, who hasn't been on this show in quite some time
But he was here last night
I randomly saw him yesterday, yes, he has smoked both Bobby and I
I don't think Bobby can see that
But like, now I don't just have to beat Bobby, I have to beat Bradley
And that's even, that's 130,000 points
I actually messed a little bit with Game Room
And I noticed I got a lot of achievements really quick by just doing stuff
You can get about 100 points doing next to nothing
But you do have to actually play games to get more
But I bought Crystal Castles
Because I had a friend over who really wanted to see Crystal
Because they remembered it from the 80s and they really wanted to play it
And I was like, okay, you know, I liked Crystal Castles enough
Where I'll spend the money to get it
You know, it's like renting a movie
You know, five bucks is about how much it costs to rent a movie
Because I buy all my games for both, computer and 360
And when we got it, I realized the control sucks
Like really sucks for that game
Because the controller analog stick is no substitute for a trackball
Not at all
Tried to play it and then I thought, oh, it'll be okay
Because I have it on the computer
And I can use the mouse
And the mouse makes a, because a mouse is basically an inverted trackball
So it makes a, it's not a perfect substitute
But it's probably the best one there is
So I figured, okay, I'll play Crystal Castles with the mouse
Nope, can't use the mouse
I remember I, irritating
I used to play that on the Apple II
Way back in the day
And a mouse worked okay then
But I guess if they don't support it at all then
I don't support it at all
It's awful
Unless, I could have missed something
But, you know, what I did is I unplugged my 360 controller
And it defaulted to keyboard controls
And I couldn't find an option in there to switch it to the mouse to control
Which makes sense because you don't have a mouse on 360
And the game is kind of made for both
And it's very obvious
But it's just, you know, it's just these little things
That are just killing Game Room for me
Like there's so much potential with Game Room
And there's so much that I really want to like about Game Room
But there's these glaring things that just irritate me
Like, oh, why didn't you find this sooner you dummy
You know, just in the servers
And, you know, just some of the things with it
Um, let's see, look at our chat room
chat.orangelandrater.com
Brad says, sucks, does not even begin to describe it
Our buddy from Pod Culture, Brad there
Ah, alright, anyhow
Um, chat.orangelandrater.com
If you want to join us
So, yeah, a little bit of Game Room
And just some random other games too
On the arcade, you know, like playing
Street Fighter and Puzzle Fighter
And Mega Man 9 and just random stuff
All throughout the week
And wow, lots of wow
I rolled a Death Knight
My Death Knight's already level, just about level 61
PVP is super fun with a Death Knight
I just want to say
It's a lot of fun
So, alright, um, let's get into some housekeeping tonight
Of which I don't have an awful lot
Um, just, you know, uh, join our Facebook
If you haven't already
Facebook.com slash OrangeLoungeRadio
You can also follow us on Twitter
At Twitter.com slash O-L-R
And definitely try to join us for a live show sometime
Sunday nights at 6 o'clock
It's a much different experience when you listen live
6 o'clock Pacific, of course, 9 o'clock Eastern
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show at AllGames.com
That's really all I have for housekeeping
We don't have any shows off that I'm aware of coming up
Or anything else
So, we're just gonna keep right on truckin'
With some gaming news
Quite a bit of gaming news coming out of Konami
They had a big press
They had their, um, uh, Gamers' Night this week, right?
Really, I didn't know
We didn't get invited
Well, you know, but it's in L.A. now
I wouldn't have been able to go anyway if we did
Oh, that's true, that's right
You know, and
I always forget that they're not
Yeah, they're not in the Bay anymore
So, yeah, I wouldn't have been able to go anyway
I don't know
It's kind of one of those things where, especially if they're
You know, one thing we don't have news on is, is DDR
And, you know, I realize that's kind of how we started
Although, I guess
I don't know if I should say this, but
I don't know if I really should say this on the air
There's a very good chance we're gonna have an interview with them at E3 this year
Very good chance
I'm trying to pull some strings
So, uh, gonna be a, gonna be a fun E3
Alright
You're going to E3?
Yep
Alright, cool
Good times
Alright, anyhow, sorry
You already could tell some news from, uh
I thought you, are you, well, you can't go
Now, I wondered why you were so, like, nope, can't go
Nope, there's no way I'm going to E3 this year
And I was like, well, what, you're not even gonna ask? What the hell?
And now that we know that the wife is pregnant
Now, that makes sense
Cause isn't that right around the due date too?
No, August
Oh no, okay
So
Well, you said a long time ago, Jamie, you couldn't go
You said school or something
I'm trying to graduate
Yeah
So
I'll go
I suppose if no one else wants to go, I'll go to E3
And, you know, do whatever
Alright, anyhow
Konami, news
Oh, I forgot to ask you
What?
Because you went to PAX East, did they have any of the PlayStation Move stuff there?
Did you get the, hm, would you play it?
No, there was no move at PAX East
Yeah, they sucked
Well, you'll have to listen to last week's show, no, I'm kidding
I don't want to listen to last week's show
Yeah, it was pretty bad
Uh, hey, this week isn't turning out much better
Uh, APB was there
I think that's the one you would have liked the most
Yeah, they had a playable, they had playable ABP
I definitely thought of you
I do have video I shot, I can show you at some point
Awesome
That was the one that, well, actually, you would have really enjoyed the line
The Crackdown 2 was out on the floor
Yep
And, uh, I don't know what else you really liked
But it just seemed there was a lot of Loki games there
Yeah, I wanted to check out Crackdown 2
But I'll wait for that
I'm actually going back to Crackdown 1 to try to finish, finish that
I mean, I finished it, but I have to find, like, ten orbs that I'm missing
Um, and, just, I'm trying to go back to some of the older stuff
But, really, I don't know, Crackdown 2 is going to be awesome
I'm so sad that they pushed it to July
It's supposed to be coming out in May
Alright, oh well
Anyway, we had Konami news at some point, right?
Yes
Alright
So let's talk about Konami
Uh, Konami is taking a page out of Capcom's book
Um, re-issuing one of their games and kind of giving it the whole HD treatment
Uh, Russian Attack Ex-Patriot is a brand new Russian Attack game
Kind of looks very similar to Bionic Commando Rearmed
And they're doing the whole 2.5D, um, kind of update to it
And it will be available on Xbox Live Arcade and Playstation Network
And, of course, um, the game looks pretty cool
Except, honestly, I don't believe I liked Russian Attack very much
Maybe just because it was very difficult
It can't be a souped up version of the old arcade game
The old arcade game was too straightforward
Like, it was a very old school 80s game
Well, this is supposed to be pretty linear too, I think
Interesting
Well, you know, the little video I saw
It's ironic that you compare it to Capcom and Bionic Commando
Because that's the first thing I thought of
And the look of it
Just the color palette and stuff reminds me
Just the look of it really looks like Bionic Commando Rearmed
But, sort of, to be fair, it looked a little bit like Shadow Complex as well
Shadow Complex kind of has that same sort of style to it
It's not bad
With the 2D, 3D look
Oh, yeah, it looked cool
The Russian Attack arcade game's okay
But here's the thing
Bionic Commando Rearmed, I think, really cashed in
I don't know why we keep comparing it to this
But it's just why, what I think when I see it
Because they did it well
They were the best example of doing this
Yes, and, but Bionic Commando had a lot of nostalgia with it
Like, I think more people remember Bionic Commando
Than remember Russian Attack
Like, quick poll of our chat room
How many of you remember Russian Attack?
Like, not just, like, name, triggers
Oh, yeah, I think that was a game somewhere
But, like, actually, like, can think of in your mind
How the game plays
Like, just, you know
Especially versus Bionic Commando
Just a quick poll of chat
Chirp, chirp
Do you remember Russian Attack, Jamie?
I remember looking at it
And she's got a freaking vault of games
I don't think we have Russian Attack
She has a freaking game that came with a dish
I mean, that's
That's true, I do have a game that came with a dish
And she doesn't remember Russian Attack very well
I mean, that ought to tell you something right there
So
And Dan's not here for us to
No, Zappy, not Russian
It's Rush in Attack
Oh, yeah, I do remember that
Rush and Attack
Yes, but with an N
No, wasn't there an arcade one?
Yes
Yeah, we had it at my arcade
Okay, oh, well, there you go
No, there was another game, though, that was
I was thinking, never mind
Yeah, we had it at my arcade
Zappy in our chat room
Russian Attack would be like Karnov
That's Russian Attack
It had that kind of oblique, all bold logo to it as well
Yeah
Yeah, I remember it
Let's see, Tigerclaw says
Rush in Attack was a game I fondly remember
I remember going to a local grocery store
And putting a ton of quarters trying to beat the game
It was hard, but then when I had fun playing it on the NES
Let's see, Tigerclaw also jumps in that
Russian Attack on the NES had two player co-op
I mean, Satsuma said
I remember playing an XBLA demo of Russian Attack
Does that count?
And yeah, that was one of those Konami games
They dumped a bunch of them on Xbox Live
When the arcade was first out
They were like a dime a dozen
I mean, some of them were notable
You know Frogger, the old arcade game
It was one of the first ones, so it was still pretty cool
JIRUS, like I really like that one
Time Pilot, and there was a lot of obscure
Scramble
They need a 2.5D HD remake of Contra
They had a Contra on it
But it was just the arcade version
Well, yeah, but they had a sequel they did for WiiWare
I mean, port that over
I'll tell you one title, Konami
That will not work with this HD remix thing
And I think you've already done it anyways
Frogger, please god, no more Frogger games
Ever, no more
I'm pretty sure it's already been done
There was a Frogger 2 on Xbox Live Arcade
But the funny thing about it
It's actually like the third or fourth Frogger 2
That's come out
Cause like back in the Commodore 64 days
There was Frogger 2 three deep
There was Frogger 2 on the Playstation
And then there was this Frogger Swampies thing
I don't know, whatever
Ooh, Dark Tetsuya has a good point
It used to be called Green Beret in Japan
If I recall correctly, I think he's right
I think that game was called something completely different overseas
I think it was called Green Beret, that's right
I remember the game on Xbox Live
But like before that, not really
You know, so again
I just, you know
If the nostalgia is what they're trying to cash in on
I don't think there's a lot of nostalgia there
So I sort of hope the game can stand on its own two feet
I mean, the game can rise above the nostalgia
If it's a great game, it won't matter
That it ties into this obscure ass 80s game nobody remembers, right?
Exactly
So we'll see, I guess
I imagine there'll be more of this
At E3?
Probably
Robert M says, Rush and Attack was on the Game Boy Advance compilation, wasn't it?
I am like 95% positive, yes it was
It was on that Game Boy Advance compilation
That had all the old school Konami games from the 80s
I don't know if they called it that
It might have been on its other name, I don't know
Anyhow, lots of games were announced at the Konami event
One of them is Saw 2
That's right, Saw 2
Is going to be coming out
It's being developed by Zombie Studios
They did the first game as well
It's coming out for Halloween
Just in time for the movie
I think they have said that they will keep making those damn movies
Until they stop making money
Considering those movies cost less than 10 million dollars to make
You're gonna have a lot of Saw movies, guys
Unfortunately
I gotta admit though
I'm kind of surprised that a Saw sequel is happening
Because I didn't think the first game did very well
I could be wrong
It didn't do that well, I don't think
Honestly, having seen all the Saw movies
The last one was alright
I kind of liked it
But
It's getting to the point
The game or the movie?
The movie
The games have nothing to do with the movies
They don't follow the plots of the movies
They try to do their own thing
Sort of
But I'm just saying
They basically killed off
Jigsaw in the second movie
The third movie
Maybe the second movie
I can't remember which one
I think it was the second one
It kind of makes it difficult
To
Keep having this guy do it
Because now you have someone else
Taking over for him
It's just getting ridiculous now
Um
You know what?
According to VGcharts.com
Again, take this with a grain of salt
Because I don't know how accurate these numbers are
But according to VGcharts.com
Saw pushed.21 million
On the Xbox 360
That's 200,000
And then.23 million on Playstation 3
So it actually sold better on Playstation 3
And so that would be a combined half million
So
Not bad
But they only sold that I think right at launch
I don't think that they really
It was a title that kind of
Made its money the first
Two months and then just
Nothing
And I should say that is worldwide
Because actually the game did much better overseas
Than it did in the Americas
Which is kind of interesting
Oh and that explains why the PS3
Sold more
Actually the Xbox 360 sold more in America
And only 100,000 on PS3
Don't get me wrong it was an alright game
Again take those sales figures with a grain of salt
Yeah and I think the game was alright
It was kind of repetitive I guess
And you know
The new game though
Apparently is going to have some better puzzles in it
They were talking about one that was
Being shown off as a demo
And apparently no one figured it out
Unless they were told how to do it
So I don't know if that's good or not
But it's interesting
They're saying of course more
Yucky gross death machines
Which is the whole thing that kind of turns me off
Of the Saw series and I will admit
It's weird like I have no problem with
Konami's other franchise
Silent Hill but it's
I have no problem with the gore in that game
But it's Saw bugs me
I can't explain it and maybe it's because
Saw is a bit too real
Whereas like Silent Hill
Obviously Pyramid Head is not real
It's supernatural
It's a little more supernatural
I can't explain what the difference is
Saw just
I don't know
I've talked about this on the show before
It's just torture porn to me
It doesn't excite me
I get that there's people into it
But I'm just not one of them
Whatever they're making a new game
I guess the first one didn't sell as bad as we all think it did
If those numbers are any indication
I don't think a half million combined worldwide is terrible
Certainly there's games that do a hell of a lot worse
But I don't think it was a launch of a franchise
As they had hoped
They were hoping that this was going to be their next Silent Hill franchise
And
I think Silent Hill does a lot better
Interesting
Well Dark Sakura
What?
You have some more news for us out of Konami
Yes I do
But I'm still kind of
About it
There is another Silent Hill game
In the works for PS3 and Xbox 360
But they didn't really give out any other information about that
Just said that it's another one
I'm surprised by this news
I assumed that Silent Hill was done
Because I assumed that Homecoming did not perform well enough
It didn't
But I mean
Shattered Memories did okay
But I actually returned my copy
Wasn't the rumor that what they were showing
Like a Shattered Memories type of game
Not necessarily like Homecoming
I thought I heard something
The rumor is it's supposed to be like a
Like what Shattered Memories was to Silent Hill 1
This is supposed to be to Silent Hill 2 or something
I don't want that
I don't want to play that
I didn't really enjoy that much of Shattered Memories
Weird
I just like
Plain old good Silent Hill
Last decent one was 4
And that's it
Silent Hill Shattered Memories on the Wii
.18 million
So that's less than
And again these numbers are coming from vgcharts.com
That's much less than what Saw moved
How did Homecoming do?
The problem is
Homecoming moved.36 million
That's on the 360
And how much on PS
Whatever the reason
You can put out really awesome mature games on it
But no one's buying them
Well the other thing that strikes me odd
About the fact that they're continuing the Silent Hill franchise
I mean even if the Silent Hill Wii game
Was critically well received
Is the departure of Akira Yamaoka
Because to me
He was such a key component of that franchise
I really don't see how they can continue it without him
I mean if it's true that they're just
Redoing the second game
I suppose I can see that
Because how much did he really
Contribute to Shattered Memories
I don't think he did a lot
For that game
Did he even do the soundtrack?
Yeah he worked on the soundtrack
I think they finally learned
That they really can't do anything else with the series
They don't have the right kind of
I think thought process to take it where it needs to go
That's just my thought
Interesting comment from the chat room
Because this could
Spar another discussion here
S.H.O. 100 Matt in our chat room
I remember the great horror movies of the 80s
When it was about the scare
No matter how cheesy the effects were
Whereas now it's shot gore
He goes on to say the thing
80s version is better than any Saw or Hostile movie
And then somebody brought up
DJ Dark Knight says
Nightmare on Elm Street, nothing more
And Friday the 13th
And it's interesting because they've remade
I mean Nightmare on Elm Street is coming out in a couple of weeks
Right?
And it seems odd to me that those are not turning into games
I mean
Sure there was a Friday the 13th game
Years and years ago on the NES
Which by the way I enjoyed way more than most people did
Just on the tangent
I actually
I hate to say it because I know I'm going to get made fun of
But I don't care
I actually enjoyed the Friday the 13th game when I was younger
It made sense to me and I had a lot of fun playing it
It was hard as hell
That angry video game nerd
His review of it, it was funny
And there was a Nightmare on Elm Street game too
If I remember right
Which was crap
It was crap, but if my memory is right
It was one of the very few Nintendo games
That used that four player expansion
They had
Remember how they had the four player thing on the NES
There was very few games that used it
I know that you could change your main character
And that it was still really lame
And every character sucked
Pretty much
With the Saw and the horror franchises
Doesn't it seem odd to anyone
That there is not a video game
Coming out for Nightmare on Elm Street
Or even that there wasn't one for Friday the 13th
There hasn't been one for Halloween
Or any of the horror movies
They've made in quite some time
No, I'm not surprised
Why is that?
First you have to pay the licenses
For that and they have an idea
Of how well
These games
Perform
And something like that it would be kind of hard to expand on
The storyline
And stuff like for example Nightmare on Elm Street
Well
What the hell would the game be about
I mean you basically going after
Freddy I guess
Or you know trying to escape him
It's just hard to expand on
How you know whether enemies and stuff
Are you going to have in it
It just doesn't translate well into a game
It's strange though
Because so many movies that come out these days
Get games with it like you know Avatar had a game
Alice in Wonderland had a game
Avatar learned itself very well to the game
Yeah that's easy though to do
There's plenty of characters in that
That you can build a game off of
And same with the Alice in Wonderland
So there's plenty of creatures and enemies
And stuff you can create for the game
I read a very interesting article this last week
That said that
It was on Yahoo
And the little teaser was
This movie franchise
Could have been a video game
Is losing tons of potential dollars
Because there is no video game
And you click on it to find out what franchise they're talking about
Any guess?
Twilight because I read this
What's funny is they forgot
There is a game based on Twilight
Well it's the scenic game
That's still a game and it's based on Twilight
So they're stupid because they did the research
I blame
No
I don't want to see it either
But they make a point
It's strange that there is no
Twilight video game
I don't want to see it either
It doesn't make a good game that's why
But if they make a game for Alice in Wonderland
And Charlie and the Chocolate Factory
There's more characters
Push A to sparkle
Exactly it's not like
She's running around slaying
Vampires or slaying werewolves or whatever
She's just some whiny emo chick
And that's
You can't make a game based on that
Push B to lock the door and cry
I mean it's seriously
You can't, you can't really do that
There's no
Enemies for the fight, she doesn't do that
It doesn't translate well, they'd be like
The equivalent of making a game based off
Of
Anything
Like the money pit
Or you know just
I'm getting yelled at by chatters because they're saying
Rama's saying no Twilight game for PS3 360
That's a smart move, Tigerclaw says don't give them any ideas
Do you really want a Twilight MMO?
Again, I have zero interest in the game
But the capitalist
Money making
America fuck yeah side of me
That's all about making money does say
You know a Twilight game on the Wii
That's not, I'm talking about an actual Twilight game
Is a lost opportunity
It really is, I have
No fucking interest in it but
I know there's a lot of girls that would play it
Here's how you do it, okay, and this is how you can
Translate most of those games that don't
Necessarily, or most of those movies that don't
Necessarily work as games into games
And have them still be
Alright
You do them the way they did
Heavy Rain
That's the only way you can do it
Is that you have some sort of context based
Game
That has a narrative
That looks just like the movie
That's really the only way you can do it because
As far as being an action game
Or anything like that, you can't do that
With these games, it makes no sense
Frisbee in our chatroom says
Hey, I'd like a Twilight game if you got to play
As Blade
They really
Could do the
A dating sim
You know
And that would sell amongst the
God, that just makes me feel dirty
What was that shirt I saw at Hot Topic?
And then Buffy staked Edward, the end
That's great
I would wear that shirt
It was pretty awesome
I knew you would wear that shirt, okay, sorry
I would rock that with pride
Look, I want to put out a formal apology to our listeners
And everybody for bringing up Twilight on
Orange Lontrenio, it was inappropriate of me
And I apologize, so
Please, let's move on with a different video game
It'll never happen again
I'm
Do you think that I'm having an allergic reaction
To that, Rob? No, you're just sparkling
Ahh
Loki, help
Loki, help! I'm sorry
Well, one easy way to defeat
The Twilight series is to take
A nice gun with a chainsaw
And rip it in half
And that's what you can possibly do in the new
Gears of War game, which, funny enough
Was supposed to be announced on the Jimmy Fallon
Show, but apparently
It got bumped to Monday
And
Nobody told Xbox Live
Because apparently on the Xbox Live
Marketplace, there is a wonderful banner
Announcing the Gears of War 3
Game, which will be
Coming April
That's a year off
Yeah
And I just want to point out
I speculated earlier this year that
Gears of War 3 would be an E3 announcement
So maybe I screwed that up, but
That it was going to support Project Natal
Is that, does that seem to be the case?
Doesn't say
Don't know, but there's been some sort of
Rumors saying that the
It will feature, I guess, underwater
Combat this time and mech suits
I
Well, I mean, not that I think it needs
To support Natal, it was just kind of my gut feeling
Was they were really, they've been really
Really quiet about such a big franchise
For them, and so I kind of thought that
It was going to be like, oh Gears of War 3
E3 and it's Natal, that's why
We've kept it so under the wrap
Under the wraps, but
I guess, you know
We'll hear more about it, maybe
If you want to watch Jimmy Fallon on Monday, I guess
Or just wait for the YouTube to hit
15 minutes later
Because, you know, I'd rather
Not subject myself to
An hour of that, I just watched the highlights
Actually, I have to admit, I'm not
Huge on Gears of War either, I'm just not
Good at it, like Gears of War
A, I suck at first person shooters
To begin with, B, the thing about
Gears of War is it's very about like cover
And very like, like stealth and being able
To move around and be very tactical
Whereas, I like, if I'm going to play
An FPS, I've got to play something like Quake 3
Which is just kamikaze, run out there
Shoot everybody with rocket launchers, kill kill
Die die, you know, type of
Stuff, I'm not good at Gears of War because
I have, I can't cover
Like, I just run out and shoot everything
And I always die
So
And it's stuff like that is why
You know, Gears of War
Makes a better game franchise than
Twilight, because there's no
Rocket launchers and
I mean, there's people dying, but
They just whine about it
SSG100Matt
Says, don't support NBC, go Team Coco
So,
It's saying that you shouldn't, you shouldn't
Watch the show anyway, you should just wait for
Whatever will show up on Xbox
Live inevitably anyway
In support of Coco
Who I'm seeing live next week
Very excited
Well, yay for you Rob
That's right, I should buy tickets for that
I think they're all sold out everywhere
Well, I meant for Sacramento
I don't know
Alright
Anyhow, moving on to another story and
Yeah, those tickets were pretty expensive
But this is even more expensive
Apparently, Warhammer Online
Or Mythic Entertainment if you will
The makers of Warhammer Online
Somehow charged a $14.99
Monthly fee several times
To gamers this past week
Dozens of times, in fact there's a screenshot
Here of a banking record where
That monthly fee was charged
It looks like
17 times on somebody's
On somebody's banking log here
And that means like
An overcharge of like
Between $200 and $500
Apparently, one player is reporting
That they were charged for
$1,013.12
Because it had just come up that a six month
Subscription was up and he got charged
For that like multiple times
Not cool because
A, you don't know what caused the error
Which is gonna be bad for EA and
Mythic
They're trying to refund the fees within 24 to 36 hours
But here's the problem
People are gonna start bouncing
Checks, they're gonna overdraft
And they're gonna threaten
Mythic or EA with this
EA's gonna have to pay for all these overdraft
Fees that they cause
Without a doubt
And so that's just not pretty for them
That sets them back, that's a big boo boo
But you gotta be, that's the one reason
To be careful with these automatic withdrawals
But it stinks because so many games
Kinda require them in this day and age
But makes you think about maybe
Using those prepaid cards instead
Because you don't want something like this
Happening to you I'm sure
I mean I don't think anybody
Did this intentionally or purposely
I mean surely it was an error, it's just
A really crappy error
That is just
Really no one wins in this scenario
No one wins
And it's not like Warhammer Online was a game that was
It kinda didn't need
Something like this on its reputation
Right now, it's very unfortunate
Can you imagine if something like that happened with WoW?
Oh my gosh
Oh my gosh, banks would go under
From all the people that would complain
And rise up
My gosh
I don't think it affected everyone that played
But I think just those that probably had their statements
Renewed on a certain day but still
Stinks, too bad for them
Let's see
Rama in our chat says
That happened to me with a hotel for Anime Boston
Took them two weeks to refund my money
So, so irritating
That companies can do that
But you know what, if it results in overdraft fees
And it's this company's fault
You should take them to task for it
They'll refund the money, they have to
Alright, anyhow
That's messed up
I know
I mean, I looked at that and I was just like
Yet another reason to hate Warhammer
You know what though, that could have happened at any game though
Because I would bet money
That EA Mythic contracts another company to handle all this
And that company botched up
And it's just really unfortunate
Because like I said, yeah, Warhammer already
Hasn't had the greatest rep
I mean, it has its loyal fan base
But it's definitely not been the wow killer
It was originally imagined to be
I played it for a while, it was okay
It's just, you know, I didn't get everything out of it
I was hoping for
Well, how about something happier?
How about it?
Doctor Who?
On PC, we get a Doctor Who game
Who?
Doctor
Do not make me go hunt down my sonic screwdriver please
Anyway
Starting on June 2010
There are going to be four
Interactive episodes
That are going to be free on the
BBC Doctor Who website
With the current cast
And the new producer, writer guy
And
A lot of
The story elements, I guess, going on with what's currently
I guess going to happen in this season
And it's being developed by Sumo Digital
They
It actually was said by
The head of drama for BBC Wales
The executive producer for Doctor Who
The director of the series
There aren't going to be
13 episodes
There will be 17 of which
Are interactive
Interesting
So they're really considering this part of the television arc
Yep
Of course if they let us download it over here
Then I will
Talk to people
Yeah, exactly
Torchwood?
Any chance we can get a Torchwood game?
Are we ever going to ever get Torchwood?
No, it's over
But that doesn't mean they won't do games
Yes it does
They ended it, they completely ended it
But can't they go back and do games
From, you know, the canon earlier
In the show or something?
I seriously doubt that's going to happen
They do that all the time with franchises that are over
They reinvigorate it for a game
Okay, I'll give you that
Where's my northern exposure?
Shut up
Actually, I'll say this not to deviate
To sci-fi nerd-dom for a minute here
But wasn't there a talk that Fox wanted to do
An American version of Torchwood?
Dear God, no, I hope not
And something about
The guy, why can't I remember his name?
The guy that plays Captain Jack
They actually were thinking of having him
Do it
No, um
Not that Captain Jack, the other one
Why can't I remember his name? Oh my God
John Barrowman
The guy that played Captain Jack
And sang all those songs and dressed up like a captain
With hoochies hanging off of him
That Captain Jack?
No, not that Captain Jack
John Barrowman
This is Captain Jack
It's such a common name
How about release dates, Loki?
Captain Gack
This week, there's
Well, there's not a lot because we're in the month of April
And April's really light
There are some notable things
First off, of course
Splinter Cell Conviction
Coming out on Xbox 360
That's pretty sweet
Grand Theft Auto episodes
From Liberty City
Making its way out onto the Playstation 3
As well as PC
Blood Bowl finally coming out
On PSP this week as well
And there's gonna be
Nothing else, I guess
That is one hell of a light week
Alright, let's go to
I need to say something real quick
Okay
Since I hate having to spell this shit out
Because apparently I do every time I state something
That's my opinion
When I say something is over
I'm typically meaning it's over for me
I don't care
It's good
It's over for me, I don't care
It's gone
Okay, well I took what you said to mean that the show is actually over
So it's not over, it's just you've written it off
Because you don't like the direction it's going in
They got rid of everybody
Except for one person
There's nothing more in that for me to watch
Okay, well as someone who doesn't watch the show
I have no idea, so there you go
Alright, Japanese release dates
No More Heroes
Is coming out on the Xbox 360
And yeah, I heard about that
That they were going to remake that for the 360
Because mature games don't do very well on the Wii
It's going to be awesome
So there it is on its way on the 360 this week
And there's lots of people like Loki
Who will probably use his new JTAG
Not creepy and ominously donated 360 to play
It could be a bomb, I haven't opened it up yet
Loki
I'm going to get that screen somewhere
Alright, on the Playstation 3
Also gets a version of No More Heroes
As well, it's a pretty dry week otherwise
I guess that's kind of the anchor
And there you go, you can import the PS3 version
If you don't have a modded console
That's true, because PS3 is region free
Of course it's all going to be in Japanese
But who cares
Might be able to get through it anyway
Nintendo Wii, not a thing this week
You got to wait until the 22nd for really any new games
Playstation 2
Clover no Kunen no Alice comes out
As well as Psycho Shogi
Gekyashashi Special
That's just a price reduction
About the equivalent of 20 bucks in Japan
So look for that, that's a gambling game though
I mean really, do you guys import gambling games?
I don't think you do
On the Nintendo DS, Let's Science with Marie and Gully
That's a big game coming out this week
On the Nintendo DS
I've never heard of this game
Let's Science, is that like Science Mama?
I don't know
I know it has little equations in it
And all this other stuff
Dekitayo Mama
Mitsugo no Kumasan
Otoko no Koko
That is not Cookie Mama, I thought it was
Because I saw Mama in the title
Otoko means boy
It's like a boy's hero
Here's a boy
Like a child's playground or something
Anyhow
That's the DS
Quickly looking at the PSP
Sokoku no Kusabi
Hiro no Kakara 3 comes out this week
That is
An action game
I'm trying to see if this is an established franchise
Because it's 3
I don't recognize it
It looks like it's based on an anime
Because it has really pretty cut scene looking things in it
A lot of talking and chatting in the game
Can't tell what that is though
Sorry, I'm not up to speed on all of my Japanese
What is this?
Maybe this is it
There's a limited edition of it coming out as well
I was trying to see if that would tell me what it is
Nope
Oh well
That's coming out on the PSP
And that's it for Japanese release dates
Dark Sakura, how about
Yeah, I just smacked the thing
How about The Old Kingdom
Well, on the 15th we have Final Fight Double Impact
We have Sam & Max The Devil's Playground Episode 1
The Penal Zone
And on the 16th we have
Samurai Shodown Sen
Grand Theft Auto 4
Episodes from Liberty City
And Splinter Cell Conviction
Just a few more stories for you guys
Then we're going to get into the classic game of the week
But first
A few more news stories for you guys
Loki
Yes, of course with the new update
3.21
That removes
Linux from the Playstation 3
Which is retarded
I'll just tell you right now
Yeah, you weren't here last week
I'm really curious about your thoughts on this whole thing
But you know, both Dark Sakura and I were kind of just like
Well, we haven't really used it
I mean, Dark Sakura is a Linux fan
So obviously she's disappointed
I don't know, what do you think?
Since Sonya made a big to-do about
Trying to patch it up, I'm not updating my system
Until I see what happens
Don't you kind of have to?
If you want to play anything online
Because it does that whole thing where it says
There is a system update available
If you want to connect to Playstation Network for anything
You have to upgrade
I don't connect to Playstation Network
Because I don't play anything on it
Well then you'll be fine, I'm just saying
I mean, even to like
Have the online leaderboards or anything
You can't play those without
Updating
Because my system wasn't updated
I haven't played anything on Playstation 3 this week
But I went into a game on there the other night
Actually I was showing a friend our little cameo
In the Namco Museum game
But that game wants to connect for leaderboards
And it was not working right
Because it needed me to update
That's when you unhook it from the internet
I'm just saying, you're going to be very limited
Until you update
I'm okay
Anyways, so what's important about this is
Apparently the guy GeoHot
Who has done different
Hacks on the iPhone
And whatnot
He's one of the first guys
Jail broke some of those I guess
Anyways
So he is
He put out a video
That shows him with the
A modded 3.21
System with actually
The option to install the other OS
Still, so basically
He patched out their patch
And just added the update or something
And he says it's very easy to do
But he also says that he's
Not going to necessarily program anything
So that people can
Build like
You know
At least the pirate stuff
But right now it's just doing it for the other operating system
But that makes me wonder
How long
Because it's just a matter of time
And in fact actually
His quote basically
He says
Basically saying that because of this
They've potentially turned
100,000 plus legit
Users into hackers
Because now they're going to try to find
They weren't caring before about trying to
Break it to add Linux to it
But now that they're removing it
They're going to be more diligent in trying to
Hack the PS3
Well it also just seems like no surprise that
You know this was cracked in minutes
You know
Is essentially what Sony did
Is they just released something that didn't like
Actually remove the feature
But just like remove the menu item
Or something you know
It sounds like this hack was so
Easy that this guy did
Like Sony didn't really take it out
They just took out your ability to access it
Well the PS3 and the PSP
For example their operating systems
Are very similar especially the way
Their patch files and stuff come over
That you know if you're familiar with the PSP
You're probably going to have an easy way
Around the Playstation 3
It's just there's certain things
That they haven't figured out yet
And apparently this guy has figured out ways
Around it
Now another kind of story that ties in with this
Is apparently there was a guy
A European PS3 owner who
Received I guess
A credit for
You know about 84 pounds
I guess
From Amazon because
He filed a complaint with the retailer
Saying that the firmware update
Violated some sort of
European law
Basically saying that the console
No longer performed as advertised
And you know and I do think that
Is something though I mean if you're putting
On the box or you had on the box
Right now they have all these slim systems and stuff
Just before you go there
In the US it's not on the box
I can't speak for the UK but I only know this
Cause last week on Bobby's show cause right before the call
He actually had the box and he said it's not on the box
Ok but still though
I don't know about the UK but this is the US
It was still a feature though that they advertised
And then I guess
But I guess you could say the same thing with
Playstation 2 backwards compatibility
It was something that you know
They removed from
Their new systems but it's not like
It was there on those systems
To begin with and then they took it out because
You know what hey we just don't want you to play
Playstation 2 games anymore
It's still no matter how insignificant
It is it still sucks
That they removed it because
I mean this is something
You may be paying for and granted it's not a feature
That I use but that'd be the same thing
If like oh well I don't really watch
Blu-ray movies on my you know PS3
And then they send a patch over that you know
Now prevents me from watching
Blu-ray movies
Granted it wasn't a feature I was using
It's still like you're removing a feature
Off the console
And yeah
People should be pissed because
Granted they're doing this for security reasons
But what if they
Find a way around you know
Something else
What other features are going to be removed
I don't know
It's just a case of a couple
Bad apples ruining the barrel I think
You know but I think it was a little silly for
You know I said this earlier but I think it was
Silly for Sony to put that feature in in the
First place
If they're closing it up because
Of piracy because Linux kind of lent itself
To piracy anyway and I'm not talking about PS3
Necessarily but everybody knew there was emulators
Out there for the NES and you know
But see now though with Linux
Installed on these systems they can sell you know
A ton of them to different like universities
Or whatever using them as number crunchers
It's an easy way to make up some console
Sales you know just uh
Hey look you can run Linux on it it's like a little
Portable super computer you know they're even
Saying oh yeah it's you know it's
A computer system it's not a game system
It's a computer system
You know when of course the rumors
Were that they were doing that to evade taxes
Or whatever but uh
Still though now you're
I don't know
It's
They can do whatever they want I guess because
Since you know then user license agreement
Anyways just basically says you're leasing the
Console from them so
If they want to take features away I guess they can
But I you know
As a consumer I will
Probably think twice when it comes to the next
PlayStation system that they are
Advertising you know can do such
And such things you'll probably think twice
You know hey
Move later because it doesn't go their
Way
It is very interesting that they can just
Kind of do that I mean I'm and we
All accept that because it's in the
Agreements that we you know hit
A to get through real fast you know
Hun the Xbox
It just seems
I don't know
Well and also if you ever
Happen to click no then you just
Don't get to use it right? Exactly
I don't know it just seems
It's just kind of
Sad there's nothing to protect me
It would be different if it was just
Connecting to their online service and I
Understand yes they can prevent you from
Going to their online service for whatever
Reason if they want you to update and you don't want to
Then fine you can't connect to their online service
But you know
Offline games if you pop in a game or
Whatever it will just automatically patch your system
Up anyways you can't just say
No I don't want to install this patch
It's going to do it regardless
And they do it obviously as a security feature
So that you know you can't go and hack
The Playstation 3 but
Whatever
Then maybe they should have figured out a way to be able to
Leave the operating system on there and not
Have it you know
Have access to whatever that's
On the Playstation 3 that you can apparently
Hack the system with
Alright
Well turning to something
That is an old
Standby and reliable and you know
These are always coming and not going to get taken away from you
Pokemon that's right
Taking a step over to the Nintendo systems
Pokemon obviously those
Other games the what was it
Gold and silver remakes were
Released not that long ago and they come with little
Trainers that were all over
PAX East well
The games were successful enough
Obviously I mean the Pokemon
Black and Pokemon White have been announced
Those are the newest games for the Pokemon
Series they are going to be
Coming out this fall in Japan for the
Nintendo DS that is
DS not the 3DS
So these are still games I mean obviously the 3DS
Will play them as we know about
The 3DS so far but these games are being
Developed for the DS
More info is supposed to come in the next few weeks but the game
Is supposed to be out in fall and I imagine we'll see some of this
At E3 as well even though
The logo design is gorgeous
Even though the games probably won't come out in America for some time
What is so gorgeous about the design for you?
I just like it I just really like it it's
Copping I have this thing for
Black and White
And just with the red Pokeball in the background I think it's
Actually really eye catching and really well done
It's very interesting that they decided
Just to go with Black and White
Like you know just very
Plain colors if you will
None of this like Ruby, Sapphire, Emerald
Black and White
Honestly I think using
Black and White is
I always thought of just using
Black and White as being more classy
Than going for the
Sparkly poo
So a classier more refined Pokemon?
I think so I think that it takes a lot more talent
I mean I just
I prefer things being
You know pretty clean
In how they're you know done
Honestly I like the logo
The fact that I can actually look at it
And read it right away
I was kind of impressed with myself
Act F in our chat room says the third version
Is going to be gray
Make it easy huh?
Uh yep so more Pokemon
I'm just kind of surprised this information
Is coming out so soon after the release of the games
We just had here but at the same time
We have to remember
This news was tailored for Japan not really
For the US and those games have been out in Japan
For some time it's kind of like the news about the 3DS
Came out what like the day
That the DSIXL was released here
Interesting
We can only learn from like you know another
Company that has announced a revision
To their system
Right as they're launching their system
Hmm
That hasn't happened before has it?
Oh wait no it has
Yeah
Bochi Kawa in our chat room says classy Pokemon
A squirrel in a top hat with a cane
Possibly
And Frisbee in chat says there's my problem
I don't know if I should buy black or white
Or wait for
Gray since it's inevitable
There will be a third version as well
It's like they have this stuff down to a
Science now how to milk the most money out of you
Pokey fans
I don't know I guess I'll buy it if it's good
I'm tempted for some weird reason I can't even
Explain to buy that DS one just cause it seems
So freaking popular
But I'll just have to shake the walking trainer cause you know
See gray will come out
On the 3DS
Maybe you never know
Alright well let's stop talking about the new stuff
I'm gonna send it to pay some tribute to the old stuff
Every week here on the show
We like to take a look at gaming's past
And take a trip to the classic vault
And look at the classic video game
Of the week where Dark Soccer will pick one game
From the archives and she says you know what
You ungrateful kids
Playing with your Pokeymans all day and collecting your mudkips
You should take some time out
To pay tribute
To those that paved the way for these games
It's the classic game of the week Dark Soccer
For the kids tonight
The game I have chosen is Samurai Shodown 2
Samurai Shodown 2
I'm starting with the sequel
I love this series so much
The Japanese title is
Shin Samurai Spirits
Haomaru Jigokuen
So it translates to
True Samurai Spirits Haomaru's Portrait of Hell
It is a fighting game
It does the big in and out scrolling
Depending on how far everybody is across the screen
It also has a bunch of easter eggs in it
Which I think is absolutely fun
And has the pow meter
Ooh pow
I actually own this game
On Mio Geo
I have the cartridge
Well technically I have the Japanese cartridge
But you know you can actually switch
Your country of origin on it
And it changes your blood to sweat
And back and forth
Like this is from the Japanese version clearly
Cause there is blood everywhere
It's white sweat for the US one
But this one had
Some of the best characters in it
Actually like
I have to say three of my favorite characters
Came about in this game
Is uh
Kibagami Genjuro
Who was Haomaru's rival
Cham Cham who replaced Tam Tam
The little cat girl
And she was fun
She had like the giant boomerang
And I don't know that she has been in anything else
She was fantastic
We had Nihot Saiger
Who was the
Oppression knight with the huge mungus gauntlet
Another one I liked was
Kathy Nicotine
Who was this little monk
He was so fun
He could turn himself into a statue
Kuroko
Who was a hidden boss in the game
Who was actually the little guy that wears all black
That waves the flags
If anyone who doesn't really know
So much about
I would say
Japanese theater
Kuroko is like
A stage hand
The person who goes behind the scenes
Wears all black
He's supposed to be invisible
He'll be like a prop or something
Or change scenery
It's a cool music video
That uses all that
It's a sister sister's video
I can't remember what song it was
Except that he's not on a black screen
He's just a dude in black
Hanging out by the scenery
It's like what I would do in Rocky
Before I was the curtain
Right
Yeah, Rocky used to climb up on me
A couple of times
Let's not give the listeners the wrong impression
Of our friendship
No
There was also
A new
Female boss in the game
Um
Named
Rashojin Mizuki
Yeah, Amakusa was not female
Amakusa was just a girly dude
Um
You also
Had a blocking
And a parry technique
Um
Basically
You would, you know, push
Against sword to sword, you'd lock
And then whoever came across it
Could get in a hit that was unlockable
And they actually
Borrowed that for Street Fighter 3
Well, the kind of parry thing
The parry thing in Street Fighter 3 was different
Um
You, um
There were cameos from other SNK characters
And different stuff would happen
My favorite easter eggs though
A weird little move that you could do
With each of the characters
That would make them chibi
They'd just be little chibi, cutesy versions
They would just show up chibi
I did one by accident one time
And I was like, dude, that's kinda cool
Um
It actually, um
It was better received than the first one
And the first one, don't get me wrong, was great
But this one just took stuff that worked
And made it even better
It seriously, to me
It's one of my favorite games ever
It's up there, I'd put this up there
In the top ten, probably one of my favorite
Fighting games ever
Um
As far as versions that came out
It only came out on Neo Geo
For like the longest time
Um
And then there was the Neo Geo CD version
Came out for Windows
And then
It actually, that version actually
Came out in the US
Um, there was a Playstation version that came out
In Samurai Spirit's Kenkaku Shinan Pack
Which, um, was the first two
And it only came out in Japan
And then the 2007 Tokyo Game Show
Um, there was an Xbox Live Arcade
And a PS2 Wii Anthology
Were announced
So
Um
It's
I, this is seriously
A fantastic game
It's one of, like I said, one of my favorites
And I think
Out of all of them, the only
Actually, no, I'd probably say that this one is my favorite
The only reason
That I would actually sometimes pick Samurai Spirit on three
Over two, sometimes
Is just to play as Rimuru
Cause she had the, um, the ice skin
Rimuru?
Bite Me Rob
That's her name, is Bite Me Rob
And then I'll go grab my cartridge in a second
That's it
Alright, there it is, your classic game of the week
Samurai Showdown 2
Not one, not three, two
But you'll probably see one and three
In future weeks
When Jamie starts running out of games
Cause you've been doing this a while now, gosh
This is probably, like, the 100th game of the week
Rob, you've seen The Vault
I know
I've got a couple thousand games in there
I'm not going to run out
Alright
Well, he's scraping the obscure if you really want to get to it
What are you going to do when you run out of Sega?
I don't think I'm going to run out of Sega
Alright, we'll see
Alright, anyhow
For now though, we're going to take a quick break
But we'll come back, there's still plenty more to talk about tonight
You know, we haven't even touched the big iPhone news this week
And yes, it does affect gaming
We're going to talk some Red Dead Redemption
Red Dead Redemption, Red Dead Redemption
That's like Hammer Rimuru
And we're going to talk about
Some of the Microsoft changes to live
That are going to be kind of interesting
Especially for those of you that like to play games on the computer
Talk about a lot of that
When we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio
So stick around, folks
We will be right back
And for those of you guys listening live tonight
On All Games Radio, we're going to take a quick music break
Stay tuned with us
Just a little bit of Poperia music tonight to listen to
We're going to be back in a few minutes
While we just take a second to rest our voices and so forth
With more of Orange Lounge Radio
We'll be right back
Welcome back everybody
To more of Orange Lounge Radio
On this Sunday night, April the 11th of 2010
We're joining you for our
362nd episode of the show
We're into Part B right now, the second half of our show
We have some rapid fire news coming up
And of course, Twitter topics
Just got a few more minutes to get those in
We already have quite a few though
If you want to ask us something on Twitter
And still some more news to get to
In tonight's program
Lots and lots of good stuff
Loki, why don't you kick it off with some rapid fire news
Yes, as it's been kind of a trend lately
There's been a lot of good games
Coming to the Xbox
Indie game service
And actually
Kind of not a stranger to
Doing some of these smaller
Indie games out there, Gameloft
They have decided to put a game on there called
Tank Battles
Actually it's pretty sweet
Kind of a high quality
Tank battling game
Almost like a souped up combat
If you will
And apparently it's kind of a port of
I want to say it's going to be a mobile game as well
And
Actually apparently it's been
Released last year on the Playstation
Network as Battle Tanks
Not sure why it hasn't been brought to
Xbox Live Arcade
Hey that's kind of cool anyways
How many of those games from the
Indie games have crossed over to regular
Xbox Live, hasn't there been like one?
Uh
Weren't they saying some time ago
That either there were going to be more that would cross over
To actual games or am I just
Making stuff up?
They do like a contest I want to say each year
And there's some that come out of that
But
Well no, they do a
Contest once a year
And they rarely port just one game from that
Um
But
I don't see a lot of them coming over the Xbox Live Arcade
But I don't really think it needs to because
Especially the ones that do win the
Contest they do get singled out
You can select I think
Contest winners or
Competition winners or whatever and you can actually see those
And then also of course now
With the new rating system and stuff
Um
It allows games that are actually pretty good
To make it to the forefront so people can sort through
All the hundreds of games that are on there
So um
It's not
Horrible, I don't know, it's getting better
That's for sure
Lots more games are coming out on there
Um
Now one game that we of course are not going to
Probably see on Indie games but
Perhaps an Xbox Live Arcade release
Or maybe something on the Playstation network
Who knows, um, Rocket Knight
Another game coming out
Of course you may remember Rocket Knight
I believe was an old Konami franchise
And um
Apparently this is going to be coming out soon
Um
Actually I believe in May
Which is pretty awesome
Not a series I can
Say I remember, maybe if I saw screenshots
It was um
I don't know if
It was like a 2D action game
And it will be coming to Xbox Live Arcade
PlayStation Network and Steam
And it was um, originally a 16 bit game
I want to see what was on like the
Super Nintendo
I don't know
But uh, yeah I don't know if the screen should
It's kind of souped up looking
So obviously the screenshots probably don't
Bring back any memories of the original game
But uh, looks neat
Alright, so that'll be coming out
Um
And then finally
Another Xbox Live Arcade game
Uh
And also going to be coming on Steam as well
Uh, Serious Sam HD
The second encounter is of course
Getting its um
Brand new HD remake I guess
And uh, should be coming
To Xbox Live soon
Um
They haven't really made an official date yet for
Xbox Live Arcade, but the Steam version is
Supposed to be coming out around
April 28th
And of course the PC version
On Steam will be available for
$17.99
And uh, I guess that'll be
If you pre-order it, otherwise
It's going to be $20
No word on exactly what it's going to cost of course
On um
Xbox Live Arcade, but probably somewhere around that
I mean $15
By the way, Rama in our chat room is clarifying
Just in case you didn't know, Rocket Knight Adventures
Was on the Sega Genesis
And the sequel Sparkster was on the
Super Nintendo and Genesis
So Sparkster was the original sequel
There you go
Alright, um, I got some other rapid
Quick stories for you guys
Couple items around Rock Band
Of course the weekly Rock Band releases
The songs that are coming out on Rock Band this week
Either on the 13th or the 15th
Depending on what system you're on
The Used will be releasing
The songs Blood on My Hands, Born to Quit
And The Taste of Ink
And some individual tracks from Surge Tunkian
Empty Walls and Sky is Over
As well as All Star
By Smash Mouth
If you haven't heard that song
500 times in 1999
You can hear it all over again
Speaking of 90's terrific things
Green Day is coming out
Of course with their own version of Rock Band
I did take a look at it a little bit
At PAX East, I didn't get to play it
But I saw other people playing it
And it definitely looked like the Beatles engine
But now they've replaced the Beatles with
You know, the punk guys of Green Day
So, you know, and giving it its own little spice
Obviously, the songs that will be in the game
I'm not gonna name them all, but I will just say
It almost looks like most of the
Dookie album, American Idiot
And 21st Century
Breakdown, almost like all those
Albums seem to be there, I mean there are some tracks missing
But big, big components of those albums
Otherwise, from
Warning, there's Minority and Warning
Nimrod has Hitchin' a Ride, Good Riddance, Time of Your Life
You know, when you need that slow jam
That quintessential goodbye song
Nice Guys Finish Last, then Insomniac has
Brain Stew, Jaded, and Geek Stink Breath
Geek Stink Breath
Downloadable content includes 21
Guns, and so forth
A few songs there
And then lastly for you guys, Squeenix
Has some Final Fantasy XIV updates this week
Including some of the races and clan
Information
Basically, your races can boil down into these
Different clans, so
You can play one of the not-Galka
But they're actually called Rogadins now
You can actually be like a
Sea Wolf Fisherman type of
Galka, I keep on calling them Galkas
But I guess they're Rogadins now
Or you can be like a fire type
Hellsguard clan, so it's like all the
Races now have clans too
So you have like a specialized sort of
Place that your race comes from
Well I'm glad they actually changed something other than the names
Well here's the other big thing is that
Some more information came out that's out there on the internet
And your characters have like first and
Last names now
A lot of instances play into
The game apparently
Where you get a lot of your own copy of the world
Dude, the game is sounding more and more like
Final Fantasy XI meets not Warcraft
But Guild Wars
Like I seriously think the game that they're making
Is like Final Fantasy XIV Guild Wars
Okay, that sounds playable
Just make it so I don't have to pay an online fee
Like Guild Wars and I'm there
Sadly I don't think that part, but there's screens from the alpha
That are leaking out there now and you can see
I'll have to show you the website here in Studio Loki
And Jamie if you want to see it too
Because your items are on like
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, like you push the button
To do the attack now
Like it's a little more wow-ish
Or Guild Wars was kind of the same way
So very curious to see how this plays out
Well as long as I can do it with a controller
Because I kind of miss playing with a controller
Well if they're developing it for PS3
Then I'm sure controller will be
I mean but it'll be weird because I don't know if you'll be able to
Put in just any old controller or what you'll have to do
Break out the old gravis pad, do it the old school way
It should be fine
We'll see what happens, more to come
When the beta for that is released
But meanwhile we just have stuff leaking out from the alpha
So I'll show you, while Jamie does her quick stories here
I'll pull up that website
That somebody texted me here in Studio
And show you guys the screenshots
And I'll post it in chat if anyone actually cares
Well some kid
Who is on Facebook
Plays Farmville
And used
Their parent's
Credit card to run up a
905 pound tab
Basically
About $13-1400
To
Pay for stuff
I guess he took his
Mother's credit card and put it in
And
Spent all that money
So they're trying to figure something out on it
I guess, I just think
I hate Farmville anyway
It's a waste of time
I know people like it, they want to do it fine
But if you got kids that play it, watch out for your
Credit card
Can I just interject something real quick
I know you don't watch a lot of TV
But this week South Park was awesome
Because they made fun of
Oh here's the screenshots of 14 by the way
You can kind of see with the little stuff at the bottom
Yeah it's very pretty looking
The Vulture 8 is dead ass up
You can see there
Just some people running around the world
It looks very pretty
South Park did a Facebook
Related episode this week and it was hilarious
But it was Facebook
For the first half and then it was Tron for the second half
Yeah I need to watch that one
It was pretty fucking funny I gotta say
So was it Face Tron?
Well it was one of those things where I gotta be honest
A lot of episodes of South Park have been like this lately
The first 15 minutes are
Really fucking funny when they're parodying
Something and they're doing it well
And then they decide to go this really like
ETF lol BBQ direction
For the last 15 minutes
That doesn't work so much
Like that's been kind of a pattern of South Park lately
Like the first 15 minutes are hilarious
And the second 15 minutes are not nearly as funny
And that's kind of sadly the Tron part
Not as funny as the rest of it
But I thought it was awesome they referenced it
I love Tron though
Namco Bandai is doing something really
Neat
We're getting Splatterhouse on
I guess they're doing
They're doing a new game
They got delayed and delayed
I was saying that
Sorry
Okay
As I was trying to say
They're doing a new Splatterhouse
And they're gonna put the original
Trilogy on
The disc
I guess this is a little fun compilation
To add on to that
It will have the original
Arcade version of Splatterhouse
As in the uncensored one
And then Splatterhouse 2 and Splatterhouse 3
That were the Genesis versions
So
That'll be pretty fun
Was this Herpographics one censored as well?
Cause I remember that being pretty
I have it but I haven't
Played it in so long that
I'd have to break it out and see
I don't recall it
Really being that censored
Really
And then
And then we have
For Xbox Live in April
Final Fight and Mega Man 10
Download Content
Basically
It's Final Fight Double Impact
And
That's gonna be on April 14th
And then
There will be
The Mall half-priced
On April 12th
And then two add-ons for Mega Man 10
Which is Base and Special Stage 1
Also known as Forte
Final Fight Double Impact
Next week
Or as I call it, Magic Sword
And some other little game
That I remember from a pizza parlor
I know I'm excited
There was no Xbox Live Arcade release this week
I don't think there was
And they tend to do that after their big huge
Promotions, then they go
Oh we just had this awesome promotion
And some old games on sale
But we just want to overlook that we have no new game this week
There's no new game this week
Because they're too busy shutting down
Xbox service
On April 15th
It's gone, it's out there
So get your taxes done
And get your last Halo 2 game in
Unless you're gonna play on PC from here on out
I hope we get a patch so we get our 100 plus friends now
It's weird though
Because they already had the big patch
For the USB support
This past week
I don't know if you heard
We were talking about it, I don't think we are
But you heard that uncrippled the hard drive
Set of consoles that got banned
Oh?
Yes, that patch did
Interesting, yeah I think that is interesting
Alright, I wanted to quickly
Answer some questions from chat
chat.orangewiseontraday.com
Frisbee's asking in reference to the South Park episode
What did you think about the chat roulette part?
Oh I forgot that they make chat roulette
I didn't even realize that was a real site
I actually had the check that I was like, holy crap that's a real site
The only way that I know that's a real site
Is that I've seen the YouTube of the guy
Well I've seen a couple YouTubes
The guy that does the piano
And starts singing the random songs
To the guys that come up on there
Which is really funny
And then there was a guy who dressed up like Lady Gaga
And did lip syncs
But he was like a really hairy guy
So it was really funny because it was obviously not a woman
And just all the people reacting to him
Was kind of funny
But yeah, you're not gonna catch me
I will die before I will go on chat roulette
Like I've never been to the website
Penis, penis, penis, penis
I thought it was funny but it was kind of one of those things
Where the joke got old
And then they kept saying it like over and over again
For like another three minutes
And I was like, okay, I'm over it
But yeah, chat roulette, not a site
I mean god, I'm barely on AIM and Skype
Why would I go on chat roulette and talk to strangers
I can't even talk to my friends online
I'm not gonna go on chat roulette
Alright let's get to some Twitter topics
Every week we let you guys ask questions on Twitter
It seems like every podcast does this now
I don't know, like I've been listening to more podcasts
Everybody has a damn Twitter segment now
I'd like to think we were one of the first
It's like we were one of the first Skype shows
But whatever
It's awesome because it's our listeners
And they ask some crazy asked questions sometimes
And share some stories with us
That we might otherwise miss on the show
That's the other very important thing
Retertainment asks, games to play while drunk
Games to play while drunk
And go
I'd play DDR drunk
Rock band if Jamie's party yesterday
Was any indication
I wasn't really drunk
You weren't drunk
Yeah any type of karaoke game
Is always funnier when drunk
Why are you aware of the Wii
I think a lot of Wii games
Are kind of funnier when you're drunk
But just be careful
There's a difference between funny and hurting yourself
That goddamn unicorn game
That Loki always fucking plays during the show
I'm sure is better when you're drunk
He's playing right now
Robot unicorn attack, there you go
Agdeft says Konami is distributing
Latin American made game
Lucha Libre AAA Heroes Del Ring
In America
Ironically it's not coming out in Mexico
I don't know, maybe another developer is putting it out there
I don't know, but if you like your
Mexican wrestling, which it is kind of a niche thing
But it's pretty cool
Yeah and it's actual stars of AAA wrestling
El Eligido
Abismo Negro Psycho Clown
Electroshock, and Charlie Manson
There's a wrestler named Charlie Manson
That's a little close to a certain
Serial killer
So there you go
You might remember Konami
This isn't the first time they put out wrestling games
Oh no, they had Rumble Roses
Remember Rumble Roses?
What's your favorite Xbox game?
I wanted to play that actually, it's a game that Dan would never pick up
But I really wanted to play it
You could probably get it now for like $3
I think I saw Dead or Alive Volleyball
Or whatever for like $10 the other day
Hey, that was fun
There's a game to play when drunk
We've got to
And yes, I've watched Dan play it while I was drunk
Portal Drunk, instant throw up
SSJ100Matt on his Twitter account says
Not so much a story, but a question for Loki
Are you paying attention Loki?
He's playing the unicorn farting game
Well he just crashed the unicorn, so here we go
What's your opinion on the kid that was caught
Trying to steal the game Breach at PAX East?
Well it was a good attempt I guess
But he got caught
Don't compliment him
Nice try kid
He doesn't deserve a compliment
It was a stupid asshole thing to do
Yeah, well his reasons were retarded
It's like, I just want to play this with my friend
Well
No, you wanted to brag that you had the game
Is what you wanted to do
And unfortunately you're stupid and you got caught
So now you're going to face fines and jail time
And all that stuff
Hope it was worth it
I'm going to say he probably shouldn't have done it in the first place
Just taking a lucky stab in the dark
Well he shouldn't have, but you know
He wanted to make a name for himself
It's kind of surprising that he had the balls to do it
And then not show up to his court date
That was pretty fun
Hilarious
He was too busy playing on Chat Roulette
No, he was playing Modern Warfare 2
Was he really?
Spazinator, a PSN on Twitter
Actually tells us
Samurai Shodown 2 was also on Xbox Live Arcade
It was released there last year
That's right
I don't remember if Jamie said it
Sometimes people tweet us while she's doing that
Yeah, I remember
I played it for a little bit, but I got to admit
I was not as big on Samurai Shodown
I was talking about Samurai Shodown 2
The one that was released on Xbox Live Arcade
But that was not the series
I was really as into on Neo Geo
I was more of a Fatal Fury person
I have Fatal Fury Special
Then after that
I would go with Art of Fighting
Then maybe Samurai Shodown
Because I like Katori Hanzo
ActDeft says DJ Hero's price
is now down to $50 at Toys R Us
and links us to a new story about the price reduction
Not surprised
That didn't move as well as they did
Now would be a good time to pick that up
for DJ Hero 2
If you want to get the controller
and have it for DJ Hero 2
They also have, if you really want to spend the money
They have these new bundles now that have two
DJ Hero controllers with the game
It's a good game
It's a bummer they didn't support the download content better
Because they could have done better
I'll pick up the sequel
Don't get me wrong, it's an awesome game
It's just typical
of Activision and their support
for the download content
If you've seen what they do for the Guitar Hero series
It's not a big surprise that we only have
three pieces of download content
Dark Tetsuya says
I just realized we haven't heard from the ferret in a while
What ever happened to him?
When we moved the show to Studio Dark Sakura
The ferret didn't really come with us
I found it while moving
So the ferret is at my place right now
Don't forget we have other mascots here
We have that stupid Dalek
That I don't think is funny at all
We also have Shirmi
Who makes a pretty awesome mascot
Remember, Shirmi shit on the floor
When we were talking about that PlayStation show The Tester
Well good, I'm glad
But that was her opinion, she was critiquing
Wait wait wait
Ferret was, oh god my ears
Ferret was better
Ferret or Dalek?
I say ferret
Ray Ayanami says
No I'm sorry I skipped one
Spaznator also sent, usually I don't do two tweets
But I will allow it tonight
Rob you asked about a month ago if I seen The Tester
Finally seen it, I have similar thoughts on it
You know I stopped watching it
I heard it ended finally
And I'm pretty sure
Season 1 ended
Oh god are they doing another one?
Well anyhow I'm pretty sure the person I thought
Was gonna win won
You know I would go on season 2 of The Tester
Why not?
I mean they probably tape it over a weekend
And you get $5,000 for winning
I mean I probably wouldn't keep the job
But I'd like to have the $5,000
That'd be pretty awesome
It might be a fame whore, why not?
That even won The Tester, what do you think?
Go Xbox
I don't know, I quit
Might be fun for the experience
It sucks, I don't wanna play Ipet
Alright Ray Ayanami says
Oh whoops that was a personal tweet here
Just it had at o-l-r in it here
Shadow Sniper says your thoughts on Hitman 5
And what you would like to see in the new game
There's a Hitman 5?
I didn't even know there was a Hitman 5 coming out
I didn't play Hitman 1 through 4
It's not really my type of game, Loki that's more of your alley
No, it's a stealth
Action game so that's not really
My forte
What would I like to see in the new game? Lots of sex and violence
That always makes for a great video game, right?
Not Timothy Orphan, whatever his name is
Yes and more lesbians
Tigerclaw305
Tweet says
GTA is being shown to school children to teach them
About violence and links us to this
News story here from vg247.com
That
Apparently great school children
Are shown imagery from Grand Theft Auto
It's in the UK
And they're showing it to children between 9 and 11
And they're trying to keep them from being
Desensitized to violent behavior
And teach them consequences
By the way they also show them
The Itchy and Scratchy show from the Simpsons
What?
Like I had to check to make sure this wasn't dated April 1st
Fight, and fight, and fight, and fight, and fight
Fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight
Just a guess but
I don't think you show people violence to get them
Not desensitized to violence
That kind of
Is, you know, the opposite of what you want to do
You know what they did when I was young to scare the shit out of me
And this wasn't necessarily about violence
But it was violent
And it was about the responsibility of having a driver's license
Is they'd show us red asphalt
Oh we laughed through that
That's, you're not supposed to laugh
It's disgusting
I actually don't think I've ever seen red asphalt
I would like not watch it
Like I just would kind of look away and not really watch it
It was disgusting
Remember that every 15 minutes, you know, they'll teach you about drunk driving
I'm like, you're wasting so much time
I don't care
I get it
This person had alcohol
This is a drunk driving accident
It's sad, it happens
Why do I have to sit here for two hours while you talk about it?
They didn't do that at my school
Did they actually drink?
No they didn't, here's what they did
This is great
And this is from how I understand that they did it
It could be a little different
Okay, first they came out on our
You know, our football field
Because we had our stadium and whatever
They had everybody sit there and they had this
Big thing covered up with a tarp or something
So they pulled the tarp off
And it's this horrible car accident
Like this person mangled or whatever
Of course it's just a person with makeup on and whatnot
And then an ambulance comes
And they realistically
Pull them out of the wreckage and stuff like that
And then
Later on
Was it like one of the students?
Yeah, it was one of the students
It was somebody, animal
And then later on they had this grim reaper
Walking around the entire day
And in 15 minutes they would take a student
And pull them out of class
And they were basically dead
And they wouldn't be there for the rest of the week
Or however long it was
You had to get out of school for a week?
Okay, but no
It's like punishment basically
And I don't know if
Wait, punishment?
What did you do to get the grim reaper to tap you?
Oh, Matt didn't do his homework, you come with me
Kid
You're a drunk driver
This is entirely accurate because
It's really fucked up if it is
Um, basically they took
Them to like some sort of location
A cabin or whatever
And made them write notes to their parents or something like that
About like
Dear mom, I am dead
I died at school today
Hello dad, I'm in hell!
Basically they said that they told their parents that they died
Or something like that
That's a horrible thing to do to your parents
Can you imagine if I wrote
I had to write a letter to my mom
Hi mom, I died at school today
The grim reaper took me out of class because I drank a drug
They didn't
They wrote letters to their parents later on
About stuff like that
Apparently the impression I was under
Is that the
The police went to their house
And told their parents that they were dead
You know
Shouldn't they be out trying to catch
Real drunk drivers?
Anyways, you know what they did at my school?
They would have the really mean, fugly PE teacher
Come in and say
If you drink and drive
You're gonna go to jail
And you're gonna stay there forever
And you're gonna have a criminal record
And if you drink and drive, you're an idiot
It took five minutes
I understand that and that makes perfect sense
Not only did we have to sit through this two hour long
You know
Accident thing
And them talking about
Every fifteen minutes and stuff
For another assembly
Where these people were crying
Their parents were crying, I thought Billy was dead
And all this stuff
It was annoying
So that's why I've learned about drunk driving
Is that it's absolutely annoying
The crap you have to deal with if you do it
So, don't do it
Because you'll get two assemblies that you'll have to sit through
No, but honestly though
I mean, duh
Drunk driving impairs you and you can die
Okay, or kill somebody
I mean, any sane person
That has some sort of common sense
Gets that
However, nowadays, kids are not being raised with common sense
So, it's no wonder that they have to have
Multiple assemblies
In order for this to sink in
And even then, it's just not going to
Well that's okay, I'm just gonna
Smoke pot instead
That's better
I'm not drinking and driving at all
Fuck you, Grim Reaper
What were we talking about before?
I don't remember
I was trying to see if they had that clip
That I remember from the 90s
That was, uh
Yeah, I think it's this
This was very much like what they did at my school
I think it's this clip
So, Beavis and Butthead
I understand Mr. McVicar has made
A little arrangement with you guys
Yeah, a little probation
You see, class Beavis and Butthead
Here are not allowed to laugh
For a whole week
That's right, and if they do laugh
They'll be expelled and they'll have to
Go to Hope High School where they'll get
Their asses kicked on a daily basis
By all the other delinquents
Yeah, okay, so
Well, I was real glad to hear that
Because this is Sex Education Week
Oh, here we go
That's right, Sex Ed Week
We're gonna be talking about the penis
We'll be talking about
The vagina
Do you think that's funny, Butthead?
Do you find it amusing that we'll be talking
About the testicles?
Yes, we're also gonna be talking
About venereal disease
Sexual intercourse
And we will definitely
Be spending a lot of time
Talking about masturbation
Laughing
That's what they did at my school
See, this is the type of letter
Actually, that they had to write
For the every 15 minutes program
Dear Mom and Dad, every 15 minutes someone dies
As a result of an alcohol related collision
Today I died and I never got the chance
To tell you blah blah blah
And that's what made them all upset
It was annoying, trust me
If you go through high school
Just get the gym teacher in there for five minutes
Scare the hell out of everyone
Do you want to see me again?
We have some other tweets
MNZeba
Follows that with a question about Pokemon
RO
Plugging the old
Pokemon RO telling us
That you can actually win a beta account
Apparently they're doing a little thing there
But the thing they linked us to didn't work
But here's my thing
For some reason the link didn't work
But here's my question about Pokemon RO
Didn't one of these Pokemon operations get shut down recently?
Like there was a Pokemon MMO going on?
Like I'm just saying
I hope it doesn't get shut down
I wouldn't like to see that happen to this
But I'm just saying if Nintendo did the other one
Just be careful kids
I've seen some of the in-game stuff
That looks pretty
Ragnarok-y, pretty good
Alright anyhow
That's it for Twitter topics tonight
Thank you guys so much for the tweets
And sorry I didn't get to everything
Well we had to play the clip from Beavis and Butthead
Twitter.com slash OLR if you want to follow us in the future
Alright Giovedea in our chatroom says
I took a college class where we had to yell
tits, ass, penis, vagina, and all that
on the first day of class
Sex education in college is actually a lot of fun
And it's educational
So those of you kids that are about the college age
Just take it, it's fun
We actually had in our class
They brought a transsexual
person in one day
Not a transvestite
We actually had to learn the difference
Transvestite is someone who just dresses
for fun and you know for
whatever
And a transsexual is someone who believes they are
the other gender
and is the ones that actually get the operations
So they had a transsexual come in
Teacher shut the door and said, okay for the next hour you can ask
anything you want and this person has agreed to
answer any gross
curiosity, whatever you've ever wanted to know
now's time to ask it
So they asked everything
Everything
But it was a highly educational day, I'll tell you that
Our 6th
grade sex ed
was hilarious because they didn't really have
We had a female teacher so the female teacher
took the girls and explained the girls stuff
And then apparently
some kid's father
was the person we had
teaching the male portion of it and the guy
was a pervert
And that was funny
Yeah they used to split up the class for us too
And then the teacher found out
the guy was a pervert
And that was the end of sex ed
You guys might find this
funny but when I was in sex ed
You know what test I did
We had like 6 different tests throughout class
Do you know which test I got the lowest score on?
Out of all the tests that they gave out in class?
Male anatomy? No
Vagina week
You'd find that funny
I thought y'all would get a kick out of that
I find that ironic
Hey gaming
news once in a while
It happens
believe it or not we talk about
video game news on this program
Oh god what happened to this show
Loki?
So what's kind of neat is there's a rumor
that Microsoft's live support
is coming to the free games that you get
with Windows. Yes you may remember
all those wonderful classics as
Solitaire, Minesweeper,
Chess, etc. Some of these
I have never heard of I guess because I don't have
Windows 7 like Purple Place
Purple Place! Yeah it's one of the new
Windows 7 games
And Windows has Mahjong now?
Yep
It's on Vista
It's on Vista and 7
It's basically the old Shanghai game but
you know now Microsoft brand
So I wonder if
that means
apparently they're gonna not only get achievements
but chat and leaderboard support
So now I can chat with people
while playing Solitaire and have leaderboards
Wow
Interesting that they're gonna integrate this
Well you know Solitaire is a huge game
on Windows I mean it's probably the number
one Windows game above
anything else you can think of
WoW, Halo
anything you can think of
Solitaire is probably a bigger game then
Yeah
So I mean if you want to and probably Minesweeper
to some extent too so if you want to enable people
so to speak or get them on board early
I suppose this is the way to do it
It just seems, I don't know, a little weird
But that's gonna be kind of interesting if I can
further inflate my E-peen
score with the
you know
Should have been working now, achievement
Played Solitaire between
the hours of 8am and 5pm, achievement
unlocked
Anyhow
Microsoft of course isn't the only one
that has a gaming network that is continuing
to grow and develop but another
big company is launching their own game network
It's Apple, that's right
One of the big things that was announced as part of the new
iPhone 4.0 OS
is Game Center
Game Center is going to be a single
online gaming experience
for the Apple devices
that will kind of link all these games together
You'll be able to invite and track friends
You'll have matchmaking with this, leaderboards
and achievements, that's right
it's very own achievements
What's kind of interesting about this
is that systems like this already exist
somewhat in Apple's world
I don't know if any of you guys grabbed the
Commodore 64 emulator
that's available on the Apple, it was free a couple
days ago, I think just for like last
weekend, so I grabbed it
It uses a technology called OpenFaint
which I believe is by the people who made Aurora
faint, which was one of the
very early early iPhone games that was
out there, that was the same type of thing
Somebody to develop like this platform
Well what happened is that now you have
OpenFaint and you have these other competing
platforms as well, and so
Apple has finally just decided to step in and say
you know what, actually, I think
we're going to do our own thing
Not just to steal a good idea
but I think to kind of
they probably see what's happening with the developers
and that more and more game developers want to be on OpenFaint
or something like this, so Apple probably just
wants to standardize it across the board
and have ownership of it
It affects their branding
I think, so
Yeah, and as much as you want to kind of say
they're big and evil for wanting to basically
shut down OpenFaint, well they're not really shutting down
OpenFaint, but they're really
trying to render it irrelevant, although
I'm sure OpenFaint will still be around for some things
I think Apple is very
big on consistency
Hence why they have such a rigid review
thing for apps
You know, there's a reason why your apps
all kind of look and feel the same
It's because it's not like you get to make
whatever buttons you want
There are limitations to what you get to do with apps
And I think it's to give consistency
And so I think Apple
wants to take kind of reign of this
to bring that same consistency because it works well
for them
But of course there's always that controversy
because they don't really publish a lot of those guidelines
on what exactly they look for when they screen things
Yeah
By the way, some other things that were announced that will affect
gamers on the iPhone, I mean obviously
there's multitasking was the big thing, although
I got a 3G, so I'm
screwed on that one, I'm not gonna get that
Hopefully they announce a new iPhone in June
because I'm eligible for an upgrade in October
It works for the 3GS
It will work for the 3GS, but I wanna
I know Apple, there will be another
newer, nicer iPhone within
the year, so I gotta hold out
for that
They've got that in common with Nintendo, don't they?
So, yeah
I really, really, really wanna get an iPad
because I'm a big fucking sheep
But I'm gonna wait, I'm gonna wait till next year
because I just know that camera
on the front will be on next year's iPad
Well, Dan and I were actually
talking about how we both want
one, but we're specifically gonna
wait until another generation
goes by
And then we're
probably gonna get them
Also, by the way, just so you know,
not just the multitasking, voice over
IP in the background, like you can have Skype
running and get calls on Skype, it's pretty neat
And, again, no, not on 3G
And folders to
organize your stuff better, which
is actually really helpful
See, I think a lot of what they're incorporating, though, is stuff that they've actually stolen
from the jailbreakers
Yeah, I'm not surprised
My friend's got a jailbroken iPhone, and
it's got folders and all kinds of stuff with it
and he can use it as a storage device
and it's kinda crazy
And what was the other one?
Oh, ads, the iAds, now they're gonna
have, Apple's gonna have its own ad platform
because I guess they just didn't like AdMob
No, it's not that they didn't like it
They wanted a piece of it, but no flash
Also, it's very
interesting, I don't want to get too techy on you guys
but it's very interesting how Apple is
kind of kicking down Adobe
and they're also kicking down Google
Like, did you know that they are taking out
I mean, you still will be able to
search on the new
iPhone 4.0 OS and you can use
Google as a search engine, but the button
will not say, like it says Google
right now, it doesn't say anything else
But they're opening it up for you to use Bing
Yahoo, whatever
That sounds pretty cool
I guess
I do like the stuff that's coming
with the 4.0 OS, you know, I'm a little bummed
that it won't work on my phone, but at the same time
I'm getting a little irritated with my phone
It locks up, it's slow
I don't know, I might need to wipe it
and reinstall everything, I don't know what the hell is
making it run so crappy
But yet, here I am, still a sheet, but I will
Could it be the Apple created CPU inside
of it?
No?
I might have all these problems, but at the end
of the day, dang, I'll tell you, I use my
iPhone so freaking much
It's a great little device to have in my pocket
I will say that
Anyhow, let's move on, something non-Apple
related, Dark Sakura
Well, there are some pretty big Final Fantasy
fans out and about
And there's one person who's doing a very
interesting translation of it
They are doing Final Fantasy in
um, Latin
Yeah
Um, it's of course
going to be a ROM with a patch, but it's
in Latin
Okay
That's hardcore
It just makes me think of Eddie
as they're talking about being mugged
and saying something to them in Latin, going
Oh no, he knows Latin, run!
But I like the little
line that uh
Excuse me
I must be allergic to Latin
Um, that Destructoid has in their
little article about it, it says, now can I get a copy
of Alundra in Esperanto?
Nice
Isn't Esperanto like a
completely made up language, like it's not something
that is like It was meant to be a universal
language, so it takes elements from different
I see And actually
it's, I'll tell you what Rob, you
can look right now at a page in Esperanto
and get an idea of what they're talking
about I see, because it derives
a little bit from every language Exactly
Well that's kind of neat And I know people who are
learning it, so That's cool It sounds
cool I had a friend that spoke
it actually, it was interesting to hear
I want to call her
in Esperanto
I do not, because I have to
talk to the call, Jamie if somebody calls
in Esperanto, you're talking to him
Uh, see
See, no
Anyhow
Loki
Something in English please
Uh, yes, Fear 3
has been announced, coming from
Warner Brothers, and
what's kind of neat about the new
franchise in this horror
shooter game, is actually
it's going to be
including cinematics created by
John Carpenter
The legendary horror
master himself
What's also cool, they're going to be having
the writer Steve Niles working
on it as well, he co-wrote
the script I guess, for the game with
Carpenter, and
Steve Niles you may not remember, he also did
I believe the vampire movie
30 days a night
So, pretty good pedigree there
and I know the franchise has been pretty good
Hell, Fear 2 had some pretty awesome
multiplayer in it, especially with like
all the maps, with like the Toy
Soldier maps
and the theme song for that trailer
which I still can't get out of my head
So
Looking forward to it, and no
timeframe yet when it's been announced
It's supposed to be scheduled to be coming out in the fall
probably around November, so
on Playstation 3, Xbox 360, and PC
Is this a game you'd probably pick up?
I haven't played the other ones
I've been kind of curious
to check it out, especially
number 2, but
maybe I'll check it out, I don't know
Well, more information coming out on
Red Dead Redemption
Of course this game was also shown off at PAX East
That was probably one of those other games that
you would have liked to see
Well, they announced this week that multiplayer
Free Rome is going to be a feature in Red Dead Redemption
I believe that's also in Grand Theft Auto 4, correct?
It's something similar
It sounds very similar to
Free Mode in
Grand Theft Auto 4, but this one's
I would say it's closer to
Party Mode in Grand Theft Auto 4
where you can join in
Let me describe it a little bit here
You can explore the full single player game world
but you'll be in a multiplayer environment
Remember Test Drive on
Xbox? It's kind of like that too
But it's separate from the single player story mode
So in Free Rome, you can either
go in by yourself, or you band together with
friends, it's together in 8
and then you can take on other little bands
You can either hunt down criminals together
or just shoot the shit out of each other
16 players in the same lobby
at once. Then you get experience points
as you do these different multiplayer modes
50 levels of character progressions
The new XP will unlock new weapons,
mounts, characters, and challenges
It sounds very similar to the Party Mode
in Grand Theft Auto 4 because you can basically
jump into
It's like a lobby
but it's basically just a portion of
the Grand Theft Auto map and if you really want to
you can just hang around in the lobby and
drive all over the entire map
or do whatever. So this is going to be
very similar to that where you can
play more of a free form version of the game
Plus they have areas where it will
launch different things like deathmatch modes
or hunting or
I believe there's a
capture the gold type
mode in there
It'll be very cool
I'm looking to try to mod this game to put
a car into it
I know the engine that they're using
is probably extremely similar to
Grand Theft Auto and if it's anything
like that game was set up it should be
very easy to do something similar like that
You and your freaking hacks
It would be hilarious. Always hacking something
rocket launchers or something
Alright, well let's get to the segment
of the show that doesn't involve cars
or bringing things
into places they shouldn't be except spam
we do get a lot of spam that shouldn't be in the
mailbag at orangelandtrader.com
mailbag at orangelandtrader.com is our email address
for you to send your
emails to every week. We read our favorites here
on the show and respond to them
DarkSakura likes to dive into the mailbag
and pull out some of her favorites and read them
right now. Again, mailbag at orangelandtrader.com
if you would like to participate sometime
dsmaster26
sent an email
Try not to sound too excited about it
It's um
very badly written and
it's giving me a headache so I think I might just
translate it into real English
Okay, go for it
I could try and read it the way
it's written
I could do it
Okay, as it's written
Dear C4 and O.L.R. Crew
I am giving
a giant F.U.
to is Microsoft because of them
raping me
in the ass for 50 bucks
Okay, I can't take it anymore, translate please
Okay, um
Dear O.L.R. Crew, I'm giving a giant F.U. to Microsoft
because of them raping me in the ass for 50 bucks a year
That is crap
I should have bought a 360
I should have bought
It's spelled B.O.U. not B.A.U
Bought the PS3
At least you should have instead of should of
I hate that
It is should have, would have, could have
So he doesn't get an F
He gets a D-
So thank you for at least avoiding one of my pet peeves
Um, here are the reasons
why
Okay
Cry
No, it's
region is R-E-G-I-O-N
Not R-E-G-I-N
Um, locking
new Beatmania to DX17
Free online play
No cost
Netflix without paying for PSN
And finally
That's all wrong
And finally, five, um
Bluetooth, okay, god this sucks
Punctuation
Do you speak it?
Thank you
Many phones have Bluetooth
Therefore, therefore ends in an E
by the way
I can use the headset for both my phone
and PS3
I'm wondering
Is it, I
I'm wondering if you have any suggestions for
Bimani titles for PS3 and 360
Please help, I'm on a Bimani binge
ever since I played 2DX17
at the arcade in Omaha
DS Master 26
There's really not a lot available on the
360 and PS3, I will tell you
no way in hell should you spend any money on Beat and Groovy
Honestly, I like DJ Hero
a lot, I know that's not Bimani technically
but as far as music game goes
it's really the best with
Rock Band
Like if you're looking for like DDR and stuff
there's just not a lot of great stuff
You can go for Dance Dance Revolution Universe
and I would say Universe 2
is probably the best of the series
You can get Universe 3 very easily though
but it's on the
auto games or whatever
Karaoke Revolution
if you like that kind of stuff
Not my favorite
And if you really want the true Bimani experience
that they've brought to you straight to the next gen system
then Rock Revolution is definitely a title for you
That'll basically tell you
what they think of the new systems
There's a PS on here
Okay
If he does a perfect attack and freestyle DDR match
he will go down, not bloody likely
How do you perfect attack a freestyle?
I think he means
a perfect attack and then
a freestyle
I've seen people do both
The guy who had one leg
Did he even play DDR anymore?
There was a guy who had one leg
that played on crutches that perfect attacked
while he did a freestyle
You know I haven't asked him
to listen to this show though
so maybe he can email us and tell us
I think he still kind of follows it
He does a lot of DJ'ing
gigs and stuff
Not DJ Hero but real actual DJ'ing
I know that's a big hobby of his now
Where are they now?
That would be a fun segment to do on OLR
someday
Where are they now? Bimani favorites
Where is Jahi?
I haven't heard from Jahi in a long time
Maybe we need to do this
on OLR special
Maybe for our anniversary
Find Bimani people from back in the day
and do a where are they now segment
A lot of our newer listeners
wouldn't understand
Who cares?
I broke out the orange bat
I know you did
Have you seen Wendell lately?
I heard he lost a lot of weight
He's looking pretty good
He's in good shape
You know what we should do? Let's plan this
By the way Wendell, I'm very proud of you
Our 8th anniversary would be the last week of June
We should try to find as many
old school Bimani players
as possible and invite them to a show
and we could tape it
Step Squad RTF reunion?
We wouldn't necessarily have to do it here
We could find a place to remote broadcast
We could go to Sweet Tomatoes
I don't know, we'll have to find a big space
That used to be where we'd all meet up to go to dinner
years and years ago
We'd go to Sweet Tomatoes and Concord
and figure something out
We're gonna do that
for our next anniversary show
Number 9
I should go on DDR for you, you can post something
NorCal famous DDR players wanted
for a reunion special or something like that
That'd be fun
I keep a lot of them on my Facebook
I swear, because there are too many people to have here
and I don't have a big garage anymore
Dave and Busters
We could do a road show
I'm set up to do that because of PAX
We could do a road show and on top of that
We just couldn't do that live
Actually, all contrary
I may have my Wi-Fi tether
on my phone working
They have a Wi-Fi tether for the 3GS
That would be tough to do
96k to all games, that would be tough
on a Wi-Fi tether
I don't know
If anybody knows how to do it, Scott probably does
because I think he's done it before
I'll talk to him about it
We'll see
Also, now
I had received the first email
that you sent me before
but I've just been so wiped out and busy
The man
that I met at the Atari party
Sal
He sent an email and he sent me
some stuff that I want to play
Was that the music guy?
I totally want to interview him
If I was not flat broke
I want to order one of the systems
that he's got
The name's for the
Atari 800 XL
Working on Outrun
Has a version of Space Harrier
that's actually really sweet
Complete with voice, by the way
I'm very impressed
I'll go ahead and give him a plug
It's
KJ Mann's
Atari Sales and Electronics
You'll find him on eBay
He's really cool
The stuff
The ports that he's worked with
are just amazing
They're amazing
I'm very impressed
We'll try to get him on the show
It'll be fun
We'll get him to come to this OLR Con
we're suddenly planning
I wonder how much it costs to rent
a big hall somewhere
Maybe we should call it OLR Con
Just do OLR Con, for real
Just fucking do it already
My brain just suddenly made
OLR Con asylum
I don't know
We'll have to think about it
How could we do OLR Con and not have it fail miserably
where we're going to spend a lot of money on it
I don't know, we have to think about this
I think it's King of Rush
Okay
Why was Rob's mom
pwning all of us with that last phrase?
That must have been texted or something
during the show
Cause she's my mother, it's where I get my sense of humor from
And don't you dare
be trash about her
Rob's mom is such a nice lady
She's fun
So, I got one from Rababa
That's an Orange Lounge
radio
wordle
And, dude, I love
anything that's typography
Oh, I saw that, it's like the art
with all the common words from our
website, kind of like if it's used
a lot, then it's big, if it's not
B4U
B4U, at the time he did that
was like being highlighted
as like the, I love that song
You know that segment, the Dark Tetsuya in Act F
that some people do for our site?
I think B4U was like the song
that was up at the moment that that happened
I'm totally going to save the pictures
I mean, it's generated in Flash, but I have this
There's this little
fun tool to grab
images off by doing
just a plain old screenshot of it
You can crop them, I love this thing
and I'm trying to remember, I think it's called Pixlr
It's a plug-in for
um
whatever the crap this program is
that I'm using
But anyway
Um
But yeah, it's really cool, I like it
And
he
I like, he puts a comment that I suppose
that wordle filters out crashwords
Um, and
then the last one is
um
from somebody
who hasn't put a name on here
I'm just going to say Brandon
because that's the
closest thing I can find
Dear OLR, after listening to OLR archive episode
I have started
to have a bimani craze
so I spent my whole allowance
$30 on tokens
and I played some BeatMania 2DX, read
Cranked
to 11
Guitar Freaks, Drummania
Parapara, DDR, Poppin' Music
and keyboardmania, it was epic fun
Rob,
we need to go
to Rviggle soon
We can go, I mean
it's just down the street
I know, but I want to play
Rob, I gotta dance
Alright
Well anyhow, let's move on
to the part of the show
where we get a little bit of angst off our
chest, it's the FUs of the week
and they're going to start right now
FU to the
big pile of
carrot cake in my fridge
I
have eaten almost nothing but carrot cake
all day, except when I came home
and ate a rib
I ate a rib
Oh, and some chips
It was very tasty rib, it was delicious
and I think
he got kosher beef too
anyway, it was really good
but anyway
I can't
I can't eat any more cake
I can't, I don't think that I can
and my
my tummy behaved
very well yesterday despite all the beer
I think all the beer broke everything else down
but today I'm suffering for it, so
fuck you gluten
done
Go ahead Logie
FU to the KFC
special sauce that they put on the
KFC Double Down, it really
ruined the Double Down and it's unfortunate
because it had the potential to be
a great, unhealthy piece of
chicken that I could have eaten
but instead it was
just all nasty sauce that they tasted
maybe next time I will have to do
the pseudo
Windows 7 burger and get a 7x7
from
Oops, Holik came in early, my bad
I was gonna say that
FU to Holik, playing early
anyways, yeah, so
a
I should do a Windows
7 pseudo burger
from In-N-Out 7x7
I've had a
4x4 before, they're really
not as filling as you would think
My FU
of the week goes to my confidence
and self esteem because I'm starting a new job
tomorrow and I'm really nervous
it's gonna be like so
different for me, they're all gonna laugh at you
laugh at me, no, I know I'll do fine
but it's just, it's weird because like guys
seriously, the day job I've had, I've been
because, okay, it was funny because when
I post, I have listeners on my Facebook and when I
posted to Facebook that I was leaving my old
job, people were like, oh, you get to do OLR full
time now and I'm like
hahaha
hahaha, that's funny
yeah
no, I mean, it's
great that people think that we could actually
profit from this show, but no, my
day job that I do
the day job I have to pay them, in fact
trying to plan this OLR con, I'm
thinking like, how do I lose the least
amount of money in planning this
but anyway
on a
serious note, I have a day job and the day job I've had
I've had for the past like seven years
so almost as long as OLR has been
going on, which is a fucking long time, just you know
and I'm changing that, I'm doing
a new job starting tomorrow and it's
kind of nerve-wracking, but
I think it'll be good, I'm
excited about what the
new position is and obviously I don't like to talk a lot about
my day job on the show, because I don't want no presents
showing up at my workplace
or bombs, you know what I mean
yeah, please no, just
no, so anyhow
yeah, I mean, I think it's great
that people send gifts, but I don't know, just something
weird about having my address out there
I'd just like to know who you are, that's all
it was also on my business card, well, our
Orange Lunch Radio business card
so you think one of our...
someone could have gotten it, I don't know, who knows, alright, anyhow
I'm over it, alright, that's it for the FUs
of the Week, couple more news stories for you guys
then the Skype line, and believe it or not
our chat, or I'm sorry
our phone works again, it was broken
last week, it works again
877-GAME-OLR works
also Orange Lunch Radio on Skype, both
of them will work, but we're not taking calls yet
we still got two more stories, Loki
yes, so let's talk a little
bit about how
not to do collector's editions
that's right, Splinter Cell
Conviction, it's a wonderful game
coming out this coming week
here, and apparently
they're dropping $10 off the
price of the collector's edition because
guess what, the USB drive that they included
with it is faulty
apparently there's
a possibility of faulty USB drives
included with the game, and so
they're knocking $10 off of it to
kind of compensate for that
and apparently none of the other
content has been affected, but
the bonus content included on the USB
drive may be inaccessible
in some copies
well that turned out
to be a bummer for someone, didn't it?
yeah, that is a bummer, and
let me tell you this much
from a
distributor, reseller
standpoint, that's gonna be
a fucking bitch when I come in on Monday
because we're gonna have to deal with all
these credits to people that
we sold the game to because
Ubisoft fucked up, so
thank you, Ubisoft
appreciate it
and whoever manufactured those little USB cards
are gonna get taken to the cleaners
you know what I mean?
yeah
and you know, really the USB cards
what they have on them here, they've got a little
artwork here
is a credit card size
USB drive that had
making of video, concept art renders
screenshots, storyboards
and wallpapers, who gives a shit
well can't you format that thing now and use it as
storage on your 360?
no you cannot because I don't believe it is over a gig
you need at least a gig
to be able to use it, so
and you really wanna have 16 gigs
cause you only get two cards, right?
this is so weird to me
so weird to me, well it was kind of a slow news week
and we found this article on
as a popular destination on Dig
and I thought what the hell, we'll bring it up on the show
it's from IGN and it talks about the most
anticipated Xbox Live arcade games
that are coming up to the service
and I thought I'd kind of gauge the reaction here
in studio, if our studio folks are excited
about these games, and those of you in chat
as well, kind of leading into
phone calls, this makes a good story
this is from IGN.com, so you know, take it with a grain of salt
Limbo
is one of the games that they talk about here
and this was pretty cool, they had
they were demoing this at PAX East, it's kind of like that
black and white, very artistic kind of
style with it, look kind of neat
Sonic the Hedgehog 4
very anticipated Xbox Live game
Yay!
Shank!
That was being shown at PAX earlier this year
it's not Shaft, but Shank
and he has a steel blade
it's very bloody, looks like your kind of game
Hydrophobia, which was also
shown at PAX East, it's like
kind of a Tomb Raider-ish type of game
but she's afraid of the water
well that makes me think of Bioshock
Puzzle Quest 2
Don't care
Speak for yourself, I am totally on this
That's why I was speaking for myself, I don't care
I do care, so I'm excited about that
Might and Magic Clash of Heroes
Don't care
Yeah, looks like it could be interesting
The art style looks really good
because it's
They have it on the DS
Super Meat Boy
Yay!
Don't care
I have a custom coffee mug
that I painted Super Meat Boy on
Oh really? That's cute
Also on the other side has Eduardo the Samurai Toaster
That's my WeWear
coffee mug that I made
And I'm actually kidding, it looks interesting
Comic Jumper
I don't know this one
Oh, The Maw and Explosion Man
That's a good developer there
Okay, Comedy Shooter
Is that supposed to be like Earthworm Jim or something?
Probably, similar
Monday Night Combat
That looks awesome
They had a business at PAX East
And they had an announcer guy out there on the show floor
So it seems like all of these games
were just PAX East games
I think someone at IGN
got a little lazy
There you go
I'm also looking forward to Magic Sword Double Impact
Or whatever they're actually calling it
That's coming out
So funny
Anyhow, the phones
are now open
And Game OLR or our username on Skype
is OrangeLoungeRadio
If you'd like to call to talk about, I don't know
Anticipated Xbox Live Arcade Games or heck anything
I know, you know, we were out
two weeks ago and then last week
we had some troubles with the phones and we were only able to
take a couple calls
So I'm sure there will be plenty of people who want to get through tonight
And that's fine, we have a little extra time for calls
I don't want to do the show too late tonight
But we have some time for calls
So again, 877 Game OLR
or our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio
It is now open and available for calls
SHA100Matt wants us to know
he played MNC at PAX East
and it was awesome
Okay, the phones are starting to ring, here we go
Hello, you're on OrangeLoungeRadio, who's this?
It's Ranma
Looks like I got through the first time once again
Look at you, you must have the
least amount of lag or something
Well, what's up?
Not too much, man
Couple of things now
To reference back to earlier in the episode
They did port Twilight Seen It
to the Nintendo DS
Came out about a couple of months ago
But Twilight Seen It
isn't like a Twilight game to me
I know, but
I get your points
But it's just like, they need to make an actual game
Well, actually they don't need to, but I'm surprised
they haven't, you know what I mean?
Well, Rob, I'm all for a
Twilight game, provided it plays
in a third person shooter like Conker's Bad Fur Day
and I get to shoot them all up
Then I will buy that
I don't know if I'd
buy it, but I might get it on Gamefly
So that way I feel like I'm not
really supporting them, but
even if I am a little bit
You won't feel as dirty
Alright, well there you go
What else is on your mind, buddy?
About an article earlier today
about the kid that stole the code from Breach
Yes, although
technically that was last week's show, but that's okay
Last week we had the phone problems
What do you think?
I was trying to call in, but
on our podcast we covered this
and my
gaming girl who did
some research on the article
it seems that
the company that did the game I think is Atomic Games
they're backed by the CIA
so I'm
kind of thinking that this was all like a little
set up, like a publicity stunt
Well, now hold on
Didn't they say that because
of what you're saying that it actually
made this theft of the code a lot
worse than it would be otherwise
like this kid is almost being
investigated by the FBI at this point
I don't know, I might be throwing in some extra
stuff there, but it seemed like
from what we were reporting last week, what he did
wasn't just bad, it was really bad
Pretty much
but if you're going to cross reference that
in, I'm just saying
because of how this came out
I don't know about you, but
if this was a big deal, don't you think everybody
at PAX would have been hearing about this?
Maybe they did, maybe it just happened
at a time we weren't around, I don't know
I certainly didn't hear anything like that
I didn't either, but at the same time
I was kind of in and out of there
we left to eat, we left
I came in late a lot of days
just because of the time zone thing
I don't know
It would be a really weird
obesity stunt type of thing
Weren't there court documents produced
and everything too?
I have no idea
I have not heard anything about it
I will believe
this guy actually did something
stupid, you know
but if there are no court documents, I call shenanigans
I see where you're coming from though
how could someone be so
colossally stupid, it just seems so fake
but some people
are that stupid, Rama
I know, I used to work
with people like that
Well
I don't know, fake or not
it certainly has got everybody talking
which, yeah
you might have hit the nail on the head of the irony
of it, is that more people are talking about this game now
than probably would have otherwise
Pretty much
Well, anything else on your mind tonight, my friend?
That's pretty much it
ActDeaf in our chat wants to say Matt posted the court files earlier
He's probably digging up the links again right now
so stay tuned to our chat rooms
Yeah, I'll definitely be following that
Alright, take care buddy
Alright, bye-bye
Let's go back to the phones
Hi, you're on Orange Laundry Radio, who's this?
Hi, it's Ray Iyanami
Hey, Ray Iyanami, what's on your mind, buddy?
I came up from Stock Card Con last week
my first Stock Card Con
You went all the way up to Seattle
to go to Stock Card Con?
Yes, I went with some friends
to meet up with some friends up there
among other things
Well, I don't know, you don't sound too happy
was it a good time, or what happened?
I'm sorry, I'm just tired for this week
so
Anyway, Stock Card Con is pretty cool, yes
I get to play a lot of games there
like Tetris or Grandmaster 3
and some other crap
Well, I'm glad you said nice things about it in the end
because our buddy John who does
Understation Live with Travis
I know is a big part of putting on Stock Card Con
Did you happen to run into him at all?
He's probably too busy
I saw him hosting the Anime Magician panel
but
I didn't get a chance to talk to him much
so I never actually got to meet him
Eh, it happens
Had you ever been to that venue before?
Because that's the same place they do PAX Prime
No, it was my first time
I was surprised at how big it was
I could actually compare it to a shopping mall
Especially since part of it is like a shopping mall
Yeah, it's kind of integrated right into the downtown scene there, isn't it?
Well, tell us a little more about the gaming they had there
Did they have like a big room? Were they doing tournaments?
What was kind of going on with gaming?
Well, they had an arcade
but it wasn't too big
Mostly DVR
In the Groove
They had a Pumped Up Pro 2 Location Test
They had NFL Day 4
guitar-proofing, drum-mania
and Patrick P, Jim's Threes and myself already
I would have played Pumped Up Pro 2
but unfortunately, like the 2DS, I was at the con
I was wearing a concept that involved dress shoes
and dress shoes and
arrow-stopping games
those seemed like a good idea
Were you cosplaying?
What were you cosplaying as?
I was cosplaying as a
shell from Pop'n Music
the librarian guy
and Apollo Justice
I wanted to cosplay as this one character
cosplay as this one character from Toho
but I didn't have a costume prepared
and
speaking of the Toho panel
there was one thing that I didn't like about it
and that was them trying to demonstrate the Toho games
they tried to demonstrate it by showing
one of the game's later stages
on lunatic difficulty
but it's basically a difficulty level of a part
and as a small fan, they kind of pissed me off
Because maybe they made the game look way harder than it really is?
Yeah, pretty much
I mean, I'm pretty sure a lot of the people who weren't really into
the Naku games were just confused
what the hell was going on
I mean, if I was running
If I was
If I had a partner running the panel
alongside the infamous stuff
I would also show demonstration using
easier stages and difficulties
Something that requires effort
to get through
but is still pretty watchable
that way people who are new to the series
can have a grasp of
what it's like to play the game
instead of just saying
Oh wow, pretty bullets, super adequate
dodge, any of that shit
Yeah, it's
I gotta say though
a lot of those shmups are so hard to me
but you know, it takes talent
to be good at them though, takes talent
That's for sure
I mean, whenever I try to show people
games, I don't go
straight to like full rising
if it's a fighting game or
showing them level 43 points on top
I try to show them
easier stuff, something you can actually understand
Like, a few months ago
I was at an arcade with a friend of mine
and she went through the top
so I kind of
popped into her use of easier
songs, even if it meant songs that
I didn't find to be as fun as
songs that I usually play
That's a really good point, is that if you're not wanting to scare someone
off, especially with the music games, you shouldn't
show off right away, like a lot of people
I think sometimes just want to like show off
how good they are at a game, so they'll pick like
the really hard song and like, look how cool this game
can be, and then people are like, ooh, I'm too scared to touch that
I don't want to touch that, so you kind of have to
warn people into it by showing them like, you know, on
the rock band, the easy mode, or you know
a one star, whatever difficulties
they're doing in pop music these days
you know, the really low end songs
and that kind of goes with video games in general, like if you
don't want to scare someone off, like you know they wouldn't
like a shooter game, don't show them Halo
or Gears of War, show them a video game
that might be more their tastes
you know, like whether that be something like
one versus a hundred, you know, might be
a really good enabler for people
to see that there's more to video games than that
or, you know, something on the Wii
I don't know, it is interesting
I think sometimes people really
scare people off from video games without realizing it
because they go right for the hard stuff
and a lot of people do get intimidated
Yeah, there
are, I think, channels and forums
I hang out at where people are not
too good at video games, so
I kind of get
how they feel about not being
able to get past the
first season for Shmopp on, even on easy
difficulty
Alright, well
we gotta let you go so we can get some more
calls, but, so, SakuraCon, do you think
you'd try to go back next year?
Um, possibly
if my spring break is around
SakuraCon again, because that lets you
one big deciding factor
in me doing it. Last year it didn't line up
with my spring break, so I didn't go
So if the timing's right, it just might be in the
cards. Alright, well, we gotta let you go
to get more calls, but take care of Ray, okay?
You too. Alright, later
Alright, I'll take a couple more calls
here. 877-GAME-OLR
or our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio
Take a few more calls
here before we call it a night at
OLR Studios. Some last minute
stories tonight we'll have in just a moment
but first, another call. Hi, you're
on OrangeLoungeRadio, who's this?
Hi, this is Spasinator
Hey, Spasinator, you're
cutting in and out a little bit, but we'll try to move
ahead. What's on your mind, buddy?
Sorry about that, I'm on a
cell phone and unfortunately some
stuff in my building interferes
with the signal. That's okay.
But anyway, I tried
calling in last week to give you
updates as to my
PlayStation 3 situation
Oh yeah, it's been a little while since we heard about that
Yeah, we had our phone issues last week. Well, what's
the latest and greatest?
I can make this short
and sweet. You know,
I'll probably gloss over the details, but
the drill points are
that I got my
PS3 back on the 30th
and
a few days later, they
started putting my
videos back onto my
download queue
because the video store
works differently than the
game side of the store. Anyway,
it took a while
for everything to show up
because they had to do
everything manually
and reauthorize everything
and I get like over several hundred
videos, but needless
to say, I
got all my videos back, so I don't have to
worry about that now.
Wow, 700 videos. Oh my gosh.
Okay.
Yeah, well, not all those videos
are paid for. Some of those are
like
the free music game
out is like promotions to get
you to buy throughout the series
or whatever that's there.
But
needless to say, I got my
videos back and
hopefully
nothing goes wrong with
the video service in the future, but
I'll just have to keep my fingers crossed
on that, so.
I'm sorry,
I didn't mean it. No, that's right.
I know you say you didn't want to get into too many of the
details, but I'm kind of curious because I know you
they were putting, I mean, it sounds like in
the end, you got what you
really needed
and deserved back. I mean, it sounds like
it had to be a very manual process
for Sony, so it sounds like they almost weren't set up
to handle a request like yours, but
I'm kind of curious, how did you ultimately
kind of get them to come
around, because you were going back and forth with them.
If you go back a few episodes in the show when you were first calling
in about this, you were going back and forth
with Sony a little bit, and we told you
you might have to speak with the supervisor or just kind of
put up a stink. I mean, is that what ultimately
happened? You sadly had to be
that guy on the phone in order for them to finally
listen to you?
This time around,
not to the same extent,
although I did
keep what you and Dr.
Zirk said in
mind the initial time I
hit this problem,
and initially
it looked like I was going to have to go that road
because the first person I spoke to
said
to sum it up,
sorry dude,
you're so low on that,
but
in subsequent calls
speaking to other reps
prior to me saying I'm a machine
and they said, yeah, once you send the machine
in and they send it
back to me,
they'll do everything and reauthorize
everything to download.
You know,
I just have to interject here,
because as someone who has worked very closely
with call centers in their
day job, to me
that's a huge issue that you
called in two times and got two different
answers. And for anybody,
you know, Sony's a big company and who knows
we might have somebody at Sony who happens to listen to
this program. To me, that's a big issue.
You should not call a call center, speak to two
different people and get two different answers.
I agree with that. I actually did customer
service for a very long time and I did
well
by the time the department was called Service Quality where we
if they had a question they could
call us and ask us and we would tell them
and make sure you repeat this.
But yeah, everyone is supposed to be
on the same page. And don't get me wrong,
I'm glad Spazinator got what he
wanted. He just should have gotten it the first
time. You know, so this is if
we can learn anything from this phone call, if
you are at Sony, there's some
edumacation to be done amongst
your reps. This is also a
prime example why every time
you talk to someone in a call center, you write down
their name, you write down the date and the time that you
spoke with them and you keep a track of what
you talked about. They have to keep notes too.
Anyway, I know Spazinator... I'm sorry. No, that's okay.
But no, it's important. Spazinator is dying to jump
in here again. Sorry Spaz.
Yeah, I was going to say,
I never worked at a call center before.
The closest thing to that is working
at a grocery store, you know,
at the front desk.
But I basically
talked about the initial
response I got to like,
perhaps, you know, the one
rep that I usually spoke to
having an off day,
you know, every deal with
Apple customers, they weren't
quite as friendly as I was
or maybe possibly
you know,
the rep
possibly having some kind of
bad information or gainer
information mixed up somehow.
But ultimately, regardless
of, you know, what the case
may be, you know, ultimately
I got my stuff back, which is
the key thing there.
So, you know,
if, God forbid,
I kept gaining the same
response time and time again,
then I would, you know,
escalate the call to
a supervisor like U3
has suggested
the first time this kind of
thing happened.
So basically you didn't come to that, but,
you know,
God forbid it.
Yeah, no, I was just going to say, yay Sony
for getting it right, but, you know,
it is a bummer that it did take you
a little bit of a run around to do it, but, you know,
they made it right and we should recognize
that, you know, at least it wasn't the doom and gloom
we thought it was going to be. But I'm
fascinated. I got to wrap up because we got to see if we can
fit in one or two more calls. Do you have anything else
or a footnote to this or anything else you want to share with
listeners?
Nothing comes to mind, but I'll keep
you guys posted on
Twitter if there's anything that comes up
or if I think anything
early during the week.
Sounds good buddy.
Alright, good luck with everything. Take care
buddy.
I just got to read this comment from chat, which is interesting.
SHA100Matt says, I'll say this again,
buy and have hard copies of your movies
from now on. This is the second time that's happened
and if you ask me it's totally not worth it going through this
hassle. You know,
it's tough because there's a lot about digital
distribution I do want to support, but you know,
SHA100Matt makes a good point. It's like
if there were hard copies, you wouldn't have had to
go through this in the first place, but
I don't know.
I don't know. I'm kind of torn because like, you know,
I've bought things online. I've done the digital
distribution thing, but I've kind of taken
a lot of that for granted maybe. Alright.
I just buy TV episodes sometimes online, like
if I'm buying on Supernatural. That's why I like
Netflix because Netflix, you know, you're not really
buying anything. You just kind of rent it.
Anyhow, let's do at least one more call here and then we're going to be on our way out.
Hey, Aaron Orange on the radio. Who's this?
Hi. This is your friendly neighborhood
Mexican. Act Deaf. Hey, Act Deaf.
I'm glad to see you weren't shaken
too bad by the earthquake that happened last
week right before the show.
Yeah, we were shaken, but
not stirred. Not stirred. Alright.
Well said. What's
on your mind tonight, buddy?
I just wanted to add about
the Twitter topic I sent
earlier about the Mexican
game being
developed and brought over
by Konami.
I just wanted to add that
it's being distributed here
in Mexico, but it's
being distributed by another company.
Okay, well that's good to know
because I think earlier I had said, oh haha, it's not
coming out of Mexico even though it's a Mexican game, but
that's just, Konami's not
putting it out there. Someone else is. Okay, that makes sense.
Yeah, it's actually made by
Colombian and Mexican
developers. It's being published
I think by
well, developed by
well, the
sorry.
The main development is being held
here in Mexico, though Colombia is
helping also over their
studios. I don't remember
the name of the development company, but
it's just starting
right now to develop games
and I hope, I really hope that
this game
at least develops or
brings a market over Mexico
because it's a
very small market and it's
starting right now.
I was going to say, I can't say
and maybe you can correct me here, but I can't say I can
think of any like big games or even
medium sized games that we can say
this game was developed in Mexico by
a Mexican company or
Colombia or any of these other places.
This seems to be like the first game we're really
at least that I'm aware of
that is developed like that.
Yeah, there's not
really a market for like
Xbox 360 or PS3
games, maybe even Wii games
that are developed
at least this large.
There may be cell phone games
that are being developed here
and are made by companies like
Gameloft and other
companies, but
for a console
it's pretty much the first.
There are
games coming out for
the Wii and the 360
that are also
based on Mexican
franchises like
soap opera even,
but at least it's starting to
grow. Do you see PS2 development?
Because my thought would be that a lot of these countries
that they're not really being supported
with the 360 and PS3, it seems that maybe
the PS2 is still big there.
Actually,
the PS2 isn't
that big right now.
It's maybe the PS3 or
the 360 maybe.
Maybe on other places
like Brazil
and especially
because of their import
and taxes over there,
the PS2 is starting to gain
momentum there, but
here, even though
the games, and I have talked about this before,
the games are pretty expensive, but
at least we're on the
same market as America.
You mentioned
Brazil and the first thing I thought of was
I thought the Master System was still big in Brazil.
Yeah, it's still big.
It's like, whoa.
They also have the re-releases. Didn't we have a story
about the Genesis repackaging that was coming
out in Brazil? There's some
interesting things going on with old school games
in Latin America.
If I recall correctly, it's called
the Bebo.
It was brought over here
in Mexico, though it didn't.
It wasn't as big
as in Brazil. Interesting.
Cool stuff. Well, we hope
the game does well. I know
it's probably not going to be a huge thing
here, but I know there's a lot of people that are
really into that Mexican wrestling stuff and
just like there are the WWE
and all that stuff, so I'm sure
it will definitely have its audience.
It doesn't look that bad.
It looks decent.
I totally love Mexican wrestling.
I've played some of the WWE games, and
they look good, and it looks
at the same part.
Alright, well, we'll see. We'll hope it does well.
At least if nothing else, it'll help the
development market down there and get some more
games out of there of some ideas.
Anything else you want to share with the listeners
real quick tonight, ACT-F?
Well, only that
we're okay over here in
Nezcali. Even though it
was a pretty big quake, there was
only pretty much
structural damages.
There were only two lives lost
and only a couple
hundred injuries, but
other
than that, we're pretty fine over here,
though there are people that
are needed
of services and maybe
like camping tents
and all that stuff, but
other than that, we're pretty
good. Hopefully,
at least here in America,
the folks want to donate to
the relief efforts. I'm sure
the Red Cross has something set up. They always do
for the cases like this, so definitely
folks should look into that. I'm glad
to hear that for the most part, everything's okay.
It's sad
that even one life was lost, but
it sounds like it could have been a lot
worse based on how bad
the quake itself was, so
I'm glad to hear that at least
you and everyone you care
about are okay.
All right, well, Act F, we're
going to let you go so we can wrap up the show, but thanks so much for the call, okay?
Thank you. All right, take care, my friend.
All right,
that's going to do it for tonight's calls, and sorry
for those folks that didn't get through.
It was ringing pretty good tonight because
we actually had
a lot of people that were trying to get in
tonight because of last week, but
yeah, we've got to wrap it up, you guys.
I'm starting
a new job tomorrow. I can't be here all night,
and you know, Dark Soccer wants to go to bed
eventually, and Matt might
want to go back to KFC and ask for a double down
with no sauce, so we'll see.
All right. I'm kind of hungry because I didn't
need anything. I offered to make ribs.
You can have cake. I don't need ribs.
I'm going to have healthy special
K cereal when I go home. All right.
Anyhow, we've got to wrap
up, you guys, and get on out of here
so we can. Ooh, or a baked potato. I'm going to have
a baked potato.
All right. We've got to, uh-oh.
Uh-oh. We have a stream
down error. Winamp has crashed.
God dammit.
All right. That's okay. We're going to just keep going here.
At least it's at the end of the show.
Yeah, at least it's at the end of the show.
Hold on, guys. Dang it.
Poopy!
All right. We're still recording for podcasts,
so can someone fill a little time here
while I get us... I'm actually trying to find something to send
you for cage match. Okay, that's fine.
And, um...
I had the same problem, but then I found something.
Well, I was
going to... Who was the winning song last time?
That would be, I think, you, Rob.
Was I with the Goldfrapp song? It wasn't me.
Yeah, you were with the Goldfrapp song. Okay, that's fine.
So I was going to do, like, a throwaway.
Okay, there we go. So we're still going.
Now we're back up, and it's streaming on all games again.
I don't know what happened. So, okay.
Now we can actually wrap up the show. Winamp froze,
you guys. I don't know why it does that.
It's irritating. Because it's Winamp.
I guess. I mean, it might need to upgrade the version
or something. We'll have to run some tests.
You need to upgrade your version.
We'll have to run some tests before the next show, I don't know.
But that's weird, because just closing
Skype shouldn't bork Winamp like that.
I don't know what happened. Alright, well
it is what it is. Anyhow, um...
We're still going to wrap up
and be on out of here for the night.
Thanks so much for our Skype callers. Thank you guys
for listening to our show and supporting our
independent radio. I gotta get
last minute stories, though, before I give my whole spiel here.
It looks like Matt has a million tabs open on
Firefox over there. Yes, I do.
A million instances of the Unicorn game.
DarkSire, do you have any last minute stories
real quick before we go?
Rawr. I just want to check.
Alright, Loki then.
Ok, so Dark Void Zero, that
wonderful 2D version
of, or 8-bit 2D version
of the game Dark Zero
that hit the DSiWare
is now going to be hitting the iPhone
and PC actually tomorrow.
So that's pretty awesome.
And it'll cost you $2.99
on the iPhone and $5 on PC.
So that's not bad. I actually may purchase that for my
arcade cabinet. I think that would fit in just
nice and easy.
And a game that I was playing earlier
this week.
I always had trouble pronouncing this.
Espacaluda 2
will be hitting the iPhone as well.
Also, actually
it should have already hit the iPhone because that would have been
on the 10th.
That's awesome.
My friend linked
a Japanese video of that in and I
was actually already looking for it.
But I don't know that...
I don't know how well I controlled it on the iPhone.
It looked pretty responsive
on that video. So I'm totally thinking
about getting it.
Very cool.
Let's see here. And then
there's some interesting
tie-ins apparently with Melgir Solid
Peace Walker.
They're going to have two different games
tie-in with it. First one, Monster Hunter
is actually
going to be tie-in with it as well.
Monster Hunter Portable 2nd-G
I guess
there's going to be content from that game
that's going to be able to
work with Peace Walker
which is weird.
Apparently the little
cat-like characters
the felines
that appear in the Monster Hunter series
are going to appear
in the Melgir Solid Peace Walker
game as well.
So that's interesting.
And then another weird one
that's a crossover. Apparently
you will also be able to link up
Melgir Solid
Peace Walker with
Front Mission Evolved
on the Playstation 3 and
Xbox 360. Players will be able
to exchange parts acquired from
Peace Walker bosses
in Front Mission Evolved.
How the hell does that work?
But that's interesting.
And you can use them for your
mechs that you build in that game.
Talk about cross-company
promotions there. That's kind of neat
actually. I actually want to
check out that new Peace Walker game.
Or Front Mission.
And then Professor Layton
is actually coming over here. It's getting a Western
release. The movie that is
developed by
Level 5 and
that looks kind of neat.
An anime movie.
People will dig that.
And of course with any
game out there with voluptuous
women, there will be
a way that they will find to strip them
of their clothes. And
that was the
exact thing that happened
with Dead or Alive Paradise.
People have found a way to
swap out the
textures in the game and now we get
wonderful, nippleous,
naked women. I'm sure it wasn't very hard with a
Dead or Alive game. So yeah, that game is
five bucks on iTunes and I'm buying it right now.
Espagluta?
Yes.
Good luck controlling it on the iPhone.
Just not my favorite
gaming platform.
And then finally, there was a patent
file for Rumble
in DS. I'm assuming
it's going to be in the 3DS.
Oh, I'm sure. Yeah, I think there's been
rumblings of Rumble for quite some time.
Yeah.
And hopefully dual analog sticks would be
nice. It would be great.
Because everybody likes dual analog sticks.
I'm not going to hold my breath though.
I got a couple things thrown at me here in chat.
SSG100Matt reminded
me that I don't think we ever mentioned the winner
of USL Madness or
the March Madness, if you will, that happens
on Orange on its Radio. I think we were off the week it
ended and then of course last week's show was just
off. Chrono Trigger
1 for the first time
was the declared the greatest game of all time
by your voting
at OrangeOnitsRadio.com. I
thoroughly disagree with your votes
but whatever. I mean it's not like Chrono Trigger is a bad game.
But I guess it was destined to win one of
these years. I've just decided
in these contests, people just vote the way
I don't vote.
And I don't know if it's a ha ha
let's make Rob mad or whatever, but whatever.
I can think of a lot of games
a lot of games worse than
Chrono Trigger. Yay Chrono Trigger
and yay everybody that participated in
boo and poop on those that didn't.
And also as Tigerclaw points out Microsoft
has changed the increments of which you have to
purchase Microsoft points to more
manageable numbers
instead of some weird rounded off numbers.
It's actually four hundred and eight hundred
and sixteen hundred and four thousand.
Is it really? Yes. I'd heard that they were doing
that so they got rid of five hundred one thousand
and all that all together? Yeah.
Well shit, now what if I have extra points I want to use?
Am I screwed?
It's like go get a card at the store?
I don't know. Tigerclaw
is cut and paste in tons of links for us.
He also posted a link that I think is worth mentioning.
Blockbuster, you know Blockbuster
is kind of hurting right now. They're closing stores left
and right. One of the things they're trying to
do to, I guess you could say either compete
with Netflix or Gamefly or both.
They are doing their games
by mail service. It's going to
cost an extra seven ninety nine
plus tax on top of the standard
I guess you could say monthly fees.
You'll be able to rent one game
at a time and that's the total number
of discs that you're allowed to have out on the plan.
So there you go. If you don't check
any games out during the one month period though
you're not charged the money. Kind of interesting
how that all works. It's currently being
tested in Cleveland, Ohio.
Because Cleveland rocks.
Cleveland rocks. Ohio.
I'm thinking actually
you say that I think of Howard the Duck.
You live in Cleveland.
Drew Carey show.
I don't watch that.
It was like ten years ago.
I didn't watch that.
They even had a Rocky Horror themed episode.
I did see that.
Well, see. Wait, how did you not watch the show
yet? See that episode. I saw the clip
on YouTube. Yeah, YouTube. YouTube
it ruins everything. Alright.
Anyhow, I think we're done. Is that it?
Did you get all your stories, Logie?
Yeah, all the ones I wanted to.
Some guy beat some Asteroids record too.
Hey now, don't haze
Tiger Claw in chat.
This is the Tiger Claw link show.
He does a good job. Act F says Tiger Claw
more efficient than Google. Seriously.
And Dan Mufroga Returns is apparently
popping up on DSiWare as well.
Cannot die.
Cannot die. This is why I like
doing a show with a live chat room because when
I don't know the answer instead of sitting here looking like an idiot
or making something up. I mean I still look like an idiot.
But I'll just go, hey chat, what was
the answer to that? Somebody always knows.
And if it involves a link, Tiger Claw has it
in five seconds. If not, SSA 100
Matt. It's like a little friendly competition.
We should have a total board.
Or something.
Alright, anyhow.
Of course, thank you guys so much. All the chatters
that help make the show happen. You guys really are
the fourth guest on the show always.
And of course, you guys for listening. I know we have a lot
of people on the podcast who just can't be here for
whatever reason Sunday night. So thank you guys so much
for downloading our show and tuning in and supporting
independent radio. You guys are awesome.
And thanks so much. Always say
if you enjoy the show, just tell somebody
about the show.
Or leave a nice review on iTunes or
some other podcast site. Just help us spread the word
because we don't have a big magazine
or a big million dollar website or game
company behind us. We're just
kids like you that like video games.
Except we're not kids anymore.
That's the sad part.
Anyhow, that's going to do it for another episode of
Orange Lounge Radio. But not until we go around to get everybody's
final thought. DarkSakura, do you have
a final thought for us tonight?
Meh. Cake!
Loki, do you have a final thought
for us tonight? I'm hoping to finish Final Fantasy
13 soon. Although I have a feeling
I'm not going to be able to because I have to get all the
achievements. And I have lots
of games to start playing.
My final thought
is the website
ffxivcore.com
is making me foam at the mouth.
That's really what it boils
down to. Anyhow,
thank you guys again. Have a great week.
We will be back next week with more
of Orange Lounge Radio to do this all over
again. New
stories and all that other stuff.
But the same old crap that you've
come to love week to week. We'll
see you next time here on Orange
Lounge
Radio.
Of course it would help if I would have the
end of the show theme song queued up.
Because when I don't have that I just
sit here in silence and it's kind of awkward.
Much better. Here we go. Good night!
See you next week!