[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, April 4th, 2010, a theft occurs at PAX East, Linux gets taken away on the PS3, and Nintendo puts the smackdown on the MMO fans were waiting for.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll get into that later.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not a good night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, we should just phone tonight's episode in.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell are we doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: We should just throw the show roll in the toilet and just do whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: If this is the first show you've ever listened to of Orange Lounge Radio, please go back in the iTunes archives and select another.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just gonna be one of those nights tonight, I can already tell.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had the fuck show already, this is the fuck it show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not here tonight, sometimes that's some of our best work though, so we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not here tonight, Tagmaster Loki, sadly is not here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he's got a holiday dinner thing going on, which is strange because the wife is Jewish, but whatever, there's a dinner.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it may be his family.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I know, I'm pretty sure it is his family.
[SPEAKER_02]: The man deserves a night off once in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wonder if Nellie is observing Passover.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, no, she can't be because, yeah, never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: And one thing I should say about Loki, you know, I'm sure he wanted to tell you all this on the show, but he posted it on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_02]: And when I say, you post it on Twitter, CNN can report on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So therefore, it's fair game, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nellie is pregnant again.
[SPEAKER_02]: So congratulations to Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: The pictures were kind of scary because I could see bones.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what babies look like when they're growing inside of you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could see bones.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just so you guys know, not only is Nellie pregnant, she's, what, about 20 weeks?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they waited, I mean, understandably, if you don't know what happened before.
[SPEAKER_08]: They waited until it was a viable pregnancy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, they wanted to wait this time to say anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: So she's about 20 weeks along at this point.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they already know it's a boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one this time, not 20.
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw the pee-pee.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, what's that?
[SPEAKER_08]: They pointed to the pee-pee on the ultrasound.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did they?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nellie would do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a very Nellie thing to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: They usually do that at the doctor's.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at my kid's penis.
[SPEAKER_02]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_08]: The doctors will usually point stuff out on the ultrasound.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to make you some dinner.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but in all seriousness, like a good woman should.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bite my ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, if you want something more disgusting, bite my sinus cavity.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I get to monologue with the listeners for a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: This should be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'll do my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can hear you from the other room, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you can.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you'll hear...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll talk to the chatters tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll talk to the chatters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, chatters.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yes, Loki is chat.orangelandrader.com, by the way, if you want to join our chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no Loki here tonight because he's having a nice family dinner, and obviously they have reasons to celebrate, so good for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: He'll be back next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's just, right now, it's just you and me, folks.
[SPEAKER_02]: You and the guys in the chat room, chat.orangelandrader.com, and we'll be opening up the Skype line a little later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, here's the other part that's, I guess, just hilarious of what's going on right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: is that I am sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can probably tell my voice sounds a little bit out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And DarkSakura, you can hear her blowing her nose like in China.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go download Bobby's show from this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sounded like an earthquake going on back there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark, she's screaming at me from the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is like the DarkSakura and Sky are married edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is going on here?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're yelling at me from the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're cooking me dinner.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob is officially my gay husband Rob is my complimentary spouse Can I talk about fist bumping for a minute?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, PAX East.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ain't no one want to shake my hand at PAX East for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a couple people, but I noticed the big thing to do is fist bumping.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how people say hello now, is they fist bump.
[SPEAKER_02]: Surely that's a sign I'm getting old, is that I don't want to fist bump.
[SPEAKER_02]: Back in my day, we shake hands.
[SPEAKER_02]: But not when you're sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, A, I wasn't sick during the con, and B, I already had swine flu in October, so I'm not going to have it again.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not cooking dinner.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll let everyone know what Rob is having.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the same thing I'm having.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's an Ezekiel 4-9 tortilla, so there's no gluten and no yeast in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: With some garlic hummus.
[SPEAKER_02]: All this healthy crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: Baby spinach.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fresh baby spinach.
[SPEAKER_02]: The wife's making me eat healthy tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yogurt cheese.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I will say more about this later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everyone knows I have digestion problems.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I figured out what's causing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Rob in the chatroom says, I got it from the beanbag and shook your hand.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it was just some people were fist bumping.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I don't... I met a...
[SPEAKER_02]: I met a blogger who blogs for a site that's commercial and they get paid for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if I told you the site, you'd all know what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she wanted a fist bump.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was like, oh, okay, is that how we do it back east?
[SPEAKER_02]: But she was actually from California, so I didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I guess maybe it was a virus thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wasn't used to that whole fist bump thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought that's what bros did when they were drunk.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft apparently is okay so I know if he's okay then it can't be too terrible so hopefully everybody is okay
[SPEAKER_02]: I know they build a lot of the structures down there I mean it's LA we're talking about so there's a lot of structural integrity down there so hopefully everybody's okay what I didn't know at the same time apparently nine minutes later an aftershock of some sort hits in NorCal
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't have really felt it anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the scary part is I was sitting on the Bay Bridge right when these earthquakes were happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know this because my sister, who is in Long Beach, texted me and said, earthquake, LOL.
[SPEAKER_02]: So thank gosh I didn't like fall off the bridge if that earthquake had been too much stronger.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, apparently it's the earthquake show.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the freaky crap show tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what the hell's going on tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're just like avoiding the topic of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, we can talk about games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get into the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's start it off as we always do with a little bit of how is your gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura is still in the kitchen, but she's bringing, ooh, yay, vitamin water.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now when my throat is parched, I will be able to quench it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: So my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can we touch you, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it wasn't that silly.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, we had a good time.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had a good discussion.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: You were a miss, DarkSakura, as was Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a bummer you guys couldn't make it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Show itself, I don't know if I really actually ended up playing a lot of video games because I didn't want to wait in line for an hour.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will say what video games I did play.
[SPEAKER_02]: Classic Gaming Arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: That big famous arcade they have out there in the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fun Spot.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fun Spot brought some of their arcade machines.
[SPEAKER_02]: Two Packs East.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I played Donkey Kong 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I took some pictures of pinball tables for DarkSakura on her Twitter.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I played the Buck Rogers arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was actually one of the sit-down cabinets.
[SPEAKER_02]: That machine kicked my ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I played some classic games.
[SPEAKER_02]: But as far as...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like jumping the sequel.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looked like I like jumping with rockets.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just people blast each other with rockets.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, I had a good time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did get DarkSakura a present, but unfortunately I neglected to bring it tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it involves a certain card game that people were playing everywhere, up and down the halls in the tabletop area.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know it's one that DarkSakura is a fan of.
[SPEAKER_08]: Magic?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not telling.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not telling.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would have been fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I had a good time at PAX.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except for the Omegathon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can we talk about the Omegathon?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that happened after the PAX show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm already starting to get sick Sunday.
[SPEAKER_02]: And my friends that I traveled with, my dear friends Sag and Amanda, they wanted to wait in line for the Omegathon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which I'm like, okay, I've never watched a final round Omegathon.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, okay, let's do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's sit in line.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's wait for the final round of the Omegathon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's watch the closing ceremony, see what happens.
[SPEAKER_02]: So final round of the Omegathon is supposed to start at 5 o'clock, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: 5.30, I noticed we're still sitting in line outside and we are cramped.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are herded like cattle.
[SPEAKER_02]: If there was a fire, we would have died.
[SPEAKER_02]: We would have all died.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's just we are in there like so tightly packed.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently they posted to their Twitter, oh, we're having problems with the final Omegathon game, LOL.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm just sitting there thinking, open the goddamn theater and test behind the curtain.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let us in.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm old and my bones can't take this standing around anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: So finally, like 5.45, they let us in.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Super Mario Brothers, Rad Racer, Tetris, I'm watching the Nintendo World Championships about 20 years late
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, that sounds like almost the exact order of a Nintendo World Championship cartridge.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what it was?
[SPEAKER_08]: For real?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was, for real.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might have been some variation in the coin numbers and the lines, but essentially it was the frickin' Nintendo World Championships.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: To the, through the little tunnel part and through to the, like the very end.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't the little dinky guy sitting in front of the gate at the first stage, was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, see, I took it to mean that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I took it to mean stage one.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the first boss is the end of stage one, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but it was all the way to the big orb thing that goes back and forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really at the end of like stage two.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's how far they had to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yippee skippee for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Without cussing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: Without cussing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Womp, womp, womp
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they were like, thanks for coming to watch the Omegathon.
[SPEAKER_02]: PAX East was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was more awesome than PAX Prime.
[SPEAKER_02]: See you next year, bitches.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm sitting like, I stood in an hour in like 30 minute line for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which I could have read about on the internet in five minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was very unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hear past Omegathons have been much better.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a very unfortunate low light of PAX.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Game Room Game Room
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is ridiculous when you're trying to get a high score saved or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might have to be hitting the button over and over.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've lost scores because the servers literally go up and down and up and down and up and down.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is just atrocious.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't know what is going on with Game Room.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's a good Game Room in there somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just they've got a lot of kinks to work out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, my gut tells me as much as there's a lot I do like about Game Room, they shouldn't have released it when they did.
[SPEAKER_02]: They should have waited until things were more stable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe they had no idea how popular it was going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think they should have waited until June.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, pro tip, I find I do better when I play on games for Windows with an Xbox 360 controller than I do on regular Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I think part of the reason is that you're sitting right there in front of the monitor just like an old school arcade cabinet you're not sitting several feet away from your TV and I think it does help the precision especially on a lot of those old games especially on things like Asteroid Deluxe where your bullets are like tiny tiny it kind of helps to be sitting right in front of the monitor as much as my mother would hate that
[SPEAKER_02]: so there you go Spyro in our chatroom says game room is free that is true the game room engine itself is free and you can get like a good like I don't know like 50 gamer score just for downloading it and putting up decorations in your room but you will have to pay at least like $3 to enjoy a game or $5 if you want them to be multi-platform which is how I've been buying all my games but I do go back and forth between Windows and 360 and some people might say $5 Rob you're crazy
[SPEAKER_02]: But, well, I mean, I paid $5 for Frogger and Joust on the 360 when it first came out, and I've honestly played Yars' Revenge more than any other game this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I did play some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the plane, I played Final Fantasy Tactics A2 on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: I borrowed that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Oshi who keeps blowing her nose and sinuses over there How is your gaming week going?
[SPEAKER_08]: I just played some Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been taking advantage of my spring break to not be at my computer or not be in front of a TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just tried to rest a lot, you know, because I've been so busy with everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I was going to actually make a good start on Final Fantasy II today.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then the allergy monster smacked me in the face.
[SPEAKER_08]: So basically every time I haven't been working on something here, I've been asleep.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I've been playing Dream.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been playing Ben and Joel the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's where you take Benadryl and see if it'll either make you high or pass out.
[SPEAKER_08]: In my case, it was pass out, and that's what's happening again because I took another Benadryl.
[SPEAKER_02]: Great.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you took drugs that are going to make you drowsy during the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I took drugs so that I could breathe, and then Dan gave me a Vicks inhaler thing, and I love those things.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a tube you stick up your nose and snort.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like a tampon applicator, honestly, from where I'm sitting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like a tampon.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like you're shoving a tampon in your nose and pushing a button.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank God it's radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is where all of you in chat are very thankful.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a camera, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyhow, where else was I with this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Talking about webcams and all that stuff Oh, I did want to say this about Rocky last night As I went to Rocky And, well, A, Alan was playing a crap ton of Peggle Which I thought was cute Because it made me think of you That's one time I thought of you last night And then the other time Are you going to put that on the OLR blog?
[SPEAKER_02]: I dare you
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura never likes pictures of herself to get up on the internet, and I dare her to put the tampon in her nose on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a reason to look like shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you putting that on the internet?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura with a tampon in her nose.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, as MaceSatsuma in chat says, it's nose pond.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going up on the internet right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: OrangeHandsRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Click refresh a million times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Only multiply if you have food because they eat your food.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: The picture should be up now.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I see this on VeryDemotivational.com, I will kill you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't tell them what website to post it to.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least you're not John McCain.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you hear about that?
[SPEAKER_08]: What the fuck happened this time?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't pay attention to that loser.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, this is funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: John McCain posted a picture of himself on the TwitPic or whatever, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I'm not starting a political thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just think this is funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it had been Obama, it would have been funny too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was he playing with his nipples or something?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would have been really funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, he posted a picture just on his iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: John McCain is really old, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: So the joke is he's probably not hip with technology, but he's showing, hey, I can take a picture of myself with my iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he did that and somebody took the picture and posted it to guyswithiphones.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: John McCain on that website.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you go to guyswithiphone.com And it's like penis, penis, balls, balls Wang, wang, butt, butt, John McCain It was funny
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, how about some housekeeping?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe we will actually talk about some video games tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be a short show tonight, kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apologies, but if you can't tell why, I don't know what show you're listening to.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it will be a bit of a short show tonight, meaning it's not part A, part B. It's just one giant part tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're going to try and wrap up this show by 8 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will still take your calls.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll take your Twitter topics, mailbag, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not going to neglect it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a few less stories tonight so we can get out of here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm reading one email.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's one email?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to read one.
[SPEAKER_02]: TigerClaw in our chatroom says, what's next?
[SPEAKER_02]: McCain gets on Chatroulette.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Talk about the cesspool of the internet, Chatroulette.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought that was 2chan or 4chan.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is no word to describe that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But like Chatroulette, there's some really funny YouTubes that come of Chatroulette.
[SPEAKER_02]: And my favorite is the guy that plays piano improv to the people on Chatroulette.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got to look this up.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's his name?
[SPEAKER_02]: Murhot?
[SPEAKER_02]: Murhot is his name, something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, gaming news, because we're a video game podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yuck, yuck, yuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Major Nelson starts off our game thing tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: And somebody hacked, hacksword Major Nelson's game card.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know Major Nelson.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's famous.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, if you're ever on the 360 and you download the Xbox, man, hi, I'm Major Nelson.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm at PAX East.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's exactly what he sounds like, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: He always goes out to the different events, and he's the mouth for Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Major Nelson is kind of the mouth for the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reggie Fils-Aimé is kind of the mouth, even though he's also the CEO.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's kind of the mouth for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: You kind of associate your Wii press conference with Reggie Fils-Aimé.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Sony... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony doesn't really have a mouth.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess there's that one girl who's on the core, but I can't even think of her name.
[SPEAKER_02]: That tells you what a mouthpiece she is.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Major Nelson is kind of like the spokesman, if you will, for 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: But his gamer card was hacked.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it happened around the time PAX was going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they picked a good time to do it, honestly.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what's weird is that, like, I don't understand why you would, like, hack somebody's thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they hacked his name to say, I'm a faggot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, ha ha, funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you're in the third grade.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, I don't know, they made the text say, any account, $100 PayPal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess meaning that you could pay these people $100 and they'll hack any account because, you know, if they can get Major Nelson, they can get your neighbor or your college friend that you're mad at or whatever as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, somebody took responsibility for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not even going to say who it was because they're trash and I'm not going to promote them here on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: But somebody took responsibility for it and they even did a YouTube video about
[SPEAKER_02]: Blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So obviously Microsoft fixed this, but this just begs the question, why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why would you hack someone's gamer card?
[SPEAKER_02]: What is to gain from that?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's EPing, Rob, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, at least like when you hack a WoW account, like, you know, in my house... It's a famous target.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's kind of like when the celebrity Twitters get hacked, and like, you know, hi, I hacked Britney Spears, you know, I have a huge vagina.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's funny to tweet as Britney Spears and say sick things.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still don't understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, there's no...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, it just seems odd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a gamer card?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why don't you just hack majornelson.com?
[SPEAKER_02]: Then you could get people to go to your trash website automatically.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that I'm saying you should do that, because you shouldn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't understand the purpose of hacking someone's gamer card to say I'm a faggot nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is stupid, but you know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_08]: What you're doing right now, talking about it, that's exactly why they do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: no I know which is why I didn't say the name of the site that took responsibility for it but I just think it's just weird to me like I think it does need to be talked about like why would people hack gamer cards or what's next this is so watch out don't make people too mad because they might send these guys $100 and your gamer card will be hacked next and everybody will think that you know you're a whatever 6th grade word they want to put in there to describe you so be careful
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe they need authenticators on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that what's going to come next?
[SPEAKER_02]: Authenticators?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, Kristen got hacked on WoW.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had read about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people are getting hacked on WoW.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you don't have an authenticator, you are going to get hacked.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have an authenticator on my phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do not think you are immune to this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got hacked on WoW and I am not stupid with stuff I downloaded.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't click banners on things that aren't legit and all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got hacked and I think I know what happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I logged in on my ex's computer and he was stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I think that's what happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't get hacked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: My account's disabled.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, yeah, you can't get hacked.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm paying for that!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, actually, actually, I've heard of them, like, re-enabling accounts and going back in.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you gotta be careful.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you are an authenticator.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think I had a friend who his account was dormant for like six months and they re-enabled it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh man, they do this dirty, dirty stuff just to get in there and mine millions of ore and sell it to people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you buy gold online, you are supporting this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I blame you as much as I blame the hackers.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you buy gold online, you support all these accounts getting hacked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Knock it off.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I remember right, in Star Trek Online, we actually do have a report if ever we see anything happening right away.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's set up in the mail and set up on the heads-up display.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which I think is smart.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember Blizzard had anything like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I liked what Ion used to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: They used to have these very public executions on the Ion server.
[SPEAKER_02]: They would have public executions of spammers.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what we need in WoW.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need... This will be the nice thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: OMG, spoiler alert coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Categories of spoiler.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plug your ears if you don't want it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, when Grosh takes over the Horde, since he's like a nasty little man, he should just start executing the spammers.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I want to see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently he's going to be executing everyone else.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he needs to execute the spammers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, end spoiler.
[SPEAKER_02]: Safe to listen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, how about other stuff, Rob?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although I have to give a shout out to Get Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Their ads are really funny and stylistically very good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: As a designer, I like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says, in Soviet Russia, games get you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Two sniffs up.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it looks like old political posters.
Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, 2K Sports, they like a move in Natal.
[SPEAKER_08]: Their marketing dude, Jason Argent, said that the sports games are a natural fit for motion control and was mentioning by name the 2K Major League Baseball series.
[SPEAKER_08]: They didn't really give anything else up on that, but I think that they're pretty pleased with it and going to keep it going.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, good for them.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, Rob, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I should be able to get that big orange bat that you recently dug up, apparently according to your Facebook and with Natal, I should be able to use that bat as I play 2K games You'd have to come over here to get it Because I won't break anything at all doing that in my house The orange bat is awesome
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: But this seems like a natural progression.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, what smarter thing to do than to incorporate that with established franchises?
[SPEAKER_08]: I need a lightsaber.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, this brings a whole new level to Rod Calibur, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think though I hope that what these games do is make this support optional and I think they will I think they know that there's still a hardcore audience especially when you're talking about 2K and you know who knows whatever EA Sports ends up doing I think they still know there's a very hardcore audience that does not want to stand there and flail their arms everywhere to pretend you know what have you
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of like what they do you know it's weird we don't talk about sports games a lot on this show but I kind of like what they do with Madden is that on the Wii they really make the Wii game kind of targeted as the easy type game if you will and then the 360 and the PS3 versions are for the hardcore
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think they should do separate versions.
[SPEAKER_02]: It should just be one version with two different modes.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we'll see what they do.
[SPEAKER_02]: You alright over there?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like death is on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even look like myself, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't believe you put that picture on the website.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't care anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie's in don't give a shit mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please go to OrangeLoungeRadio.com quickly before DarkSakura realizes what she did.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it's really a horrid picture.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think I've ever looked that bad in my life.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what we need?
[SPEAKER_02]: We need like a blingy competition with that picture.
[SPEAKER_02]: A blingy, haven't you ever, well you don't use MySpace, so blingy is the site that puts the glitter and the hearts and all that just MySpace trash all over a picture.
[SPEAKER_02]: So somebody needs to take your picture and blingy-fy it to make it pretty.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the most horrible picture of you ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is wrong with this show tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, we need you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I came home and I washed my face and I was like, fuck it, I don't care how it looks tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it's just you.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just little old me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love these Vicks inhaler things though.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're perfect.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might have to get one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I feel okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm getting better.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just last week was bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I teach for a living and I couldn't talk Wednesday and Thursday and that's bad for a teacher.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's really bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Toegak, by the way, is blingifying your picture right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_08]: Please do not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or I'll never put another picture of me online again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Toegak, send it to me private message, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't post it publicly.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, at least you're not a dirty thief.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that makes it okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: He stole about 14 megs of the code before somebody caught him.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's so messed up.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, the alleged thief, Justin D. May.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wilmington, Delaware is where he lives, apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he's got a lovely little picture all over the internet now.
[SPEAKER_02]: His little mugshot hit all the gaming blogs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, he said, I got online using the Ethernet cable hanging outside their booth because Wi-Fi wasn't working.
[SPEAKER_02]: They stopped me, checked my computer, and saw the Xbox Neighborhood application.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that was on there, they accused me of stealing Breach, even though it's not on my computer.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what he's saying in his defense.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: apparently though the Atomic staff is counter responding to this saying he said several times he knew people and could give us bigger and more important people and he could name names however I have no idea if these people are on the show floor or just hackers at home I would hate to think he got someone's full code and their title is going to be compromised due to this guy I just need to make it clear he didn't say anything specific boy oh boy
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently this guy, oh my god, this guy apparently even spoke up at a panel earlier in the day about Xbox Live Enforcement and the thief wanted to get his gamer tag unbanned.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stephen Tolous, I probably mispronounced that wrong, Tolous, I'm distracted by Jamie's nose blowing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stephen Tolous, the Director of Policy and Enforcement for Xbox Live actually asked the guy what he did and the hacker said he played Forza 3 before release and he said, well, you shouldn't have done that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now if you buy games early from a retailer that breaks street date, that doesn't get players banned, but illegal pre-release play does.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good gosh.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a mess.
[SPEAKER_02]: S2100, Matt in our chatroom says, How stupid does this kid have to be to steal a game that had an ex-Marine at the booth?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't steal shit, especially when there are 60,000 witnesses around.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't steal shit to begin with, but really don't steal shit when there's that many people around.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sometimes the best thefts happen in plain sight.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just dumb.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a dummy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, how about something else that's dumb?
[SPEAKER_08]: Although I kind of get it, but I still think it's a little on the stupid side.
[SPEAKER_08]: The 3.21 firmware update for PS3 removes the option to install other OS.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, no more Linux.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're getting rid of that because of security concerns, they said.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're going to start taking features away from our PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just like, nope, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You shouldn't have this feature anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not smart of Sony to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Sony is getting cocky with all this hacking scene thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I just point to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every time Sony releases some patch, they say it's unhackable, unwinnable.
[SPEAKER_02]: The hackers will never succeed.
[SPEAKER_02]: They will never hack the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is unhackable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Two days later, it's hacked.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, this is what I say.
[SPEAKER_08]: If people want something badly enough, they'll find a way to make it happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so sure enough, they're going to shut off this because apparently there's some exploit now in the PS3 Linux.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm surprised it took that long.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now they are taking away... One bad apple ruins the barrel.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're taking it away from everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: and saying, well, this exploit is just undoable now.
[SPEAKER_02]: We took away Linux, so now you can't do this at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there is a hacker named George Hotz, who was an iPhone hacker, who apparently did crack the code on PS3, and then that's what might have started this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: but the point is is that if people want the hack bad enough there will be something that will reverse engineer the PS3 back to the old patch I mean they do it all the time with the PSP
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think though for the majority of people, for the common person, hardly anyone's going to notice this happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, come on listeners, how many of you were really using this feature?
[SPEAKER_02]: And maybe there's going to be a couple of you that are like, me, me, me, me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if that's you, then you're probably continuing to use your PS3 for its Linux features and therefore you're not going to want to take your PS3 on PlayStation Network and get the update.
[SPEAKER_02]: because that's the only way you're going to be forced to update is when you try to play a game online or if you try to buy a new game, you know, that eventually, you know, the firmware will be on the disks for that later game, Uncharted 3 or whatever game comes later that everybody has to have.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, it's pretty big.
[SPEAKER_08]: I might just put this in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because the way this guy has done it, I actually could see why Sony would make some changes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's just a matter of time before he finds another.
[SPEAKER_02]: He'll find an exploit in a game or something to reverse the firmware back to something old.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on the PSP all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure if Loki were here, he'd say he'd already done it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, it's just...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's too bad that Sony felt the need to patch it out for everyone because this was found when this isn't going to stop it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my point.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is not going to stop the hacking process.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to make it more difficult, yeah, but it's not going to stop it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those that really want to do it are still going to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's just kind of a bummer to those that were using Linux legitimately.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time, I just can't think of a whole lots of reasons.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, yeah, the computer in there was kind of unique, but I think if you harnessed its power for whatever, you're not really playing games with it, and therefore you won't be affected anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's just going to be such a minority of users affected by this.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it still sucks for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should send those angry cards and letters to Sony.
[SPEAKER_02]: What I love about the patch that they did, didn't add a damn thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It didn't add anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was no silver lining to this patch.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, yep, we're just taking this feature away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Toagak says, actually, they are having issues downgrading the PSP from recent firmware as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, it's getting harder.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not going to stop them.
[SPEAKER_02]: It won't stop them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, moving on to other news regarding the Xbox and talking about Game Room.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been playing Game Room a little bit here and there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like it overall.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they probably should have waited about three more months to release it for them to work out some of the bugs, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's showing promise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's put it that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Game Room Game Room
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you were hoping for more games, nope, not going to happen right away.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to Pitfall and Kaboom and some of the other Activision classics and who knows what other little arcade gems they might dig up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Burger time, anyone?
[SPEAKER_02]: But we're not going to start seeing those until late April.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting tidbit, by the way, because I don't think this came up on our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I mentioned it on Bobby's show on the call, but I actually was with a pal, Seg.
[SPEAKER_02]: My friend Seg was playing Game Room on the show floor at Microsoft's booth.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what's really funny is that he actually got the blue screen to death on the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And honestly, it seemed like all he did was set the controller down on top of the computer and it just threw the whole damn thing off balance and it blue screened to death right in front of everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we were playing Game Room on the show floor, and before he managed to crash the thing, I asked the guy, I said, so they're going to be doing weekly releases with this?
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard something like a thousand games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep in mind, I don't have a media badge on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't go to Pax's Media, so I'm just the everyday gamer.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the guy said to me, he said, well, I don't know if weekly releases is what they're going to end up doing, but they want to look at doing regular releases.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know if it'll be weekly.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're already starting to backtrack a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Releases that eat their fiber?
[SPEAKER_02]: It will not be regular.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will be just sporadic and all over the place.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a McDonald's inspired release.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, how about other stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about Miyamoto?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think being a little foolish.
[SPEAKER_08]: He basically thinks that Nintendo has a responsibility to educate the larger audiences about the benefits of gaming that he thinks that most people are afraid of gaming technology.
[SPEAKER_08]: That
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, once they become accustomed to it, there's nothing to be afraid at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about just people don't like games?
[SPEAKER_08]: Some of them just don't like video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think there's a little truth to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, like, my parents don't like video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: My dad doesn't care, but he doesn't really play them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think there are a lot of people that don't get games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, going back to PAX a little bit,
[SPEAKER_02]: Part of the whole, you know, people were very moved by Wil Wheaton's opening speech and all this stuff, which I get because it was very rah, rah, rah.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is our culture.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is our time.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is your place.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nobody's going to judge you here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can be a gamer here and nobody's going to care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well, that says to me that even we as gamers recognize that not everybody gets gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: And don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, games are no different than movies in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you know... It's interactive entertainment.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's interactive entertainment.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, Nookie is interactive entertainment.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, it just depends on what you like.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't get people that hate on games, but I think we recognize there are people that just don't get it for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of stuff I don't get.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like The Hills.
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard The Hills got cancelled finally.
[SPEAKER_02]: It took like five years for this to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't get the hills.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, Heidi and Spencer, why are they famous?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't get that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And some people don't get why Final Fantasy XIII is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: so there are people out there that just aren't going to get games I mean wasn't that Nintendo's whole little thing was that they were going to try and make games more accessible to everybody and they somewhat I don't know I think they somewhat succeeded I mean they've sold tons of consoles and people are all about you know Wii Fit and Wii Sports and all these games that have seemed to cross over into the mainstream you know
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, there is a quote from him I want to read.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has to do with Sony and Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_08]: We feel it's an honor that some form of entertainment style we created is now going to be taken for granted thanks to the attitude taken by other companies.
[SPEAKER_08]: Meaning their adoption of motion control.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aha, so it's the kind of thing where it's like, well, everybody else seems to agree.
[SPEAKER_08]: Imitation is the best form of...
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus, you're forgetting, Microsoft does an incredibly good job of stealing people's ideas and making them better.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think that's what they're trying to do with this whole Natal thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to make it better.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's still debatable.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't really argue that until the system or game or whatever you want to call it itself comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation Move, you know, some of the early feedback was pretty good that it's way more responsive than the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just competition, my friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: Competition.
[SPEAKER_02]: All these companies trying to one-up each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of which, there are a lot of companies out there that are currently trying to get your dollar as far as selling their video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we'll start with Japan this week for the release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a lot of new games on the 360 in Japan this week, but a crap ton of price reductions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Death Smiles, Far Cry 2, Mass Effect, Ninja Blade, Prince of Persia, Tom Clancy, Hawk, all getting price reductions this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, just price reductions.
[SPEAKER_02]: No new games.
[SPEAKER_02]: X-Blades and Tom Clancy's HAWK or Hux.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo Wii, nothing this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really kind of a dry week.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 2, Clover, no Kuni, no Alice.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like the only new game I'm seeing there on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, nothing really new this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a slow week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd think like there's a Dragon Warrior game or something coming out or everything's getting out of the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the PSP, Monochrome is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe that's the sequel to Echochrome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there is one other game coming out, Jude no Atelier, Grimmonaut no Rekinjutsu, Toraware no Morito from Gust, which is, well, it looks like there's this like, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: it's like a time traveling game and cute little slime looking characters and little teddy bears and cute stuff and chicks with enormous breasts so you're very like anime infused game it's a PSP remake apparently of an older game so there you go
[SPEAKER_08]: I've got a couple of UK releases if you're ready Yippee Just two Blue Toad Murder Files Episodes 4, 5, and 6 And Lead and Gold Gangs of the Wild West That's it
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: a game called Again on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an action game from Koei Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then my personal favorite here of the week that's coming out, Squishy Tank on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I love the cover.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course it's from Natsume.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the cover art.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you look at the cover art, it looks like imagine a slime from the Dragon Quest series and somebody is poking it and so it has the angry face because it's being poked, yet it is a tank.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Squishy Tank for $20.
[SPEAKER_07]: Squithy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like match-up colored blocks and make tanks squishy.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Squizzy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Squizzy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, we're ready to get into, I guess, the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're at that part of the show where we're going to dive into the mailbag and read some of your emails here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm reading three.
[SPEAKER_02]: And DarkSakura will try her best to not sniff through them all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you everyone for keeping them short.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, if you want to send us emails, please do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next week, hopefully, we'll be better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com is the place you send emails and DarkSakura reads them like she's going to do right now while I munch on this tortilla.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you haven't eaten it yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been talking.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't eat and talk.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll fucking eat already.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, you talk.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll eat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me know how it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was listening to your podcast at work and noticed Rob wonder why Final Fight and Magic Sword are getting packaged together.
[SPEAKER_08]: The reason?
[SPEAKER_08]: Simply that the developers of the company who are doing the port love Magic Sword.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only way they would have been able to get it released is to bundle it with another game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So can you... So you can think they're completely selfish acts as the reason you're getting Magic Sword.
[SPEAKER_08]: P. A-Z-H-P.
[SPEAKER_08]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: When Rob asks Loki to be a lady...
[SPEAKER_08]: For some reason I had an image of Rob singing Loki Be A Lady to the tune of Luck Be A Lady by Frank Sinatra.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki Be A Lady tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, if you've been a lady to begin with, Loki Be A Lady tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really did that on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I told Loki to be a lady.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently I was drunk.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wink, wink, nudge, nudge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for the email.
[SPEAKER_02]: There should be more random tangents and acts of love.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know there's Guardian Legend fans out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Help me out.
[SPEAKER_08]: But thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so excited about Magic Sword I could piddle.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good evening, Originals Radio and fellow listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is Jeet.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's writing in again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seeing as it's my birthday today, then that I am in the process of getting ready for a night out, I realize I won't be able to attend the live show today, which I regret as it is always something fun and enlightening.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember myself when I was under the age of 18 and had no problem purchasing one of the worst slash best murder simulators of all time, Grand Theft Auto 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am not really shocked that I managed to pull it off, but I am a bit dismayed that the retailers don't seem to care.
[SPEAKER_08]: So the question is, Do you think it's too easy for children to acquire mature rated games, or are the measures taken by retailers good enough?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry for any and all spelling errors and or grammatical mistakes, and have a happy Easter, everyone.
[SPEAKER_08]: G. Ditz, The Other Swede
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: If the kid gets the game that's on the parent, not on the store.
[SPEAKER_02]: I pretty much agree with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Totally.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stores do the best they can.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think if stores are shown to not be following the rules, then action should be taken accordingly.
[SPEAKER_02]: They do the same thing with cigarettes and alcohol and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But ultimately, it's up to the parents.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you don't know if somebody might have an older brother who will go in and buy the game for them or a friend who's older, a cousin, I don't know, that's kind of like the hookup.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's nothing the stores can do about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if a kid wants an M-rated game bad enough and finds that hookup, then they're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless the parents say, if I catch you playing that game, I'm going to fucking throw your Xbox in the trash.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's something my parents would have said.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what it ultimately comes down to.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think my mom would have said, when did you get this?
Rob, that is gross.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is that game that you're playing?
[SPEAKER_02]: That is gross.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, did he just knock the head off?
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, what are you playing?
[SPEAKER_11]: Mortal Kombat Fatalities are funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Last one.
[SPEAKER_08]: He put a lot of information on here, but I'm not going to say it until I have his express permission to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just wanted to give you a quick update on the whole fiasco going on with GameCrazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is the guy who's the manager in Colorado.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: My store, along with four others in the Denver slash Pueblo area, the only two stores in Colorado remain, is now starting liquidation this Friday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie, I really hope that Dan is still safe, and if not, I guess we are all in this together.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wish me luck with everything that will be coming my and or our way.
[SPEAKER_08]: And to think I almost bought a 3D HDTV at Best Buy yesterday, but my little guardian angel was telling me not to, and now I know why.
[SPEAKER_08]: Frowny face.
[SPEAKER_08]: Please let me know what is going on in your neck of the woods.
[SPEAKER_08]: One good thing to pass on, a lot of my customers are now listening to your show and love it, so keep it up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care, dude.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, then I apologize to your customer base for tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm sorry to hear it, dude.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope it works out for the best.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I hope you're able to find something somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, those customers are going to have to go somewhere, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: This is also dated from March 22nd, so he might have heard already.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dan dodged the bullet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good for him.
[SPEAKER_08]: They closed down a bunch of other stores, but Dan's store was still a pretty well-performing store.
[SPEAKER_08]: So he's like, we didn't get any inventory.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were running out and we were sad and we thought we were going to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we got a shipment.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then they said, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Dan's store is still around for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dan is also awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a thought that his might be one of the ones to survive Chapter 11 if the company survives.
[SPEAKER_08]: He just said he was a little disappointed because he hates driving to Cameron Park.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's far.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've never been there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It snows and shit there, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of far.
[SPEAKER_08]: so um manager dude which I'm calling you until you say I can actually say it's you I mean it put a store number and everything but I don't want to jump the gun yeah yeah um
[SPEAKER_08]: I say write it out through liquidation.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take your unemployment.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I hope that you... Oh my god, this show is so broken.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I hope that something works out well for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And thank you for, by the way, spreading us around like a disease.
[SPEAKER_08]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Robin, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did I ever tell you about the Dorbola?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was the... Not Anime Expo.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was...
[SPEAKER_08]: Faname 2000, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: My first Faname.
[SPEAKER_08]: When I did my Emmy cosplay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, all the Bay Area DDR players and everything were getting sick from an illness that was, in theory, started by a certain moderator at the time on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I thought, oh, I'm not going to get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all over.
[SPEAKER_08]: The epidemic's gone.
[SPEAKER_08]: I came back home sick with Dorbola.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Con, con crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I did get your email on my personal email address and I've just been swamped, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, I have heard that there are game stores out there and like little computer places, well, not little, but you know, like LAN centers and stuff that actually play this show at the center.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think that's rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, thank you guys so much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, we really ought to tone down the swearing so that it would be okay for more places to play us.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't say shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet we're a heck of a lot more interesting than those stupid tapes they probably send them to play with all the like, you know, Hi, I'm Jeff Keighley and let's see what game's coming out next.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, like that stuff probably gets really old to see on loop over and over again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think, you know, podcasts are kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll have to think about cleaning it up someday.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're verbal kitsch, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're verbal kitsch.
[SPEAKER_08]: But back to the subject at hand, dude, I feel really rotten for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shoot me another email to my real email and I will respond to you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just so sorry that this crap is happening.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of it is their own fault for their marketing strategy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that GameStop really started dominating the market.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might just want to send with your email, though, some E. Perel.
[SPEAKER_02]: As SalaciousPop in chat says, this episode needs to come with some Perel.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie's about to go flush her head in the toilet to get it to stop hurting.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, backing up to some earlier messages in chat room from when I was impersonating my mother.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mamesatsuma says, Sky's parents were from Sesame Street.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tigerclaw said, Rob was probably like, hey mom, watch this.
[SPEAKER_02]: He does a fatality in the game and she just goes ballistic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Julian went up to Becky and picked his nose and said, Yummy!
[SPEAKER_08]: With a big grin on his face.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just to, I guess, see reaction.
[SPEAKER_08]: This two-year-old has mastered smart, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's a smart kid.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then he shook his head and goes, Yucky.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yucky.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100 Matt says no don't tone down the language everybody's getting freaked out that we're suddenly going to go G-rated no we're not going to tone down the language it would be nice if I had the time or one of us had the time or somebody had the time that we could go through the episode and beep out obscenities and that way you could have like a G-rated version you know safe for broadcast but let's face it we're all too lazy it's not going to happen I mean Loki's on this program I mean there's just it's not going to happen not going to happen
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, by the way, if you want to send in some emails, you should do so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com is the place to send them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now's the part of the show where we show a little angst and anger and say, F you, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess I'll start the FUs tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no, you're back?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura starts off tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Something fell.
[SPEAKER_08]: A few of my allergies and the Sacramento area for being rife with plant life.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope it all burns.
[SPEAKER_08]: Except for me and my stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And yours.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need to see your new house.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's quaint.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come over next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no, you have other stuff next weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come over soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's have breakfast on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to Pax East Plague.
[SPEAKER_02]: Am I the only one that has it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I am.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you, Pax East Plague.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I would like to say non-F you to these lovely triple chocolate M&Ms that DarkSakura just gave me.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are purple and sparkly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to take pictures of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the gayest food I think I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dude, that's what I said in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob, I'm going to bring you some of the gayest food I've ever eaten.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is very gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Matt in the chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a good question.
[SPEAKER_02]: And sure, we'll let chatters derail the flow of the show tonight because I don't care tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, this show is already fucked up as it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Matt says, serious question for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did your parents think of you guys playing DDR?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dance Dance Revolution, the game that brought this show together.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, what did your parents think?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, well, you were really living with your parents at that time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was trying to explain it to my mom.
[SPEAKER_08]: She was like, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was pretty much it with my parents, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, obviously, I'd moved out of the house by then.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was living on my own.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would have been like, God, what year did we all start playing DDR?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was 2000 for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'd have been 21.
[SPEAKER_02]: You were just a young'un.
[SPEAKER_02]: 10 years ago, I'd have been 21.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: I was already out of the house by then so my parents didn't really know but they found out later on because when we started doing the tournaments and stuff like remember we ended up on the news sometimes and then like you know our show ended up on the news and some of that stuff and so my parents were kind of like okay well like I think they just don't get it I think my mom just kind of giggles like I think she kind of points and laughs at me but doesn't like outright do that because I'm her kid
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just in that kind of mood tonight where I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's give somebody a call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's find out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I need to know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just have to know the answer to this question.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a very good question that S.J.
[SPEAKER_02]: and her mat's posing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi mom, it's Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: She hung up on me.
[SPEAKER_02]: My mother just hung up on me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe she doesn't want to be on the radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's try this again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Live radio, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it working?
[SPEAKER_02]: Stupid Skype.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's try this one more time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then I'm going to give up.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do tape live every Sunday night at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com, right after the Bobby Blackwolf show, 6 o'clock Pacific.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, All Games Radio, for letting us steal your bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Scott has a new show starting, Appaday TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can call mine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, it's Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you there?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You keep hanging up on me.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I didn't hang up on you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're on the radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: all right say hi what say hi to the listeners mommy
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, Mommy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, this is Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't seen you in a while, but hi.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now everybody at work is sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh
[SPEAKER_02]: What did you think of it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I knew.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was good exercise.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was good exercise.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was probably never at my thinnest, or I was never thinner than I was when I played that, huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: Except when you had pancreatitis.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's absolutely true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Am I supposed to not like it or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me ask you this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Were there ever video games that I played growing up that you didn't like?
[SPEAKER_05]: That I didn't like?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't particularly fond of the very violent games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I just don't think it's particularly good for children to be playing those kind of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: War games and things like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you ever catch me playing a bad video game and you grounded me?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I don't really remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just remember you... No, because you had pretty good taste.
[SPEAKER_05]: You didn't really like those violent games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now that's not true.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, I was really good at hiding it from you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, maybe so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe I just... Never tell your mother how sneaky and devious you were as a child.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, she knows all about that stuff now because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: My sister and I will get together and exchange stories with my mother sitting right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, but the other thing... Do you remember a game called Mortal Kombat that I used to play?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I didn't like that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, wasn't it gross?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was pretty gross.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I was doing an impersonation earlier that you would come in the room and you would say, Rob, what is that game?
[SPEAKER_02]: That is a gross game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Turn off that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's gross.
[SPEAKER_05]: You were a little older then, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: You weren't real.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you were like 14, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it was okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was at the point where it was okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you weren't real.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm thinking 5, 6, 7, 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't think that would be appropriate for a child that age.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a matter of taste, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: And for one thing, I'm not that well coordinated.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd probably fail at it, you know, because
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you've been doing it ever since you were a little kid, so you're pretty well-coordinated.
[SPEAKER_05]: As far as using the joystick and stuff, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'd rather be entertained rather than trying to entertain myself like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not interested in getting a Wii?
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't want to do Wii bowling?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you going to give me a Wii?
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to give me a Wii?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you want a Wii?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that what you want for Christmas?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but you acted like you were trying to get me to say, oh, yeah, I'd love to have a Wii so you could get me one.
[SPEAKER_02]: You wouldn't use it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why I'm not going to get you one.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first time I'd wear myself out and then I'd say never again.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything you want to say to the listeners of our fine radio program, the five people?
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to ask them why they don't have something better to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: 10-15 on the East Coast
[SPEAKER_08]: My mom doesn't live on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_08]: She lives in Central Time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Central Time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So 9-15.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wake her up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, here you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Punch in the number one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mobile.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Easter with the family here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it did not like that number.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did I do wrong?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mom's phone number acts wonky sometimes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you show it to me one more time here?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, give me a sec.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: The top one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here it goes.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's calling.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, it's all you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on, Mom.
[SPEAKER_02]: She went to bed.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're in trouble.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's not sleeping.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's out partying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's leave her a voicemail.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, this is Kathy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry I can't take your call right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please leave me a message.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's so adorable.
[SPEAKER_00]: At the tone, please record your message.
[SPEAKER_00]: When you have finished recording, you may hang up or press 1 for more options.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi Mommy, it's your spawn.
[SPEAKER_08]: The female one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your voicemail is live on Orange Nolts Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were trying to call you because it was funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you would have been an internet celebrity.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you missed your chance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry Mom.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were going to ask you about video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: The terrible influence they had on your child.
[SPEAKER_08]: So call back this number.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it'll work.
[SPEAKER_02]: It shows up as like 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll poo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Text Jamie and we'll call you back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Love you, Mom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye, Mom's voicemail.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now we've successfully derailed the show three times over.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, and we had a canine visitor.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, and I'm not a big fan of big dogs, so that kind of scared the hell out of me, but thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: All of a sudden, I just turn around.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a dog in my life.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drew, did you know I was bit by a dog when I was five years old?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've had issues with them ever since.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what you said.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just in case the listeners don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not a fan of big dogs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, how about video games?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I put up the picture of the very gay M&M's.
[SPEAKER_02]: Grand Theft Auto Chinatown Wars
[SPEAKER_02]: So meaning that when you take the other M-rated titles, Dementium, The Ward, Resident Evil Deadly Silence, Touch the Dead, Core, Ultimate Mortal Kombat, and all these games, and you add them all up, it doesn't match what Grand Theft Auto Chinatown Wars has sold.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is kind of interesting because Grand Theft Auto Chinatown Wars, the sales overall, have tended to be considered a disappointment.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they even came out and said, you know, they were blaming it on piracy.
[SPEAKER_02]: That the commercial performance of Chinatown Wars has certainly suffered at the hands of piracy was an earlier quote about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's interesting because it just goes to show M-rated games are not selling on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time, I kind of think, well, duh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Most DS owners are kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, true story.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was at Outback last night.
[SPEAKER_02]: The table next to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: What does the little kid have that's waiting for his little...
[SPEAKER_02]: Little Joey, you know what they call the young kangaroo menu, the Joey menu, waiting for his little kid steak.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was playing a DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably Pokemon or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Pokemanses.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the DS is like most popular with kids, like tweens, if you will.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, of course, the M-rated games are not going to sell that well because my mother would not have bought me that game when I was growing up.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe they just need to make some better games, but honestly, I just don't think the DS is the platform for an M-rated game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's mostly kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, what's up next?
[SPEAKER_08]: Some stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy IX, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are planning on putting Final Fantasy IX on PSN, and it was confirmed by Yoichi Iwata that it would join Final Fantasy VII and VIII on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yay, all the VV you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's free money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, for putting a nostalgic game that everybody knows and loves back on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although it was probably a Final Fantasy a lot of people skipped over.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think IX sold quite as well as the other ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't play that much of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I played more of IX than I did of VIII because I actually liked IX.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually got past the first disc on IX.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't beat it, but I went pretty far in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a good game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was, you know, that more traditional Final Fantasy as opposed to that cyberpunk kind of looking thing, and that was its big thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about some Twitter topics?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know if we got Twitter topics tonight, but we're going to go ahead and take some Twitter topics now on our Twitter, twitter.com slash O-L-R.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I'm trying to load the Twitter right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully I'll be able to filter out all the tweets about Justin Bieber.
[SPEAKER_02]: Saga confirms closure of internal Iron Man and Golden Axe developer Do you know where that Sega office was located?
[SPEAKER_02]: San Francisco oh yeah I've driven by there yeah a lot of us have it's right there off I-80 you can't miss it yeah Sega Studios San Francisco has been closed they were making the Iron Man movie tie-in games Golden Axe, Beast Rider unfortunately the rumors were going around and they closed it that one hits very close to home that's a bummer
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought Sega was having a resurgence in popularity with Bayonetta.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, that game they showed, Resonance of Fate, was that what it was called?
[SPEAKER_02]: At PAX East?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, it looked pretty rad, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Sega's having a renaissance, but I guess the Iron Man movie tie-in games are not exactly how to do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if it's something I would spend the extra money on, but I think it's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, it's cool that the game's kind of coming to the US at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, like, we just talked about how I think it was getting a limited edition in Japan, but I guess this whole, actually this giant collection is only like 50 bucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, can't say I'm a huge fan of it, so I don't know if I could justify spending that kind of money, but I think it's cool that it's even coming out at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe a friend of mine will get it and I can check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alex P. Carson says, your OLR logo is my Xbox gamer picture.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you know, and it's been a long time, but you can actually search for what's called community gamer pics on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're in the pack two.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like the all games radio pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Evil Protagonist says, I don't have a topic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to tell you all how much I look forward to listening each and every week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for all you do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's very nice and I apologize for this week's show because it's kind of shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: BlueSwim also says, Rob, your mom's burn on the OLR listeners was epic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, that's where I get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lastly, Spazinator, our good buddy, asks a WTF question.
[SPEAKER_02]: If Major Nelson is the mouth of Microsoft, who is the asshole or appendix of Microsoft?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, that's a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's the asshole of Microsoft?
[SPEAKER_02]: um my best guess I mean I don't think there's anybody who's just like a straight up jerk that I can think of but definitely a lot of what comes out of Peter Molyneux's mouth is so that would be my best guess for you there it is ah Rob you know what I just got done typing what's that she'll cut a bitch for what it's a Kathy Griffin album oh isn't that a book or something
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I think that it's one of our shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: A couple more news stories for you guys, and we have the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeehaw.
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft, speaking of which, well, this is kind of an asshole thing to do, but not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: I get why they're doing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are suing Datel over the TurboFire controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Wildfire is what it's called in the UK, which is where Datel is from.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, they say, you know what, this looks a little bit too much like an Xbox 360 controller, and I gotta say...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it definitely kind of looks like an Xbox 360 controller, but I kind of always thought the third-party controllers all resembled the original controllers somewhat.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, Microsoft is seeking monetary compensation and an injunction preventing the company from manufacturing any more of the devices.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, Datel and Microsoft, they've been going back and forth for a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would guess that this was not a licensed Microsoft peripheral and that's part of the problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you might remember Datel, they made the memory cards that got the shaft from Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think that's what this... This is just these two companies just kind of going back and forth at each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a bummer because maybe the D-pad on this thing would have been better.
[SPEAKER_02]: And judging from the looks of it, it doesn't look so like a round D-pad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might have actually been a little better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of a bummer.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft, you know, they did make that controller and they patented it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you make something a little too close, that's why people get sued.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially when you're not already in the company's good favor.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sony's gonna sue.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody loves to sue.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish I could sue my face.
[SPEAKER_08]: What a quote.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there's an MMO that's called PokéNet that was a fan-run MMORPG based on Pokémon.
[SPEAKER_08]: And...
[SPEAKER_08]: It was... Actually, Nintendo sent the request for them to shut it down at the end of March.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they postponed closing it, but they actually formally shut it down on April Fool's Day.
[SPEAKER_02]: And... And that's no joke.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's just a number of them that have been shut down, but this is just the newest one.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then they said, for the code that they created for the game, they're joking about using it for Digimon or Monster Ranger.
[SPEAKER_08]: But most of their devs are giving up.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be a funny little FU, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a bummer, but it's not a surprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pokemon is one of Nintendo's most treasured MMOs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see that these guys are just trying to make the game that everybody wants, which is the Pokemon MMO.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what tons and tons of gamers everywhere want.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've talked about it on this show.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be a great thing for the franchise, and for whatever reason, Nintendo is just refusing to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably because of the fact that it's a kid-based game, and that would be very hard to keep safe and clean.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's probably part of the reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: but I mean it's a bummer but I think Nintendo's within their rights certainly you know especially if it wasn't a quality product but I do think if the guys are that passionate about the product they should go back and make it a different type of monster
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean that would take a lot of re-art and all that stuff and plus if it's too close to the Pokemon idea it might still get the smackdown but I mean Pokemon and Digimon can coexist and you know they're not that different I mean yes there's differences but they come down to little pocket monsters and collecting catch them all yada yada but Nintendo's done that a lot lately they shut down the Zelda project the movie thing remember that
[SPEAKER_02]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't just go around making all this fake stuff because somebody out there is going to think it's real and that's where the real problems start.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, this was real, and this was licensed by Nintendo, and no matter what, Nintendo will never make this go away.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Super Show!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, the one with, rest in peace, Captain Lou Albano, starred as Mario, and of course, you know, they would do all these cute little live-action skits, and then they had the cartoons.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if you want to relive this from your childhood, or if you never got to experience this as a child to begin with, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on Netflix!
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can actually go check this out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe it is on instant Netflix right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can go stream volume one of the collection and check out what you missed as a kid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually have either volume one or volume two.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have one of the collections on DVD and it is so cheesy cheeserific.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to give you a clue how amazing, here's a blast from the past.
[SPEAKER_02]: Listen up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey Bizanos, it's the Mario Brothers Super Show!
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll be hooked on the brothers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you ever watch this show growing up, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, except I was really religious about watching Zelda on Friday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, excuse me, princess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't believe that is a part of this because the Zelda collection's different.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zelda was on a different DVD.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know if you can stream those yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the chatroom's bitching about the audio quality.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, boo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_02]: all right anyhow it's that part of the show where we really like to take a look back at classic gaming's history and pick one game to spotlight in a segment we call our classic game of the week
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura is going to dig through the gaming vaults, she's going to dive in head first, and she's going to sniff really loud, and whatever sticks to her nose first will be the game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So DarkSakura, what did NosePond pick as the game of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, it was Dan that picked the game, so you can blame him.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's a fabulous game you picked this week, so I thank Dan for this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's Super Mario World 2 Yoshi's Island.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw yeah, one of the best ones in the whole damn series.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, you go around as Yoshi and you have baby Mario on your back.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you can play different Yoshis.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's supposed to be a prequel for Super Mario World, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Technically, by the story.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I mean, your life bar is your baby Mario when he falls off your back.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to go, he floats around in a little bubble and you have to go catch him.
[SPEAKER_08]: And he gives the single most annoying cry ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously, I think this game scared me away from children for a long time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um... But, I mean, you go through.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's also, uh... Eating certain enemies give you certain colored eggs.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can throw them.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can eat certain enemies and shoot them just right back at themselves.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, um... This is a pretty fun little game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: and also if you get a perfect score in all 8 of the regular levels you'll get a secret level and there are 5 flowers that you can pick up in each stage and you have red coins and all kinds of fun stuff that you can find um
[SPEAKER_08]: So basically, you have to go and get baby Luigi back from Magikoopa Comic.
[SPEAKER_08]: It also uses the Super FX 2 for sprite scaling and polygon effects.
[SPEAKER_08]: And all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But...
[SPEAKER_08]: It was actually, the particular style for it, the rumor is that it came from an internal evaluation committee conflict with the Nintendo, and Miyamoto was instructed to use the Donkey Kong Country style of pre-rendered graphics, and so he altered them to look as if they had been drawn with crayons.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I always thought this game kind of had a unique look to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of cool that that's where it came from.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that actually was given the award for Best Game of 1995 by EGM.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a great game.
[SPEAKER_08]: As far as sequels, though, we've had Yoshi Touch and Go and Yoshi's Universal Graviton for the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember Touch and Go.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then Yoshi's Story came out on Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was Yoshi's Island DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yoshi's Island was used in the SNES and Game Boy versions of Tetris Attack as a background game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is this on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure the chatters will correct me if I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it is on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Yoshi.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is also the game with Touch Fuzzy Get Dizzy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was an amazing moment in gaming history.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you don't know what Touch Fuzzy Get Dizzy is, I'm sure... It's got to be on YouTube somewhere, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Please tell me it's on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Touch...
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuzzy.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't type today.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sick and there's earthquakes and I can't type.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Touch Fuzzy, get dizzy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is the level that's hilarious because when you would touch these big fuzzy looking things, then your guy would just go psycho.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, I think this is like a speed run.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about this one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Touch Fuzzy, get stoned.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fucking people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently someone put in clips of a Raiden DX.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that has everything to do with Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Comments from our chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shaoran says, that game, it kicked my ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not afraid to admit it.
[SPEAKER_02]: TigerClaw said, never played this game, but it seems like Nintendo always retconned the Mario games.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Mario and Luigi knew about the Mushroom Kingdom since they were toddlers.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were that young.
[SPEAKER_07]: They wouldn't have remembered it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Salacious Pops says, I thought it had some kind of new chip in it that they debuted with the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it was the FX2 chip, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it was the Super FX2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It made it a bitch to emulate for a long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember that was one of the prized emulated games when it finally happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, believe it or not, we're reaching the end of our show and the part where we're going to open up the Skype line to your calls.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: The phone lines are open.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're taking calls right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a short show tonight because as you can tell, we're a little bit sick and out of it tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Benadryl
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn it, call us, people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next week, Loki should be back, and hopefully he won't be sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: He'll be fresh from my birthday beer potluck.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully I'll be feeling better.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm having a beer potluck for my birthday.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm coming.
[SPEAKER_08]: So soon?
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what was something we ought to look into for the show, by the way?
[SPEAKER_02]: Last night at the show at Rocky, somebody had this app on their iPhone 3GS that was a Ustream app so you could actually stream video from your iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you might want to look into that for your phone to see if we can do webcam again with your iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you could be the camera woman on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: That might be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is no one calling in?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing's happening?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to call in and share a story with us, you can.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alpha Cananogram says I should leave a drunk voicemail from the beer potluck.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll probably have to drive, so I don't think that'll be happening because I'm a good boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some callers are saying that they get the voicemail when they call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, nothing is ringing through, so keep trying, folks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, DarkTetsuya is probably calling in trying to talk about WonderCon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you know that happened this weekend, WonderCon?
[SPEAKER_02]: A big, big convention that happened in San Francisco over the weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a huge deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's like the second biggest comic book convention only next to Comic Con and yeah I was going on in San Francisco this weekend sadly I couldn't go I was in San Francisco but I'm still so sick and I was kind of conned out which is also bad you know what I'm gonna restart Skype just in case something is going wrong with the Skypey thing let me just quit quit quit I'm gonna quit and I'm gonna reboot Skype and we'll see if we get a call
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, I have to log in because I don't ever save the password.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it is Easter, so it's a little bit slower of a night anyway, so we might not get a lot of calls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby apparently had no calls on his show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought he had at least one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody said they were trying to call, but they got a busy signal, so I thought, okay, let's restart Skype and see what happens.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's my mom.
[SPEAKER_02]: She did something.
[SPEAKER_02]: My mother, when she told all the listeners to go outside, basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: She grounded Skype.
[SPEAKER_02]: She did.
[SPEAKER_02]: She put Skype on timeout.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe, um...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably doing homework, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Non-stop party for you, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: What are you studying these days?
[SPEAKER_02]: What are you going to be when you grow up?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully a designer, which I'm already doing now, but I'm working on a website for my Dreamweaver class.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank God, we're getting a call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Lines Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yar had his revenge.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yars Revenge
[SPEAKER_10]: Astro Smash.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: And no, I've been playing Final Fantasy XIII as the real game, quote-unquote, that I've been playing.
[SPEAKER_10]: How far are you into that game at this point?
[SPEAKER_10]: I am on Chapter 10, so if I was on the Xbox 360, I would have just put in Disc 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, you are way past me because I think I'm on, like, Chapter 9.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the best place to farm gill.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the airship, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm way back then.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like maybe chapter 7.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm in Palimporum.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I just... I got to Hope's dad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, I'm not trying to spoil too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's where I quit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got Hope's dad in the little emo scene with that and then I stopped.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like right after that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_10]: Best place to farm money.
[SPEAKER_10]: All those soldiers drop those credit chips and incentive chips, and those give 500 gil and 2,500 gil each.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So when I'm on the airship, I should farm a crap ton of gil.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pro tip.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good tip.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any games that you're looking forward to that are coming out in the near future, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: E3 this year?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm hoping to go to E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did finally get my tax return so I can finally start booking things.
[SPEAKER_10]: I couldn't go to PAX East because I decided buying a house was more important.
[SPEAKER_02]: Priorities.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm still a renter so I had that disposable income that you needed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm definitely going to E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm making it happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have you guys talked about the Blur beta at all?
[SPEAKER_02]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you want to say about it?
[SPEAKER_10]: I still haven't figured out if it's insanely good or insanely bad yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_10]: What makes the game insane?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it's Mario Kart meets Need for Speed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which is a great idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's basically what the game is.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it depends on the map that you're playing.
[SPEAKER_10]: If it's fair or not, if you're not extremely good at it or know all the sight lines and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: And what sucks is that I'm only good at one map and that's the one map nobody chooses.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it is fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's actually a game I don't mind playing with random people because I just don't listen to them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't turn on my headset when I'm playing that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But do you think you'll pick up the full version when it comes out?
[SPEAKER_10]: I will at least rent it because I want to see how the single player is.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm still looking forward to Split Second.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: But what worries me about Split Second is that I don't want... Because I loved Full Auto.
[SPEAKER_10]: because the demo I played at E3 was amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then I got the game and I didn't like it all that much.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know Loki did, but he's not there.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm afraid Split Second made an amazing demo and the rest of the game won't live up to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm really afraid of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know what's interesting is that they were parading split second around PAX East, and it looks like they brought the same damn booth to PAX East that they had at E3, although it was configured differently for the space.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was the same demo, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't say that with 100% certainty because I don't remember that far back, but I think it was the same darn demo that we had at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's interesting that this game is still not out.
[SPEAKER_10]: At the airport or something where the control tower's crashing around you and stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it seemed like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I honestly didn't really play it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I watched for a little bit, and it just seemed the same to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looked like I was looking at the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't pick out a lot of those little graphical things and things like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, imagine it has to be a newer version, but it was probably like the same stages or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: not really because I guess looking from a game developer point of view they're not going to spend too much more resources just to show kids at PAX East true because the PAX demo at PAX Prime was the same as the E3 demo so it's very possible that they just instead of spending the money making a new demo they're trying to get the game out in time because I think it's supposed to come out before E3 so they're not going to spend time making a new E3 demo no
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't see them for PAX East, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't see them spending all that time making a new demo when they have a perfectly good one from E3 that is impressive.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: And probably a lot of people that were at that expo had never played it before because it was a totally different crowd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Bobby, anything else on your mind before we try to go back and see if we get any other calls tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or maybe it'll just be you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yar.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to work on that this week, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I told you on your show, I've never been better at Yar's Revenge of My Life until you inspired me to kick your butt.
[SPEAKER_10]: and you haven't kicked it yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've one-upped you a couple times.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've made you work.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to admit that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I made you work.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, you did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then you bowed down and... Alright, shut up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Somebody else call in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't make it just me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, have a good one, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: See ya.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so we know it works.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby got through.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least the Skype line works.
[SPEAKER_02]: We know that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know it calls out okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: We called my mommy earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: 877-GAME-OLR Username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm starting to feel like really headachy so I don't know how much longer we can keep this show going but we're gonna try to get at least one more call in on our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then we're going to wrap up the show we will be back next week with an all new edition of Orange Lounge Radio of course same bat time, same bat channel I think I mentioned it a minute ago but I should make sure to plug this because after all we do steal the man's bandwidth every week our old putty putty, silly putty
[SPEAKER_02]: Our old buddy, Scott Rubin, who hosts, he's kind of the grand poobah, if you will, of All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: He is starting his own little show, but it's actually a big show, at Appaday.tv, and he's reunited with Diane Miazota.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like G4 back when they were cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, we're getting a call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Henderson, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hi, Henderson, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome to the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I've been a long-time listener.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've probably listened for like the last two years.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, it was your show that introduced me to All Games Radio years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now I have my own live show on Saturdays on All Games.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is your show?
[SPEAKER_04]: Distributed Failure, we come on at 3 p.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pacific time on Saturdays.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have heard of that program.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: So make sure Scott knows that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: People have heard of us.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what is on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_02]: What do we owe the phone call tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wanted to say, you know, you guys look like you're having trouble with Skype, and I just wanted to call in and say hey, and tell you guys I'm a long-time listener, and I did finish Final Fantasy XIII, which I thought was decent, but I still think it's low on the totem pole of Final Fantasy games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not as low as VIII.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think VIII is the worst Final Fantasy game ever created.
[SPEAKER_04]: You and I can agree on at least one thing, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would rather play I didn't care much for 7 either but I did love 9 I think 9 is one of the best at least it's the best one on the PS1 era I would rather level a character from 1 through 75 on Final Fantasy 11 than play 5 more minutes of Final Fantasy 8
[SPEAKER_04]: I even bought the PSN version to try to go back and finish it because it's like one of the only ones I've never finished and I couldn't do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still couldn't get to our first disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: What made me mad originally when I played it is I got to a section of the game and it's kind of spoiler-ish but not really because basically... There's only a six month moratorium on spoilers and it's passed so spoil away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, your female character that's supposed to be your girlfriend in the game, I can't think of her name right now, but there's a section of the game where you go to a location because she gets taken, and when she gets taken, she's in this tower where all the enemies are level 1, and you're supposed to have a special summons or whatever that can raise the levels so you can gain levels.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I got stuck at a boss there and couldn't get past the boss because the boss was too tough, but I couldn't gain any levels because everything was like level 1.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I tried to leave and it wouldn't let you leave so I got stuck in this endless loop and I just eventually couldn't do anything so I just quit playing the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stupid ass system in that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a dumb ass system.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean the whole weapon system was ridiculous where you had to go around finding these items to upgrade your weapon so basically every battle in that game ended up being oh I'll just summon this monster that takes forever to watch all of its animation.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wonderful story, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will say this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy VIII had a great story.
[SPEAKER_02]: They should have just made it the movie, honestly.
[SPEAKER_02]: They should have just made it the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it did have a great story, but yeah, that was, the gameplay ruined that game so, so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I try to go back to it on PSP, and it actually looks decent on PSP, which is amazing because, you know, it is a PlayStation 1 game, but that smaller screen and everything being so compact, it does make the graphics stand out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It makes it better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even Yars' Revenge looks awesome on my LCD monitor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know, there's just a certain, there's just something to it that we didn't have back in, you know, back in the day of gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been tempted to play that game because I remember playing that game when I was like five and six years old, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I just remember you go in that little middle section and the bullets wouldn't hurt you and all that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But man, I picked up Adventure on there, but I haven't tried it yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to pick it up because, you know, it's Adventure.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I also picked up Crystal Castle, which is kind of hard to control on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because that game needs a trackball, not an analog stick.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't imagine that that... I haven't played that one yet, I'll be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've kind of avoided it because I know it can't control that well, but I worry about the whole trackball versus analog stick.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Yars' Revenge, seriously, best five bucks I've spent on Xbox Live in the past six months.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: GameRoom
[SPEAKER_02]: Bad Dudes vs. Dragon Age
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you a bad enough dude to eat a cheeseburger with the mayor?
[SPEAKER_02]: The president.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the mayor was final fight.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's okay, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then that'll get a lot of eyes back on Game Room, but hopefully they get all their stinking server problems figured out by that point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, did you happen to see that Data East collection that came out on Wii?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if that's came out yet or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got BurgerTime and Bad Dudes on there, so that's why I'm kind of hoping it'll come to Game Room.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't played it myself, but I believe it has the sequel to BurgerTime as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love me some BurgerTime.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been tempted to try to find that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it seems like a pretty good deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't played it myself, but it'll be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, DarkTetsu's reminding me in chat, NARC is M-rated anyway, so it can't come to Game Room.
[SPEAKER_00]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Technicality.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just turn the blood into sweat.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what they did back in my day.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, Henderson, man, we're going to let you go to try and squeeze in one more call.
[SPEAKER_02]: But thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_02]: And distributed failure... Distributed fail... I'm sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Distributed... Distributed failure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Failure.
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said you can find the archives at distributedfailure.com so if anybody wants to listen and check it out, it's there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're live on Saturdays.
[SPEAKER_02]: Best of luck with your show, sir.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you very much, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell the crew at Distributed Failure we all said hey.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, and bye, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, sniffle sniffle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's try to get at least one more call in.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something seems to be borked with the phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: The actual phone people, I think, are having problems tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_02]: You all heard me call my mother.
[SPEAKER_02]: It seemed to be working fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I don't know what's up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your guess is as good as mine.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll give it just a couple more minutes for a call to come in, and if it doesn't come in, then I'll just chalk up the phone's not working to just yet another thing going wrong today between the earthquakes and the rainstorm and the plague.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think Zombie Jesus did it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, Ranma's trying to call in.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkTetsuya's trying to call in.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Spazinator on Twitter said he was going to call in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something appears to be wrong with the phone line itself.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, watch.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet if I call... Like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Watch, I'm going to call my cell right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's calling.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there, my phone's ringing.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's working.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: The phone's stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the earthquakes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's blame it on the earthquakes.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess we're just going to have to close up shop for the night and blame the earthquakes for taking down Skype tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: you can always leave voicemails send us emails as well mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com I know DarkSakura probably wanted to call in to talk about WonderCon but he also did a fabulous write up that's available on the site orangeloungeradio.com if you want to read that he has a whole little wrap up on WonderCon hopefully we'll get some of these people in next week I'm sure Ranma wanted to call in to talk about Anime Boston I know he was there but sadly Skype got earthquakeed or something I don't know what's going on
[SPEAKER_02]: Shaoran in chat says, blame it on the rain.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blame it on the rain Blame it on the rain Blame it on the rain
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, thanks for being here and sticking it out through the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I live here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you have a final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: My Ben Angel's kind of working.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought is Mucinex is my friend, and I'm going to go take some more right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a great night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see you next week with another edition of Orange Lounge Radio that won't be so broken.
[SPEAKER_02]: And have a plan in case of an earthquake.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Over this next week, have your earthquake plan prepared.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good night!
[SPEAKER_01]: But we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next week!