Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts? DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
April Fools is always a hoot now that we are Google Map Pokemon Masters and own our own flux capacitors
But the top joke this week was Amazon taking over our TV
Music, movies, and TV shows aren't new but they said it would play games too
Tell us your favorite joke on the show where every gamer has a voice
Wait, what? That wasn't on April 1st?
I guess I'm the fool
Orange Lounge Radio
Yes, Jason, that actually happened
That is an actual, actual thing we'll get into later
Hi everybody, hi internet
Welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
It is Orange Lounge Radio live on this April the 6th of 2014 with episode number 547 of our show
Here with you guys at vognetwork.com
That's vognetwork.com where we do tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show to talk about video games, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle
I'm here with you, I'm Rob Roberts
And joining me, as always, say hello to the one and only DarkSakura or Jamie Summers
Hi
Hi, how are you?
Less frustrated, very happy
I just noticed, I'm like, yay, DarkSakura was able to get in the chatroom after all
Yeah, just still got a little bit of a headache from my movie adventures today
Yes, what did you go see today?
I went to see Captain America, Winter Soldier
It seems like everybody in the nation went and saw you
Well, it was just really freaking loud and the 3D hurt my eyes
It was just sort of too much of everything at once, so I figured that next time I go to a movie, I'm just going to start bringing earplugs and sunglasses
But was it good?
It was really good, but make sure that you stay not just for the after the special part of the credits, but after the all of the credits
Because trust me, it's a Marvel movie, it's safe for everything
Exactly, absolutely right
There it is, alright, well also joining us as he does every week, here in studio, say hello to Techmaster Loki
Hey, Loki, and you're not doing so well from what I understand, right?
Yeah, starting to get a little sick?
I hear you, you're your stay-at-home dad right now, right?
Just for a few weeks with the whole, they let you have leave when you have a new kid and all that stuff, right?
How's it going?
Oh, is your, are we not hearing Loki?
Sorry guys
Oops, Loki was muted, sorry about that Loki, try again, that's the joys of live radio everybody
Try again, Loki, how are you doing?
Congested
Congested in your home with the baby
Yes, I'm home with the baby
Let's see, so yeah, he just doesn't want to take a bottle
So I have to try to feed him and that usually takes about, I don't know, maybe an hour to get him to take an ounce
So it's like, come on, take the damn bottle
You need to get one of those fake boobies that dads get to be able to feed
There's no amount of niggling that's going to get that baby to take anything
I've had to do syringes just to get him to take something
I don't know, it's just because he's breastfed
We were doing both, we were feeding him a bottle at night and that kind of stuff
And then we kind of backed off on that and so he's just confused
That's fine, my son Josh wakes up at like 5.45 every day
Even though he doesn't have to wake up for school until like 6.45
But I get up every day at 5.45 now
But there's a nice three hour break in between when he gets up and when the baby gets up
My son usually gets up at 8.30 so I work on my computer and stuff
Either doing programming in Unity or just playing games or something
Until my son comes up and says, what are you doing? I want to watch that, do this
I was watching a game video the other day and he was telling me how to play the game
He's like, go up, go up! I'm like, it's a video, I can't do anything
So yeah, that's what it's been
And then I usually take him to Nellie for lunch and then he sleeps when they get back for an hour, hour, two hours
So is Josh at that age yet where he's actually, because you say he's standing up behind you while you're watching game videos
Is he at that age where he's actually able to play games?
No
No, he's not quite there yet?
He doesn't know how to do anything
I mean the best he can do is, I got him to play Forza Horizon a while back a little bit
Just because I have the whole racing setup where he could steer and need the pedals and everything
But he doesn't have the dexterity to do it on his own
And it's kind of hard to teach him because he's left handed
So I don't know how he would feel
But he's interested in pictures and stuff
I had him watch a Mega Man video today, like I put that on while I went and did something
You need to get him to start like the rest of us started on Atari 2600
I don't really remember playing games, probably about four years old at this release I remember, four or five for sure
Five was when we got the Commodore 64, so I remember that
He likes Bubble Bubble on the arcade, Kevin, he just doesn't understand how to move the joystick and push the buttons at the same time
That was the thing about Atari 2600 games, they were easy
There's one thing to them, combat, pinball, boxing, very one note, easy to do
If you are listening to us live, hello and welcome, you can join our chat room over at live.vognetwork.com
Again that's live.vognetwork.com, I know we're up against some big TV stuff going on tonight
So if you are here live, I appreciate you being here
If you are listening to us on the podcast, you know what, that's okay too
If you decided to watch your wrestling and you're listening to us on Monday morning
Well that's okay too, we appreciate your support either way
And yeah, this is a show where every gamer has a voice
If you can't be here live with us, be sure you send us an email
Which you can do at participate at orangeonsready.com
Or you can send us a tweet at OLR
And we like to get your voices all on the show as well
Going to our chat room, I see some folks talking about the old school games
Dungeon Buster says Yars' Revenge, that was a little more complicated of a 2600 game
After they got all the simple stuff done, then it started getting a little weirder
If you look at Yars' Revenge and you have no idea what to do
It is kind of difficult to figure out what the hell that game is
I don't know if you've ever seen Yars' Revenge, but Google it
Make sure you're looking at the Atari 2600 version, not that weirdo remake they did a few years ago
Which was nothing like the original
But you have that storm cloud that comes down the middle of the screen
Which is actually like a safe zone I believe
And then you have a wall around the gun
And you try to shoot through the wall
And then you have to touch the gun
And once you touch the gun, which is randomly shooting so you gotta be careful
You get a bullet on the left side of the screen
You hit the fire button one more time and you blow up the gun
See that one's complicated, some of them get really complicated
Because they did all the simple stuff
But Yars' Revenge was one of the greatest Atari 2600 games they ever did
And then try to explain a game like E.T.
Well, don't bother
Although I seem to remember a couple years ago somebody had hacked the E.T. ROM to make it playable
They changed collision detection and some other stuff to make E.T. playable
Which is kind of funny
Love that idea
Speaking of hacks and joking and fooling around
For the kickoff topic tonight I wanted to talk a little bit about April Fools' Day
Because April Fools' Day was this past week
Some years we've done things here at OLR or VOG Network where our show is heard
This year we sat out
Just because our show was nowhere close to April Fools' Day this year
And we were actually working on a new feature for the site at vognetwork.com
Like a real thing that actually launched on April 2nd
Because we want people to believe it's real
It's our new TV section
Presented by the fantastic folks over at Critical Myth
Which you can hear on VOG Network Monday, Wednesday, Friday at 4 o'clock Pacific, 7 o'clock Eastern
They have a brand new TV review section over at VOG Network
And you can access that at tv.vognetwork.com
What's really cool about it, it's got all the same gamification elements that the rest of the site has
Meaning you can leave your response reviews right underneath the reviews of the shows that are there
You can comment and thumbs up, thumbs down, all that stuff
So you can really participate with those reviews
And it's TV so it's
A lot of people watch these shows and trust me
The guys over at Critical Myth, they have a pretty big staff
And so they review something like 40 shows
Now they used to run their own website, criticalmyth.com
But due to some, and I have no better way to word this
Than due to some fuckery
Which is completely out of their hands and not their fault
But due to some fuckery, they don't have Crystal Myth
Or did I say crystalmyth.com?
Criticalmyth.com
Or you know, Critical Myth, CrystalMyth.com
It's even more popular
I think somebody hacked their domain to sell it for meth
I think that's what happened
But anyway, criticalmyth.com is not there in the same way
I think he kind of has it to do some podcast hosting
But they unfortunately lost a bunch of reviews
But they're starting anew over at VOG Network
And they review a lot of shows
This isn't like Marvel Agents of SHIELD and one other show
You go over there, there's a ton of shows they're reviewing right now
So probably one of your geeky favorites is up over there
So check that out
Once again, tv.vognetwork.com
Plug plug
So where was I? April Fools
April Fools
Lots of April Fools jokes always happen around the game industry
We've had some real classic stuff in the past
But what did you guys think of this year's offerings?
We had a few things this year
What did you think of this year's April Fools offerings?
Loki, is there any that...
I mean there was a few that kind of stood out
But a lot of them were just kind of eh
I mean, I like the
Spent new Smash Brothers character reveal which was Nester
But see that's the thing though
It's like, it kind of falls into two categories
There's April Fools jokes that are kind of like
Okay haha that's funny
And then there's those April Fools jokes where it's like
Oh man that's really cool
Why is this just an April Fools joke?
Why can't we have this actually be a real thing?
And so in that category there was
The Nester reveal and then also
The Optimus Prime
DLC for Titanfall
Where you'd have Optimus Prime
Which I gotta admit though he did kind of look a little derpy in that
But whatever
I guess it was generation one but it looked
It looked like derpy generation one
So that was kind of neat
Wait let me cut in because I don't want you to name everything
I want to give Jamie a chance
I don't know if she was really following all the April Fools stuff
But was there any gags that caught your eye this year Jamie
That you thought were funny? Or anything you thought was lame?
After being reminded by Bobby I did the NPR stunt
That was really smart
Do people actually pay attention?
That wasn't gaming per se
But a great commentary on social media
And the social game we play every day on Facebook
That's a great commentary on my Facebook
On everybody's Facebook
I mean seriously
That's actually a great commentary on my mother
And every conversation I ever have with her
And just to recap
I know a lot of people probably listen to Bobby's show
But just for those that are listening to our show first
For whatever reason on Monday
They posted an article
That said something like
Americans don't read as much as they used to
Or something like that
But you click in the article
And it says this is our April Fools joke
Hey you should like the post
But don't comment on it
To prove that you read it
And all these people commenting on the post
Saying what kind of travesty is this?
What are you talking about NPR?
NPR you guys are full of crap
People who just made an impression
Based off the headline
Didn't bother to read the story
Hilarious
It sort of goes back to
Something I've been pointing to before
Through a couple of different shows
Just how society itself
Has become
Can't be bothered to do anything
And this
Would never be true in the gaming industry
Right Dark Sakura?
The gaming fans never judge things based on headlines alone
Do we?
You know what?
It's a human thing
The path of least resistance
We would never have
Like a click baiting website
That would just try to get attention grabbing headlines
For people to share on Facebook
We would never have anything like that
Right?
Website
April Fools
Yeah and who's the fool this time?
Who is the fool?
Go into our chat room over at live.vognetwork.com
Dungeon Buster agrees
The Optimus DLC was very funny
The pagan Jew with one
I can't believe Dark Sakura forgot about this
I just wanted this to be real
The pagan Jew says the BioWare store stuff
The Garris body pillow
That was a big joke anyway
There were reviews up of it
Besides that
I don't want a Garris body pillow
Unless it's like a full size plushie
I could deal with that
But Dan would be completely freaked out
Raginator
Going to keep it at old school and saying
The best April Fools gag ever
Was the EGM Shang Long joke
That is always interesting
Back when you didn't really have the internet
The way you have it now
And gaming magazines were very prolific
And in the April issue
There would always be some type of
Joke
And it was always really funny to me
When that stuff would cross over into actual
Cannon
The one that pops into my head is when they said
Ermac was in Mortal Kombat
The red ninja Ermac was available
You did all this crazy stuff
And you could unlock it
What did the developers of Mortal Kombat do?
They put a character called Ermac in one of the later games
We always knew it would happen
They started trolling people by putting
Random text in the bios
Or whatever
Any jokes that you guys
Have ever come across on April Fools day
In the gaming world or maybe in the tech world
That just weren't funny
Because sometimes
What's the old adage?
I can only think of the RuPaul version
Bear with me here
The RuPaul version is
Throwing shade takes creativity
Being a bitch takes none
And what I mean by that is that
Some April Fools jokes are funny
Because they're thought out
They're well executed and so forth
But there's so much sloppy shit that happens
On April Fools day that's just mean spirited
And dumb
So what do you guys think has happened in the game industry
And I pose this to our chat room as well
That was on that side of
Bitchy that was just dumb
There was the Firefly one
Oh Netflix is reviving Firefly
I was like fuck all of you
That was kind of being a bitch
If it wasn't that you were doing the Jessica Jones
And Luke Cage series I would just say fuck you
Forever for the rest of the year
Until you redeemed yourselves if that was at all possible
Hitstun says that Nester
Won this year was lame
Disagrees with Loki
There was the
Enter the dominatrix
April Fools joke
Oh what would that tell us more about that
That's for Saints Row
They were teasing it as an
April Fools joke originally
That became a thing
Then it was going to become an expansion
Saints Row 4
God having played the DLC
It would have been fucking terrible
Even more terrible than Saints Row 4 was
I do have to say that
The only getting into
April Fools that I did
Was playing Animal Crossing
And having to tell who was the right one
And I'm very sad that I did not guess the correct
Margie
Because it made her sad and she better not move
I forgot that April Fools was a thing
In Animal Crossing
Blanca shows up
And she impersonates another townsperson
And so sometimes they'll give a clue by their
Birthday or whatever
But it's stupid
It's one of those like how much have you been paying attention
And Margie's my favorite and I got her wrong
For a second there I thought you had a really epic
Capcom crossover there
Like oh Blanca shows up that's awesome
No she's the one that had the face
That you drew her face in before
Blanca shows up and starts electrocuting your villagers
Oh
I support this
He just
He spotted Ed and then launched himself
In the one of those
Blanca balls at Ed's face
And murdered him from Jamie's village
Yeah I did
Let's see I got
I got Groucho right
I like Groucho so I have his picture
And I got D.Va
Which I just like her because her name is D.Va
But she's a fucking frog
So her eyes are sitting on top of her head and it's fucking weird
You know I thought the meanest April Fools joke
Where somebody was being a total bitch that was played
Was when Notch
Wrote that blog post
About how he wasn't gonna make Minecraft for the Oculus Rift
Because Facebook bought them
And then Yeti turned around and now they're gonna do
You know, pocket Minecraft on the Amazon Fire
I thought that was a really bitchy April Fools joke
But
That's because the Amazon Fire
They already have controller support for Minecraft Pocket
You're just putting it on another damn console
Oh wait wait you're saying that wasn't an April Fools joke?
That wasn't an April Fools joke
It's not technically in 3
What a bitch
It's kind of stupid to call it Minecraft
Pocket on a fucking TV
I can't fit that TV in my pocket
Alright how big do you think my pocket is?
Alright
I can't afford big fucking pockets
Because I'm going to reach into your pocket
And take out $7.99
It's for the people with the deep pockets
Yes it's for people with deep pockets
Alright
You gotta have a pouch of holding for that shit
Alright all bitchiness aside
We'll get to the Amazon Fire stuff
I know it's on everybody's mind
We'll get to that in the news in a little bit
But let's establish our frame of reference for the week
In a segment we call
How is your gaming week?
So DarkSakura what type of games have you been playing this week?
Animal Crossing
I played some Final Fantasy 14
I did some Mass Effect
But I really need to start over on my game again
And for some reason
My mods aren't working again
So whatever the fuck
I was playing something else
Oh yeah um
I think I mentioned it last week I might have
That I started the Shiva
Which um
It's actually
It's done in those old sprite
You know point and click adventure games
But it's really
It's very Jewish
I mean the Shiva
What a Shiva is
Is if you don't know it's like a week long
Period of mourning when someone dies
Where the family in mourning
Sits on the floor everyone brings them food
You know you're supposed to
You don't have to do much to take care of yourself
You're supposed to get your grief out of your system
And you know after you've buried the dead
And so in this case
It's a rabbi who
Has a dwindling congregation about to lose
His synagogue and then
Somebody that
He had actually
Kicked out of his congregation
Left him a whole bunch of money
But the guy was murdered
So it's
This whole murder mystery
Around
Just around trying to get
To the bottom of it
Why would this guy who he kicked out
Leave him money
Who's behind it
It's pretty
It's really actually more of an insight into
I think into modern Jewish culture
I've really been enjoying it
And on top of that
It's an old school point and click adventure game
Yeah it's called the shiva
The pagan Jewish
That's a real game I need to look this up
Yeah it's really
Good and it's actually not super expensive
But I've been really getting into the story behind it
Nice
I played a little bit more
Dominique Pablos
But the problem I have with it
Is that I
Have problems with hearing anything off pitch
And
Not all of the singing is on pitch
It's a very intentional
Sort of sing songy
That's
I had this problem in band
You know what perfect pitch is right
When you can hear pitch
I saw pitch perfect
I loved Fat Amy she was my favorite
Well I have perfect pitch for listening
And so I can hear when anything
Is off it starts to sound like
Instead of a constant sound
You hear all the sound waves between it
And so for me it's just like
A cringe I can't even listen to myself sing
When I'm off pitch
So that's why I don't do karaoke
Turn the volume down turn subtitles on
Probably what I'm going to end up doing
Except the songs are cute the music is cute
So I've been enjoying what I'm playing of it
And that's not anything having to do with the game
That's having to do with me
So I take it in bursts I'm having a good time
It is such a little art film
It is I love it it's so cute
I just sort of want my own
Dominique doll
We know people you can call
To maybe arrange that
I might make one
And thank you Dungeon Buster for doing a link to the
Shiva in there because I would really like
To see more games like this
I would love to see more people
Explore this game and learn more
About you know the culture behind it
Well and in a way you just brought up
Dominique Pamplemousse too which is a very
Similar sort of thing being able to explore
The mind of somebody
You might not otherwise
Have thought about relating to before
And I love the main character
I really do like Dominique
But that being said
I have to take it in doses
And I'm actually kind of
Considered getting Titanfall
Except I would throw up so quickly
This doesn't sound like you at all
I mean don't get me wrong Titanfall is pretty cool
But what's your attraction
To Titanfall? I want to see the story behind it
Because I actually it was funny because we were
Alright we were watching
At Captain America today we were watching
The little commercials
They do in front of it they had a really
Good one for Titanfall and I was like oh that's kind of
Interesting and then you see the pilots bouncing
From wall to wall I was like oh my god
It's like Attack on Titanfall
I was like I'm kind of
Interested now because it says it's got a story
And it's multiplayer and I was like well
There will be people on the same learning curve as me I'm sure
The story is very short because
The game is only multiplayer and so there's
Like multiplayer
multiplayer match oh something story related
multiplayer match and then that's it
And then later on oh something else
Story related oh whatever
Oh and now you have to play the other side
Maybe I'll just stick with drunken robot
Pornography then
You can watch the story on YouTube
Seriously I think it's short enough to where you could do that
Well I don't know I've actually
When I gave up playing through
Half Life 2
I just watched the rest of the story online
Well how do you think sites like Twitch TV
Are a thing people like to watch
People play through stories but I do want
To have a mass effect multiplayer
Night where we stream again
I wonder if my game is up to date
I don't even know because then I need to drink a lot
That'd be fun and play because drunken
Mass effect multiplayer on bronze
Is the funniest thing ever and for the record
Ragenator I did get goat simulator
Or as you said goat stimulator
And it's fucked up
Also
Another comment in our chat room you may
Not be alone in some of your music
Things dark soccer
says when I hear death metal
I lose my balance and I get dizzy right away
I have the problem actually
With certain ones like okay I'm fine
With speed metal but anything
That's the super bass heavy and
Screechy oh like through the fire and the flames
Yeah I'm fine with speed metal because
It actually is sort of melodic it has
A pattern and I mean if anyone
Wants to okay the stuff that I listen
To to calm me down when I'm about you know at
Meltdown phase is I listen to Philip Glass
And believe it or not I've actually
Found a little bit of correlation with
Some of the patterns that come up in Philip Glass's music
And certain types
Of speed metal just the melodic
And repetitive how it
Builds and builds and builds on something so
It's actually very calming to me but
Death metal no I get sick actually get nauseous
If it's I've listened to too much
So yeah
Alright
Well let's move on back to I don't know
How we got into talking about death metal from video games
We did Loki how was
Your gaming week I've actually been listening to lots of music
Not death metal but I've been trying
To find because the thing is
I've been trying to find music that's of a
Certain genre but I don't know what genre it is
It's you know like pendulum
Where it's a cross between like heavy metal
Drum and bass and electronica
I guess but how do you say
I want
Heavy metal drum and bass
Electronica music half pandora
Or check like last.fm
Well the problem is I'm looking for
Indie music that's of that same genre
And I've found a few things but it's just like
They have so many tags on it
There's no fucking way I'm gonna go find this
Anyways the actual games I played
Or I should say game
I really only played goat simulator this week
Because I haven't really played much at all
As far as games go I did
Load up South Park for like
Literally two minutes just to show my friend
And that was that
He proceeded to use all my
Single day
Summons so I had to
Not save and you know
Go back and actually
Play that section again
But yeah goat simulator is fun
I liked how they changed some of the things
Probably for copyright issues
The Yoshi goat is now Italian dinosaur goat
Which is funny
They added a dragon
Shout goat which I haven't actually used yet
But there's a lot more
Mods on there now
Some new maps
So fun stuff
Just got the achievement for doing all the flips
The trick is to go into the low
Gravity area and you can flip forever
In there
Yeah so
That's all I played this week hopefully
Gonna get in some Call of Duty
Modern Warfare 2 later this week
Got a ton of friends now
That are playing that so it'll be fun
Alright
My gaming week I actually kept myself pretty busy
I've played a few games this week
Sadly none of it is really new things for me to talk about
I've been continuing to play Final Fantasy 10
The HD remake
I played that a little bit towards the beginning of the week
I got a copy of South Park
On Playstation 3
So I finally got a chance to play the South Park game
I'm not super far into it
I'm just like at the beginning still where you're going around town
With Butters trying to recruit the people for your
You know
For your army or whatever
And I'm like isn't this the same plot from the show
But that's alright
It's really funny of course the game is hilarious
Because it's written by
The guys who do the actual show
Matt Park or Trey Stone
And I thought it was interesting how there's all these little side quests
The way the game plays
Obviously it has the RPG elements
But it reminds me of
A 90's
Click adventure game from the PC
Like King's Quest or Loom or some shit
I don't know why
Maybe it's because you keep going from static scene to static scene
And you interact with things in the scene
Be it with your slingshot
Or you're looking at things that are yellow
Or things you can open up or whatever
So I just kind of
I don't know I thought that was kind of neat
It kind of was a throwback to those games
But yeah the game is funny
And definitely worth a look at if you're a South Park fan
Other games I've been playing this week
Diablo 3
Having an experience boost weekend
So I'm still trying to beat Act 5
Because I'm level 69 now
So there's only one more level for me to gain
So I've got to be close to the end
But yeah I wanted to play that during the experience boost weekend
So I've been playing a little bit of that
Also this weekend Final Fantasy 14 is doing its
Second beta on Playstation 4
And this is the beta where you can use
Your characters from the PC
Or the Playstation 3
If you still haven't checked out the Final Fantasy 14
Beta on Playstation 4
I hate to say it I think you missed your chance
I mean you can start the download now
And depending on your connection you might be able to get
A couple hours in to at least get a feel for it
But at this point if you haven't played it
Now is your chance to try out the game for free
Yeah it comes out in like a week
Yeah it's out the pre-order
Starts on the 11th and those people can play
And I believe Playstation 3 users
Who are converting their licenses
Also get to start playing that day
And then the 14th is when the game comes out
SSJ 100 Matt by the way says
You need to play South Park in front of your mom
I will I'll invite her over she loves South Park
I have not seen your mom
In ages and she's wonderful
Yeah I should invite her on the show sometime
Maybe for Mother's Day or something
We'll have her on the show in the new studio
It'll be fun
Huh
That's a good idea
And by the way
What?
Next week I will be doing another Blue Roses giveaway in Animal Crossing
You gonna work on farming those blue roses?
Oh I've got like a whole flower bed full now
Alright stay tuned
Blue roses the Animal Crossing equivalent of
Crystal meth
Apparently, apparently
Uh see I've been playing the Final Fantasy 14 beta
On Playstation 4
I am impressed with the technology in that little box
I gotta say
Because the game runs great
It runs better than it does on my 5 year old PC
Because my PC is 5 years old
But the frame rate is fantastic
The game looks great
And I can broadcast to Twitch
Using the whole built in thing
And my network thing doesn't suffer
The graphics look good
You know I actually played through
The 2.2 patch content last night
I streamed it
I really wish Twitch archived
The Playstation 4 stuff
It doesn't
I'm kinda bummed out
Because I did the Leviathan fight for the first time
Last night on the feed with Shane
And uh
I actually thought of a pretty clever way
Cause you know when I do my live streams
I almost always have somebody on Skype
That I can kinda banter with
So it's not just watching my little head in the box
Or listening to rock music
Like I just
I have to be different
So I always like to banter with somebody on Skype
So you know
Usually Shane is almost always there
Or Extifer
Or Grandpa from Hoardouse
Or somebody's
Usually they're bantering with me
Well
On the Playstation 4 it's a little more difficult right
Cause you can't plug in a mixing board or anything right
But what I figured out you can do
I get my iPhone
And I call Shane on the Skype app on my iPhone
And I set the iPhone right next to the camera
So he can hear me when I'm talking
And then the listeners hear him
Or the viewers hear him through the camera mic
And it works
So then the viewers are actually listeners too?
Yes, both
Unless they're deaf
Then they're just viewers
And they don't care about the banter
Between Shane and I
Cause there's no subtitles
We should find a way to subtitle the show by the way
Yeah I don't know
It'd be a lot of work
So
You could use one of those automated things
That are kinda hit and miss
But yeah
Final Fantasy XIV on Playstation 4 is great
And I'm probably gonna switch to playing on Playstation 4
When it comes out
Since I got it on Playstation 3
And here's
If you're interested in the game
I would really urge you to
Try to find a cheap copy on Playstation 3 right now
And then just convert your license to Playstation 4
That's the cheapest way to do it
And get 30 days free with the game
You can probably find a copy for 15-20 bucks right now
Out there
Just make sure it's not used
Cause you need to have a code
But
There you go
That was pretty much my gaming week honestly
Lots of other stuff I need to try
I've got an EverQuest Landmark beta code
That I'm waiting to use
I gotta get in there and play that
And
Let's see
I'll describe it
And
Let's see
Elder Scrolls Online came out
But I lost my chance at that
I didn't really play that
And
Wild Stars in beta too
And I'm the one to test that out
And I really want to try Wild Stars
I really want
And I doubt anybody from Blizzard
Listens to this show
But if you do
If I happen to have a fan out there
That I did not know about
That's got the hookup at Blizzard
Please flag my account
For the Heroes of the Storm alpha
Thank you, thank you
Kiss kiss hug hug
I really wanna
I can't
I'm losing my resistance Rob
What?
Cause the space goats
Oh you wanna go back to WoW?
I kinda do
When the expansion comes out
Uh oh
That was the other one
That was really awesome
I don't remember if it was League of Legends
Or I think it was League of Legends
But they had
And I'm assuming it's a joke
The
Goat simulator goat in there
As a playable character
And it was
I think it was one of those like
You know
Dota type games or something
But
I wanna say it was League of Legends
Maybe it wasn't League of Legends
But
There's a lot of people doing a lot of goat simulator things
And that right there
That's the April Fools game right there
That just keeps on giving
Because it's a legit game
You know MMOs do some of the best April Fools gags
They do some of the worst
Oh my god
What was it?
Guild Wars 2
Had the whole retro level last year
That was amazing
Oh you know
There's something else that I did
It wasn't video game related
But it wasn't anime
I started Kill la Kill
Is that the one that Rama told you to watch?
No
Oh
Several many other people have told me to watch it
And so finally I just broke down and started watching it
Oh my god
That's all I have to say
Going to our chat
Going to our chat room at
Live.vognetwork.com
Dark Tetsuya says
Well doesn't YouTube kind of have closed captioning?
Not sure it's 100% accurate
But anyway
Yes it does
I don't know if our videos that Jason puts on the Orange Launch Radio channel at YouTube
Has that like
That you can use that
But I bet it's hilariously bad
Because there's some really bad YouTube captioning out there
Maybe we should check out
I'm gonna check it out
You should check out a prior episode
See if that's there
Also going to more chat
Let's see
Hitstun says
Wildstar and Elder Scrolls Online were really big at PAX East last year
But they're still not out yet
Elder Scrolls Online actually launched on Friday
So that is now out
Wildstar I believe is June
Is when that's coming out
S2100Matt says
We need to use our
Tell a friend about the show duty
And find a friend that is also a stenographer
And get them hooked to OLR
That would be great
I'd love that
Alright
Anyhow
So that is it
I believe for our gaming weeks
That's everybody
Quick housekeeping
And then we will get to the show
With the news and everything
Add us on Twitter
Twitter.com slash OLR
You can also add us on Facebook
Facebook.com slash Orange Launch Radio
And Google Plus
Google.com slash Plus Orange Lounge Radio
A couple shout outs
I want to give here
At the top of the show
I want to shout out the website
Outcasts with a Z
Outcasts.com
Really awesome
This has not happened to me before
But they actually ran a feature on me
On their site
And it talked about
It talked about the history of Orange Lounge Radio
Talking about a little bit of my broadcast background
With Understation Live and everything
Outcasts.com is like a GLBT nerd gaming culture site
And Jamie got a name drop even
I mentioned you in the interview
I am sorry you did not make the story
I knew that was going to get called out
What happened? What was with me?
Because your name is in the interview
Because it talks about how OLR started
So it talks about Rob and Jamie started OLR
Da da da da da
But the problem is
I said in another part
I talked about how Loki is with it now
But they didn't use that part of it
Because technically
Loki didn't start the show with us
But it's like
He just kept showing up
Yeah but it's one of those things
Now how could we ever have the show without him
So I am very sorry Loki
But that was the interviewer's person
I know Travis and Jessica got shout outs too
For the Understation Live stuff
Loki none for Loki bye
The captioning is hilarious
Is it?
It's just like it's terrible
I mean it's got some
Okay so Orange Lounge Radio
You know the little intro part
The way they translate
Way but sprawled hollow
Let's see here
There was an
Oh
I don't even know what part this is
Doing next
It's all Sky this week gonna kill the Bens
And intriguing publishing Google recently
I'm gonna kill the Bens y'all
Look out if your name's Ben
Oh man that's hilarious
Yeah just watch it with the subtitles on it's hilarious
That's great
Hey give me
There's actually a series of things
They do like that for Mass Effect 2 as well
Oh yeah
The bad closed captioning
Good stuff
Yeah
I'm sure there's a lot of that out there
So anyway
Shout out for our YouTube channel
Check out the bad closed captioning
At Orange Lounge Radio on YouTube
Oh okay
So the
The Sky is Sweet thing
It's on this week
You know something about Amazon
Or something like that
That's what it
It's Jason's little
Yeah yeah
His little intro
The Sky this week gonna kill the Bens
Gonna kill the Bens
Alright
Where was I?
Stop interrupting me
Outkast
Loki's just mad because he somehow was missing from the article
Outkast.com and a big thanks to them
I really appreciate that
Give them all your clicks
Also another website to give all your clicks to
A fantastic little show called Troll in the Dungeon
Which is a World of Warcraft focused podcast
Had me on their show this past Saturday
I don't think the episode is posted on the feed yet
But it will be in the coming days
So check them out
That's Troll in the Dungeon over on iTunes and Stitcher and all that good stuff
And that was the episode from just this past
What was April 6th
Or no today is April 6th
April 5th would be the show I was on
Oh my god Rob
What?
Not next weekend but the weekend after
Gonna be older
Your birthday
What's your birthday plans? Anything?
Hopefully going to Sakura, Matsuri
I need to make sure it's that weekend
But I wanna hang out in San Francisco
And eat all the food I don't normally eat
Except the problem
It's also Passover
Oh
I was gonna say you should go to Dave and Busters
And do your get drunk as hell thing
That means I'm just gonna have to eat nothing but mochi
I'm voting that we change the name of our show
According to what it thinks our name of the show is
It's Orange Allow Injure Radio
Alright put that thing away
That's because of how you pronounce lounge Rob
You say lounge like
Lounge
Cause you extra enunciate when you do the intro
That's not my voice in the intro
Well I mean but when you do another episode of Orange Lounger Radio
You say lounger
Oh
Which is powerful
You sound almost like you're an evil dictator
This is Orange Allow Injure Radio
Orange Lounger Radio
I'll take it
Dark soccer
Close it
Well you know I do have an affinity for kicking balls
There's her little clip in the next intro
Alright let's get into gaming news
Loki's gonna put away the closed captioning
And talk to us about what is going on in the gaming world
Here at Orange Allow Injure Radio
So the ever rumored Amazon set top box type thing
Was finally announced during a press event
They had it live blogged and everything
And it's the Amazon Fire TV
And it's actually a device that you know
Like most of those set top boxes out there
That you can stream you know Netflix
And of course you know the Amazon Video stuff
Hulu
All that sort of things
It runs Android so you can run different apps on it and stuff
Remotes and all that fun stuff
But the other cool thing about it though
Is it also
Is a device that you can game on
So they actually have a controller that you can buy for 40 bucks
That looks like you know a console controller
And you can play games
Of course you know they have the whole Amazon Game Studios
So there's that
It's kind of cool
The device is only $99
So there's your final nail in the coffin Uya
You're irrelevant now
Sounds like a big splat
Some of the games of course
Well hold up to be fair the Uya is $99 with a controller
If you want to play games on the Amazon Fire
You're telling me it's really $139
Spec wise though it's way more powerful than Uya
And it's got one thing that the Uya doesn't have
Which is Minecraft Pocket Edition
Well here's the $139 question though
Are you going to buy one?
Am I going to buy one?
I don't know if the wife would let me buy another set top box
I wanted to
Because we have the Boxee right now
But it's kind of crap
Yeah if my Boxee were to die somehow
Some unforeseen accident
Then yes I would totally pick one up
I'm going to be honest why?
I can't see the need to get
I mean I get why this Amazon Fire exists
It's a great appealing thing for my mom and my dad
Who are never going to buy a game console but want to have Netflix
Like the people that buy Roku's and things like that
That's great for them
That's exactly why I'd buy it
I wouldn't buy it to play games on it
Maybe Minecraft
I wouldn't even play Minecraft
Why would you even play Minecraft?
I would buy it for games
Well not games but maybe
I don't know
It would be kind of cool to publish something to that
Well let's not forget
Amazon bought a developer recently
Yeah
So they're going to have something exclusive
Well they do
It's a game called Sev Zero
It's a first person shooter type thing
So they've got that
Some of the things they're showing
Asphalt 8 and Minecraft
And the other thing though is it does work with other Bluetooth controllers
So maybe it would work with a DualShock controller
If you have one already
Andrew's pretty friendly with anything Bluetooth
I don't know it's not a huge deal
And also I think if you buy the controller
You get like some
I don't know how it works but it's like Amazon coins or something like that
It's like a thousand of that
Buy books or something
Buy things with that
I don't know the ratio of coins to money
So they've got that
And I don't know I'm kind of interested
Like I said I would mainly use it for
Just like TV stuff
It would be cool though because I didn't really get to see a lot of the interface thing
Because I had friends over at the time
But if it's
Like I think it is where I think it might combine
Like all the different
Like you're not going into dedicated apps for different things
I think it's just like
Okay I want to watch like
Game of Thrones or something
Maybe Game of Thrones is a bad example
I want to watch
The Office or something
And it will bring up all the different
Providers that have The Office
And where you can watch that
Or different movies and things
So it kind of aggregates it all together
Instead of like
Oh crap was that show on Netflix
Or was it on Hulu
I don't know I have to go browse Netflix
Oh it's not here okay
Browse Hulu
Amazon has it
That's smart
It's like a modern day TV guide
Yeah it's just instead of having
The Boxy tried doing that
It does it terribly
But they tried to do that
With a lot of the website streaming services and stuff
And then of course
Yeah so it does work
With their Bluetooth controllers and stuff
Let me read some chat comments real quick
Over at live.vognetwork.com
Tiger Claw says
What the Amazon Fire TV lacks
Is the ability to shop and buy stuff
In the Amazon store
That does seem like a pretty
Obviously missing thing right
Well I mean you could
Well I think
Well I think even with Amazon
Like when you're using the Amazon movies
Or TV
Like I know when you use the app on the Xbox 360
You're more than welcome to buy those things
Right there in the app and watch them
I think you can buy stuff
Yeah
You're talking about like buying like off of amazon.com
Yeah I think that's
They have mobile apps for them
And I'm pretty sure that's probably one of the apps
That's in the Amazon marketplace
Yeah
Which is not something they probably featured
Well yeah I mean they're not gonna show
Every single app that's available for you
Here's a way you can give us more money
Let's see
Kaijuto with some strong opinions on Pocket Minecraft
Pocket Minecraft blows
It's still in alpha
Waste of money
Yeah I have no interest in Pocket Edition
I do agree with you
I think it is kind of cheap
And it's just
You're saying that
Ooh it runs Minecraft
It's Android it runs Minecraft
I mean come on it's you know
All Android devices are a hell
You know all iOS devices run Minecraft
So
It's not a big deal
And because this device is based on one of those mobile platforms
I'm very interested to see what the PlayStation 4 version brings to the table
Now granted you know PC
But I know the console games have started to kind of go their direction
And the PC kind of has its direction or whatever
So I'm very curious what the extra oomph of the PlayStation 4 brings to Minecraft
And I'm not like I know people are going
But the graphics are never gonna get any better
I get that
I think they could actually
They could
And the space in the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 versions is limited
Which you know it's a huge space
It would be cool if you did like the Sonic ether you know
Shaders or if you could select what type of shaders you want
Cause the Sonic ether stuff looks fucking awesome
Maybe they'll be able to have some of that stuff where you put your own skins
And things like that in there too
Like cause you see a little
They'll sell you skins
Yeah that's true
You see a little bit of that in the 360 version
With the mass effect and the Skyrim
They have like the PS3 one now too
Oh yeah
Yeah they don't have like you know dedicated packs
Where you get like levels and stuff
But they had one like they had like a city texture pack and stuff
And they have some character packs but
Could be interesting
I mean I don't know it's
Put it this way like for ninety nine bucks
That's about the price that you're gonna be paying for a lot of these set top boxes
They range around seventy nine to ninety nine anyways
And the fact that this one is about three times more powerful than those
It has a dedicated GPU in it
You might as well get this one even if you don't want a game on it
Cause maybe there's something down the road you know
There'll be like some free apps on it or something that you want to try out
Or who knows what people are gonna develop for
If it's popular enough
Which I think at that price point it's pretty
It's almost an impulse buy for like you know tech stuff
Well and come Black Friday they're gonna slice it down to seventy nine dollars
Or something even cheaper
Yeah I mean
For prime people I'm sure
It's definitely like if I didn't have the boxy
I would definitely consider picking that up
Now will a drone fly it to my house?
That's what I wanna know
Oh I don't think that
I don't think that's gonna happen anytime soon but
It would be
I mean might as well
I mean cause it's more powerful
It's gonna be able to run even just video apps and stuff
Better than some of these other systems
Cause I gotta be honest like
My set top box is pretty old
And it shows it's really laggy
And just
I mean it does video okay
But you know the interfaces are just not very snappy
So it would be cool to check this out
That being said though
I'm kinda curious to see then
If this is really popular how Apple kinda combats it with like a new Apple TV or something
So I mean cause
It's only a moment
It's only a matter of time before there's like
Apple's overdue for a press conference I think
You know you'd be at an iPad update or
Not the iPhones
iPhones would be later in the year but
We know there's gonna be like some Apple TV thing at some point
Yeah absolutely
Alright well
There you go
Well one game that will not be on the Amazon Fire
Because you know what it just
It just needs
It needs more oomph behind it
It needs the kind of oomph that the Wii U can deliver
And that is Mario Kart 8 is on the horizon
There was quite the information dump on Mario Kart 8 this week
Because we're only what
We're about a month and a half out
I guess maybe two months
But May 30th is the big day for Mario Kart 8
And there's new information coming out on the game
Through some trailers this week
And it looks great
A lot of people very pumped for it
Which is really good news for Wii U
Cause there's nothing to get excited about
It does like it is
On the horizon
I gotta be honest so like
You know before
I was just like well
You know it's just Mario Kart
It doesn't look that much better
The new trailer is actually
It does look a lot better
I mean game play wise
I'm not really sure
But the tracks look pretty
And the engine looks nice
So
Quickly some of the things that are new
That were from this trailer
There's now a spin boost
So when you're racing upside down
Or on walls
Cause remember this is kind of the new thing
For Mario Kart
Is that it's getting all F-Zero
And you can be upside down on walls
You can bump into other racers
And certain obstacles
To get a speed boost
And there's a spin boost
That will basically
They say is gonna change
The way players boost
And everything
So that could be very interesting
Some new characters announced
That are returning from prior games
Metal Mario
Lakitu
And Shy Guy
All coming back
Which is great
I loved Shy Guy
He was a great racer
So I'm looking forward to that
This is joining the cast
With the Kooplings
And I'm sure a bunch of the other standards
There as well
Some new items
In the game
The Piranha Plant
Which will attach to the front of the car
And then it chomps at other characters
Or banana peels on the track
And even shells
No word if that
Mother fucker blue shell
Will get eaten by the Piranha Plant
And you know the blue shell
Is gonna be invincible
And everybody's bane
Well like I was reading some comments
On people talking about it
They said that if they had the blue shell
Like they had it in Mario Kart 64
Where it was pretty rare to get it
Not just like
Oh you're in last place
You're gonna get it every single time
Yeah yeah yeah
That would have been a lot better
Also a new item called the Boomerang Flower
Which you know
The Boomerang Hammer Brothers and stuff
You've seen this item in the Mario games before
The Boomerang Flower
Will let you throw a Boomerang at opponents
And it will stun them
And the arc that the Boomerang takes
Will allow you to hit multiple players
You can throw it forward or backward three times
That sounds pretty powerful
They also showed off some remixed courses
Such as Moo Moo Meadows
From Mario Kart Wii
Toad's Turnpike from 64
Yes
That's really sweet
That's the best track
Yes
Donut Plains from Super Mario Kart redesigned
And instead of going with the retro looking graphics
They actually took that old course
And made it with the new graphics
I mean it definitely has that retro block look to it
But you'll see it when you see the video
Live recorded music
Which I think is kind of neat
And yeah various control schemes
The Wii U gamepad
The Wii U Pro Controller
And the wheel
Rainbow Road 64
Yes
Looks great
Fantastic
Now by the way
You know one of the kind of most people agree
This is the weakest game that ever came out in the series
Maybe not everybody agrees
But you know not a lot of love for Mario Kart Double Dash
Over the years
Which was the GameCube version
Where two people were racing at a time
And a very interesting interview with IGN
Where Hideki Kono said
Talking about possibly implementing this in the future titles
Quote
It wasn't just a simple case of
Hey we're not going to do that again
We really think the two racers together
In one kart of Double Dash was really unique
And we thought it worked really well
We've got that in our pocket
So if we come up with any new cool ideas
That utilize having two players racing together
We'll grab that
And possibly bring it back out
Having two players racing together
It does have a pretty high cost in terms of processing power
So that's an obstacle
That being said
If we could come up with some ways around that processing cost
We may have two players
Maybe even three players racing together
So they're not done with that idea yet
Maybe I don't know
I wouldn't exert too much development staff time on that
So I'm pretty sure that we're not going to see this in Mario Kart 8
That just might be something in the future
One other quick thing I want to drop in Nintendo News
Because they did do the info dump on Mario Kart 8
And I mentioned it's really the only game on the horizon
That we have to look forward to
Certainly there's a lot of stuff down the road
You know like the Bayonetta 2
And we know there's this stuff way down the road
Way way down there
But one of the other games that's inching closer and closer
Is the new Super Smash Brothers
They're having a big direct next week
I believe on Tuesday
It is a Nintendo Direct dedicated to Smash Brothers
Some people thinking we're going to get the release date
I'm thinking you might
You might get the month
Which we're finally going to know if it's holiday
Which we're finally going to know if it's holiday this year or next year
I think you're going to get the name
The real name will finally be out there
So I think that's the big thing that they're going to tell you
Super Smash Brothers U
Well it's on 3DS as well
So I don't know if that's the way they can go with it
Super Smash Brothers U and 3DS
3DU? Who knows? Who knows?
Alright let's move on
Dark Sakura
Well you know I have to say that kids are very resourceful
And sometimes find ways to make things happen
And in this case a 5 year old found a security hole in the Xbox One account login
A little kid named Christopher
Tried to log into his dad's Xbox One
And he didn't know the password
So all he did was keep entering spaces
After every time it failed
And it let him in
So basically this was reported
And Microsoft thanked him for finding the security hole
Which is actually funny
It said his dad is a security researcher
But basically after they found it and recorded it
Microsoft sent them some gifts as a thank you
After of course they patched this out
So they gave the kid and his dad
They acknowledged them as Microsoft security researchers for March 2014
Gave them $50 for Xbox One games and a year of Xbox Live Gold
So I guess if a kid's gonna try to sneak into daddy's account
I guess there are worse things that could happen for it
But I don't know I think
It shouldn't have been that easy
But at least it's something that was when it was discovered
It was reported and not used maliciously
Of course then again the dad's also a security researcher
So that makes sense
I don't know did you hear about that?
I heard about it but I mean if there's an exploit
That a 5 year old can accidentally find
That's pretty bad
I mean I don't know
Why is anyone able to log into someone's account
By just hitting the space bar
Or not the space bar but hitting space a bunch of times
That's just I don't know
It seems really lazy
Well maybe it's just that they didn't figure that
I mean it could possibly be something that was put in for system testing at the time
And then they figured it out after the fact
I don't know
It just
So
Anyways
So the Xbox One
Oh one last thing Kajudo also said that kid broke into his dad's cell phone
That kid's gonna grow up to be a hacker
Well he's just a little brat now isn't he
So the Xbox One
One of the things that it kind of lacked
Compared to some of it's competition
Is the ability to upgrade it's internal storage
Well now they're gonna be adding some external storage options
Coming soon
Apparently Major Nelson confirmed that
They will be adding external data support
And apparently
At a later time
Hopefully that means actual hard drives
You know a lot of these Xbox One games
Do require installations
And hell if you wanted to even go the whole digital route
If you're in my opinion dumb enough to do it
That takes up a lot of space
And you can only store so much in there in the first place
And hell they just I think added
The ability to see what you have on there as far as storage space goes
Because before it was pretty convoluted
What they had on there
I just don't understand how
Something like that
A core piece of functionality is just
Eh we'll just get to it later on
You know we don't really need to have the ability to
You know install your games on an external device or anything
In case you run out of space
Eh screw that we'll just
We'll just leave you to fend with the 500 gigabyte hard drive
Which you know 500 gigabytes is not that bad
Like the Xbox 360 or something
But when the file sizes of these games
Can be up to 10 times the size of an Xbox 360 game
That adds up pretty fast
Are you, you don't even
Is Xbox One even on your radar to get low key so you can
Oh fuck no
Eh still not
Not really ours either
Unless they announced
Even like let me put it this way
Even if they announced that Grand Theft Auto 5
Was coming next gen
I would not buy an Xbox One
That's a pretty strong statement
I'll get an Xbox One eventually
But it's just gonna take probably the next Halo
And Quantum Break
Which I'm anticipating would be this holiday
I don't see why they won't
Or at least
Even if Halo is not this holiday
I wonder if they'll do like
Halo 2 Anniversary Edition or something
But to be fair though
Like even the PlayStation 4
There's not really much that wants me
You know infamous Second Son looks pretty awesome
I've heard a lot of good things about that one
You know what might sell me on an Xbox One
Is if the new Crackdown game was really awesome
Like that might
You know the Crackdown is pretty awesome
I kinda like that game but
Right now there's just not anything upcoming
Especially the multiplatform stuff
Nothing really says oh I need to get this on next gen
What if they cut the price for the holiday
It would have to be by a lot
Like a lot a lot
Like we're talking down to $2.99 or something
I would not
Like even like that's the thing I was looking at
We use oh maybe I want Mario Kart 8
You know maybe
Maybe I do want one of those systems
But
It's just not cheap enough for me
Like I don't
I'm not gonna really buy a system for one game
And
You know spending like $200 even
Yeah $200 or more on it
Just doesn't seem worth it to me
To register participation for this week's episode
Of Orange On Radio at vognetwork.com
Going to our chatroom over at
Live.vognetwork.com
VXChaseNXV says who the hell wants to plug in
Mass storage into their game console
I don't even like to do that with my computer
I only do it begrudgingly
There's probably not a lot of reason for it right now
With so many limited games although the games are huge
But I do know like people like to download
Especially when you're downloading like entire TV series
Which you can do on Playstation 3
And some people have done it
And Xbox as well
You need a place to put those files
The reason why they have it that you can't
Fucking upgrade your drive in the Xbox
One or Xbox 360
Without buying one that's officially
From Microsoft is because they have their
Fucking stupid file system in there that's
What is it? FATX or XFAT
Or something like that
It's just some really stupid
File system that they have that
Is exclusive to those stupid consoles
I mean they have
XFAT's not exclusive to a console
Well they have ways to like you know format them
With like you know homemade programs
And stuff like that but
It's not like it's running
You know FAT32
Like the Playstation 3 was
They don't have just a standardized
File system in there
So you can't just pop in the hard drive
They want you to buy the 10 times more expensive
Hard drive that's going to be exclusive
For that console
Alright well moving on to more Xbox news
This news came out early in the week
That is certainly huge as
To the direction of Microsoft
Phil Spencer who was formerly
The corporate vice president of
Microsoft Studios is now the head of
Xbox over at Microsoft
And there was an interview that he did with
Major Nelson or Larry Erb
The day that you know or the day after
It was announced there
They're talking a little bit about E3 already
And you know some of the things hyping up there
Some people warming up to Phil Spencer because
It does seem like one of the first things
He's doing is he's making the conversation about the games
And he also essentially said
I mean I'm going to
Well I do have a quote here I'll say this
I know a lot of times people give nods to the different forums
Out there the different communities of people
I will honestly say I learn a ton
From listening to the feedback
Reading the forum ideas
I saw just when I was announced in the position
The first things that Phil Spencer should do as head of Xbox
There were a lot of great ideas there
Oh yeah I saw that too
He better bring back Shenmue 3
Which I think he said was like the number one most requested game
For Xbox
It's crazy which I don't even know how they would do that
Without a massive Sega partnership
Well then Sega let the trademark right now
They would just go up to Sega
And Sega would be like
Oh hey what the hell
What's all this money being thrown at me
Hey you want to play a game of Lucky Hit?
Anyway
So yeah you know
You notice that Phil Spencer
Does seem to be in tune with
The internet critics for better or for worse
I don't know if that's always necessarily a good thing
But he does definitely want to take the conversation
To games and he's talking about E3
And how they're already you know
They don't want to have a bunch of suits up there
They want the game makers out on stage
Talking about the games and you betcha
They're already planning E3
I mean they're already talking about you know
How many minutes are we going to give
What game and how's that all going to go
You bet all that stuff is being finalized right now
So
I'm excited to see where Phil Spencer takes the company
He certainly qualified for the job
So let's see what happens
Hopefully
We'll appease the people that were not happy
With the movies movies movies
Sports sports sports direction of the Xbox
But you know what I
I still think that
You know if Xbox really does
Make this full fleshed
Entertainment channel I think that's a huge
Asset
I don't think that's really been done
Like as far as the whole TV integration
Aside from being able to plug
I'm not even talking about that I'm talking about original content
Like the Halo thing with Spielberg and some of that stuff
I don't know
That's almost like the same stuff that we see on Netflix
And Amazon where they have their own original shows
I mean that's cool
But Netflix has Emmy award winning
Shows like Orange is the New Black
And House of Cards I don't believe Halo is going to be
Getting any sort of fucking Emmys
Well but could they get nerd cred
Equivalent
I don't know I saw their
Halo live action movie that they just
Did or whatever someone did
They licensed to
But I just
Think though the whole point though is they were
Focusing like oh it's going to be
This really integrated experience and stuff like that
And it kind of reminded me a whole bunch when they were
Talking about the whole
Second screen experience that you would get
With the
Xbox 360 even
And even kind of bringing it back to the Xbox One
Where it's like oh you can watch Game of Thrones
And there's all this interactive material on there
And where is that?
You know is that going to be happening
You know today I mean
Where is that stuff because
They talk a big game but
In the end it seemed like this is just
It's just like ooh
I can plug in my cable boxes to the back of
You know my game system like I could
A VCR
Well it's going to be a very
Interesting E3 to say the least
So we will be staying tuned
And the news is going to
Start to dry up as we get a little closer to
E3 and then once we hit like mid-May
Then all that news starts kind of leaking out so it's
Going to be a very interesting ramp up
Here to the June E3 show
Anyway more news DarkSakura
Well everyone knows I'm a big Treasure fan right?
Well this is something that's pretty happy
So basically
Treasure is actually working with Capcom to make
A sequel to
The game that they did on 3DS
Called Geist Crusher
And they're actually doing a version called
Geist Crusher God
That is basically
You go around and
Hunt boss creatures and kill them
That's the game but it's Treasure
So you know it's always got a twist to it
Really neat game but I thought that this one
Given that Treasure has done
Nothing but awesome games
Would definitely be something a lot of people would want to keep on their radar
The
The uh
Just the voice acting though in the trailer
Is pretty hilarious
This is Geist Crusher God
You know so it's like
It sounds like they're really gonna
Push for that level
So yeah just a little something
Alright well I'm sure that makes you happy
To hear about what's going on there
I love Treasure
Well let's talk about games that will be coming out a little bit
Sooner as we travel around the world and look at
The release dates
Loki why don't you start off with the US
Loki you're dead quiet again
I think you turned the mic on
Ok so anyways as I was saying
The Xbox 360 version
Of Titanfall was finally released
That is coming out
And from what I hear
It's actually pretty good
Except it runs at 30 frames per second
There's that I guess
Also this week Lego The Hobbit
Which is coming out on Playstation 3
Xbox 360, Playstation 4
Xbox One
3DS and Vita
And PC
The Wii U version
Though not coming out yet
Which is kind of surprising
And then um
Also later this week we've got
A game called Putty Squad
On Vita and Playstation 3
Lego Friends on the DS
And
Hopefully still coming out this week
Not delayed again but Hello Kitty Cruisers
On the Wii U
I guess that was released digitally already
But the physical version is just
Not out yet
And also
The one game I think that so far
Is actually going to be utilizing the Kinect
In a non-danced way
Kinect Sports Rivals coming to
Xbox One this week
Might be worth picking up
If you have that
And Jamie
This is something that you might want to pick up
Disney Magical World
For 3DS coming out on Friday
That's that game that crosses
Kind of like Animal Crossing with Disney characters
I need this in my life
So there's that
Alright well traveling to Japan
Yay I'm traveling to Japan
Looking at the releases there
Hey there's a Playstation 4 game out in Japan this week
It is Final Fantasy XIV Online
Just like we're getting here in the US
So that is a worldwide release
Coming out of Japan as well on April the 14th
On the Playstation 3
Excuse me
Sorry about that
On the Playstation 3 this week on the 10th
You can check out Dream Club Go Go
Is out on the Playstation 3
As well as Mato Kiranai
Yuge Kitai
Tokyo Twilight Ghost Hunters
Comes out from Arc System Works on April the 10th
Also
Oretache ni Subasa wa Nai
Under the Innocent Sky
So
A few games there on the Playstation 3
On the Xbox 360 this week just Titanfall
Titanfall gets its Japanese release as well
On the 360 this week
On the Playstation Vita
Some similar games there
The Oretache ni Subasa wa Nai
Under the Innocent Sky is out there
As is the Tokyo Twilight Ghost Hunters game
Those are both out on the Vita this week
On April the 10th
And on the Wii U this week
Nothing, they don't have anything until a Monster Hunter
That comes out on April 23rd
But the 3DS does have
Crayon Shin-chan
Crayon Shin-chan still
Arashi wo Yobu
Kasukabe Iga Stars
From Bandai Namco
That's a series that won't die
That is out on the 3DS this week
And that is a series that won't die
But you can make your own mini movies
And stuff it looks like
And look, there's Booty
In this little cartoon Booty
In the game
Doesn't he usually have his pants down or something like that?
I think that's the joke
There you go, that's the releases for Japan
How about the UK Dark Sakura?
Well on the 8th we have
Looks like
It's not actually in the name, I think it's 0
On PS4 and Xbox One
And then Max The Curse of the Brotherhood
On April 9th
On the 10th is Family Guy The Quest
For Stuff
On iOS and Android
Warlock II The Exiled
And another one on PC
That they're not giving me the name of
Which I'm going to see if I can find out what it is
Oh Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Online
And then on the 11th
We have Football Manager Classic 2014
Kinect Sports Rivals
Lego The Hobbit
A bunch of Lego The Hobbit
And a bunch more Lego The Hobbit
So yeah, that's it
Well good news for Lego The Hobbit fans
Alright, just a few more stories for you guys
This is the classic game of the week
And it's a good one tonight
Alright, so this is kind of disappointing
But apparently the Resistance
Games, they are going offline
Starting April 8th
And that is of course the online
Multiplayer portion of the game
You will not be able to play that anymore
Come April 8th
I don't know, I had a lot of fun
Playing Resistance, the first one at least
Split screen multiplayer
That was kind of fun to be able to do that
Didn't really get too much into
Two or three of those
Still disappointing to see that
They are taking that down
Not a lot of people are playing it anymore
Alright, well one more thing going offline
Not just Resistance going offline
But this one is having a huge impact
The GameSpy network is going offline
This is going offline
On May 31st
We sort of saw the hint of this coming
When Nintendo suddenly decided they were going to
Pull the Wii online stuff
And it was theorized that
There is probably something larger going on with GameSpy
And that they are increasing fees
And Nintendo didn't want to pay them
Sure enough, the whole damn plug is getting pulled
On all of GameSpy
GameSpy technologies
Closing the matchmaking service on May 31st
This is really the end of an era
Because I remember using GameSpy to find a game of
Quake to play online
Correct me if I'm wrong though
Aren't some modern games actually using GameSpy
Borderlands does
Yes, Borderlands does use GameSpy
So there are some games that
We are out there
That are no longer going to work anymore
Now I don't think
Anybody has used GameSpy since
Which is when Borderlands 1
But Borderlands 2 uses it as well
No it doesn't, Borderlands 2 doesn't use GameSpy
Are you sure about that?
I think it uses Steamworks
Chatter can correct me if I'm wrong
So yeah, if the company doesn't have the funding
Or the reason to go back and
Make another network work with the game
It's going to not work anymore
So this shouldn't be a huge surprise
GameSpy stopped making editorial content
In 2013
Glue Mobile, the mobile games publisher
Actually bought this in 2012
They kind of just ran it into the ground
Literally
And Bobby Blackwolf confirmed that
Borderlands 2 used GameSpy
And what's funny is that Bobby said
When he interviewed them, I even asked them that
And they were like, no, fuck GameSpy
So I guess they're not too happy
About the first time around, who knows
So, yeah, again, the end of an era
GameSpy was originally launched actually
As a Quake server search program
I used to use that to play Quake games
Man, I miss those days
So
Alright, well
Let's see what we got here
So we've got
Alright, well
You know, here on this show we like to
Look back at an era long gone
With a segment we call the classic game of the week
DarkSakura's going to dive into the gaming vault
And find a game that she thinks, hey
You should play this game right now
If you can find it
DarkSakura, in the original form
Good luck
DarkSakura, what is the classic
Game of the week?
The classic game of the week
The classic game of the week is
Where in the world is Carmen Sandiego?
What?
Sorry, I was trying to get your attention offline
You okay over there?
No, my mic got caught under the cord
Oh no
The joys of live radio, there we go
Alright, so
As we were saying, where in the world is Carmen Sandiego?
Yep
And of course the one with enough music
To actually play is the
1990 version
I am specifically referring to the original
That came out in 1985
When I was nine years old
I would play the crap
Out of this game
And it was
Released
Like I said in 1985
And distributed by the World
Ominak and Books of Facts
That was published by Feros Books
It was
Included with some versions
Of the Amiga 500
And there was also like I said
An enhanced version that came out in 1990
That did not have the
Ominak copy protection
But it had disc based copy protection
And there was a further deluxe
Expanded version that came out in 1992
So basically
You have to use your knowledge
Of geography and clues
To chase down Carmen's henchmen
Or henchwomen
Because there were henchwomen
Then eventually arrest Carmen herself
So you'd have to go to the country
That the crime happened
And then use hints about where to go next
And you basically chase all over the world
And some of the, there were some fun
Jokes, you know there were definitely some puns
Going about
And some inaccuracies
For some of the pictures
Like for example
When you go to Peru instead of
Showing you a picture of Lima when you're there
It actually shows you Machu Picchu
But at any rate
If you go to the incorrect location
You get fake clues
And you have to backtrack
Until you can find which way
The vile henchmen went to
It's V-I-L-E
And then your case will run
Out of time
And your culprit will escape
And basically you're reporting to Interpol
And everything
So eventually though if you do keep going
Along the case you can basically
Exclude all but one of the suspects
And then you can
Issue an arrest warrant which is actually really
Inaccurate because
I love some of the cheesy animations that were in the game
Like you have a little burglar dancing across the screen right now
It's V-I-L-E henchmen
The arrest warrant thing
Was actually super inaccurate because
Interpol actually uses what's called red notices
Which means that you have
The right to ask the local government
To arrest somebody instead of you
Actually having an arrest warrant
You have to go through the local governments
Anyway, going back to the game world
You can be promoted
If you answer different geography questions
Right
And you use the reference book that came with the program
So it's really
Edutainment
As far as some of the different locations
That are in the game
You had Buenos Aires
You had Sydney
You had
Bamako in Mali
You had Tokyo
You had
Moscow
All kinds of places all over the world
And there's something else
That really came along with this
There's been certain things
Kept canon
Through different versions of the game
I think
It's been established that there are different universes
For the Carmen Sandiego franchise
But there's one thing that's always
Remained constant
Is Carmen herself
Her outfits have changed
And they've changed her hair color like once
But she's always been
Latina
And always
Really strong and in control of the company
And her vile group
But the whole point of it was that
She was doing it for the challenge
And not necessarily for any kind of
Really overly malicious
Purpose
And the fact that she can keep all these people
Under control
Is a really tightly run, I'd say, organization
It's actually made her
Kind of a role model
For young girls
Even if, yeah, she's breaking the law
But still
There were, of course, many other games
In the series
We've had
Multiple versions of
Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego
We've had the Treasures of Knowledge version
That came out in 2001
And then
There were also
Where in Time
Is Carmen Sandiego
There were also various
Other, there was Where in the USA
Where in Space
Junior Detective Where in America
Has Passed
Where in North Dakota, which was a prototype
Where in Time is probably one of my favorites
Because I was really good at it
There was Where in Europe
Where in the USA
Think Quick Challenge
Great Chase Through Time World Detective
Math Detective Treasures of Knowledge
Secret of the Stolen Drums
Uh, Mystral Baud de Monde
Wow, I didn't even know all these other ones
Actually, you talking about the other versions
I'm gonna use this opportunity to switch over
To some footage from the original
Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego
Yeah
Uh, there was also
Um, the TV
Show, which was Where in the World
Where in Time, Where on Earth was an animation
And Where in the Universe was a planetarium
Show. There were also albums
That was Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego
And Out of This World
So, uh, we've had
Tons of, uh, different
You know, pretty reputable, uh, publishers
And distributors. We had PBS
Uh, okay, I will
Take anything with Fox
With a grain of salt, but it was Fox Family Channel
And Fox Kids
But we've had, uh, BAM Entertainment
Mindscape, uh, The Learning Company
Broderbund, which was the original publisher
Or developer, I should say
Uh, just all kinds of, you know, really
Good, I think, has come
Out of, uh,
You know, the franchise
And, of course, you also worked for the
ACME Detective Agency
That worked worldwide
So
But I'm trying to see
Okay, ACME VILE
Was, um, let's see if I can find what VILE
Stood for, because that was the one
Thing that's eluding me
Um
Okay, VILE was not an acronym
It was just V-I-L-E
But it didn't really
It didn't really mean anything
So that's probably why I didn't know what it meant
So, there you go
And, of course, the leader of ACME is the chief
Who was a sassy black lady
That didn't need no man
She was awesome
In the TV show, yes, which everybody in chat
Talking about the TV show, dying for me to play the theme
But, well, you have to stay tuned
To the very end of the show
That's right, you just sit down and shut up and wait
Maybe the same person who picks the classic game
Also picks the fortune cookie
So
But, yeah, that's
Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego?
Maybe in China, according to this player right now
Who knows, so there it is, your classic game of the week
Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego?
Great series
One of the all-time best
Vegetainment games from my youth
You've got Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego?
Number Munchers
And
Oregon Trail, that's about it
Those are the huge ones from Oregon
Oregon Trail
Dungeon Buster says
Do you think they retconned that in?
Through the Meaning has consistently been maintained
Since 1985
Well, see, I didn't realize that
It wasn't in any of my stuff
So
You learned something from our chat room today
Well, I forgot anyway
I haven't touched the game in like
Probably since I was 11
You know, Jamie, it's okay
It's okay to make mistakes
You know what, I'm making the big W off
The line because it's the whatevs
Whatever
Alright
That is it for this
Part of Orange Lounge Radio
But don't go anywhere, you guys
We've got plenty more Orange Lounge Radio to come
Right after a quick
Break, we're going to talk to
You guys in the Skype segment
1877 Game OLR, username on Skype
Orange Lounge Radio
We've got the FUGO Question of the Week
Rapid Fire news and plenty more gaming news
When we come back, right after this
With more of Orange Lounge Radio
Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio
Live on this
April the 6th of 2014
With episode number 547 of our show
And if
I don't know, if
Game of Swords or whatever's done
And Rasslin' is done and all that stuff
Is it Chair of Swords?
By the way, Honest Game Trailer
Or Honest Trailers, whatever
Finally did a
Chair of Swords one
I like the compilation of
All the death scenes
Featuring the most uncomfortable chair ever
But anyway, all that stuff
All that is hopefully wrapping up
By now so some of you guys might be joining us
Just after that
Well you missed some chatter in the first
We were talking about April Fools Joke
The new Amazon Fire, Mario Kart 8
So you're just going to have to
Check this out on the podcast feed
Which will be available
Tomorrow morning
Both on iTunes Store
And of course Stitcher Radio
And if you do listen to us, wherever it is
You listen to our show on the podcast
Or what have you, be sure to leave us a nice
Review, help spread the word about the show
We really appreciate it
Oh Jason's telling me in chat, wrestling is not over
Oh well
I thought it was because people started showing up all of a sudden
So I was like, oh maybe it's finished
Fine, maybe it'll be done by the time phone calls start
Alright
In the meantime, let's get some rapid fire
News
Let's start with Loki
Alright so this was a game I actually played
At least the second one in the series
Metro
You may remember
Metro 2033 and Metro Last Light
Well there was something that leaked
Out that was apparently
An internal document from Deep Silver
And it was showing
A title called Metro Redux
Which is basically
A redo
Or
An HDerfied
New version of those two games
For consoles for Playstation 4 and
Xbox One
It was later confirmed
Actually by 4A Games
And Deep Silver
That it is a title that's in development
And they're going to be sharing more
They say this side of E3
Sometime before E3
You'll find out more about it
And
I don't know, I'd be excited about that
Cause those games are pretty good
Had really good storylines
The Grand Theft Auto 5
iFruit app
Is now available on Vita
That was something that was released originally
On Windows Phone, iOS
And Android
That was basically like a little fake
The iFruit is their
Apple clone in the game
And it had a bunch of different apps
On there for customizing your cars
Customizing your license plates
And they even had a little Tamagotchi game
For Chop where you can kind of train
And raise them
Now you can do that if you have a Vita
That's kind of cool
And it is free to download
It works with the Playstation 3 version of the game of course
And last but not least
The Call of Duty
Ghost Devastation
DLC
Is seriously Jump the Shark
I gotta be honest
I don't know what the fuck
Other than having fun with the series
Cool, that's awesome
But like
The stuff that they've done for Call of Duty
Hasn't really made a lot of sense for ghosts
They have
Basically the ability
To play as the predator in one of the maps
And what they've done
Kind of with
Call of Duty Ghost is each map has its own
Kind of like
Basically it's like a killstreak that you get
That's exclusive to that map
And one of them in this case is actually
Playing as the predator
And I think one of the other maps
I think it was Ghost
I don't think it was Black Ops 2
But Ghost had it
I want to say where there was a map where you could play as Michael Myers
From Halloween
What do you mean William Shatner?
So
It's just
I don't know, cool
They're having fun with it
People enjoy that kind of thing, that's cool
That actually launched last week
On Xbox One
Xbox 360
The
PlayStation 4, PlayStation 3 versions
I'm assuming are coming later on
Oh and PC later on as well
Xbox gets that exclusive window
Alright well
Moving on to a short
Window of time for you to get tickets
For the Dota 2
International 2014
The Dota 2 International
Championship for 2014
Is taking place at the Key Arena in Seattle
It will be taking place from
July 18th to July 21st
And if you wanted to go
Well guess what, you're already out of luck
Because the tickets sold out in an hour
So you had one hour window to catch that
10,000 tickets sold within an hour
So Dota 2
It's kind of popular there
So you can check that out in Seattle
Huh? A bit
Yeah you can check that out in Seattle at the Key Arena
You can get your tickets on eBay
To go see that
The Key Arena, that's where the
Supersonics used to play
But sadly Seattle doesn't have a team anymore
And they were unsuccessful in taking ours
So Key Arena, at least still able to have
These big events such as the Dota 2 International
You can try to find the tickets on eBay
If you really want to go
But I'm sure they'll sell the whole viewing passes
Online and all that good stuff
Blizzard
Taking Hearthstone
Finally to the iPad
They've been talking about doing this for a little bit
When they first announced the game
And now that the game is live
It's time to start the 18 month beta process
That Blizzard will go through
I'm exaggerating here
But with Hearthstone on the iPad
But here's the catch, you can only download this
In Australia, Canada, and New Zealand
Those are the only places where Hearthstone
Is actually available on the store
But some of you crafty people have figured out
How you make an account in another country
You can download the game to your device anyway
There's quite a few people that are doing that
So there's all these walkthroughs out there
It doesn't involve anything about having iTunes cards
For those countries, does it?
I don't think so
I know that's the way that they do it for music
But don't quote me
I don't care enough about Hearthstone
To go to the Canadian store and make a fake account
And download it
Neither do I, but
But with like a review, a review would be nice
Well I reviewed it on the PC
I mean hearing more from our listeners
In those countries, we would like reviews from them
Oh sure, of course, of course
I'd like to hear if you thought it was as mediocre as I did
There you go
Hearthstone on the iPad
I know there's some fans out there
That are gonna be angry at me for saying that
But you know, I got my opinion
You got yours, email us if you want
Participate at orangeslawnsradio.com
Lastly, this was news
This is actually old news
But it slipped under our radar
So I need to bring this up
Because this news came out the week that we had the short show
Because I was moving
So this completely was not on our radar
But it was brought to my attention this week
That there is a Gauntlet reboot happening
And there's a trailer out there now
And you can actually check this out
Maybe I'll play a little bit of this here in studio
I don't remember
If there's narration or what have you
But just for Dark Soccer's sake
You can see there it's coming from WB Games
It better have the music
I don't think it does have the original music
Crying
But you can see there it's very Diablo-esque in how it looks
So it looks like it's taking elements of Gauntlet
And mixing it with Diablo
Okay
So that's what the new Gauntlet looks like
And luckily they still call them
Warrior, Valkyrie, Elf
They try to give them names and all this stuff
This is Bob the Elf
We have Gertrude the Valkyrie
They're saying it is a completely modernized action RPG
It's going to be direct to digital
WB Games vault
Which means you're pretty much only going to be able to get it
On the Steam
And those types of places
What is interesting about this though
It's being made by Arrowhead as I mentioned
You may not know their other game
But it's Magica
Magica was cute
Yeah Magica was a huge game
And it was pretty cool
And the Tron Robes
Yeah the Tron Robes and all that stuff
So those are the people we can Gauntlet
So that's pretty exciting there
So there you go
Gauntlet is being remade
And supposedly out this summer
On digital platforms
Which means the price should be right as well
We'll see
Dark Soccer what do you have for us?
Disney Disney Disney Disney Disney
Okay
So yeah
As Loki said during the last part
Disney's Magical World 3DS
Is supposed to be coming out
But there is a
It's supposed to be an exclusive
The 3DS XL that goes with it
Is an exclusive for Walmart
And I don't care enough to go to Walmart to get it
But there will also be coming out
There's the Mickey 3DS XL
There's also a Peach Pink Nintendo 2DS
That's an exclusive for GameStop
That will be coming out to celebrate
Disney's Magical World launch
The game will be out on April 11th
And you know my birthday is this month
Just saying people
Also there are Australian ratings out for Castlevania Aria of Sorrow
F-Zero GP Legend
I'm starting to get tongue tied
And those are listed for the Wii U's Gameboy Advance store
So we should be seeing those probably before too long
And then last but not least
There is a statement from the Sonic Lost World producer
Who wants to do more Nintendo DLC
That's Iizuka Takashi
Who created Sonic Lost World
Basically wants to do more levels
Working with Nintendo
But that could be for Zelda or Yoshi levels
It could use other Nintendo IPs
But it is just different things that they want to do
Going out for Sonic Lost World
And that's it
Alright
That Sonic Lost World DLC sure looked interesting
I didn't believe
I thought it was like an April Fools Joker
I didn't believe it was a thing until I actually was
Seeing the screenshots and the videos in motion
I was like wow
I didn't think they were going to go that far with it
But that's kind of neat
Alright
Let's get to the foogle question of the week
Every week we ask a question on our Facebook
And our Google Plus communities
You slam those words together and you get
Foogle
Let's get to the question
Which has to do with that new fangled Amazon fire
We were talking about earlier
When we posted to our communities
A new challenger approaches
The long rumors
Of Amazon jumping into the
Gaming arena proved true this week
With the announcement of the Amazon fire
What did you think of the announcement?
Do you think the Amazon fire will impact gaming?
And more importantly, are you getting one?
Let's get to some of the answers
Our buddy Shane answered
Shane Alinko answered
And said is this not the Ouya 2.0
But maybe done better?
I have faith that Amazon will support it
But I don't think it's going to be huge competition
Let's get to the main three
No desire to get one because of that
Critical Myth
The man behind tv.vognetwork.com
With his crew over at the Critical Myth show
Says it's a bit closer
To what the Ouya claimed it would be
But I still don't see a need for it
Those already using the Amazon
Fire services might feel differently
Brett the Hayes says
I like the idea that someone like Amazon
Is trying this out despite their efforts
With the not so warm reception of the Fire tablets
Since they have somewhat of an ecosystem
In place already
I don't think they'll do anything for hardcore gaming
Except maybe push Sony to bring Vita TV
To the US
It is interesting that one Amazon
Exec was making a distinction that this device
Is not a gaming device
And probably shows their fear of ending up like
Ouya and probably why they're marketing
The Fire TV as a set-top box
First
Blood Drunk says
Never really had any interest in those TV boxes
The announcement of Fire TV doesn't really change that
I still think that having a laptop
And desktop plugged in with wireless keyboard and mouse
Is the way to go
More power and diversity
Burr replied and said
I think it has the best chance of making an Android
A credible console platform
But in the end it's stuck in a hard place
Where anything with wide enough appeal would probably play just as well
On a tablet or smartphone
And anything that would get the hardcore gamer's attention
Would have to compete with more established platforms
Felipe A. replied
I hope I said your name right
Fire TV will be a great boost
To the local economies it is marketed in
The amount of jobs created to dispose of them
Will open up new positions in the waste management sector
Not since the plastic guitars from Guitar Hero
Or the Ouya
Has a sizable increase in landfill size
Been needed
Anyone here owning a Zune or a Gizmondo
Knows
Well where things like this end up
Welcome to your new home Fire TV
That was a sassy answer
I don't think it's gonna go anywhere
He's saying it's going to the dump
Going with your game.com
What the hell were those tacos
Hey for the record we gave our game comms away
What were the taco phones called
The Nokia
The Engage
We gave those away too and I think we sold one
It's because they didn't have Patrick Stewart as a pitchman
For that you know that's why that didn't end up working out
Engage
Alright
Nemesis 47 replies and said
Though this has potential it's not going to be enough
To beat the big three as far as gaming
And will be the next Ouya
I don't got any intention of buying the system
I'll stick to my PlayStation 3
Tech 2030 says
I think this will have a better chance of being a third
Console than something like Ouya or GameStick
Considering it has great
Video streaming functionality
Our pal Tiara replies
And she says this will be the Philips
CDI of a new generation
Ouch
And Tigerclaw says
It could do better than the Ouya
If the processing power is better
Which we know it's going to be so
We'll see
Going over to Google Plus I don't want to ignore our
Pals over there on Google Plus
Again you can follow us on Google Plus
If you just go to
Google.com
Slash plus orange lounge radio
And
We didn't get a single answer on Google Plus
Hey Rob
Confirmed you guys
No one's using Google Plus
I was just thinking if we're calling it Fugal
Would the opposite be Goobook
We could call it Goobook I don't know
Is that, it's a little
That's a little bit more even between Google and
Facebook
But yeah not a single answer on our Google
Where's actdeft and Flaco Jones
Redertainment the guys that usually answer over there
They're eating a pizza
You're all watching Wrestlemania
Everyone's talking about trying to compete with
Home consoles it's not
It's trying to be a set top box
It's trying to push Amazon shit
That they have on Android
And their services like their video streaming services
That's all it is
That being said though
It's going to be way fucking better than the Ouya
And I think they've already said
That they're probably going to get the
Was it the
Ouya the run on it anyway
So
You know
What's interesting and I think very telling
About those answers I don't think a single person in there
Said they're getting one
Not a single one I mean granted
Us gamers were not the target audience
I suppose but I don't know
Well like I wouldn't get it for any of the games that they have
On there cause like you know
Had it come out like several years ago
Before Minecraft
Was on consoles then that would have been like
Oh yeah I can play Minecraft on my
TV now but now it's just like
Eh whatever
Alright
Well let's move on with some more news
Low key
So there's a survey sent out
About the Playstation 4 and mainly
The Playstation network services and stuff
And there's some stuff that they were asking about
That
Kind of leads people to believe that
They're going to be doing a reputation system
Kind of like what they have on the Xbox One
Which I think is a great idea
Basically saying the system would assign
Users reputation ratings
Based on feedback from fellow players
And mentions
I guess an improved matchmaking system
Also they were saying that
It was going to take reputation into
Considerational appearance so basically
What I want to see is
I want to see
Amazon style reviews
For players like on your profile
This player
Sucks one star
No that sounds like it would be horrible
I can't even imagine
Oh my gosh
You'd have the people that found it helpful
People that didn't find it helpful
You know
A metacritic score maybe
Can you imagine what your profile would say
This guy is so angry and he kicked my ass
At grand theft auto 5
I don't talk on my headset really
No because I'm in the room with
Yes if my co-workers
Were playing with me
They would probably fill me out
And say quite negative things about me
They always say I'm hacking
Even though
I can play any
We've switched consoles so many times now
It's like oh he's hacking
Fine I'll beat you on your console
I'll play on yours you play on mine
Oh he's just hacking that one now too
People
Alright
Let's go to
Some more news
This is kind of interesting
Where have your favorite franchises ended up?
Going to
Pachinko machines
And the newest characters that will be coming
To Pachinko machines
Fatal Fury and Samurai's Showdown
What?
These are Pachi's slot machines
That are headed for Japan
Yeah SNK Playmore is using
The Fatal Fury and Samurai's Showdown names
To make these Japanese
Slot machines which are I guess
I've never played these but I guess it's kind of like Pachinko
They don't license anything
I mean seriously remember when they were licensing
What was that I think
I don't know if it was Samurai's Showdown
Or King of Fighters or something
It was that Shmup game
I think it was the King of Fighters Shmup game
Well these series haven't had
Games in a very very very long time
So Fatal Fury Premium
Is one of the games
And Samurai Spirits
Because that's what it was always called overseas
There's actually trailers
For these I have not watched this yet
I think I should what do you guys think should I watch this
Trailer here? Alright let's take a look
Let's do it where no one else can see it
Well if you're watching OLR on YouTube
You can see the trailer here
What?
Wait wait wait wait wait wait stop
I'm stopping? Okay stop
Pause
Black Wolf just said RIP Mickey Rooney
Did Mickey Rooney die?
I thought
Didn't he die a long time ago?
No?
Oh
Hold on
Okay play it I'm gonna look this up
You stopped that trailer just to say
That a celebrity had passed away?
Dude it's fucking Mickey Rooney
Yeah I know but I kind of thought he was already dead
No offense I mean
You also thought Shirley Temple was dead
I did think she was dead
Girl
There's a lot of people I think are dead
Speaking of dead let's go back to the franchise
For these uh
For these series
Let's go back to the trailer for these franchises that are super dead
Uh oh yeah TMZ reporting that Mickey Rooney died
That's what everybody's saying in the chat
Well
Sad
When was the last time Mickey Rooney was out in public?
Well he was in a night at the museum and
Alright anyhow here it is
Uh going to back to the trailer
Oh man this is so rude because when you see this
You're like oh man it's gonna be a new game
But you see all the characters
It's got the rock music and all this stuff
You're like oh my god
Geese Howard
So like yeah you're like thinking new game
And then it's
I just love the little power ballad playing in the back
Yeah next gen fighting game
I know right
Doesn't it look like oh my god it's gonna be a next gen Fatal Fury
I'm so fucking excited and then it's like
Oh wait but he's in a casino
What's he doing in a casino
I wanna see how long into this trailer it takes
Before it's given away that it's a slot machine
Oh not until the end I'm guessing
Oh that's so rude
Boom
Yeah we're already like three quarters of the way through the trailer
I will be willing but yeah it's not until like the very end of the trailer
Do we get to see some balls?
Cause you know Pachinko
Yeah it's not until like the very end of the trailer
Do we get to see some balls?
Cause you know Pachinko
It's Pachinko
And yeah next level
There it is
They show one little machine
What a troll
Jerks
Alright Dark Sakura
Do you have some better news for us?
John Panette died too
He's funny
Is everybody dying today? What's going on with that?
Well you know Game of Thrones was on
It's become self aware
It's killing people outside of the show now
Bye
Bye everybody
What do you have for us?
I have growling
Well speaking of things that I guess
I'm not even gonna go there
I'm not gonna say things that are dead
Things that are gonna be dug up years from now?
I...
Come on you were thinking it
Literally cannot even
Oh what was the joke?
Things in the ground? Was that the joke?
Things that should stay dead
Listen
That's not fair
They're not buried yet
I'm sorry
Are you guys done?
I'm waiting to hear about these cartridges
That's all I'm talking about
These were cartridges
You just spoiled the story Mr. Spoilerbutt
I didn't say none
Mr. I'm gonna spoil the Hunger Games for Jamie
Earlier even though I asked you to
Whatever
It's true
Good to know that my powers of deduction
Are accurate
Anyway, so remember that group that was trying to dig up ET?
Okay sorry
Oh my god they're digging up Elizabeth Taylor?
Elizabeth Taylor?
God she just died
She didn't just die
That's so rude
Oh you mean the game ET
The Atari 2600 version of ET
There was a group that was gonna film
A documentary about trying to
Dig it up out of the dump in New Mexico
And they got
The
OKs from the NMEB
Environmental Protection Division of Solid Waste Bureau
They approved
A waste evacuation
And it was submitted by
Xbox Entertainment Studios
Who is going to apparently
I guess be publishing this documentary
And filming it
So we have efforts from Lightbox Entertainment
And Xbox Entertainment
To let the dig happen
This is gonna be about as
You know as
Okay did anyone remember
Anybody remember
When Geraldo
Tried to go into Al Capone's
Vault or whatever the fuck it was
This is gonna end up just like that you know what's gonna be in there
Nothing
They're gonna find shit
And
They will actually find shit
Now it would be funny though if they actually find like
Neat relics from the 80s
That are broken
No it's gonna be nothing
They might find like some like decomposed
Cabbage patch kids and like maybe a speaking
Spell that still works in there somewhere
I suppose Cabbage Patch Kid be
A garbage pail kid at that point
Might possibly be
For the record
Bobby I'm not watching the movies
Yet I'm reading the books
But when you do watch the movies
Bobby will be quick to point out that the second one
Catching Fire the Capitol
Is one of the Dragon Con hotels
And it really is
It's pretty awesome to be in there and be like
Oh I'm at the Capitol
At any rate I'm reading the books first
Alright fair enough fair enough
So you could be let down by the movies
No I'm just kidding the movies are great
Loki what politically incorrect thing do you have for us next
Well let's see
I've got basically
Just
Wolfenstein
You know they have that Doom beta planned
For just PlayStation 4, Xbox One
And PC and I remember
Correctly and I wanted to say I looked it up
But then I saw something shiny and I
Forgot to look it up but I want to say that
That whole Doom beta thing is actually
On all the box art for
All the games
So that's kind of a little misleading if you think about it
That they're only doing the beta for
You know select versions of the game
But
They're going to feature it on the box
Yep there it is Xbox 360 preorder
For Doom beta access
Asterix
These certain systems here
I guess it could be very far out
You'd expect that you're going to have a
Brand new console
I'm willing to bet that the next Doom game
Is only going to be
For the PlayStation 4, Xbox One and PC
Which is probably why the beta is not on the current gen
I don't see why it wouldn't be
I think the current gen
Stuff is starting to sunset a little bit
I'm sorry last gen at this point
Well yeah
We're kind of in between now so yeah
I think the 360 PlayStation 3 era
You're starting to see the sunset on it
I think we still have some big games this year
I mean we still know that the Kingdom Hearts 2
Remake is happening at some point
That was announced before
There's some other little things here and there
That will probably take us into 2015
I think especially by next holiday
Will be like the last
Stuff you see on those consoles
And even this holiday it's going to start
To thin out because they want you to buy the new stuff
So that's where all the games are
And I'm sure the Doom game is only on those consoles
So yeah I think that's why they have it
They figure between now and whenever
That beta comes out
Because that could either be the end of this year or next year
Who knows
A lot of people will have
Another console by then
Alright well speaking of
Betas and things that ended up launching
On the current
No actually it's on your current PCs
And it will be on the next gen hardware
Soon enough
Scrolls Online was released
On the PC this week
And they had some hiccups going into
The launch but the game is now out
And kind of the
Resounding
There's some people that are really into it
That are really enjoying it
But I'm hearing a lot of resounding feedback
And this has been true on Horde House leading up to the show too
That
Why are we paying for this?
That it's not
Able to compete with some of the other pay MMOs right now
Now I don't know
I kind of think that's the way
All these games tend to be when they announce a pay subscription
You know Final Fantasy 14
Has a subscription right now
World of Warcraft still has a subscription right now
That's how these games kind of go
I think Elder Scrolls will be able to ride it out for a little bit
But it's all about can they
Bring the players in
And can they catch that buzz wave
Right now there's been a lot of people that have tried it
That have been like meh
I'd rather just play Skyrim
When they first announced
I was like oh yeah Skyrim
But it's going to be online and stuff
That's going to be awesome
And then it was just kind of from there
Just kind of a downward slope
The more and more I saw about the game
The less and less interested I was in the game
And then I played the beta and I was like nope
And why was that?
Why were you turned off?
It just wasn't engaging
It was very
I don't know it just didn't feel like Elder Scrolls to me
I was just trying to shoehorn Elder Scrolls into an MMO
And
I just didn't like it
Also another big pet peeve
It didn't support controllers
Well I think it's going to have to if they put it out on Playstation 4
Well yeah
But it just wasn't very interesting
Once again I
Don't want to pay for an MMO
Because I just don't
The amount of time I get to play that kind of stuff
Is just very mixed
So I just can't dedicate $15
A month to something that I probably
You know I may not play that month
Dungeonbuster in our chat room
Over at live.vognetwork.com says
Elder Scrolls Online should have spent a bit more time
In beta from what I've read
Some bugs and broken quests I've seen in the beta
Were still issues
Uh oh, that's not good
So there it is Elder Scrolls
Is out, you know if you feel
Differently if you're really enjoying the game let us know
You know I gotta be honest I haven't really played it
But I don't really
There's no demo right now or there's no way to like
Download it and play free to level 10
Or anything like that because it's new
I assume that'll happen in the coming months or there'll be the Playstation 4 beta
So I'll check it out at that point
But for now I just don't see the reason
I'm juggling Final Fantasy 14
I know I'm going to get sucked back into World of Warcraft
When Warlords of Draenor comes out
There's still Diablo 3
In the interim which technically isn't an MMO
But close enough
I just don't got time for it
And nobody got time for that Elder Scrolls
I think people want the Elder Scrolls Skyrim
But with
Some way to play co-op or something
I think people want Elder Scrolls 6
Is what they really want
If the next Elder Scrolls game comes out
If Elder Scrolls 6 comes out and it has
Like 4 player co-op or even 2 player co-op
I think that people are just not going to care
Well Elder Scrolls 6 is going to be announced for a while
You're still going to have Fallout 4
Yeah Fallout's next
Or Doom I guess
Alright well let's go
Go to the mailbag
Every week you guys send us emails
Sometimes we have wrong opinions on things
And you want to set us on the right path
So you can do that
Participate at orangelaungeradio.com
Is the place where you can participate with the show
Again our email address participate at orangelaungeradio.com
Darsakra dives into the mailbag head first
And pulls out
She finds Carmen Sandiego in there
Yeah she's hiding right there
But I'm busy talking about food with Ikuma-san
Well you're going to have to take a break
And we're going to be sharing our emails with our listeners
Over at live.vognetwork.com right now
Alright well first email
Comes from
I'm going to say Jonathan
Because that's all I get
Hey OLR crew
My only problem with Oculus Rift
Is that Kickstarter is for
Indies that can't get a company to fund them
Let be real
Oculus Rift could
Have been funded from the start
I think the typing on here
Why are the little Kickstarter
Pledgers money not worth any returns
In the end it's the backers fault though
Thanks Jonathan
I kind of think Oculus did try to get
The other type of funding in the start
But people laughed at it because we all laughed at the
Virtual reality stuff in the 90's
You know the lawn mower man
Came and went
Kickstarter was how this thing got funded
And I think it did
I mean if you look at Facebook
Buying them for 2 billion dollars
This investment was successful
The only problem is it's Kickstarter
You don't own any equity in it
If you don't like that don't
Kickstart companies
They got a return
They got a dev kit win
That's true
You get whatever prize you pledge for
Or perk
So this one comes from Robert M
I was going to ask this in chat last week
But was out late so are you worried
That the negative reaction to the Facebook
Acquisition of Oculus may be a
Self-fulfilling prophecy
When Zynga bought the developer of Draw Something
Those hating the publisher for valid
Reasons and those joining the outcry
Stopped supporting the game
Seeing less for the profit than forecast
Zynga closed down OMG Pop
Detractors told you so
This view may be over simplistic
And perhaps come across as apologetic
But could a similar relatively unwarranted
Exodus endanger the rift
Sorry if Bobby Black Wolf has already covered this
This is from Robert M
What was the question in there?
Okay if
If Facebook purchasing
Oculus
And people saying well I'm not going to support
This and stop adding their support to it
Is going to make it fail
The way that when Zynga
Acquired Draw Something
Ah sort of
Like is the
Internet damming it without
Necessarily giving it a chance
Exactly I have a feeling
And here's something to keep in mind
Facebook
Wants to target non-gamers
As well
And that's a huge wild card
But when you look at
What Zuckerberg said about the Oculus Rift
And the big plan for it
I mean games are in there too don't get me wrong
But he
I don't want to put words in his mouth
But I get the sense that they don't need
To be successful
Not really
There's plenty of other applications for the technology
But um
I think also the proof is in the pudding
I would bet
I would bet money
Because this is the internet and this is gaming culture
I would bet a large sum of money
That at least 75%
If not more
Of the people bitching about Oculus Rift
And how they're never going to play one
Never have
Or never intended to anyway
Or there's also this let's go back to NPR's
Little prank never bothered to read
Anything about the acquisition either
Or still will buy it when it comes out
So I think
There I mean
The comparison to draw
Something and Zynga is interesting
But I think we have to remember
That iPhone games especially
Tend to be very flash in the pan
And you know it's popular
One week you're in, one week you're out
You know
One week you're
Threes
Then your 2048
Goes out for free
And kind of bites into those sales
I mean that's the nature of the iPhone
Gaming the very volatile free
And 99 cent market
Well I would like to read what Bobby said in chat
Please
Zuckerberg said Oculus will do the game stuff first
And then he'd use the Facebook power to do
The non-game stuff
It basically lets the Oculus concentrate on gaming
And further said most of the Reddit
Most of the Reddit bitching
Were from people who never posted on the
Oculus subreddit before
They all left and it's back to normal now
But I mean it goes back to the people
Just wanting something to bitch about and not actually
Doing any research on it
Basically like a conversation with my mom
Well that's interesting though
That they are still going to focus on gaming first
Okay so I'm corrected a little bit there
But I still think the point stands that they are
Looking at doing more than
Just gaming
And you know what? At the end of the day
If gaming doesn't end up making
Them money
But premium events
Using the Oculus Rift to be able to attend
Premium events live and selling it as an
Entertainment device if that works for them
Then guess where they're going to end up focusing
When I was a teenager
A young teenager
We used to pay for pay per views
So that we could watch new kids on the block concerts
You know I think there's a lot of people
Out there who bought a pay per view this evening
Yes they did
I wonder
How many people would be interested in watching an event
Like Wrestlemania on the Oculus Rift
Good for thought
At any rate
The next email actually has something to do with
The wrestling
It says Oculus idea
Dearest peoples
As you were talking about the possible future of
Facebook infused Oculus Rift
I had an idea as to what the future could be
It's not video games, it's a different experience entirely
As you read this
Wrestlemania
30 is streaming live
On the WWE network
WWE's exclusive online platform
Is not the only place where live events
Are streamed
I watched Nine Inch Nails perform live at Lollapalooza
Via YouTube
WWE has streamed their pre-shows on Facebook
For over a year now and you can watch UFC PPV
Events live on Ustream
What is the next experience?
Imagine if you could be in a crowd during a concert
And by this I don't mean the broadcast slash concert
Film experience you get now
I mean actually being in the crowd for a concert
Or a sporting event
This is what I think could be done with the
Facebook infused Oculus Rift
Selling concert tickets for people
To be able to see live events
From the comfort of their own home
If you could see something live
And where I say the Rolling Stones last tour
Or the upcoming Monty Python performances
Or a concert from a performer
Who thinks your city is too small to perform in
I'm looking at you Kanye
You could bet people
Would buy tickets to see that event
Also you could sell different tickets
In different parts of the arena enabling the corporation
Providing the event to make more money
Off the live stream than the one size fits all
Approach they get now
That makes the experience appealing for consumers
And way profitable for corporations
Yay!
Stay black entertainment
This message has been brought to you by Tacos
You know one idea
That pops in my mind too
Is that sometimes you have those one night
Only shows somewhere in the world
That maybe doesn't necessarily
Tour or anything like that
Right now maybe get a Blu Ray
Or a movie out of it
But imagine being able to be there live for the experience
One thing that pops into my mind
When he passed away he was prepping to do those shows
At the London O2 arena or whatever
He was going to do a bunch of shows
And then this is it right
I'm done no more
He's going to retire just like Cher
But that was supposed to be it
If I could turn back time
There would have been a lot of people
That would have paid to see that
There's a problem
With this
There's a big problem with this one
Is that to make it work
In that type of area
You would have to have multiple rendering cameras
Open at all times
That would be unobstructed by
The other concert goers
You could do it
The issue being
Is that they would all have to still
Re-render that data
Into the oculus
Including the ground, including the ceiling
The various sides
And make it look seamless and also
Not cause someone to have a seizure
He's not there yet but I bet it will be Sunday
Well they had even back on PlayStation
I want to say it's PlayStation 2
They had something with Britney Spears
Where it was an interactive video
That you could change the view on it
You could actually rotate the camera around
Was that Britney's dance beat?
No it was actually a video
I think it was Britney Spears
It may have been some other group
But there was somebody
Those are filled with a special type of panoramic camera
I'm sure they could come out with something
Get two panoramic cameras
That's ten years ago at this point
What's going to be ten years from now?
I don't care what it's called, I'm not getting one
And I was
Reading emails
So whatever
Everyone else is calling
Bobby's huffy because he didn't get
Any emails about the oculus
And I'm not the one calling it anything
Oculus is the company
I know that
Don't mansplain shit to me
Do we have more emails on
Yes we got one more
On the Oculus Rift, hopefully
I don't know, I really don't care if it is
Hi guys and gal, thank you
Thank you for being
Equal opportunity in your greeting
Greetings from your other Mexican
Listener, Dr. Noir
From Quito
Is it Quito? Is that how it's pronounced?
In Ecuador
I just want to recommend a delightful platformer
Called Sortigo
I have hours on my android phone
All for the price of free
And there's a link to it at the Google store
It reminds me of classic Mega Man and Metroid
Because of the platforming and ability acquisition
With a nod to Zelda and the gameplay and currency
Gems that spawn from mowed plants
It is exactly the kind of game
I want to see more of even though I can't
For the love of all understand
For the love of all understand how they're making money
Hope you like it, adios amigos
Well sadly I am
Not an android phone user
So I can't check out this game myself
Did they pay you to send this email?
No, I'm okay with it
Because this guy's emailed us plenty of times
Before I know he's a good guy so I trust his recommendation
But I kind of laughed
Because I was like, is this a paid email?
So what was the name of the game again?
Sortigo
Sortigo, Dr. Noir approved
Yes
Oh Bobby okay I forgive you for not trying to mansplain
Alright
Is that it for the emails?
Do you know I had to actually tell somebody what mansplaining was?
Well I don't think that's what Bobby was doing at all
Well no I know that's not what Bobby was doing
I was poking back
I wasn't over
Good lord can I not tell a remote teasing
Giving someone shit when I get shit in return?
I suppose
I'm allowed to give shit
I'm human
And humans shit
Can I make another joke about Makeruini dying?
This is your house
So I can't kick you out
No I actually had to explain to somebody what mansplaining was
It was very sad
Well what if a listener doesn't know
You might as well explain it
It's when a man's trying to explain something to a woman
And talks down to her as if it's something she shouldn't know anything about
Oh I got you
So that would be like me going like
You see that is an Xbox
Behind you and that's what we use
To play video games
Sit and spin
Now would you like me to show you how to access the food network
On that?
Would you like for me to shove this so far
Up your ass
That you start tasting fingernails
And I was indicating with my middle finger
Thank you
Alright
Oh hi bones you missed some
Stuff
Raginator says
If there's mansplaining there's probably
Womansplaining too right?
Yes I would argue yes
I'm gonna tell you
There is womansplaining yes there is
You tell me what you believe womansplaining is
I'm gonna tell you what I believe it is
That's when the guy is completely
Acting uninterested in what you're saying
And you're trying to explain something
As thoroughly as possible and he's completely
Overlooking everything that you're saying
And you come off being a nag
Okay I believe that womansplaining
Is when you know you are
Hovering too much and you're being annoying
And you're around a woman so a woman
Just starts talking about her period
So that you'll go away
That's womansplaining
No that's called defense mechanism
It's called
You know what I'm really sick of hearing you talk about football
So how about I tell you about
How once a month I you know
My vagina does this
And cramps are the
Worst
Not on the show
What have they done to you?
We need the subscribers
We need more women
You know when I first looked at chat
I thought it said manscaping
And I was like well that's a whole other episode
That's after the womansplaining
Moving on to the FUs
Of the week
How appropriate it would be this time
To get to the FUs of the week
Here is justice
Here is punishment
Here is
This is fucked up
FU to the movie theater
For being so fucking loud
And this is sad
I actually do like going to 3D movies
But it's like the way that
The Winter Soldier was filmed for its 3D
Was just completely
My eyes ended up hurting and the theater was
So loud that I actually
My neck stiffened up
And I had like a killer
Headache you know before I came in
So um
It was just that and then of course
You know getting bitched at because it put me in a bad mood
And therefore I was
You know saying hey my neck hurts
Would you mind rubbing my neck?
Complaining
Fine
Soon
Yeah
Happy in the cold
And finally getting four hours of sleep
You're so quiet this week I bet your
Listers can probably barely hear you because you're just
It's taking all the energy out of you
Compared to previous weeks
I'm sorry I feel better
Hey I made the death jokes so you know
I've got the energy for that
Uh I don't know
My FU of the week goes to
Oh the fact that
Our washer and dryer
That came with the house as is
That the landlord took great
Care to mention that the washer and dryer
Would be as is
We knew kind of in the back of our mind
Oh yeah this means they're not going to last very long
Well very long ended up being
Three weeks and the dryer broke
So FU did the fact that I just dropped
$100
Plus on
A new washer and dryer
It's pretty disgusting isn't it
It costs a lot of money to keep your clothes
Smelling spring fresh
I'll tell you I'm going to pass on
A little bit of advice to everybody
That when you go to buy
A new washer and dryer or fridge
Or another appliance look at the returns
Because typically returns are for
Cosmetic damage and it's
Like for a fridge if the side of it is dented
Who's going to look at the fucking side of the fridge
It's usually shoved in an alcove or
In between something
Our washer and dryer had a big dent in it
Now our washer and dryer
Were $500 and $600 each
We got $300 knocked down off the price of each of them
Nice
I'll say it at Best Buy
But because we had damaged returns
We went there first
And I'll say it
And nobody was around to help
So we went somewhere else where we ended up dropping
A large sum of money
You know what? Write them
Give them feedback
Oh really?
I'm all for coupons
Oh we're sorry we lost your business
Thanks for letting us know
By the way
Now the FUs of the week are done
I have to read this hilarious comment from AkumaJP
Although DarkSaga's not going to like it
But I love AkumaJP's idea of woman-splaining
Did you get that?
Did you hear me? Are you listening?
That's my mother
I countered with
I don't woman-splain, I bitch
Bitch please
I give disapproving looks
Including the ADS
The absolute death stare
Which thankfully
You've never received the absolute death stare
My husband has lots though
Alright
Just a few more stories for you guys
And then we're going to open up the skype line
If you want a man-splain
Or a woman-splain
Or they-splain
Whatever you are-splain
Tell us what you're thinking
In gaming culture this week
But first, a story from Loki
Sadly
We don't have great news
But apparently the producer
Or music producer of Rhythm Heaven
He has cancer
Unfortunately
It was
Was it
Sunku I guess
Is that guy's name?
He has been diagnosed with
Laryngeal
cancer
So throat cancer
And of course
Being a singer
That's not great news either
It's like hey you have cancer
Oh hey you can't sing anymore
So hopefully
Hopefully he's able to beat that
Because that sucks
Yeah
Our thoughts go out definitely
Play some Rhythm Heaven this week
Well I mean he's still
He's just diagnosed he hasn't passed away or anything
So he's still fighting it but
Our thoughts definitely go out to him
And we'll play some Rhythm Heaven this week
Alright going over to one story
That is sad
And I know I was
Cracking some jokes about Mickey Rooney earlier
But look Mickey Rooney was in his 90's
It's very tragic to report on
Somebody who died in their 40's
And that's unfortunately what happened this week
Masuda passed away at the age of 48
Now you may not
Recognize that name but Masuda
Actually designed the game
Pro Wrestling by himself
This ties into WrestleMania tonight folks
Pro Wrestling by himself with another
Developer doing the game's graphics
This was all released for the Famicom
In 1986
Which ended up being released for the NES
You remember the old school Pro Wrestling
Like before WrestleMania and the licensed stuff
There was the original Pro Wrestling game
That was by this guy Masato Masuda
He also created the series
Fire Pro Wrestling
So yeah very sad to hear about this
But then you hear he's 48
Now do the math you guys
This Pro Wrestling
The original came out in 1986
That means when he made this game
He was like 19 or 20
And it just makes you go
Wow what was I doing at 19 or 20
Moving to California
Right or just you know
Like I wasn't doing this kind of stuff
But then you know this guy went and made
You know a real classic video game
Was making video games at least he accomplished a lot
So rest in peace
Masato Masuda
So sorry to hear about that
48 is young
Very very very young
Alright one 877
Game OLR or a username on Skype
Orange Lounge Radio is the place to call us
If you would like to participate with our show
The phone lines are open
Right now
Do we have any last minute stories while we wait
I know I've seen some tweets come in over at twitter.com
Slash OLR so I'll pull those up
But in the meantime
Loki any last minute stories?
Unfortunately no
I don't have any last minute stories
It was kind of a slower news week
That's the thing about April Fools day
It really cuts into like the actual news
Oh we do have a phone call coming in though
So we will go to it
And hello you're on Orange Lounge Radio who's this
It's your local residential convention
Hora Ranma
Hey Ranma how you doing
I'm a little tired, my feet hurt
My back hurts but other than that I'm doing good
Yeah but let me think though
Were you here for the entire show
Or were you cheating on us with some pro wrestlers
Umm
Better things to spend my money on
If I'm cheating on OLR
I'm cheating on OLR with a bunch of hot cosplayers
I mean come on
Give me some kind of credit
Alright fair enough Ranma fair enough
So what's on your mind tonight buddy
I want to talk about where in the world
Is Carmen Sandiego
F yes the classic game of the week
The dark soccer pick this week
What do you want to talk about with it
When I was in junior high after school
There was about 10 of us we actually had
The Acme Detective Agency club
Okay we would sit there
On our Apple IIe's and just
Play the game and we would just
Go through it and they would put our names
On the board and like
Who can do the most
Umm cases and rank
Up and so forth
And that was pretty fun
And it's like we're looking at
Each other trying to figure out where one person
Is where one person's at and
Back then
There was maybe
Two copies of the game
And the disc was
Copied several times but only two
Almanacs so pretty much
At the end of the school that you had to run
To the computer lab be the first one to
Grab the disc and the almanac
Rama don't copy that floppy
Psssh
No I know I think
A lot of people did back in the day that's why they had
The copy protection
Yeah but that's why also Manning
Created tape
What
Don't forget
Well for the
Disc copy protection to get around it you just cover
The red notch with a piece of tape
Oh yeah that whole thing I do remember that
Oh my god that's right or yeah
You can flip the little thing on the three and a half
Floppy or yeah you get covered with the tape
Oh my god that's old school
Definitely yeah sorry it took me
A minute to like remember that and then I just suddenly had
The image of my childhood of like get the masking tape
It's
Quite alright and then you used to have
The thing that you could actually a little hole punch that you could
Actually punch the discs to put that notch in it
It's crazy
Anyway
So any other
Copy floppy stories from your childhood
You want to share with us?
That's the only one and by the way
For thinking
For the fact you thought these celebrities were already dead Rob
That was bad and you should feel bad
It was funny as hell
And you know it
Yeah I know especially what Loki said I was like
I was ready to walk out of my house
Right there
That was just terrible
I'm going to go under where Loki sits just for next time
He needs to drop the mic and walk away
Are you going to use that Mario pillow?
I might
That's a good use for it
I use that pillow for my back a lot actually
So Rob's butt is closer to it
That's right Mario can smell my butt
Are you pretty much telling Mario to kiss your ass?
I guess so
Because
I'm a Luigi fan Rama
I'm a Luigi fan
And you know my favorite
My favorite is black Luigi
By the way
Ronchon
You know I'm going to be back in the cosplay circuit
Come July
Are you doing Ugyo?
No
You're going to be so sad
So very very sad
Sailor Venus?
No
I'm doing two homestuck cosplays
I've learned to
Love and tolerate the homestuck fandom
As Marco said in My Little Pony
I will learn to love and tolerate
Respect and understanding
The gaming community needs more of it
I have given My Little Pony a chance
And I found some of it amusing
That's good
Even though Applejack's accent is horrible
But I have developed
A love of Rainbow Dash
Because
20% cooler
Yes
And don't forget
They had the figures at McDonald's this week
I'm not that into it
No thank you
Alright
Well Rama I'm going to let you go
So we can get some more calls
But listen to Anime Jam Session or You Suck
Right?
We'll be talking about Castle Point this week
A convention we hit up today
And after that we're getting ready for PAX East
Oh boy, big weekend coming up
You're telling me
I'm just glad I got the time off for it
Have fun at PAX East
Bye my friend
1877 Game OLR
Or a username on Skype
Orange Lounge Radio if you would like to give the show a call
The phone lines are once again open
Again that's 1877 Game OLR
Or a username on Skype
Orange Lounge Radio
I'm trying to go to the Twitters
To see what's going on here on Twitter
Tigerclaw sending us a tweet
The Wreck-It Ralph sequel is officially in the works
According to the composer
We haven't had any official confirmation
But Wreck-It Ralph of course the Disney movie
From last year that was great with all its throwbacks
To classic gaming
Very happy to hear about the sequel
I just hope it's not direct to video
That would be very sad
But yeah I'm excited to hear about it
I hope we get maybe a new Wreck-It Ralph game
That isn't exclusive to the Nintendo
Platforms
I'd like to see it out there in more places
Hi you're on Orange Lounge Radio who's this?
It's Shane
How are you doing?
I'm good
Hi Shane
Wow you're making the rounds on every podcast that I co-host this week
Right? I have no life
You even guessed it on Reading is Fundamental
And now you're here what's up?
I just want to do my
Due diligence as a
DJ Max fan and put out the PSA
That on the iOS
Platform we now have
The Technica game finally
In America
And it's expensive
So don't buy it
Wait a minute so you're doing your due diligence to tell us
That it's out there but then you're saying don't buy it
Yes
Why not?
Because you get the base game for free
And it comes with like six songs
I think seven maybe
And a couple of them
Are pretty decent songs
And then you have to buy
The rest of them you can earn
The credit stuff
To buy the songs by playing the games
But you don't really earn a whole lot
Each song is like 20 of these credits
So they want you to pay real money
If you want every single
Song that they have there
And they're sold in packs
You can also buy them individually but that's not as good
You have to pay 96 bucks
For a phone game
But does it have flea?
It does not
Fuck it then
It has one of the exclusives from the
What's it called?
DJ Max Ray on the iPhone
And it's not bad
But they are really asking
For a lot of money for songs
That don't translate as well to
The iPhone and probably iPad
As they do like in the arcade
But there will be some people that buy it
Right Shane?
Yep there will be
Not me though I did not buy any
Wow
So I don't have the money for it
Or else I'll buy it
But yeah
Everybody has to know
So they can download it and get the free version
And then eventually
If you are drunk
Or just
Dumb
You buy the other songs
Well if you have some more disposable income
Out there and you want to drop the money on this
And some of the songs
Let us know how it is
There are some good songs
I earned enough to buy
One of my own songs
Without paying money
And
I don't know
It has a two line mode and a three line mode
And it's okay
I bet this is much better on an iPad
Than a little dinky iPhone
But you know
If you need a DJ Max fix
Go play portable on PSP
And not this
Any other game reviews
You want to share with us tonight?
I have already professed my love for Infamous
Because it's amazing
Did you hear that Loki?
Loki said he wasn't sure on
Infamous Second Sign
No I said that was the only one that looked interesting
It is really interesting
It's got a decent story
I don't think the other ones supposedly have that great of stories
I really got invested
Into this one
And I've been playing a lot of Final Fantasy 14
Because of Leviathan
And his mid 90's alternative
Rock song
It's the best
Playing that fight over and over
Jamie if you get that far don't play it
You might get motion sick
It does a lot of bobbing up and down
I'll probably wait for you guys to do it anyway
You fight Leviathan on a barge
And during the fight
Leviathan will fly up in the air
And land on the barge
Which causes the barge to tilt
And you all fly down the barge
Whatever way
It's really fun
Actually it's a rad mechanic
I'll just wait until I have you guys to do it with me
There you go
You can pretty much sleep through it once you get there
It's really not hard whatsoever
If you can get past Titan hard mode
Then shit anything is easy after that
The only reason I got past Titan at all
Was because of you guys while I slept in the fire
That was just regular mode
Wait until you see hard mode
It'll make you cry
You have no idea how angry I was that night
I was angry enough that I was in tears
And I got up and left my computer
I was that angry
Remember when I said
Fuck it, just finish it
After that I got up and left
No video games worth getting that
I was already in a really bad mood
I did that
I was already in a really bad mood that night
But just having all that happen
After I had put off doing
The fight for three games until there were people
To do it with me
I was just so frustrated
I'm going to warn you
It gets worse
The hard mode is extremely unforgiving
I would love to try it again
If I can
But I was so mad
Sure
Well Shane I'm going to let you go
See if we get any other callers
Thanks for the call
I'm going to play more Leviathan
Leviathan
That's not even the good part
Bye
This is a tweet from SSJ100Matt
Sometimes you guys want to bring stories
That might have slipped off of our radar
You want to bring that to our attention
Let's see
Washington State University researchers
Programmed a computer to teach another how to play
Ms. Pac-Man
Let's see
Right now robots are quote very dumb
Saying Matthew E. Taylor at WSU
Who is a professor of artificial intelligence
And so as robots become
More common it will be easier if they're capable
Of learning how to perform tasks from
Other robots
We don't want this information to be lost
Once your home robot knows how you like your bath
How you like your house cleaned
You don't want to lose that information
So huh that's interesting
And there's a whole little YouTube that goes with it
I'm not going to play it right now
But that's really neat
So they use Ms. Pac-Man as a way
Now can you teach me how to play?
Because I get killed in that game really easy
Alright
Akuma JP in our chatroom
At live.vognetware.com talking about
Final Fantasy 14 saying
The reason I left Final Fantasy 14 is because I got
Kicked from the server while in a fight with
Odin
That Odin fight will kill servers
Like there's so many people that show up for those fights
It kind of can't handle it
Which is not okay
They need to fix that somehow
So no MMO
Is perfect and that's where Square Enix is struggling
Is with some of those server issues
And they encourage every single player
On the damn server to show up in one zone
All at the same time
So I will put out one more call
For phone calls at 1877 game OLR
Or username on Skype orange lounge radio
I'm trying to look back
Sometimes I miss tweets that were sent early in the week
If I don't scroll back
So I'm going to do that right now
But unfortunately
There's no last minute stories to help
Give me time here
And stuff is
Let's see code man had sent us that same story
About the five year old and the security flaw
With Xbox one
But you know that story is like making the rounds
It's everywhere because I'm sure the associated press
Picked it up and it's a hilarious story to put
On the front of
Your local newspaper and things like that
Five year old that hacks Xbox
Oh Pete Caruno had sent some tweets
At the beginning of the week when he was listening to the show
Saying I believe it's illegal to
Rent games in Japan
That's why there's a thriving second hand market
To replace it
Renting CDs is legal
We were talking about that a little bit on the show last week
I think we were talking about red box and all that stuff
And Pete Caruno said
I successfully used the money in my Xbox account
To buy DJ Hero DLC yesterday
Even managing to partly pay with points
And credit card
Well you're doing better
Did you do that though through the website?
He didn't say
It was a tweet
Through the website
No
I do need to figure out
What I'm going to spend the rest of that on
I was hoping the DLC for Grand Theft Auto 5
Would come out but nope
Not yet
Alright
That's it I guess we're going to close up the Skype line
No other calls are coming in
Alas
And AkumaJP by the way is verifying
Yes it's illegal to rent games
They tried to do that here
It happened Nintendo was not a fan of that
But no this is Murica
So anyway
If you want to participate with the show
If you were too busy with WrestleMania or Game of Thrones
Or what else was tonight something else tonight
Too busy
Simpsons with a Minecraft intro
Who cares
If you were too busy with any of that stuff you can always email us
Participate at orangelaunchradio.com
Or you can send us a tweet twitter.com
Slash O L R
But with that we are going to wrap up the show here tonight
I want to thank you guys for listening and tuning into the show
Thank you as always for your support
If you liked what you heard here at Orange Lawn Tradio
Don't forget to tell a friend or two about the show
We don't ask for your money
Although I will say just a heads up you guys
We are going to be looking at ways here in the coming
Weeks and months and so forth
And these are things you guys have been asking for
Can I get a shirt
Can I get Orange Lawn Tradio merchandise
Will you sign something and send it to us
We are looking at ways to do that
But again totally optional
Stuff that will be out there if you want to get it
And support the show that is fucking awesome
And you rule for it but you know we are not going to be like
We are not going to record our show
For a month if you don't do it
I am still planning on doing VOG the book
Which I do need to speak with some of our people
That would be very hilarious
Kickstart the most expensive episode of Orange Lawn Tradio ever
To one episode
And then we donate the money to charity
Namely the Jamie needs art supplies
And candy
Actually the donate to charity is against the rules
So you can't do that
Can you do it on InigoGo
At any rate
Bobby also makes a point that Cosmos
Was on
And Cosmos is fucking amazing
Well there you go
Well that's going to do it
Thank you guys so much for listening to the show
Let's go around and get everybody's final thought tonight
I'll start
Because you know Loki when you bring Carl's Jr.
To the studio you make me crave Chris cut fries
You're a jerk
And I didn't even get the Chris cut fries
I ate their natural cut fries
You know what Rob we could get pinkberry
I gotta go get Allen
I was going to have pinkberry today
But my son had to fucking have an accident
After he was sitting there
Bouncing up down like you have to go to the bathroom
Let's go to the bathroom, no I don't have to go to the bathroom
Two seconds later
Oh I have to go to the bathroom
Get him in the, okay let's go to the pinkberry
Get him in the car, hey wait a second
Pants are wet
Thanks
Womp womp
Dark soccer your final thought tonight
I'm glad I only have to deal with my cat
And last but not least
Loki your final thought tonight
I hope I can get some more programming done this week
My brain has been mushed the last few days
That's what I get for staying up
Well feel better dammit
It's actually, I can only code with Red Bull
I have to drink lots of Red Bull
And then that actually works out
The problem is though I'm getting to the point though
Where it's like okay what do I work on next
What part do I work on next
It's just deciding what the best thing to work on
I don't know
I'm trying to like set myself goals and stuff
But it's just like a lot of stuff
That I need to work on
You know I gotta do everything
Alright
That's it, thank you guys so much for downloading the show
And checking us out, we appreciate it
Have a wonderful week, be safe
Don't be jerks to each other online
Keep gaming positive, have a wonderful week
We'll see you next week here
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio
Orange Lounge Radio
Is a production of OLR Studios
To join us for a live show
Tune into fognetwork.com
Sunday nights
At 6 PM Pacific
9 PM Eastern
The views and opinions expressed in this program
Do not necessarily reflect
Those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio
Or VOG Network
But you know they were all still true
See you next week
Thanks for watching!