[SPEAKER_19]: Far too easily Save your tears, cause I won't come back I could hear that you whispered as you walked through that door But still I swore to hide the pain when I turned back the pages Shouting might have been the answer
[SPEAKER_19]: What if I cried my eyes out and begged you not to pause?
[SPEAKER_19]: But now I'm not afraid to say what's in my heart So a thousand words have never been spoken So fly to you, I'll be over the top
[SPEAKER_19]: and a thousand words, one thousand confessions.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll create a field, making all the birds
[SPEAKER_19]: Dream isn't over yet, though I often say I can't forget I still relive that day, you've been there with me all the way
[SPEAKER_19]: But still I swore to hide the doubt when I turned back the pages Anger might have been the answer What if I'd hung my head and said that I couldn't wait But now I'm strong
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, a thousand words, a thousand embraces Will create a view, become all of your very days before
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format
Oh, God.
Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_15]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_15]: This is episode number 137.
[SPEAKER_08]: For this, March the 27th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it's Easter Sunday today.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are still live, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'd think we'd have somewhere better to be, like church or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no, we're here to provide you with three hours of entertainment on this lovely evening.
[SPEAKER_08]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_08]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_08]: Joining me, as always, my awesome, awesome co-host.
[SPEAKER_08]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm.
[SPEAKER_08]: Say hello to Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know her better as Stark.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, this is actually supposed to be a pagan fertility holiday, but oh well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blame those people in Italy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, DarkSakura, by the way, she's kind of the mother of the program.
[SPEAKER_08]: She'll just tell it to you like it is, honestly.
[SPEAKER_08]: But she does it because she loves you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't let the attitude fool you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't say the M word.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some friends of mine and Dan brought their baby to our brunch.
I...
[SPEAKER_02]: I need a hysterectomy
[SPEAKER_08]: You know I've got to ask what you're building, but we'll talk about it when we come back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you going to do it on the cam, though?
[SPEAKER_08]: Can they do it on the cam right now?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, right now I'm trying to make the mess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, another one of those.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I've been looking for this one piece.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's piece hunting right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have ten gallons of Legos, and honestly, finding four pieces in ten gallons is like a needle in a haystack.
[SPEAKER_07]: I found three of the four needles, so I just need to find the last one.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you find the marble and the oatmeal?
[SPEAKER_08]: Say hello as well to our regular guest.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I can't say special guest because, I mean, damn, she's been here for like the past eight weeks, Nirvana.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's a regular guest now.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_08]: How you doing, Angel?
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's wet outside.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it's raining here in lovely Sacramento where we based this show, but as Jamie said to me last week, you call that a storm?
[SPEAKER_08]: Weather wimp?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, you know, all I said was it was raining outside.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't say it was horrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just wet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is wet, but anyway...
[SPEAKER_08]: We're high and dry in here and we've got plenty of stuff to talk about tonight We've got some general video gaming news, of course your favorite segments, how was your week, how was your day We're doing a giveaway tonight, we're going to give away some stuff to a lucky listener So you're definitely going to want to be in on this and you can win a prize And that prize is not a 10 gallon of Legos No, it's not 10 gallons of Legos, it's something people might actually want And we're having another guest who's currently on his way with something neat Pie?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, dammit
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't eat this, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, your fiancé is on his way, yes?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, with a something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm excited about this.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll have to talk about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's his new appendage, damn it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Except this is not for giving away.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell no!
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that the door?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm... Oh, it's probably the Legos screwing with me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll get to it right after a quick break.
[SPEAKER_08]: Featuring some music this first break from 2DX Nightstyle.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brand new game.
[SPEAKER_08]: We talked about it a little bit last week, but I think a lot more people are starting to actually get into it and play it this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to celebrate a little bit by playing some music from Nightstyle.
[SPEAKER_08]: We will tonight during the show, not this break, but a little later on, play the brand new consumer tracks.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to premiere those here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I understand we may have some new listeners tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: So hello to you new listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we'll tell you why that's happening, why we're expecting an increase in visibility, if you haven't already heard.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very strange news.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's exciting, but it's strange.
[SPEAKER_08]: Strange things are afoot at Circle K. Yeah, strange things are afoot at Circle K slash OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll talk about that when we come back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sad if we have to broadcast from the Circle K. We should broadcast from the Circle K. I'm going to see you live from Circle K, and I'm not even supposed to be here today.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to start it off with some Ram with Act.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, join our chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: www.orangeloungeradio.com Click on chat.
I'm saying your birthday, I'm saying you won't run away I'm saying you'll be the one saying it to you
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge Radio is proud to present a celebrity interview.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you introduce yourself for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm Miss Cleo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it's great to have you on the show today.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello, how are you today?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm great, thanks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you have a question?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, yes, actually I wanted to know... Can I please have your first name only and your birth date, please?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, well, no, I actually just wanted to know what you thought of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, what do you think of Loki, one of the three hosts of Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is he incarcerated?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, actually, no, he's not.
[SPEAKER_08]: But what do you think of the ever-ranty DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, dear, how are you?
[SPEAKER_11]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see you two must know each other.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, what do you think of Sky?
[SPEAKER_11]: Did he used to play football when he was in high school?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, actually, no, he didn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, what do you think of Intern Zero?
[SPEAKER_11]: I want you to really remember the pill, all right?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm seeing some forgetting, possibly.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm seeing a new baby in the next three months.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, well, thanks for being on Orange Lounge Radio today.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, I don't mean to sidetrack your question here, but who are all of these nosy people?
[SPEAKER_11]: Outside influences I'm seeing around you by the moon card.
[SPEAKER_16]: Get away from me.
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge Radio, helping to free your mind and spirit.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm Miss Cleo.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio live on this Easter Sunday, March 27, 2005.
[SPEAKER_08]: Happy Easter to those of you guys out there who celebrate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: To those of you that don't, happy Sunday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hope you got candy anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're here doing our thing here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello to anybody who might be new to our program.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: So we went to the ceremony, and we lost.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a station that played porn music all day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it was a porn station.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's certainly something you wouldn't hear on AM FM radio all day, so it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there was them.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this year, we got nominated for that award again, thanks to our listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: We also got nominated.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know how this happened, but we got nominated Broadcaster of the Year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Us, Orange Lawn Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we have our personal ninja to thank for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, this little dorky station dedicated to video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Half the people on Live365 probably don't even... No, three quarters of the people on Live365 probably don't even know what DDR or Bomani is.
[SPEAKER_02]: D.D.R.
[SPEAKER_02]: is a type of Ram.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're definitely going to the awards ceremony again.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you guys want to attend, we're going to post the information on their website.
[SPEAKER_08]: There were not a whole lot of fans last year of stations.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I think if we were not only to go ourselves, but to get other people, like a whole little entourage to be coming to the awards ceremony too, that would kick butt.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can come to the awards ceremony and you can watch Dark Sakura and I drink like we did last year.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to just start doing vodka shots.
[SPEAKER_02]: That way I'll be able to stay coherent longer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so actually we had a good time at the award show last year, so I'm looking forward to doing it again.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're certainly not expecting anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're nominated against some pretty powerhouse stations in Broadcaster of the Year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just some really good stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some well-respected folks in the community.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think there's a really popular rock station and a couple regular radio stations that went to the internet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think there's an oldie station as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: All really great stations.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're just like shocked that we're even in that category.
[SPEAKER_08]: To take this station about video games and put it amongst these other four really, really great stations.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just like, damn.
[SPEAKER_02]: We win at the internet.
[SPEAKER_08]: We totally just won at the internet this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're very excited.
[SPEAKER_08]: So thank you guys so much for your help.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, if you want to vote for us, hey, we would love it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a link below.
[SPEAKER_08]: On our website, www.orangeontario.com, there's a link there where you can go and you can vote not only for the Broadcaster of the Year, but also most likely not to hear on AMFM Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think we're up against the Pokemon Radio and, I don't know, there was a bunch of others.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Pokemon one sticks out in my mind because I've played Pokemon and I have Pikachu dolls up here, so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, that's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, hello to those of you guys who are new to this station.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hope you enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is the live three-hour show we do every Sunday night where we talk about not just music, video games, but really over the past two and a half years we've been doing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just mutated into a show where we're just kind of sitting around, a bunch of geeks that are into video games, just talking about what's up.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we always start off the show by doing a little segment called, How was your week?
[SPEAKER_08]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_08]: Where we answer that question.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_08]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_08]: So we'll start off with the lovely Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: My week, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well...
[SPEAKER_02]: There wasn't really too much going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did a lot of exercise because I'm training for the Mud Run.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm working out with Iguana Girl four to five times a week now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, what is the Mud Run, for those who don't know?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Mud Run, and I'll see if I can't post something in the chat room, like a map of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a military obstacle course set up by the Marines every year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the Marines do a five-mile obstacle course first, and then it's open to civilians.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've opened up a two-mile course.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does the winner of this mud run, do they win immunity?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, you do get a trophy, and it's a... You know how they do the bronze baby shoes?
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a gold boot.
[SPEAKER_07]: No bags of rice or fire for this one.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, and a phone call home, or a chance to go out on the boat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good luck with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take pictures.
[SPEAKER_08]: We want to see, like, because we need to get bio pictures for the website, so we want to see a picture of you after this thing is over, just looking like hell.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll give you a picture of bio.
[SPEAKER_13]: You guys have to come.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys have to come watch.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll watch.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, this is the ironic thing that DarkSakura, you know, she may sound like, you know, she's nice and sweet and all that, but damn, she's the toughest one here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm a big chicken.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could never do that mud run, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have chocolate.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, I'm cheating like hell today because we went to Marie Callender's for their brunch like we do with a group of friends of mine every year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except there's some stupid drama going on now, so one person and then several more people didn't come because one other person was going to be there.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then some friends of ours brought their baby, which convinced me never to, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll have chocolate.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thursday, Dan brought home his new appendage.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which is?
[SPEAKER_02]: The PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want a PSP so bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate being poor.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I was really down on the PSP for a while, but now I'm really into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's got that nice wide screen on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The games look so much better...
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, you're carrying around a PS2, whereas with the DS, you're carrying around an N64.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I really think that Sony took advantage of... Well, actually, I've heard that the PSP is about equivalent of Dreamcast power, as far as 3D is concerned.
[SPEAKER_02]: You haven't played Ridge Racer then.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the games, whatever the hardware is it runs on, the games look pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did check this out because I was over at your house on Thursday as well and I was checking it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were playing Ridge Racer and dang, that game was pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, it was so much better looking than I remember the PSP from E3 last year.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that was pretty cool to see.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was, it was, oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am very pleased with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Darkstalkers.
[SPEAKER_02]: My one complaint is that
[SPEAKER_02]: It hurts my left hand when I play.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was on DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: The analog button is so awesome on that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you happen to notice that on the bottom left there was just this little circle?
[SPEAKER_08]: I totally... I was too entranced looking at the visuals on the screen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had no time to look at the actual system.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was looking at it going, what's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: And Dan's like, it's your analog stick.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really easy to look over it.
[SPEAKER_02]: At any rate, we've been...
[SPEAKER_02]: We have five games for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Wipeout Pure.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Metal Gear Solid Acid, which is a strategy game, so I'm like, eh, on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ridge Racer, that puzzle game, what was it called?
[SPEAKER_02]: Lumines?
[SPEAKER_08]: I want that Lumines game.
[SPEAKER_08]: How is that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you play that at all?
[SPEAKER_08]: I've heard Lumines.
[SPEAKER_08]: Something that, like, if you're into the music video games, you know, because it's by the guy who did, what, Rez and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you like music video games, I hear Lumines is just the poo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'll give it a try this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, um, I really, though, me, I'm a fighting game nut.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had to play DarkSakura, so it was really awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the sound is really good on that thing, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't sound all tinny, like some things do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I should hope so, with Sony putting it out and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, um, we also, though, found a webpage.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can't hear you, hon.
[SPEAKER_02]: We also found something on a webpage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Dan found this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wipeout Pure
[SPEAKER_08]: Now I've heard that actually one big popular thing going on on the PSP right now is loading pornography on the memory sticks.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can have video with you to go, and of course people go straight for porn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, um, they actually, we actually were looking for a one gigabyte memory stick, but they didn't have them anywhere where we went.
[SPEAKER_02]: GameStop is supposed to be carrying them soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want, if I were to get that, the first thing I'd load on, it would not be porn, it'd be robot chicken.
[SPEAKER_02]: We put some video game trailers and stuff on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Dan, of course, had to have some songs on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like the two songs he really likes in 2DX, which is the one from Gradius 2, Burning Heat, and Twimmy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I played a whole crap load of Silent Hill 3 yesterday.
[SPEAKER_07]: So probably next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I cheated so bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then we went to the brunch today and I got my graphics tablet yesterday too I have a Wacom Intuos I think it's gorgeous and it's so lightweight and it's like the perfect thing so I can sit back you know sort of half in my lap and half hanging on my keyboard desk and I can just draw it's awesome so I'm trying to practice how to ink a little bit and then
[SPEAKER_02]: I sort of feel like I've been hiding out under a rock for the past three years, but I have finally discovered the universe of Gorillaz fandom.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I've gone completely bonkers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you talking about Gorillaz and the Mist, or what?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, like the band.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else you want to share about your week?
[SPEAKER_08]: I had pizza.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Eat that pizza.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_08]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_07]: My week is okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, first, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: First off, I hate to cut you off, but first off, tell us what the hell you're building over there with the Legos, which, by the way, you can see on camera right now, www.warnsonsradio.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I haven't built anything yet because I was trying to find this goddamn piece, and I cannot find it for the life of me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have, like, eight of them, and I only found three, and I need four.
[SPEAKER_07]: But because I'm smart, I'll make it work.
[SPEAKER_07]: So now what I'm building is, and you can find the link to this on our website because I posted it there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a Nintendo DS charging dock.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it holds games and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's a link to the instructions on our website.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: www.orangeloungerated.com
[SPEAKER_07]: And this was posted on a bunch of different websites they had, this guy made it, and it's pretty nifty.
[SPEAKER_08]: So wait, is it like with the iPod, how you have those little chargers?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's supposed to emulate that, but for a DS?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, the charging cord or whatever, it just sits there and you set the DS right on top of it, and away you go, and it has spots for games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I thought, because I saw the charger over there sitting there, I was like, you know, that'd be pretty cool to put one over there and just set a DS on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, that's what I'm building right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, this hat's hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Game Sales Position Game Sales Position
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been playing a lot of God of War and some of this, I mentioned it last week, the Dog's Life where you can eat poop and throw it and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's lovely.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all dogs do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I also got Gran Turismo 4, which I just remembered after I purchased Gran Turismo 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't play much of Gran Turismo 1 when I bought it, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't played much of Gran Turismo 4 when I bought it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a remedy for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me bring over the Logitech wheel.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I also got TimeSplitters 3 because I have all three TimeSplitters games now.
[SPEAKER_07]: You gotta love a game where you can actually drive a cat.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I love TimeSplitters.
[SPEAKER_07]: 150 unlockable characters.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, I love that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just so much fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think people don't really look at it as...
[SPEAKER_07]: A very good... I mean, it's like a shooter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everyone's always looking at Halo.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the best thing about this, it's actually an online game for the PS2.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I've got to try the online mode with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'd be interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's what I've been doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty much, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and lots of Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Leveled my Black Mage to 56.
[SPEAKER_09]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: My week and my day, let's see, not a whole lot because we're looking for the new Orange Lounge studio right now or at least the one that's going to hold us over the next phase of Orange Lounge because as you know, Loki and I live together and that's where we do this show right now is out of this house.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, we're moving out at the end of April.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: because I thought, hey, it's a nerd party, so I'm going to take my DS and we'll be able to do some wireless.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was the only person there that brought a DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then they were making fun of my carrying case, which is, yes, the same one you bought me, DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were making fun of the carrying case because they said it looked like a makeup case.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I was, you know, just messing around and I would open up the case, like pretend it was a makeup case, and I'd take out the stylus and pretend to be painting my eyelashes with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I don't know, I guess it's something you have to see, which doesn't work on radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the highlight of the week was watching America's Top Model.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, the highlight of my week was for the first time, I can't believe I've been missing this gem of a show on UPN, America's Next Top Model.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just a bunch of bitches fighting with each other.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you've got to love a show that next week has flesh-eating viruses in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got to love that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously, I know there's a lot of hatred for reality TV out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: But damn, is it entertaining.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's certainly more entertaining than turning on the news and hearing about that woman in Florida for the gazillionth time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm so over her.
[SPEAKER_07]: I forgot to mention earlier, I got some new movies, and I think I mentioned it to Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: We watched this one called Red Silk or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: and it was the weirdest movie I've ever seen where these women were naked like the entire time and they were old and nasty looking and there was just like some weird dream sequences with like a kaleidoscope and stuff and it made no sense and you couldn't understand them and in fact I actually had to read the back of the box to figure out what the plot was because I couldn't figure it out from just watching it and then it's just really strange but then I also got this movie called and this is like typical fashion for me um
[SPEAKER_07]: Inbred Redneck Alien Abduction Bloodsucking Vampire Rednecks That's nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love bad movies.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can I talk about my week again now?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, let's, so I went to the party, so nobody really had, um, a DS, so we were playing Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: Melee, which is always a good time, and I'm so upset that they have not made a sequel to that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, how can they have not made a sequel to Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: yet?
[SPEAKER_08]: I played that just the other day.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm, I, why don't they have something yet on DS yet?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, I forgot, the DS doesn't have any games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, oh well.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we played that, we played a little bit of Mario Party, which also needs to come out on the DS, although I guess they have a GBA version?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm so lost on the handheld loop right now because I'm all bitter because I can't have a PSP yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that was pretty much my week of my day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing else that exciting going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR Angel, how about you?
[SPEAKER_08]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: I played Bomani this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's a DDR and in the groove.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can see.
[SPEAKER_09]: What did you think of in the groove?
[SPEAKER_04]: We already talked about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, small arrows.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I noticed that, uh... How do I even say that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it starts off small and then it pans out kind of a thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I'm talking about?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, the way the arrows scroll?
[SPEAKER_08]: The weird scrolling thing it does?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just call it the weird in-the-groove scrolling thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That makes no sense, and I'm like, damn.
[SPEAKER_04]: You only see that, though, if you're, like, really paying attention to the arrows.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of funky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also... Let's see, what else did I do this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I got to play a different GameCube game this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Star Fox Assault.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Star Fox-y.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, well...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, not too much else.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to find my Chains of Promethea discs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn it!
[SPEAKER_04]: They've sprung legs and walked away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it's telling me not to install it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I can't find them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Eh, I'll fix it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll find some way to play again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I need to.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't forget, you guys, you can join our chatroom, www.orangelinger.com, click on chat, and we're going to have the Skype line open up a little bit later so you guys can call in and interact with us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just head on over to www.orangelinger.com, click on interact with us for all the details.
[SPEAKER_08]: And as I hinted at the beginning of the program...
[SPEAKER_08]: We're actually going to be doing a giveaway a little later on this evening, so you have to be either in chat or able to call us on the Skype line, because we're going to be doing a giveaway with Match Game later on tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to have somebody on the Skype line versus somebody in the chat room, and they're going to be battling it out for a Resident Evil 4...
[SPEAKER_08]: CD Sampler of Music, and the ESPN NBA 2005 soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, I know we usually don't talk about sports games a whole lot on this show, but the way we see it, hey, it's free music.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, what the heck.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, we're going to give those away, and then we'll throw in a little something extra as well from us, the Orange Lounge Radio hosts as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, get ready for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't send in anything in chat room or on Skype line just yet, because we'll be getting to that a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll let you know when.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway,
[SPEAKER_08]: Meanwhile, of course, as you know, we do this show based out of Northern California.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we try to keep tabs on what's going on in the NorCal DDR scene.
[SPEAKER_08]: We always like hearing from you guys what's going on in your neck of the woods via the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, we did have a large tournament that took place yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the March Madness tournament.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I feel kind of bad because this is the very first year, I think, where I have not gone to March Madness, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just had some other stuff going on that day.
[SPEAKER_08]: But March Madness was going on
[SPEAKER_08]: Freestyle was won by Thinner Mr. Wendell
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I haven't seen where the Perfect Attack scores are, but I'm trying to dig through the thread right here, trying to figure out what's going on, looking at the wrap-up over on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_08]: The winner was Billy Jr., it looks like, for Perfect Attack, with second place, Chaos.
[SPEAKER_08]: The last round, Max Shuffle.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this is the interesting part.
[SPEAKER_08]: Only 24 people entered Perfect Attack this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which is kind of... Yeah, it's kind of a little bit down from where it was previously.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I really feel bad that I wasn't able to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just had other stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: But is this a sign that the DDR tournaments are running out of steam?
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, Jamie, you've won a lot of DDR tournaments.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think it's starting to run out of steam or what's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't... I mean, I'm kind of sad that I missed out on going to this one, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Dance Gaming Community as it is, so I think a lot of folks, you know, if they're not in the groove, they're not going to check out one of these tournaments.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I don't know, it's just kind of too bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope it's not a sign that DDR is dying in the arcades, but at the same time, without new DDR, the heck are we supposed to do?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: People are coming up with clever ideas, though, to keep it fresh, so, you know, hats off to them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, any thoughts on the tournament?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, I haven't been in a tournament in a long time, it's just not my thing, I don't know I think a lot of people are just, I don't know, just tournaments Maybe because the crowd that's getting into it now is more new at it or something And that's why they feel maybe a little intimidated to go up against these people
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe that's my guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or the fact that these people that are coming in are getting introduced to it on the home console.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe they're just not really getting into it with the environment, like the crowd and stuff, as they would if they started off in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's my guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I think it's just kind of too bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that it's just not the huge thing it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you're right, maybe a lot of that is because people are starting on the home mixes now.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm surprised that I don't see more, if that's the case, more of these tournaments that are conducted on home mixes.
[SPEAKER_08]: But maybe that's because of the fact that...
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe that's because of the fact that it's kind of harder to run a fair tournament on home mixes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, what do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think it's possible to run a fair tournament on home mixes with home pads and stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely, we did it at Shaft.
[SPEAKER_02]: When we had to do a quick fix, we pulled out modded pads and he won second place.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, the fiancé of DarkSakura has just joined us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dan the Man is back.
[SPEAKER_08]: You may remember him from a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was here telling you guys to go buy ignition pads at his local GameStop.
[SPEAKER_08]: My second legendary appearance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So did it work?
[SPEAKER_00]: Did anybody buy any?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_00]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nobody buys the ignition pads.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's too bad to hear.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think we sold one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, that was from us.
[SPEAKER_00]: So to replace it, they sent me two cheap GameStop brand knockoff ignition pads.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, hooray.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck y'all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, now you brought a treat to show us here in studio tonight, correct?
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_00]: My pants.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_08]: No, really, what did you bring?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that a PSP?
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got to put that on cam.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we'll be showing that on cam during the break so you guys can see how pretty it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's try to get some of the music on it if we can get the speakers to pick it up.
[SPEAKER_08]: We might be able to do something where we can hook it into the mixing board.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got USB connection on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, right on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: So we'll be back after this next break.
[SPEAKER_08]: In this next break, we're actually going to play some music from 2DX Night Style.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this is brand new music from the home version.
[SPEAKER_08]: We call these consumer tracks.
[SPEAKER_08]: So when they are songs specifically made for the home release of the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to hear some brand new 2DX Night Style songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to start it off with a brand new LED song.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's called Photogenic.
[SPEAKER_08]: So enjoy this and three other songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we'll be back after this.
DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_19]: So I come into the world to be someone Taking you to the place with you
and many more.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: Come join our party, see how we play
[SPEAKER_19]: Hatsune Miku Hatsune Miku Hatsune Miku
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: And now, let's listen in to an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting as they debate some of the new programming coming to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie, I have a suggestion about some of the music in our Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can we talk about that?
[SPEAKER_19]: No subject will ever be taboo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I was thinking maybe we should move Pump Up the Volume from Tuesday Nights.
[SPEAKER_08]: Except, of course, a subject that was just under discussion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, what would you think if maybe we cut back on some of the tack music we play on the station?
[SPEAKER_19]: I collect your fucking head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just like this fucker here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, why did you do that to Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: The holic thing on episode 69 was just a joke!
[SPEAKER_14]: Now if any of you sons of bitches got anything else to say, now's the fucking time!
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge Radio, where everybody has a say.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hope you enjoyed that break.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some brand new music we're playing on Orange Lounge Radio for the first time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some tracks from 2DX Night Style, the consumer version.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had a night break.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had some LED with Photogenic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ota 2 with Usual Days, a remix there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gupperslope with 80's Capsule and the brand new Jaeger remix which I guess is to complete some type of trilogy or something going on there so I don't know how I feel about that new Jaeger remix though because it sounds to me like it's the hamster dance they need the Jaeger Meister mix now now that would be awesome but the video is kind of cool so what can you do about that all the strong Jaeger ones are pretty cool alright alright
[SPEAKER_08]: So what we're going to do now is we actually are going to take...
[SPEAKER_08]: I call that my influence.
[SPEAKER_02]: As the resident female.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I know, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can change anything I want.
[SPEAKER_08]: As the resident moody female, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moody?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just, love ya.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what we're going to do, actually, is we also had, just recently come out within this past week, we had Service Pack... I'm sorry, I keep calling these things Service Pack.
[SPEAKER_08]: Song Pack 9 just came out for DDR Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what we're going to do is we're actually going to have Loki play some of these songs on air, and he's going to give us his feedback to the steps to these songs live as he dances to them.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is our excuse because they think I'm too fat, and so they said, you've got to work, you've got to exercise.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki has to dance because he is the pudgiest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not fair.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the bacon.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's basically what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what we're going to do... We weren't able to set this up to do on Xbox Live, huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because we have our... Well... You want to set it up on Xbox?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't take too long to get an opponent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's bring in the ultimate two sounds.
[SPEAKER_08]: you gotta find a song from Song Pack 9 alright alright but don't you dare play Forever Sunshine cause I hate that crap gotcha pick a skill level now you can see I don't want any ass shots here and the background live on cam www.orangeloungeradio.com alright ok that's fine go to the left it'll be faster you know alright let's see here
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, Regret, Ogia, there's Jelly Kiss.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, you're going back into Song Pack 7 and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go over to... Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, for a five-footer, I mean, there's not much to expect of this one.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's five on heavy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of hard for a five-footer.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's got, like, offbeat notes and everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look at us.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of like fast stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: This seems kind of hard for a five to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would be different like a six.
[SPEAKER_02]: If our listeners are watching the webcam on OrangeRomeRadio.com, they can get a pretty good view of us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_08]: And just so you know, yes, my colors are all screwed up on the notes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll tell you why I do that after Loki finishes.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's my way of kind of like getting an edge up on Xbox Live when I play.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cheater.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not a cheater, I'm just exploiting something in the game.
This is not a five, I'm sorry.
That is not a five.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seven, maybe?
[SPEAKER_07]: But then again, I can't really judge song difficulty anymore, because, like, I'm out of shape.
[SPEAKER_02]: This plays about like a seven.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, how many calories would you say you burned on that one?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could tell you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: About 40.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see what kind of grade Loki got on that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, 37 greats, I'd say that's about a C. Oh, he got an A!
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I rock.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so what did you think of those steps?
[SPEAKER_07]: Eh, they were okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were kind of fun, except that, you know, I hate free stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, now you've got to do the kata, do Disable the Flaw.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here, I'll hold the mic for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, make him hold the mic while he does it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want him to trip.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want feedback.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't want him to trip up the cord and die.
[SPEAKER_08]: He'll live.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here, I'll hold the cord up so you don't trip.
[SPEAKER_02]: I promise to set you on fire at your funeral.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm gonna hate you, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: We will launch you out to sea when you die.
[SPEAKER_02]: In a catapult.
[SPEAKER_08]: What, this song's only like a minute ten.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't fail.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're on the internet right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: They'll all know if you fail this crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_08]: Cool down break.
[SPEAKER_08]: I gotta cut up some slack on this mic cord.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh man.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is like classic Kata stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love this song, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is like a real gem in this song.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would say this is my favorite song in this song pack.
[SPEAKER_08]: Miss, miss, miss, miss, miss, miss, miss, miss, miss, miss, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, he's got, he's got a... Huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am so out of shape.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really need to go back and play.
[SPEAKER_08]: What'd you think of those steps?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, is it a worthy download?
[SPEAKER_08]: Would you pay?
[SPEAKER_08]: You got a D. Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: D for, uh, the bum ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I would say, if you're out of shape like me, don't play the Cat is on Pat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Would you spend $5 for that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to turn down the Ultramix music there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I would.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really, they're kind of stretching for songs now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, your D is on the webcam, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm done, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, you're done?
[SPEAKER_08]: You sure you don't want to do one Forever Sunshine, Jamie, for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to get Jamie to get up there.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't play Forever Sunshine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was totally kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you play Forever Sunshine, I will cut off your ankles.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like Ogia.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would have to say, yeah, it's worth a download.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, the steps are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: They weren't retarded like, say, you know, was it...
[SPEAKER_07]: Outer Limits or anything like that, where it's just ridiculous fast and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Table of Flaw, they had stuff sort of like your old school Katas, where it's a long run of eighth notes and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, for those of you guys that are wondering, why the hell does it show the red notes and blue notes and yellow notes?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why doesn't it look right?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's because, actually, the way my system is set up on the Xbox, I actually have it set to show the notes, the different colors on purpose.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because the reason why I do that is so that when I go on Xbox Live, it shows up that way, and it makes it so much easier to read the notes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you really can't change things when you play on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: What other songs came out in that song pack?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Gia.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that
[SPEAKER_07]: This is Guitar Freaks, I think?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, this is originally from Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, and then we've got Regret, which is, what was that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think, okay, well, Regret I think was Beatmania, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then we have Jelly Kiss from 2DX7, I believe.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then we've got Disabled, The Flaw, which is Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_07]: Beatmania and I think Poppin' Music.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Forever Sunshine, which is Max, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: And everyone remembers that song for being so awful.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: For five bucks, I mean, you can't beat it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just download it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait for the next pack.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's better than some of the other song packs they put out not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just as long as we don't get a whole song pack of mixes of Let Them Move, then it's not too bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are we going to do one more?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, one more.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do Oh Yeah!
[SPEAKER_07]: I like that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh Yeah?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's bring up the Ultramix 2 music again.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like this song.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Done by Asmat Nemi.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_19]: Here we go!
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh Yeah!
[SPEAKER_08]: From what I remember about this song, it's just one constant stream of notes, really.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a very poppin' music.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what it looks like?
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like that they actually put in, like, new background videos, though, in some of this, which I think is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or at least, like, background videos we haven't really seen before, so...
[SPEAKER_19]: That was very wormy.
[SPEAKER_19]: I like this song because it's different for DDR.
[SPEAKER_19]: Like, you're like, what the heck is this?
[SPEAKER_19]: It's like Bollywood or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love those runs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love those cheap runs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, dude, Loki's like hecka sweating.
Look at that.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is called out of the game.
[SPEAKER_19]: Dance, monkey, dance.
[SPEAKER_08]: When we bring the webcam back up, I want to zoom in on Loki's sweat to show what a workout he's getting there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh man, my legs feel like weights.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm surprised I could play something, but I don't want to play any of those songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those songs still seem very fun to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: You want to do something from Song Pack 8?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright Jamie, come on, show us how to do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, actually, the chatroom is suggesting you do a freestyle to this one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Freestyle, freestyle, freestyle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chatroom, love y'all, but y'all suck.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, she got a D. Or, I'm sorry, he got a D. Another D. Jamie's here to pretty up the photo op.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not really much, though, because Loki's a damn sexy man.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need to play some more.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do another regular Ultimax 2 songs.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can see a dance in your dance.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now that's... That's the picture to get.
[SPEAKER_00]: The agony of defeat.
[SPEAKER_19]: Play Max 300.
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Japanese tourists taking pictures, man.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's because you're an American tourist attraction.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's like, I'm in heaven or close your eyes or skulk or something.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dude, there's a song called Gyrus.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's totally sweet.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a remix of the Gyrus theme from... Dude!
[SPEAKER_08]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie's apologizing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's taking her so long to pick a song, but she's just kind of picky.
[SPEAKER_08]: Four weeks later.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, we hardly ever actually play DDR on the show, so this is a rare opportunity for you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: As if you can't tell by the wheezing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I play a lot of DDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold down B. No, I lied.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hit A. And this time hold down A. Hold down.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then you can go down to...
[SPEAKER_08]: Other.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's where you can turn off the freeze arrows.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh no, there it is, right there, freeze.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is going to be the last one, and Jamie's going to give you her thoughts on Chasmic Cowgirl.
[SPEAKER_07]: She says she hasn't played DDR in a month.
[SPEAKER_00]: She's making it look good with so many crepes on Perfects.
[SPEAKER_00]: Go, Jamie!
[SPEAKER_08]: I used to love this song when I was in Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I was just thinking, man, this makes me want to play Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do you guys have Guitar Freaks?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, sadly not here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Damn, I should have brought mine.
[SPEAKER_19]: You got us shaking our butts now, Mr. DJ.
[SPEAKER_00]: You do got us shaking our butts now, Mr. DJ.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, she just has to go and show me up now.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's no fair.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's because she's more in shape than I am.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, she's been preparing for that mud run, so you know she's got the stamina for this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been preparing for a Big Mac.
[SPEAKER_00]: Two all-beef patties, special sauce, lettuce, cheese, pickles, onions, and get this, sesame seed bun, baby.
[SPEAKER_00]: Too much burger for one man to handle.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was so freaking easy, that wasn't an 8 Okay, so that, you know, they have an 8 Kill us, your moves And a 5 for New high score The verdict is a B She got a slightly better score than Loki, thank you That's cause he said something that made me laugh It was a new high score I broke someone's goal, whore Alright, so what'd you think of that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's your chair, Beck.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fun?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe I need to start doing DDR again.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because the ironic thing is, even though we talk about these music games a whole lot here on the station, we haven't played them in quite a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, I played Step Mania, but that's with my hand.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played the Button Button Revolution, and that's still kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I now know why people don't exercise in jeans.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, can we go back to regular?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: What we're going to do now is we're going to go ahead and open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_08]: For those of you guys that have any feedback, you want to talk about 2DX Night Style, or you want to talk about what else is going on in the scene, we were talking a little bit about Bawani tournaments going on earlier, and if you have any feedback on Ultramix 2 and the performance of DarkSakura and Loki, we certainly would love to hear that as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, we are going to go ahead and open up the Skype line, so go ahead and give us a call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, to do that, head on over to www.orangeloungeradio.com, click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's go ahead, we got one coming in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, you are on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Legend of Zaku here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hello, Zaku, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_12]: As always, I'm... Yes, I'm... Hi, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just coming back from Spring Break and all, and managing to play 2DX10 style, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wait, you did get to play 2DX10 style?
[SPEAKER_12]: It was kind of like, yeah...
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, because, you know, Long Island, not far from the city, has a place that has 2DX10.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I managed to travel out there by bus, like a couple of weeks ago on a Saturday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Getting on the bus to go nerd it up, huh?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, but it was worth the trip, you know, because, you know, not only did they have that, they also had in the groove poppin' music, they had Flash Bees, which is basically Step Mania in a solo cabinet with poppin' music buttons.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, I've heard of that game, it was, god, I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean I saw other folks breaking out the towel and putting it on there, but... I can't play without a towel.
[SPEAKER_12]: But anyways, you know, I'm hearing word that 2DX12 Happy Sky is going up for location testing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: That name is so... You repeat us to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were going to talk about that a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yes, they've announced 2DX12 style, also known as Happy Sky.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which is ironic when you consider what my online name is, Sky.
[SPEAKER_08]: Happy Sky!
[SPEAKER_08]: That made you Happy Sky.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm so happy!
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm happy that this game's coming.
[SPEAKER_12]: At this point, I mean...
[SPEAKER_12]: We managed to get the upgrade in that place that managed to get 10th style.
[SPEAKER_12]: See, it was originally 9th, but late last year they managed to go up to 10th, seeing that they got the 2DX machine earlier last year.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, I'm assuming that, you know, according to the thread, once I mention, you know, 12, that they'll try to plan to just go after getting that upgrade kit, same way they did for 10th.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that surprises us when we manage to get 10th, you know?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, it really depends, because in our area, I mean, we're having tournaments.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're about to have a big tournament, hopefully in April, next month in Albany.
[SPEAKER_12]: We already had a slew of smaller, low-level tournaments, one of which almost ended up in fighting, as I told you last time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_08]: With the drama?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, there's one reason why you don't have the... No, but I mean, that was because of the locals who basically acted like assholes and, you know, basically started, you know, disrespecting other, you know, outsiders.
[SPEAKER_12]: Outside players were beating them to it.
[SPEAKER_12]: So what do you think is causing the decline out here, then?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not really that much of a decline.
[SPEAKER_12]: It really depends on where you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it depends on where a scene thrives.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can understand where Northern California, you know, I can understand your scene over there because it's striving for something new, like in the group.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think you're on the verge, in my honest opinion, you're on the verge of just switching on to more in-the-group tournaments.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know how I feel about that, though, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know how I feel about In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, to be honest, though, In The Groove, I'm not sure about the freestyle part of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's the problem.
[SPEAKER_12]: In The Groove was made for Perfect Attack tournaments, but freestyle... Yes, the East Coast already held In The Groove tournaments and ate on the break late last year.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it was a pretty good turnout.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't, I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just, it doesn't seem like the game's really that, I mean, you're always hearing about the thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: It may be.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I know it was built for, like, really, for, like, basically DDR on crack because of the fact that it's going to be on 10 foot and 10 feet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, I mean, you're talking, like, 10 footers, 12, 13.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's in the groove.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well said!
[SPEAKER_12]: Indigroove in a nutshell is DDR on crack!
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what it is!
[SPEAKER_02]: Indigroove in a nutshell is DDR on crap!
[SPEAKER_12]: But wait till Indigroove 2 comes out, and then you know, they're gonna start thinking.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, I've been warming up to Indigroove.
[SPEAKER_08]: I honestly cannot knock the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's...
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you've become desensitized.
[SPEAKER_12]: Tournaments are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, you know, the tournament scene is still there.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just, you know, it needs something good.
[SPEAKER_12]: It needs something new to go on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Para, para.
[SPEAKER_10]: We need more para, para.
[SPEAKER_12]: We were so grateful of managing to pull off a Nationals tournament last year.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that created, that got a big turnout.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not only that, we managed to expose DDR to a lot of things.
[SPEAKER_12]: To a lot of people that probably never heard of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: and we're getting DDR the limelight it deserves.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, you know, tournaments in fact are doing, you know, more great things for, you know, it depends on where it is though.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: They're preparing, well, from what I heard, they are preparing for this year's.
[SPEAKER_12]: They might do another Nationals tournament this year in October.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all talk until something happens.
[SPEAKER_02]: This whole exposure thing, though, I don't think it's necessarily that good of a thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, but think about it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's in New York City, and you have mods such as Frequency Busting putting foot to ass trying to help, you know, help it get out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it's usually when something gets to be a little too popular that it starts getting...
[SPEAKER_12]: and it's basically what you make of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whether or not you want to decide to pedal in the groove and in the groove 2, which is coming out, which could be an alternative to people who've been sucking on Xtreme for what now?
[SPEAKER_08]: Almost two and a half years?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I mean, we will see.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's really all we can say right now is we will see.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we got to go because the Skype line is ringing.
[SPEAKER_08]: But is there any other final thought you have for us, Zaku?
[SPEAKER_12]: Basically, just, you know...
[SPEAKER_12]: Just basically, you know, In The Groove 2 might, you know, just be ready in case.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just try not, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will give In The Groove 2 a fair shot just like I gave In The Groove a fair shot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just be even with it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just be fair.
[SPEAKER_08]: You promise, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: You promise?
[SPEAKER_08]: Open mind, In The Groove?
[SPEAKER_02]: At least be ajar.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've still got to try it, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Zach.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Later.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's take another call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go to this one.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi, you are on Orange Lounge Radio Merching from the shadows of Bermondi Style, here's your resident 2DX bastard, DarkLineXVI Hello, our resident 2DX bastard, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_17]: I finally got my copy of 2DX Night Style Hurrah, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, it's really good Did you get the one with all the stickers?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, I don't have a sticker, I only have the regular edition I want all the DVDs and the stickers So what are your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_17]: Tell us what you think
[SPEAKER_17]: It's really good, actually.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's almost like in the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wait, what about the timing?
[SPEAKER_17]: We haven't talked about the timing.
[SPEAKER_17]: Specifically, not the timing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They think the timing's okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: The timing is okay, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need mine.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was the deciding factor is the timing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to say, because, you know, with the arcade there, of course, you're upgrading the hardware and stuff, so you've got the timing issues for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But with the home version, it's pretty much just, you know, they reskin it, throw new songs in, you're done.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's pretty much, you know, all for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, of course, the timing should be right on, you know, compared with some of the other ones, it should be just fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, anyways, you enjoy it?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, of course I do enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hey Sky, remember the videos that I sent you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so I was going to ask you, because you sent me actually one of your, you know, videos where you actually hooked it up, so you're playing 2DX, and you can see, you actually, like, you were playing Love Shine, and you see the notes falling.
[SPEAKER_17]: I did play Love Love Shine, it's one of my Tatsujin videos.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right, it's a new Tatsujin video, but you set it up in your house so that we can see your fingers playing the song instead of the typical video.
[SPEAKER_08]: How'd you set that up?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, you know, I use a tripod, I use a camcorder, and then I use my PC as my monitor.
[SPEAKER_17]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_17]: Speaking of which, I'm going to send you a link of what my setting looks like.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, put that on our chat room, www.orangelaunchradio.com, clicking on chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go ahead and slap that up in our chat room so our folks there can check it out, the link.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, this is what my setup looks like.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, now do you have a site where we can actually download the Tatsujin videos for those that want to see what this looks like?
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you going to throw them on Vimani style like everyone else that does Tatsujin videos?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, mine is different, so... I got it from DustBacon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you really made out of iron?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, there's a difference between Tatsujin and Tetsujin.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_17]: Here's the link for my Tatsujin videos, as well as a Seastar player and others.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let me log into my photobucket so I can give you the link to what my aesthetic looks like.
[SPEAKER_08]: While you're doing that, what would you say would be your favorite of the new consumer songs that are in 9th style?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, my favorite... Here's a correction.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's not photogenic, it's photongenic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I read it quickly.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's Photongenic.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, my favorite.
[SPEAKER_17]: Is that your favorite?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, Photongenic's my favorite.
[SPEAKER_17]: Other than that, it's also, I like Jaeger Final Attack.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jaeger Hamster Dance, as I call it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Is it just me, or has Denjin Jaeger gone fat?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I haven't actually seen the video that goes along with the song just yet, so I couldn't really tell you that.
[SPEAKER_17]: I do have the video.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're going to have to send that to me at some point so I can check it out.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll send it to you after this call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there anything else you wanted to say, Siggy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I've got to let you go to get somebody else here on the line, but is there anything else you wanted to say?
[SPEAKER_17]: Nothing much else, but I'm just happy that I have my night style.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep us posted on any developments going on in the 2DX world.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, I already sent you the link to what my settings look like.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll check that out in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, have a good one, bud.
[SPEAKER_17]: Later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Later.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's try to pick up a call here, if I can.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, it's Jimmy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not much?
[SPEAKER_01]: How's it going?
[SPEAKER_01]: I gotta turn down my window real quick.
[SPEAKER_01]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's alright, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: First rule of calling into radio, turn off your radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I know how that is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just going off of the first caller, the ITG, the way tournaments are going here in SoCal.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's basically all in the groove now.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you're saying in Southern California now, it's all about in the groove?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does that include freestyle?
[SPEAKER_01]: The first big one was in Stonewood, and everyone was pretty much going nuts, because you can see the percentages on the screen, and you get instant feedback while the people are playing, instead of having to count the greats while people are going.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so you can kind of watch the scores go up, because In the Groove is one of those games where it's considered acceptable to use the scores as something that determines how well you do in the tournament.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, because basically everyone knows exactly how the scoring system works.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's just a good scoring system, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, well, what I have to know, I have no doubt that In the Groove is a great game for tournaments, but I have to know, freestyle.
[SPEAKER_08]: How does freestyle work?
[SPEAKER_01]: I've yet to see a freestyle tournament for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's only been... Yeah, there's a reason for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Told you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, the songs just aren't there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've freestyled, and I really don't think there's a whole lot of freestyable songs on ITG.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_01]: With the DDR crossovers, I guess we'll call them.
[SPEAKER_01]: That will definitely be cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Follow the Sun and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, anything else you wanted to share with us, my friend?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm hoping to get to the X-Night style soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we all want it, but we're poor.
[SPEAKER_08]: What can we say?
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, free sound in the group doesn't really work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully they will fix that within the group too.
[SPEAKER_08]: We shall see.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what I'm hoping for.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks a lot, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: You too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's take one more call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Tons Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the one and only token black cosplayer, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_05]: How you guys doing tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, our token black cosplayer friend.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm good, I'm good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, you do have competition out here in the form of J-Ryoga.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know J-Ryoga H?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, a long time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, he's one of my friends.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knew?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's more than one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Small world.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you doing, my friend?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had a cosplay photo shoot in Central Park today.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got kicked out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now this I have to hear about.
[SPEAKER_08]: So for those who don't know, because remember we have new listeners on tonight, what is cosplay, for those who don't know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Cosplay or Costume Play.
[SPEAKER_05]: You dress up as your favorite anime, video game, or manga characters at anime conventions.
[SPEAKER_08]: And sometimes this can be scantily clad females from fighting games, or this can be just like downright ugly guys from who knows what.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Downright ugly guys cosplaying as scantily clad female video game players.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I've seen that too.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, okay, I have to know, how did you guys...
[SPEAKER_08]: What were you guys setting up to do in Central Park, and how did you get kicked out?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what I have to know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We didn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: We were just taking pictures of ourselves in costumes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: You were dressed up like freaks!
[SPEAKER_05]: You were freaks, and the freaks have to go!
[SPEAKER_05]: It was mostly hot EGL girls.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, were you guys all dressing up like ghosts in a big group and having a rally, and you know, then they might have kicked you out because of that?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, we were more...
[SPEAKER_05]: More like, you know, less than that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, you know, whenever cosplay events in the park happen, like, say, in Tokyo, then a bajillion people take pictures of it and it ends up in Fruits Magazine, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, but there was only like five people from outside that were walking around and took pictures of us.
[SPEAKER_08]: What I'm curious about, was it the scantily clad females that got you kicked out of Central Park?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_05]: It seems that you need a permit to take pictures in Central Park.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Everybody and their mother was going to Central Park to take pictures of the gates.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did they get a permit for that?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's just it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what we argued.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said because it's for commercial purposes, we need a permit.
[SPEAKER_05]: And on the weekends, we need special permission from the mayor.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this for commercial purposes?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, this is for amateur stuff for our websites.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I say next time you're there, burn down the gates.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gator already gone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_08]: See?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mission accomplished!
[SPEAKER_07]: They've been replaced by Altercade machines.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, that's just so ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I used to do LARP vampire games in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we were just all kinds of insane.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alabama parking lot or whatever you did is slightly different than Central Park.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we would do it in downtown Mobile at Bienville Square.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is a historical landmark.
[SPEAKER_08]: They should have told them it was for a school project.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a historical landmark.
[SPEAKER_08]: We did.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we never got anything for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's the easy excuse whenever you need to get out of something.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's for a school project.
[SPEAKER_08]: We didn't know we were doing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not this time.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything going on in your gaming world you want to share with us, buddy?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was at the PSP release at my job.
[SPEAKER_05]: We sold 260 of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: 20 came back.
[SPEAKER_05]: and 15 came back the next day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that the dead pixel thing that's going on with the new PSPs I'm hearing about?
[SPEAKER_05]: They're too anal.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, are they really that bad?
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you seen them?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some are, some aren't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since we're Geek Squad, we have to take a look at these things.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got Dan, who's actually a manager of a GameStop in town.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very, very minor and these people are too anal.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, I got... You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you send me some of those defective PSPs?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'll take them off your hands.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, don't you think I tried?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, quote unquote defective.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, Dan, I know you're dying to say something.
[SPEAKER_00]: The people who are bitching about one or two dead pixels on their PSPs are anal retentive bastards who should be shot on sight.
[SPEAKER_05]: No shit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_00]: The official line now is, we don't take them back, they gotta go to Sony if they have dead pixels.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Sony doesn't care.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, Sony does care.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sony is replacing them.
[SPEAKER_00]: Are they really?
[SPEAKER_00]: Which is very, very decent of Sony.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, what you're going to get back is another dead pixel PSP that they fixed.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: But as for anyone who has problems with dead pixels on their PSP, stick with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: They'll either go away or you'll adjust.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, out of the gajillions of pixels, if one or two are dead, hey, consider yourself lucky.
[SPEAKER_00]: Some people have a couple dozen.
[SPEAKER_00]: They should be mad.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: 30 people Well, you know, considering how much they charge for those things, though, you'd think the thing would run absolutely perfectly.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the only issue.
[SPEAKER_08]: You ever bought a tire for your car?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did it go flat?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, but they replaced it for free.
[SPEAKER_00]: LCD screens have dead pixels.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sony will replace it for free.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, that's it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It just happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you have it lucky.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have to take them back.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where do you work?
[SPEAKER_05]: Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, is that because you sell that extra insurance or whatever?
[SPEAKER_05]: Even without the extra insurance, they bring it back.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have to take it back, we stamp it out, de-vote, we send it back to the manufacturer.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the thing is, Sony doesn't reimburse the manufacturer for that return.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to take out your frustration on the whole machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: We get most of it back, like 85% of the value we get back, more or less.
[SPEAKER_00]: They won't do it with the dead pixels because they don't consider those to be a defect.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: Best Buy's policy will change.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right now, I think they're doing the right thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think, hey, if we had 100 extra systems in stock, and I had 10 people wanting to bring them back and exchange them, hey, no problem.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, according to Sony, Sony, Sony, Sony, their whole take on it is, this is how PSPs are, there's a problem with the pixels, you send them to us, we'll take care of it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't bother the retailer.
[SPEAKER_00]: And most of the smaller retailers have said, hey, we can't take them back for that reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't this supposed to be virtually invisible anyway when you're playing?
[SPEAKER_00]: In game, you don't see it unless it's a solid color screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, or from what I was told, when you turn it off, you see the dead pixels.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, yeah, and that's the thing is these people, they're not...
[SPEAKER_00]: They're not, you know, trying it for a couple hours and saying, wow, this doesn't interrupt my gameplay.
[SPEAKER_00]: They turn it on on the boot up screen, see a pixel that's green when it should be white, and lose their minds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it makes sense after they just spent $250 on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: If they'd run the Spider-Man DVD through it, 90% of the time the pixels unfreeze since they're just frozen, not dead.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that's weird.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the thing is, two months down the road, you might have a whole different set of dead pixels.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because it's not like you're going to get one that's going to work forever.
[SPEAKER_00]: LCD screens do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyone who has an LCD monitor can tell you that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've heard the dead pixel thing going on with the DS as well, so it's not just, you know, PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's nature of technology.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, we've got to let you go, bud.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got to let you go, bud.
[SPEAKER_08]: But have a good one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for calling us.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, later.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've got to take one more because this guy's been calling us pretty constantly.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I just want to do one more and then we're going to get into the cage.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're so kind.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, I'm so kind.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you hear us?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, hey.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, there you are.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_17]: So, what's up?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that might be really bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is my mom.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can hear you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you hear us, buddy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you hear me now?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think he can hear us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, bud.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can't hear you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, he hung up on us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we tried.
[SPEAKER_08]: We tried.
[SPEAKER_08]: For those of you guys that are still trying to get in, thanks, but we are going to just come back to this later.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll do the match game, don't forget, we've got that coming up a little later on.
[SPEAKER_08]: But for now we're going to get into the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, for those of you guys unfamiliar with the Cage Match, the way it works, we're going to play three songs for you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we're going to play three songs, and you guys have to be in the chat room to vote.
[SPEAKER_08]: www.orangeloungeradio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we will play these songs, and then you're going to pick your favorite, and your favorite song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio's Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the winner gets a break from having to pick a song mixed with each other.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Jamie, it's your break because you won last week, and it's Yoko Kanno, and the song is Rise.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, remember, there's no rhyme or reason for why we picked these songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's three songs we like, you pick your favorite, and it goes in rotation.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, so here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: You only get a clip of this song, though, because it did win last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's a clip.
[SPEAKER_08]: Song number one, Yoko Kanno, Rise.
[SPEAKER_08]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, that was a clip of song number one.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was Yoko Kanno with Rise.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now you get to hear two new songs in their entirety.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to start it off with my pick for tonight's Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, you might remember, or you may not if this is your first time listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: If so, welcome.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we've retired a couple songs from the Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_08]: When a song wins four times, we retire it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the first song that ever got retired was a Top 40 hit.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was Gwen Stefani, remember that?
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to try... I'm going to try... Hey, hey, you watch it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like my Gwen, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm going to try my Top 40 luck again because I love this chick.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't roll your eyes at me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, the listeners don't see that.
[SPEAKER_08]: They do when I get upset.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So anyway, I'm going to try my Top 40 luck.
[SPEAKER_08]: What, what, what, what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to do a dance remix, though, of a Top 40 hit.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this is...
[SPEAKER_07]: One of those stupid Hataway songs again.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not Hataway.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is actually Kelly Clarkson.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get the zero automatically.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: You listen to it first.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, so it's a bathroom break.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is Kelly Clarkson.
[SPEAKER_08]: You haters.
[SPEAKER_08]: The song is Since You Been Gone, and it's the Jason Nevins Rock the Club mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: Enjoy, guys.
[SPEAKER_19]: And all you'd ever need
[SPEAKER_19]: Thanks to you, now I get what I want Since you've been gone How can I put it, you put me on I even fell for that stupid love song Yeah, yeah, since you've been gone How come I never hear
[SPEAKER_19]: I just wanna be with you Guess you never felt that way But since you've been gone I can't breathe for the first time I'm so moving on, yeah, yeah Thanks to you, now I get
[SPEAKER_19]: I just can't say again Again and again and again and again Did you think I would?
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: I've rocked something and now I have to go to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_03]: It gets a three.
[SPEAKER_00]: No more talking for you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Shut up, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dan the Man, since you have a mic.
[SPEAKER_13]: Get in the kitchen and make me a pie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dan the Man, since you have a mic, what do you think of Since You've Been Gone?
[SPEAKER_08]: Unimpressive.
[SPEAKER_08]: On a scale of one to ten?
[SPEAKER_07]: Negative four.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is no amount of alcohol in this world that would make that song good.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was awful.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you could remix that song to hell and it would still suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: It gets a 1.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's Killing Clarkson.
[SPEAKER_07]: What were you thinking?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you flipped me off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bad Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: This coming from the guy who brings his girlfriend over every Tuesday to watch American Idol.
[SPEAKER_07]: Doesn't mean I'm going to buy any of their albums, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, they gave us clay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like reality TV sometimes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just because I watch reality TV does not mean that I'm going to buy the music.
[SPEAKER_08]: Clay Aiken is funny looking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kelly Clarkson is a hot mama.
[SPEAKER_00]: Clay Aiken is funny looking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think you people who, especially considering some of the DDR songs you guys like, need to respect Kelly a little more.
[SPEAKER_08]: I give it like a 9.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like that remix.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, Angel.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like girly stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, 5.
[SPEAKER_08]: God, I can't even get a pity vote from Angel.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see how Loki's song spares tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, what did you pick for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Last song.
[SPEAKER_07]: I picked the song from everyone's favorite Kill Bill soundtrack artist.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know I'm going to butcher this name.
[SPEAKER_07]: You picked something at random.
[SPEAKER_07]: I picked something, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I had three of those bottle caps from Pepsi sitting here at my desk, and I was like, God damn it, I've got to go on iTunes now and get something.
[SPEAKER_07]: So today I found this guy, and of course you'll recognize him from his ever-famous song, A Battle Without Honor or Humanity.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is Frozen Memories by, I only remember the guy's name.
[SPEAKER_08]: Try Tomoyasu Hote.
[SPEAKER_08]: How does that sound right?
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Song number three, Tomoyasu Hote with Frozen Memories.
[SPEAKER_08]: Enjoy.
It was not too bad, but kind of generic.
[SPEAKER_02]: It gets a solid 7.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Angel, what did you think of that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked it.
8.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought it was good, but not as good as Kelly Clarkson.
7.5.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, what did you think of Tomiyasu Hotei?
[SPEAKER_07]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was interesting because I was very tempted to put in Battle Without Honor and Humanity for another...
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the wailing guitar sound.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was totally sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: That song would rock in Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it definitely gets at least an 8.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe 8.725.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Totally hard.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay guys, it's time to vote.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember, you have to be in our chatroom to vote.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everything we have said to this point doesn't matter because it's you guys that make the ultimate decision.
[SPEAKER_08]: So here it is, one more time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Song number one, Yoko Kanno with Rise.
[SPEAKER_08]: And song number two you can vote for tonight, Kelly Clarkson, Since You've Been Gone, Jason Nevins edit.
[SPEAKER_08]: And song number three you can vote for tonight is Tomoyasu Hote with Frozen Memories.
[SPEAKER_08]: Place vote now!
[SPEAKER_08]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the one that gets the most votes will walk away the winner.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: And in case the viewing public was unsure of who the mystery person was, well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob, do you want to explain?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, did he go?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, he's gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: We gave him our contact information.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, just so you guys know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Screw you guys, I'm going home.
[SPEAKER_08]: If the show sounded a little weird just then, and you noticed we were doing some different stuff, there was a photographer from a local paper that was here taking pictures for like the past hour.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was here a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, he was on the webcam.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, so yeah, maybe he's on the webcam.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's what was going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're famous!
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going to be famous!
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going to be in the paper!
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we'll see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really hope they got a shot of Jamie while she was in mid-air.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I saw the camera right here, like a couple close-up shots of me going... You know what's funny is that when he first showed up, he thought our whole show was us dancing while talking.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, you want us to dance?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, Dance Monkey Dance.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're like, free publicity?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure, we'll get out the pad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's dance.
[SPEAKER_09]: What else do you want me to do?
[SPEAKER_08]: Eh, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: It works out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, anyway, finish your votes there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send them over a private message to Sky.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, as long as you got the microphone there, tell us what's going on in the sim scene this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, not too much as it was last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm still waiting for some actual sim files to come out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think, if I remember correctly, there was that Setmania pack that's coming out with a bunch of songs called, uh,
[SPEAKER_07]: DDR, uh, it's like XXMix or something like that, oh, there's some link on, um, there's some link on the actual, um, Bomani style site that, um, they have there, and they were saying there was going to be an April 1st release for that, so, look for that, there's a whole thread to it, and, um, so that'd be pretty interesting, other than that, um, oh, um, pretty soon, DDR UK's relaunching pretty soon, should be this week, actually, I think Monday or Tuesday, I can't remember,
[SPEAKER_07]: So they're coming back, and DDR Mania X is saying that they're coming back at some point.
[SPEAKER_07]: But actually, DDR UK, they are saying they're coming back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's Monday, Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember what exactly the day is on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they're coming back, so look for good stuff from them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really know what the situation is with SimFiles, what they're going to be doing, because I think the reason they got taken down the first time was because they had licensed music on there and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So look forward to that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That should be pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just glad that I'll have more websites to read again.
[SPEAKER_07]: And really, other than that, not too much else going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's some sim files out there that are pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: More crappy remixes, of course, out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they give me some ideas for stuff, so I may look to doing that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been kind of hitting a musician's block lately, so I haven't been making anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, lots of fun stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go download some music, songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to take the last call for cage match votes now.
[SPEAKER_08]: So hopefully you guys are getting those votes in.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what we're going to do, we're going to take a break and we're going to come back and play Match Game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Match Game tonight has prizes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, we are going to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, we need one contestant on the Skype line and one contestant actually in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Everybody send a message to Sky.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to participate in tonight's match game and you're in the chat room, send a message to Sky that says match game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we will pick one person at random to play the match game tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie will pick a number and we will have our contestant from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: 3 minutes during the break here It's between 1 and 666
[SPEAKER_08]: In this break, let's do some DDR songs, because we haven't done some DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's just do a mix here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's do Volume 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to start off with some Volume 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
Thanks for watching!
DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got some exposed visibility lately thanks to our listeners getting us nominated for Broadcaster of the Year over on Live 365.
[SPEAKER_08]: So hello to any folks listening for the first time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hope you enjoy Orange Lounge Radio, our little nerd fest that we have here every Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, our station does run 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, describe Pump Up the Volume in one word.
[SPEAKER_02]: Random.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then Thursday nights, we will be back this week with Outside the Box, 7 o'clock Pacific Standard Time, all your favorite gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't forget, we also have a podcast completely separate.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a completely separate show we do about 25, 30 minutes in length that just talks about video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Check that out over on our website, orangelaundry.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Check out the to-go edition.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, first off, let's see who won tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somewhat of a closer cage match, certainly closer cage match tonight than it was last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: But in the end, there was one winner, and the winner of tonight's cage match is... Yoko Kanno, once again, with Rise.
[SPEAKER_08]: Another week off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Another week.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love you, chat room.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, we're going to be doing the match game here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Two contestants battling to the death, or something like that, for these CDs we have.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, we need one person from the chat room and one person on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can start hammering the Skype line now.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to pick one call at random on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't go away because we will be picking up just a random call.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let it ring and tell you here that we picked up someone else's call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then stop calling.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the meantime, we've got to find out who's playing from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, who is playing from chat?
[SPEAKER_08]: You've got to pick a number between 1 and 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to pick a number between 1 and 500.
[SPEAKER_08]: As long as that number happens to also be between 1 and 10, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pick a number between 1 and 500.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, 1 and 500.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoever gets closest wins.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just pick a number between 1 and 10 so I can count which person's getting it.
7.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can tell.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie says this person gets it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we have in our chat room tonight... Oh, this should be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Legend of Zaku is our chat person that's going to be participating tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, so now let's go over to the Skype line and pick up a random call.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got all these people calling in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's pick up this one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Me?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_10]: This is LemonLimeJump.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, LemonLimeJump.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_08]: You are our other contestant for the match game tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Aren't you excited?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, especially since I'm a noob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, Noob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, Noob.
[SPEAKER_02]: First call to the station.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so you're going to be playing match game tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, do you know how match game works?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you have to finish a sentence with a word or a phrase.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're already a pro at this.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're not much of a noob, because you already know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, we're going to read a sentence, and it's going to have a blank in it, and it's your job to best answer what you think the rest of us are going to put in that blank.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, without further ado, let's get some music here for Match Game.
[SPEAKER_08]: We definitely need some background music if we're going to be playing Match Game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, we don't have the rights to use the actual Match Game theme.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura is one celebrity you're going to try to match tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dan the Man is another celebrity you're going to try to match tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR Angel, Loki, and myself.
[SPEAKER_08]: Five people.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, now let me let him jump.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to read the question, and you just think about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You think about it for a minute, and then we'll let you know when we're ready for your answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right?
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Question number one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob was very sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's me, I'm Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob was very sad that he was unable to attend the March Madness DDR Tournament this past Saturday.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, he had more important things to do, such as stay home and blank.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob was very sad he couldn't attend the March Madness DDR Tournament this past Saturday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everybody in the room is thinking about that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Celebrities, please ding when you have an answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, you dinged?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Daddy says he loves me with his belt.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just waiting on our chatroom contestant, but that was my fault because I was a little late in pasting the question to him because it might be a little far behind there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard a ding.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think everybody's in.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: LemonLimeJump, you start us off, my friend.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob was very sad that he was unable to attend the March Madness DDR Tournament this past Saturday.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, he had more important things to do, such as stay at home and... Pick that Kelly Clarkson song for the cage match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pick the Kelly Clarkson song for tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was actually something I did do yesterday, so that's something...
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see what Legend of Zaku says.
[SPEAKER_08]: Legend of Zaku said he had to stay home and play 9th style while on Vicodin and forcing a ferret to play Lion Ski 7 key.
[SPEAKER_08]: Blink, blink, blink, blink, blink.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see if it's a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob had to stay home and... Build a cake for DarkSakura, Pedro style.
[SPEAKER_08]: Build a cake for DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, that's not a match, either one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dan...
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob had to stay home and... Download Prawn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Download Prawn!
[SPEAKER_08]: Excellent answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: What was the other answer?
[SPEAKER_07]: The other one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Play Nine Style, and then LemonLimeJump said that he had to pick the Kelly Clarkson song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, I had a mental lapse there for a second.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry that happened to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, Rob had to stay home and... Watch America's Next Top Model.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, watch America's Next Top Model!
[SPEAKER_07]: Not a match, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was Team Loki and Loki's fiance, Nelly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Had to get that out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Angel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob had to stay at home and... Watch reruns of Robot Chicken.
[SPEAKER_08]: Watch reruns of Robot Chicken.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: My answer, Rob had to stay home and look sexy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, you know, that's what I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I had to practice my model walk.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, let's get to question number two.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, LemonLimeJump, you didn't get it on that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you have a chance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you going to redeem yourself on this one?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I hope so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, Zaku sucked on that last one too, so don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least hers made sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here is question number two.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie is very excited...
[SPEAKER_08]: Also known as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie is very excited to be attending the upcoming Best of Live 365 ceremony in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, she will not be attending if they do not have any blank at the ceremony.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura is very excited to be attending the upcoming Best of Live 365 ceremony.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, she won't be attending if they don't have any blank at the ceremony.
[SPEAKER_08]: Think about that one for a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guests, or sorry, celebrities, please let me know when you have dinged.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Angel's thinking.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see her with a pen to the paper.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't lose hope, Angel.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just write the first thing that comes to mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: She won't be attending if they don't have any... And you know that there's other live 365 broadcasters out there that are listening right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, this might be important for them to know.
[SPEAKER_08]: That Jamie is not coming unless Blank is there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, Angel, you got it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I see her writing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay!
[SPEAKER_08]: LemonLimeJump, you're up first.
[SPEAKER_08]: She will not be attending if they do not have any... Cheese.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any cheese!
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zaku!
[SPEAKER_08]: says, Jamie is very excited to be attending.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, she will not be attending the Best of Life 365 ceremony if they do not have any Jesus juice at the ceremony.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jesus juice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, Michael Jackson, the wine and the Diet Coke.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: It could be a match with one of our celebrities, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's find out.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: She will not be attending if they do not have any booze.
[SPEAKER_08]: Booze!
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, that's not a good enough match with Jesus Juice.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't allow that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: DanTheMan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do we have a mic for DanTheMan?
[SPEAKER_08]: Will not be attending if they do not have any... Pie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pie!
[SPEAKER_08]: Excellent answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: She will not be attending if they do not have any... Pie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pie!
[SPEAKER_08]: Another one for Pie.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would have been a good one to pick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_08]: She will not be attending if they do not have any... Guinness.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guinness!
[SPEAKER_08]: and I said she will not be attending if they do not have any Guinness.
[SPEAKER_08]: I also put Guinness, so... That was actually the first thing I put.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guinness and pie were the two, but unfortunately not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, LemonLimeJump.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have one more chance, though, LemonLimeJump.
[SPEAKER_08]: One more chance.
[SPEAKER_08]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: The last question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Question number three.
[SPEAKER_08]: As you heard earlier this evening...
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki is building a charger for the DS out of Legos.
[SPEAKER_08]: He borrowed this idea from another website.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, soon, Loki will be writing another Lego building FAQ for OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's called, How to Build a Blank for Your PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: Out of Legos.
[SPEAKER_08]: He'll be doing another Lego FAQ.
[SPEAKER_08]: How to Build a Blank for Your PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: Think about that one for a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Celebrities, let me know when you've dinged.
[SPEAKER_08]: A ding, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm hearing some dings.
[SPEAKER_08]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're in the middle of match game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lemon Lime Jump versus Legend of Zaku on the line.
[SPEAKER_08]: Two sampler CDs, one for Resident Evil 4 and NBA 2005.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all tied up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's nothing right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: We will see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, is everybody dinged?
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you dinged?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, Angel's still there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you want to see some chat room suggestions here, Angel?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, you guys...
[SPEAKER_08]: Battery Charger
[SPEAKER_08]: Battery Charger for your PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: A nice, logical answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see if it pays off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zaku says, how to build a ghetto-rigged iPod 40 gigabytes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: For your PSP, we will find out.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, how to build a... Catapult.
[SPEAKER_08]: Catapult!
[SPEAKER_08]: Is not a match, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: DanTheMan, Loki will be showing how to build a...
[SPEAKER_08]: Stand of displayness.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stand of displayness out of LEGOs for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a match, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess I'll be designing a Portal to Hell device.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: A Portal to Hell for your PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: A device to talk to the dead.
[SPEAKER_08]: Out of LEGOs.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like Portal to Hell.
[SPEAKER_08]: Still not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_08]: He'll show you how to build a... Ghetto game dispenser.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't ask.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not original tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ghetto Game Dispenser.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, he has something to hold your games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I said that he will be showing how to build a feeding tube for your PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, it's all tied up at 0-0, which means, unfortunately, LemonLimeJump and Zaku have both lost tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's okay, because that means they get to split the loot!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay, so Lemon Lime Jump, you still win.
[SPEAKER_08]: Aren't you happy?
[SPEAKER_20]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, since I have you on the line, that was a genuine excitement.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lemon Lime Jump, what do you want?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you want the Resident Evil 4 CD, or do you want the NBA 2005 CD?
[SPEAKER_10]: Resident Evil, because I was... wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: Decisions, decisions.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's taking the Resident Evil 4 soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zaku, you don't go home a loser.
[SPEAKER_08]: You get the NBA 2005 soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks so much for playing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me line jump.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll be in touch and chat, alright?
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, thanks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need to get your address.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for playing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Later.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: I liked her wow was the best part of that whole segment.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was hoping that it was a woman, because I called her a her, and if it was a guy, that would have been really bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you saying she sounds like a man?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm saying that some guys, some kids sound like women.
[SPEAKER_08]: Most of our listeners are males, so it's nice to have some more females listening to the program.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's go to a break.
[SPEAKER_08]: When we come back from break, we're going to get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dig through those Legos, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, we'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to start it off.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to do just a mix of music here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Start it off with some AM3P from Old School DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio and the FUs of the Week and more.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stay tuned.
Orange Lounge Radio
Thank you for watching!
Hey, come with me, come with me, come with me, just come on and cheer me like a child.
Hey, come with me, come with me.
Thanks for watching!
I tried to turn down the record
[SPEAKER_19]: Thanks for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: Kishiro kirashite itsumo no basho made Konya wa nidome no kurismasu Nei, kaeru kise ni fukedashite watashi wa koko ni iru wa Sorry, yoshita nara kizu o shite nei ki ga tomaru hodo
[SPEAKER_19]: From the Step Squad to Orange Lab, this D.R.
[SPEAKER_19]: sucks!
[SPEAKER_19]: Holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler!
[SPEAKER_08]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 137 on this Easter Sunday, March 27, 2005.
[SPEAKER_08]: On what has been quite an interesting show tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very interesting vibe going on tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had some good calls on the Skype line a little earlier tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually getting out the DDR mat and playing Ultramix live on air.
[SPEAKER_20]: First CD I've played in a month.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm always looking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which is weird because I was hearing these stories about, oh my gosh, PSPs are sold out everywhere and you can't get one no matter what.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, mic down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get down a mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, Lego boy.
[SPEAKER_00]: The only reason we would have any left is because some weren't picked up by the fools who laid down $50 and just decided they didn't want them.
[SPEAKER_08]: $50 reserve.
[SPEAKER_00]: $50 deposit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: And do these people get their $50 back or no?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, a GameStop reservation is totally refundable, unlike an EB reservation that they make you spend in the store because EB sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now we have some EB employees that listen to this show, so be nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: They can suck it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Be nice, be nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can't we all just get along?
[SPEAKER_08]: They're babies, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what EB stands for.
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't there enough hate in this world?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to spread love here on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: GameStop and EB should come together in harmony.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then Best Buy could join in.
[SPEAKER_08]: But not Walmart.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not Walmart.
[SPEAKER_08]: Walmart's evil.
[SPEAKER_08]: Screw EB.
[SPEAKER_00]: Screw GameCrazy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't screw the people who work there because they suffer just like I do.
[SPEAKER_00]: You obviously didn't come to my store where we've had assloads of them forever.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't.
[SPEAKER_00]: As well as red octane ignition pads.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I ended up going to the GameStop up the street and I did pick up Ultramix 2 there.
[SPEAKER_08]: They just didn't have it at my usual GameStop up the street.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you, Dan.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We do a little segment.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to get into the FUs of the week here shortly, but before we get into that, we're going to get into a segment we like to do here on the show called the...
[SPEAKER_08]: No, not FNA.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to do the DDR Freak Post of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, it's the kitties one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I don't have the kitties one, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's in the imaging form.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's everyone posting pictures of their cats.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it's not the kitty post.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was there enough room on the desktop for that?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, you need to shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those of you guys listening to Orange Launch Radio for the first time, welcome.
[SPEAKER_08]: And DDR Freak, for those that may not know, because I think some of our new listeners may be unfamiliar with DDR, it's the largest website out there dedicated to Dance Dance Revolution, the video game that really started us off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although we're about gaming in general now, DDR is really what started us off.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we still show our love to DDR Freak by honoring their post of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know it's got a forum with, what, like 50,000 users?
[SPEAKER_08]: So there's always somebody interesting posting.
[SPEAKER_08]: By interesting, you mean stupid, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I wasn't going to say that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just got a call as I see it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually had a hard time finding a really stupid post this week, so I found a WTF post.
[SPEAKER_08]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: This was in the DDR console games section, and the subject is, Is anyone this desperate?
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the message.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am now starting to create step charts on my games that aren't the right songs that go with the song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like I created PS on Max 300 for DDR Max.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to also make Cartoon Heroes and Across the Nightmare.
[SPEAKER_08]: When I do this, I have the music mute or just have claps in training mode.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does anyone else do this or am I just weird?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if I'm understanding that post correctly, he mutes the TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: The whole point of DDR is to dance to the song.
[SPEAKER_08]: He mutes the TV and creates his own stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: He has step charts for songs that aren't in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: They did this a long-ass time ago when The Legend of Max was coming out and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were making Max on dropout and stuff and putting the steps on there to prepare for it and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: This has been done before.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did that to an edit that I made once just to listen to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you remember my really evil one that I did to DXY?
[SPEAKER_02]: The another edit?
[SPEAKER_02]: It just sounded really cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just... People really, really badly want Cartoon Heroes and USDDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: They will go to great lengths to get this song in DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just a song, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just a song.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it really means that much to you, pay the money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get an import PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what to tell you.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go to another segment we like to do here called the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what do we do during the FUs of the Week?
[SPEAKER_08]: We get ranty.
[SPEAKER_08]: We do this every single week for you folks that are new to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We set a bunch of people on fire.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's just a chance for us to kind of unload a little bit and feel better by venting.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, DarkSakura, why is it we have to do this every single week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, you know, I don't really have too much in the way of angst tonight, being that I'm in a generally good mood.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: A big F you go to your bathroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all I'm gonna say.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, oh yeah, an idiot's on the road.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, cause I'm in a generally good mood.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, that's amazing.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, well let's move on then to Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, first off, I'd like to say, um, fuck him at work for taking so long to get back to me on whether or not I have this job.
[SPEAKER_07]: I understand that you're busy, like, interviewing people because they keep stealing people out of your department, but, you know, I would like to know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm gonna live.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, fuck you drivers because there are so many bad drivers out there that are not paying attention.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even though most of them seem to be women.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, ow!
[SPEAKER_07]: Nelly gives an F you to me for saying that, and she also gives an F you to me for playing with my Legos.
[SPEAKER_07]: And F you to the lack of pie from her.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd like to give an F you to the local pizza places for not being open today.
[SPEAKER_08]: I realize that it's Easter and it's a religious holiday and people are spending time with their families and yada yada, but I put in my time with my family this morning.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: You pizza people can do that too.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's putting your time in the morning and then be there to make me a pizza in the evening because I'm lazy and I don't cook.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not even on Easter.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also an F you to the fact that I did not get a single piece of candy today being Easter.
[SPEAKER_08]: I went the whole day without a single... F you to not getting two pieces of candy today on Easter.
[SPEAKER_08]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nelly did give me a peanut butter cup.
[SPEAKER_08]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: An F you to myself for being a forgetful jerk and making myself sound like an ass on the radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: One more.
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to Rob for making me play the dancing game.
[SPEAKER_07]: and Get Tired, because I'm out of shape.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait until the picture shows up in the paper, then you can give me an FU.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I would like to give an FU to... An FU to having to wait to find out if I'm going to get this new apartment or not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I don't like waiting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Waiting sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's go on to other folks and their FUs.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll start it off with DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_04]: FU to not being able to find my expansion discs for Final Fantasy XI because, I don't know, I just want to install it all at once and then, you know, do that massive patch download and then just play.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to, you know, have to find the discs later and install them and crap because no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that means more downloading patches later and I'd rather just do it all at once.
[SPEAKER_04]: FU to running out of spring break because I want more but,
[SPEAKER_04]: I have school this week, so damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm going to not play DDR more because I really lost my stamina and I really want it back, so that means I'm going to play more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: More to come later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does Dan the Man have any FUs?
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's hear some FUs from Dan the Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can we get Dan the Man to mic?
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: FUs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you have any FUs of the week, Dan the Man?
[SPEAKER_00]: Not few to me.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm addicted to Lumines.
[SPEAKER_00]: An F you to Rob for making me look away from Lumines to answer this question.
[SPEAKER_00]: And an F you to Sony for shoddy quality control and dead pixels.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fix the fucking problem!
[SPEAKER_00]: Fix it!
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Back to my game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get to chatroom FUs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Legend of Zaku says, F you to not being able to find a Konami 2DX controller, new or used, for around $50 to $60.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's part of the problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to Old Man Winter for making it the coldest winter ever for New York.
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to my ever so shitty stamina for holding me back from playing 9-footers in DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: And F you to sucking horribly at playing 2DX in the arcades.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dark Tetsuya says, a continued FU to G4 for killing off the screensavers.
[SPEAKER_08]: An FU to whatever corrupted my extreme US data several months of work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dark Knight says, my FU goes to my job for opening on Easter Sunday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Know that the rest of the mall was closed, so we were the only store in the mall open today and it was slow.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ 100 Matt says, F you not being able to get into the anime convention in Arizona.
[SPEAKER_08]: It turns out they only let 850 people in, thus shutting out hundreds of anime fans.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, that is poor planning.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would have been pissed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shame, shame.
[SPEAKER_07]: Real quick, I'd like to give an F you to see herpes.
[SPEAKER_19]: I just see herpes.
[SPEAKER_08]: If herpes is coming from lobsters, quit ruining the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: SS2100Matt also says, F you to Golfland for closing the arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only day I have off.
[SPEAKER_08]: And for Ivan Drago killing Apollo Creed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gotta love the never-ending Rocky movie marathon on AMC.
[SPEAKER_08]: LemonLimeJump says, F you to websites that don't show up properly in Firefox.
[SPEAKER_08]: BlackDevilerX says F you to the fact that I haven't been able to listen lately F you to the fact that it's Easter and I didn't get any candy at all Are you sure somebody didn't secretly give you a peanut butter cup?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they'll be really ticked off if they hear that
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Tyrant says, F you to Spring Break, being only one week, knowing almost for certain that I won't be qualifying at RDC in San Diego for In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_08]: World of Warcraft taking over my life, 2DX9 style not at my house yet, Electric Avenue not upgrading to 2DX Red, and school.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sephiroth 1215 says, F you for 1 gig memory sticks being so damn expensive, and to Best Buy for still not sending out my Lumines, forcing me to play Metal Gear, which is cool, but can get tiring.
[SPEAKER_08]: and they are telling me that I'm mispronouncing Lumines.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's actually Luminous.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like Lumines better.
[SPEAKER_08]: Luminous.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe it's the French.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like Lumines.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I didn't know it was French, I'd write it as Luminous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not us, it would be F.
[SPEAKER_08]: Illusion says, F you to last week's robot, tomato, tomato.
[SPEAKER_08]: Illusion says, F you to last week's robot, chicken, for sucking all kinds of ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: I swear I didn't laugh even once.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, this last week wasn't nearly as good as the past week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, this week, a rumor from what I heard, because I know they have a segment in there that's called Kill Bunny, and I know they're going to be playing it today because it's Easter, and it's Jesus.
[SPEAKER_07]: as the bride from Kill Bill, Killing the Easter Bunny in Santa Claus.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gotta love that.
[SPEAKER_07]: How you gonna top that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: 11.30 tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're on the East Coast, you gotta TiVo it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, we need to make them pay for those ads, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't help it.
[SPEAKER_08]: The show kicks ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Illusion also says, F you to being sick and missing one day of school.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was so close to getting a perfect attendance certificate, and I didn't get it because of sickness.
[SPEAKER_08]: Agh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, and all your bases are belong to Robotron 2002.
[SPEAKER_08]: MPQ says F you to myself for knowing some obscure kanji that a lot of Japanese people don't when I can't speak any Japanese.
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to Sampling Masters Mega for making a really catchy song that I can't find.
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to that PSP golf game I pre-ordered that doesn't come out until June.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I guess F you to that Stepmania theme for changing the pi that I was looking for.
[SPEAKER_08]: P-I?
[SPEAKER_08]: Pi?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Ranma S says, Fuck you to the Parks Department for canceling our photoshoot in Central Park.
[SPEAKER_08]: Permit my ass, I'm sending Manfe after you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Manfe, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: John Field says, F you to being lazy and not catching up on my schoolwork.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rice, RYC3, says, F you to Planet X slash GameStop for the longest fucking line I've been in at the mall for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: The end.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: And lastly...
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Takuya says, F you for not having a 2DX machine in Virginia.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if I horribly mispronounced your name, my bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Another F you segment bites the dust.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to do a quickie break, and when we come back from this break, we're going to do some Ask Orange Lounge, and then we're going to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, send some questions to Sky in the chat room with any questions you have for us, and we will get to them when we come back from this break, featuring... Huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I already played Lemmings during that few, so we'll do the In the Groove thing later.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll do some Taku, start it off, and we'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_08]: A couple songs, just two songs this break.
[SPEAKER_08]: With Ask Orange Lounge, we'll be back.
Thanks for watching!
DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_19]: And in the midst of all these troubled comics...
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ask Orange Lounge
[SPEAKER_08]: Me putting in the chatroom how you ask questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: But somebody will fill you in.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have some nice people in chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_08]: What will we find out tonight on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_08]: Something people want to know is will we tone it down because we got nominated Broadcaster of the Year and my answer is HELL NO!
[SPEAKER_07]: No, seriously, somebody was... And for those who want to know, yes, the song is supposed to suck that bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody in chat actually asked me, are you guys toning it down tonight because of the Broadcaster of the Year thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm like, no, we're just kind of, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the ham, the sedatives in the ham.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, actually, I think it is because we've all eaten really well today.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even though we did not get pie, we ate very well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, Nelly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't make pouty face.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've all eaten very well, so I think we're just a little happier today.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nelly has... Please put that on camera.
[SPEAKER_08]: OrangeSongsRadio.com Nelly will be showing her LEGO creations there on cam.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have a lot of freaking questions to get to in very little time, so let's get to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Takuya says, What are your thoughts on the flyer announcing 2DX12 Happy Sky?
[SPEAKER_08]: My thought is I like the name.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, um, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just a flyer.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't really start forming opinions until I see, like, some more screenshots and some song titles.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's my opinion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anybody else care to interject?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to say, I love the flyer so far.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just hope the timing on the flyer is still pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only kickass about that flyer is so goddamn versatile.
[SPEAKER_07]: Paper Wad, Paper Airplane, little, like, you know, Pac-Man thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Takuya also wants to know, what do you think is the future of 2DX for the console with PS3 looming in the future?
[SPEAKER_08]: Any thoughts on that, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even want to think about the future systems until I actually have something tangible on them.
[SPEAKER_02]: So speculation, I'm not going to.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Dan the Man.
[SPEAKER_00]: And remember, generally the Bimani games are real slow to adapt to new hardware.
[SPEAKER_00]: Since the PS3 will be backwards compatible...
[SPEAKER_00]: Unless they do something crazy go nuts with the arcade version, you can probably expect to see it playable on PS2 for a good long time until they absolutely have to start making it for PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's go to a question from BlackDevilerX.
[SPEAKER_08]: What piece is Loki missing?
[SPEAKER_08]: I downloaded the zip from the site and noticed that I have a lot of the special pieces.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe he can describe it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't want to hear what special pieces Loki's missing from his list.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, how is the Lego construction going over there?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the one that looks like a seat, and I'm on step four right now, because I've started running out of black pieces.
[SPEAKER_08]: And again, for those that tuned in late tonight's show, Loki is building a charger for the Nintendo DS out of Legos, and that's something that's actually on the website over at www.orangenautoradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a question for anyone in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: How do I freaking download streaming movies as to permanently non-streaming, like recording them?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's driving me nuts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Send a private message over to DarkSakura if you know the answer.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure she'll appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: She'll love you forever and ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or send us a copy of the Star Wars 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or send me a freaking non-streaming copy of that new video.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see...
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, yes, Loki, comment on episode 3 trailer since it came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is a downloadable version out there, you just have to find it because I have it on my computer at work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: RPGKing7, RPGKing7 wants to know, my question is for everyone in studio and in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can anyone give me any good cosplay websites, please?
[SPEAKER_08]: I was asked for a job interview I have to cosplay a favorite movie character.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a hell of an interview, I've got to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: But okay, good cosplay tips.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, who's your favorite movie character?
[SPEAKER_02]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go to the thrift store.
[SPEAKER_02]: Modify.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the question is about cosplay websites.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are there any good cosplay websites that might have tips?
[SPEAKER_08]: Cosplay.com?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there really one?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or you can order some of those cosplay magazines that they have.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you know any of the names of any of them?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's also, I think, Cospa.net or .co.jp is C-O-S-P-A.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a Japanese cosplay site.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they have individual pieces there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can see what they look like.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully some folks in the chat room can help out with that, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, you can sometimes find costume pieces on eBay.
[SPEAKER_08]: They sell everything on eBay.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, any help with the cosplay question?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I need it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's what I thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good luck, bud.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get that job.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're going to dress up as a movie character, dress up as... What did they call her?
[SPEAKER_08]: What was the name of the diva from the fifth element?
[SPEAKER_02]: The blue... The diva.
[SPEAKER_08]: The diva?
[SPEAKER_08]: Was that just her name?
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought she had a name.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dress up as her.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Illusion.
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard a rumor that DJ Potatoes Company will be publishing the next frequency game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you heard anything about this?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think there is a company.
[SPEAKER_08]: The closest thing I think you might be thinking of is Neon FM, and the reason why it might be getting mixed up with frequency is because Freeze Pop is showing up in Neon FM.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can look at the website neonfm.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I don't know of any frequency amplitude thing that he's involved with.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I guess anything's possible, but a rumor's a rumor as far as I'm concerned.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, do you have anything you want to add to that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I honestly didn't know he had a company.
[SPEAKER_07]: Prava Laguna was the name of the D.Va.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100Matt What's a good price to whore yourself?
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll answer just about anything on here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I spent all my money on the PSP this week and I need money slash zenny slash gil.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you going to get Gil by being a whore?
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you going to whore out your character in Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_08]: I've actually seen people do this in Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_08]: They play the little Taru characters, and then they'll say, We'll do the panic dance for 100 Gil.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't whore yourself for a PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not worth it.
[SPEAKER_08]: PSPs are nice and all, but don't whore yourself for one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Totally worth it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whore yourself out.
[SPEAKER_08]: A buck a pop if you have to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get a PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's the standard?
[SPEAKER_08]: 50 for a BJ?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's inflation.
[SPEAKER_08]: 50 for an HJ, 100 for a BJ.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sucky, fucky, five bucky.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just...
[SPEAKER_08]: Go on the internet and answer a personal ad from a sugar daddy or a sugar mommy, maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: You might even be able to find an old lady sugar mommy, depending on what you're into.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then you can get anything you want just by putting out.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you only have to put out for one person.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if it is a sugar mommy, chances are she doesn't have the organs to reproduce anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've stopped working a while ago, so you might luck out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why did I answer that question?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm an idiot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, we've got a lot of questions tonight, so I'm trying to get through some of them here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jaded2005 wants to know, my girlfriend who is listening wants to know, hi girlfriend who's listening, wants to know how did you come up with your name?
[SPEAKER_08]: How did we come up with the Orange Launch Radio name?
[SPEAKER_02]: Guilty!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, DarkSakura, how did that work?
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, DDR Freak Radio was taken, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were trying to think of Bimani-sounding station names, and Orange Lounge came out just because of lounge music, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we were bored on the part.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: People think that we're our lounge music station, like we sit here and we play lounge music, and don't get me wrong, lounge music's pretty rad, but we're actually video game radio, so it kind of throws people, they're like, whoa, I was expecting lounge music, what's this geeky stuff?
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish we had a more interesting story than that, but that's really just it, we just picked a Bomani-related name for our show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe we can fit in one more question.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll do it from Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_08]: And sorry to those of you guys that also submitted questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: We didn't get to them tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I apologize.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll get to them next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send them in later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Legend of Zaku wants to know, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: Now that you're moving, and Orange Lounge Radio might have its own room, how do you plan to design it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you going to use a ferret theme?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe, you know what I should do?
[SPEAKER_08]: This would be a great idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: Allow the listeners to send us decorations.
[SPEAKER_08]: That way, I don't have to worry about it, and people buy me stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's an excellent idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, the listeners will be decorating the walls of the new studio.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll give you guys details on that later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, yes, actually, the ferret will be hanging from a noose on the ceiling.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just high enough so that Dark Sakura can't reach it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, that's gonna do it for tonight's Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you guys very much for submitting your questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's just about it for tonight's show, you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're just about out of time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks so much for tuning in tonight and listening.
[SPEAKER_08]: We hope you had a good time.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're gonna go around now and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR Angel, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: More DDR this week, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can do it on my own, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dan the Man, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bust Kill Brain.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: My final thought is I'm running out of black pieces.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's almost done!
[SPEAKER_08]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought is I'm really craving a marshmallow peep right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: And no, I'm not going to microwave it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, and I get to touch the PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, so hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to sit over here and oogle.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where are my lasers at?
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're forgetting somebody.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you guys for tuning in tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next week, more randomness here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some more segments.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully we're going to be doing another giveaway next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also talking about the latest news and what's going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to try and get some different special guests next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're trying to line up some special guests for next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Should be a good show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Come back on for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can't tell you what we got though until everything's confirmed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also coming to the station very soon, some big changes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know we've been saying that for the past two months, but we're really serious.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we'll let you know about that when time gets closer.
[SPEAKER_08]: But for the meantime, I have a PSP to play.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we've got to end this.
[SPEAKER_08]: So the final word of the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nelly, one word.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sum it all up.
[SPEAKER_16]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_16]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_18]: and now I'm happier this way yeah I knew I'd miss her so I had to keep her she's buried right in my backyard that's right folks she's buried right in
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you very much for listening and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, for those of you guys that are requesting songs, I'm so sorry, but we don't have time because we have to get to taping our podcast for tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are updating our Bomani Music & More program, though, to include some of those In The Groove songs you guys have been asking about, and as well as some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lots of big variety coming to the station soon, so please check out our Bomani Music & More program, which runs 24 hours a day, 7 days a week on this station when we're not here.
[SPEAKER_08]: But for now, we're signing off for tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Please reconnect to the station.