[SPEAKER_25]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format
Oh, God.
Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_22]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_22]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_22]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_22]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_22]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_22]: And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are live, and this is episode number 135 for this March the 13th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're tuned in to the B-Money Scenes, most last minute radio station of all things gaming and the money.
[SPEAKER_03]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts,
[SPEAKER_03]: In this corner, say hello to the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now lung-free.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, no lung butter this week.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, some, but I'm mostly better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: And in this corner, saving our sound at the last second here tonight, we are having some major sound issues just 30 seconds ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hello to Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, and also joining us tonight...
[SPEAKER_03]: A veteran of our program, a veteran guest, she's been down in the trenches and she knows how to butter the host of the show up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hello to DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it should be another fun-filled show tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got, you know, all the regular stuff you like to hear.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our weeks, our day, cage match, and who knows what else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Possibly some Bomani news and all that fun stuff as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: We will get into that when we come back from a quick break.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this break, I don't really have an idea for music that I want to hear in particular.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think we'll just kind of do some Bomani randomness.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll start it off with some Thomas Howard Lichtenstein.
[SPEAKER_03]: La Senorita, we'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_11]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_11]: Feeling good over you, like you knew she would When she smiles, it's like the sun's shining on your face Falling and stretching, the land of the lame And she's a hot one, California, hula señorita California, hula señorita, hula señorita
I was the happiest guy, that's what everyone said
Thank you for watching.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whoops, we didn't have another song queued up there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were trying to queue up one more song and made a little bit of a mistake there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It happens, you know, stuff happens.
[SPEAKER_19]: So Ballad For You was a mistake.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Ballad For You was not a mistake.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just like this next song, The Torture Will Continue Here with Thomas Howard.
[SPEAKER_03]: One more song, we'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Such a special day
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio, Bomani Music, and more.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, we are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hope you enjoyed that break full of Thomas Howard.
[SPEAKER_19]: He's named after a small country in Europe.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_19]: If they hate us so much, why are they listening?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they know the next break will be something decent.
[SPEAKER_03]: We play things from the entire Bomani spectrum.
[SPEAKER_19]: It'll be a break of nothing, but I love that feeling.
[SPEAKER_02]: Little do they realize it's the Thomas Howard show today, and they won't be getting anything else.
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear to God, I will be playing Forever Sunshine next break.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: Play the song and I will kill you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's actually damn good reason to be playing Forever Sunshine next break.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'll get into that later.
[SPEAKER_19]: I will kill you with a ferret.
[SPEAKER_19]: I will kill you in a house.
[SPEAKER_19]: I will kill you with a mouse.
[SPEAKER_03]: Will you kill me in a bus?
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't this like six weeks ago when we got into this Dr. Seuss show?
[SPEAKER_17]: Dr. Redfish Bluefish and you got a deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Would you piss on a train?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, I was going to say that I liked El Mullet's statement in our chat room over at www.orangehunterradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: El Mullet says, I love this station.
[SPEAKER_03]: Giving the fans what they don't want.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's us.
[SPEAKER_03]: F.E.A.T.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mania FM
[SPEAKER_03]: I only played once this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually played DDR today.
[SPEAKER_03]: Granted, I was playing Controller on Ultramix 2 on Xbox Live, but I was actually having fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'll get into that later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's start off tonight's show as we always do, playing a little bit of How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day, starting off with the lovely DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_19]: I spent the whole week on codeine.
[SPEAKER_19]: I went to the doctor, and he gave me some lovely drugs, except I misread the label in my sickness and read teaspoon as tablespoon.
[SPEAKER_19]: So all Monday at work I was taking this
[SPEAKER_19]: with codeine syrup at basically triple doses four times a day.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was high as a kite and feeling a little pain.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was very happy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember, kids, drugs are bad.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But... It's not endorsed drug use.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_19]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_03]: We do endorse burping off the... You endorse recreational Waltussin use?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't take Waltussin anymore.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's got sugar in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_19]: But they make sugar-free cola.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why things that aren't usually funny are funny tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe I'm high on codeine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You sound like you're still coughing up a little bit of lung butter over there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, but it's a good thing because I have a voice finally.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_19]: I could sing with my CD player today, it was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tonight you don't sound like Grandma Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_19]: I got a pair of three.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sure did.
[SPEAKER_19]: But, you know, the week was pretty much normal crap.
[SPEAKER_19]: I, of course, didn't go to the gym, but I did go yesterday.
[SPEAKER_19]: I went to spin class.
[SPEAKER_19]: and I was very sad because the teacher who I wanted to teach a spin class wasn't teaching it because she might be sick with other issues and so I'm really worried.
[SPEAKER_03]: But my friend... I just ferreted Jamie's laptop.
[SPEAKER_19]: You touch the precious and you die.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_19]: You go to hell and you die!
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob just picked his nose.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did not pick my nose, I scratched my nose.
[SPEAKER_03]: If the webcam phased over here, I'd demand an instant replay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, too bad that you'd have to be picking your nose for like a minute straight for that to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, you really did futz with that mic.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's good and loud now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I tell you, it's probably just because pulling chords out over the audio board there
[SPEAKER_02]: Every now and then a cord gets stuck on a knob, and then, you know, the knob turns, and then the audio gets all fucked up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Needs to be, like, in a glass case or something.
[SPEAKER_17]: Loki has his magic gummy bears again.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dun-dun-dun!
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, if you guys were listening to the podcast this last week, Loki was, like, turned down to, like, 20% level or something, but it was pleasant, because his anger was subdued.
[SPEAKER_19]: You don't like subduing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: I keep interrupting you.
[SPEAKER_19]: I still have to tell you about my damn week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is why... For those people wondering why this segment takes so damn long, this is why right here.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's called We Digress.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_19]: I hung out with my friend Melody yesterday who is not Shark's girl.
[SPEAKER_19]: She is a friend of mine who I worked with at the evil student loan company.
[SPEAKER_19]: And she...
[SPEAKER_19]: Met her fiancé through work, and he lives in Delaware, so she's moving to Delaware next month.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're in Delaware!
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, knock it off.
[SPEAKER_19]: But anyway, this is the last chance I'd really get to hang out with her, so we went to see Constantine yesterday, which I actually liked.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I've even read a little bit of the Hellblazer comics, so where it was a bit different, I actually liked it as a movie.
[SPEAKER_19]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think that's how I like movies that just totally screw with theology and, you know, that's also, I guess, the reason why I like Angel Sanctuary, too.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway, we saw that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I went to her apartment to meet her cat, Simon.
[SPEAKER_19]: She went to my apartment to meet Shermie.
[SPEAKER_19]: She took two pictures of me and five pictures of Shermie.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway, I took her to meet Dan, and Dan did his stuff he was working.
[SPEAKER_19]: Then we went to Chevy's.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did he manage to sell any ignition pads?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't keep up with that.
[SPEAKER_19]: He's off to an inventory tonight.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: But we went to Chevy's, and then went to Cheesecake Factory.
[SPEAKER_19]: I decided to make yesterday my cheat day.
[SPEAKER_19]: So the box of Samoas is going to wait until my birthday, because that's my next cheat day.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm having two cheat days next month.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, then we went back, um, and Dan came home when we were hanging out at my place because I was burning off a copy of Battle Royale for her.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, and, uh, we watched The Ring and, uh, the part of, uh, An Evening with Kevin Smith.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't The Ring 2 out this week?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, this Friday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_19]: Holy shit, I have to go.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because,
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm looking to see, I want to see because I heard they were trying to incorporate some stuff from the books and I really like the books over the movies because the books go in such a completely different direction which I kind of wish the movies had but it would not have been realistic so I'm really curious and otherwise today's been kind of oh yeah today I actually was outside taking pictures of nature
[SPEAKER_19]: Because for my Photoshop class, I have to do a composite of three pictures into a fantasy setting.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I've got one of a bridge and two other ones.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to play with them.
[SPEAKER_19]: I got my pictures from Alabama developed.
[SPEAKER_19]: I managed to spend $75 at Walgreens.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do they let you do digital photography in photo classes now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because when I was in college, you had to use the old cameras.
[SPEAKER_19]: This isn't a photo class.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is Photoshop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_19]: And he doesn't care how we get him as long as we get him.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got you.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um... But... That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I got to hang out with Dan and Julie today.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then Dan had to go to work and I went back home.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_19]: I like fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's it for your week and your day.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't do much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just, um, played Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um, Attic.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else did I do?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know there was other crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, I went and saw, um, what was it, uh, Robots yesterday.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was free.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a lot of popcorn.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that was all good.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, um, yesterday we watched, um, SpongeBob SquarePants.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a goopy goober, yeah You're a goopy goober, yeah That movie was so random, it's just...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I was kind of a fan of SpongeBob SquarePants before, but now, like, oh my god, he's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: I can safely say I've never, ever, ever, ever seen any.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to see the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: And Blackout refused to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, I hate SpongeBob SquarePants, but the movie was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I liked the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I find Spongebob Squarepants to be completely retarded and just annoying.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the movie was just, it was so different from the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was kind of weird, because it was actually, you know, very random, sort of like... It was what Nellie said, it was a stoner movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a stoner movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just like, and it was like, they had so many homosexual innuendos in that movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, especially the ending, where they do like a kiss type ending.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if there was a Kiss movie, I'm sure there was.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's totally the Kiss ending, and then Patrick is wearing fishnet stockings.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, and stilettos.
[SPEAKER_02]: And stilettos.
[SPEAKER_03]: And stripper boots.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, it was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just completely different.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then earlier in the week I had watched White Noise.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that movie was, yeah, it was weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just so gonna... It just, like, had an ending that made no sense in that movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, you're leading up, you find there's this guy, you know, and there's these three ghosts that have been killing people, and then, you know, the resolution to the movie, the ghosts break every bone in this guy's body and throw him off a building.
[SPEAKER_02]: The end.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, oh, gee, thanks!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Will sell soul for Gil
[SPEAKER_02]: I just did nothing, like usual.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still waiting for my damn interview for the game sales position.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still waiting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Angel, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, before we get into that, I actually got a clip.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, Angel.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got a clip of that song, Girls Butts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Miklatov somehow had it, and he sent it over to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Aw yeah!
[SPEAKER_08]: Aw yeah!
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish this week never existed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish it never existed.
[SPEAKER_17]: Monday through Wednesday was just fine.
[SPEAKER_17]: And all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: Went to school and worked a little and just all that other stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then Thursday was school.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then I come to find out when I come home as soon as I sat down for my computer.
[SPEAKER_17]: that my friend had passed away and it's one of the guys that I knew two years in the DJ field you know on the radio and stuff and let's just say since Thursday it's been kind of a screwed up four days and sleep's been a joke and just you know
[SPEAKER_17]: Me and my other friends have been hanging around there and just comforting each other and just you know stuff that you need to do when somebody passes away and just I haven't felt this much like
[SPEAKER_17]: I just had a really hard week or at least the last four days.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's getting better, but, you know, there's just little things that remind you of this, you know, somebody, like, you'll be walking down the street and you'll see somebody wear a shirt, and that shirt, like, reminds you of the person that you just lost, and just little stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_17]: And so, yeah, I've been grieving all week, except for the first three days of the week, so it's been pretty shitty week.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I really don't really want to think about it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyway, that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry to hear about it, and I hope things get better for you and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, how the hell do I follow that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Angel?
[SPEAKER_17]: Being here helps.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we should play the Girls Butts songs again.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, jeez.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, maybe if I play the Girls Butts song again, Angel will feel a little better.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Did Girls Butts get rid of your cough?
[SPEAKER_19]: I guess so, wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Girls Butts has healed me!
[SPEAKER_01]: I felt the power of the Girls Butts!
[SPEAKER_01]: Praise the Lord!
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my God, this song cures cancer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't tell me that Orange Lounge doesn't better your life, everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: My week and my day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shit, what did I do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing that exciting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also watched the SpongeBob SquarePants movie Friday night, which I thought was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also watched this other movie last night, which was very odd.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was called The Final Cut.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Cut with Robin Williams.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which, I'd never heard of this movie in theaters.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was very limited.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very, very, very limited, apparently.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, there was that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought that movie was very... Well, obviously, it's not what you'd expect from a Robin Williams movie, because it was very dark.
[SPEAKER_17]: He also did the one-hour photo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: That one's weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, all sorts of, like, very unsettling movies there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, yeah, it was different.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I liked it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a thought-provoking movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: It kind of made you go, hmm, that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Friday night I went out to the bar, and it was cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because there was this guy that thought it was cool that I played games, so we talked for a little while.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was weird, though, because he's not... He's kind of...
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a big Nintendo supporter.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I had to talk to him about why I believe the GameCube is awesome and all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it was interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And outside of that, you know, just same old stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Went out to karaoke earlier this week because I'm a total karaoke whore.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I went twice this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what a big karaoke whore I am.
[SPEAKER_03]: I went on Monday night when it's not the usual karaoke guy that I'm used to.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just wasn't the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: It really wasn't the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to get into another break here.
[SPEAKER_03]: and in this break we're going to play two songs and these two songs have something in common and I'll talk about what these songs have in common when we come back after this you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio and we'll be back
Thank you for watching!
DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: Music, Music, Music, Music, Music,
[SPEAKER_03]: Those two songs have something in common.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you haven't figured it out yet, we'll play two more songs that should give you a little bit of a hint.
I didn't notice the light with this beam Fly away to fantasy Feeling the insolence Until we reach eternity
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you feel it?
[SPEAKER_22]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: You can feel it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, what happens to you if you don't listen to it again?
[SPEAKER_18]: I... what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, wait, what's this crazy bitch doing coming out of my computer screen?
[SPEAKER_22]: Orange Lounge Radio, listen or die!
[SPEAKER_03]: We haven't had an excuse to play that one in a while, but since you guys were talking about, you know, The Ring 2 coming out soon, and you talking about, you know, you watching The Ring this week and stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can totally see up my nose in this picture.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that makes for great radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Dan's smile.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's like, ah.
[SPEAKER_03]: He looks like Spongebob did in that movie when he got all happy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Do not compare my man to Spongebob.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so if you didn't figure it out, Forever Sunshine and Regret, a song from Keyboard Mania that we played in there, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: You may not have recognized that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are two songs that are assumably in the next song pack.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, we haven't heard anything official yet, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: So people are just pretty much assuming they've got them right.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Regret and Forever Sunshine, two of the songs that are going to be in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we'll play some of the other songs a little bit more later.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, I Feel the Junk, Circuit Mix, and More Deep were songs that were in the last song pack.
[SPEAKER_03]: So a little hint for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yes, boys and girls, you get to download Forever Sunshine in the next song pack for DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Doesn't that make you excited?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_19]: We.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now,
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, wow, you're really quiet right now, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is Rob on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, tell me about Forever Sunshine being in the next song pack.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you mean tell you about it?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's there, and it's awesome, and everybody who hates it should just go and die.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did you put, why Forever Sunshine?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this your fault?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you do this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's my fault.
[SPEAKER_03]: How is this your fault?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I picked a whole bunch of songs that I personally like.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't care if the other people liked them or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like Forever Sunshine, and like Follow Laika, That's All Me Right There, OGC, Regret.
[SPEAKER_07]: Those are songs I like, and I was like, well, they'd be cool for DDR, so I suggested them.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Forever Sunshine was already in DDR, and it sucks!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, well, it was that, or you could have let them move.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd almost rather have let them move.
[SPEAKER_03]: Would it be like a junk circuit mix?
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't count now, do you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess not.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm mad at you.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can take it out on me by hitting me at E3 when you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, are we going to expect to see crappy songs that you picked in the next song pack?
[SPEAKER_07]: Heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if you remember way back when Ultramix 2 was done and they started announcing stuff about song packs, one of the other Vivid members
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, any choice words for Sigurd?
[SPEAKER_03]: Dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, any choice words for Sigurd on his selection of Forever Sunshine?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I already have that stupid song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Inceptmania.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not buying no fucking song pack, nor am I getting Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't even have an Xbox, so you don't count.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I have an Xbox shell.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um,
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, hello?
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's pick Forever Sunshine, because that's so much better than... I can't hear Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_03]: What, Sigurd?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I was saying, what's cooler than Forever Sunshine?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can stay $5 for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should still privilege.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, how about every other Bomani song in existence is cooler than Forever Sunshine?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have an idea!
[SPEAKER_02]: Forever Sunshine rocks!
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's just get that, because, you know, songs like The Fall, or Hellscraper, or, I don't know, whatever else we can put out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, maybe anything that's in 2DX, you know, Ted Style, or anything below that, or, I don't know, Beat Manium, you know, all those songs suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_07]: One song that's appeared in only one mix, you know, just appear out of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got 2DX songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't need more 2DX songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're done with 2DX.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why I take songs from Keyboard Mania and Drum Mania and one-time uses in DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sigurd, I have a question for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you like the Muppets?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, because Forever Sunshine sounds like Miss Piggy singing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you know that Malcolm in the Middle guy sounds like Kermit now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is the Rainbow Connection going to be in the next song pack?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I'm curious about.
[SPEAKER_07]: The what?
[SPEAKER_03]: The Rainbow Connection.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, forget it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_03]: My insults are lost on you.
[SPEAKER_07]: They really are.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well thanks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else you want to share with our listeners, Seeger, before I hang up on you out of pure anger?
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess they should just learn to deal with what they're given.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They should shut up and quit being like DDR freaks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I'm gonna let you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm still mad at him.
[SPEAKER_03]: Forever Sunshine and DDR, what the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's people like him that come up with wonderful ideas like stealing the karaoke revolution songs and put them in DDR extreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I, speaking of Karaoke Revolution and Bomani, you know what I, like, was announced like a month ago and I completely forgot to mention on this program until just right now?
[SPEAKER_03]: That Bomani Karaoke Revolution game got cancelled.
[SPEAKER_03]: So those of you guys that wanted to sing at Love Shine, sing Love Shine at home and stuff, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: No karaoke for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I saw, um,
[SPEAKER_02]: The Forever Sunshine was in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I guess Forever Sunshine was in the next Karaoke Revolution game, the Mamani one, and so they had to cancel it because they realized that that sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: They couldn't put Forever Sunshine in there because, I don't know, it just sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had something there, but it just went away.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to eat more gummy bears.
[SPEAKER_03]: Out of curiosity, you started off last week with a five pound bag of gummy bears.
[SPEAKER_03]: How many pounds are left?
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably like a pound and a half.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a lot of gummy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I helped, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did help.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have about a pound left.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was offering gummy bears to people.
[SPEAKER_03]: I said, hi, I know these are my roommates, but you want some gummy bears?
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll get more.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Dance Mania Speed G4 has been announced.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I have issues with this already.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there's G4 in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's the name of the album is Dance Mania Speed G4.
[SPEAKER_03]: And how appropriate that it should be named that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get songs like Toxic, the Trance Speedo mix by Helen.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you get other songs like Let's Groove by Beatbox featuring DJ Speedo.
[SPEAKER_03]: and a song called Wookiee Wookiee by Jenny Rom.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Piano Concerto No.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1 in B-flat minor by Speedmaster.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's like they're mixing that classical speed thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Speedmaster!
[SPEAKER_03]: And how can we forget Hostile Takeover, the B4 is a beat mix?
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotta love that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, this has got to be the coolest thing that's on there, Theme from Miami Vice by The Extra Terror Sound.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's a speed version, so I don't know what to expect from that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, Smoke on the Water, that's worth mentioning.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys will want to check out the full song list.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is posted to our website, www.orangelongeradio.com But you know what's even cooler?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what else is coming out soon?
[SPEAKER_02]: Airwolf Season 1 on DVD.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what Dance Mania Speed G4 doesn't have that Airwolf has?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: A fucking kick-ass helicopter, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that I've successfully... I have one helicopter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but you don't have a cool helicopter like... I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was like Thunder in Paradise, but in the air.
[SPEAKER_19]: But I have a Humvee.
[SPEAKER_02]: And without, you know... Hulk Hogan.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh my god, I had the coolest dream.
[SPEAKER_19]: I dreamt I really had a Humvee with a missile turret on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what were you doing with it?
[SPEAKER_19]: It was just my normal car.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you were in, I don't know, Cruisin' World?
[SPEAKER_19]: I think it was Cruisin' World.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wasn't it that had the Humvee?
[SPEAKER_19]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: I used to always use the three-wheeled truck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, other Bomani news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_19]: School Bus!
[SPEAKER_03]: You know DDR Freak?
[SPEAKER_03]: You've ever heard of that website?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not sure if you've heard of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know it's a site.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know they actually syndicate our program on Friday nights over on DDR Freak Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't know if you've heard of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Check them out someday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we should.
[SPEAKER_03]: DDRFreak.com turned five years old this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Five years old.
[SPEAKER_03]: How old does that make you feel?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I remember when DDR Freak did not look like it did today.
[SPEAKER_03]: It didn't even have the same address and everything.
[SPEAKER_19]: I remember it being green.
[SPEAKER_02]: And did it have the same bad grammar that we've learned to come in love?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, indeed.
[SPEAKER_19]: I remember having the biggest post count back in the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: What happened with that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is it that you had the biggest post count?
[SPEAKER_19]: Because I don't really post that much.
[SPEAKER_19]: I just watch threads now, that's all I do.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, this is stupid.
[SPEAKER_19]: No flames here, moving on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Nothing to see here.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can't lock a thread for being too stupid, but it has to be pointlessly stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I thought maybe we could go around and kind of talk about the first time we visited DDR Freak and what we thought of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I read, this is a tribute, by the way, to DDR Freak Turning 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: I read the, what was it, DDR USA, the manual, and in the back there was a special thanks to DDRFreak.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how I first found the website.
[SPEAKER_02]: To which then I first found the regional forums, to which I found the link to Sakpamani.
[SPEAKER_02]: All links to the DDR USA manual.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, there are people that actually read that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I was that bored.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was gonna say, that's like tiny-ass print in the back of the manual there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was that bored.
[SPEAKER_03]: So on your first visit to DDR Freak, you learned about the locals here, so that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, your first visit to DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_19]: This had to have been... It was right before AX2000.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, actually right around the time of AX2000, because I was just getting into a lot of it, I was looking for more people who play, and I just started posting there, found people who had other interests, and then I randomly made the Sacramentals thread on DDR Freak and...
[SPEAKER_03]: And oh my god, did we get yelled at in that thread?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we were random.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'll tell you what, it was nothing compared to the random chat you see today on DDR Free.
[SPEAKER_19]: But man, people were like, you guys are losers, right?
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: They didn't want to see it.
[SPEAKER_19]: They didn't have to click that thread.
[SPEAKER_03]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_03]: How'd you end up becoming a moderator over there?
[SPEAKER_19]: Because I was a good babysitter.
[SPEAKER_19]: I had this habit of insinuating myself between people's arguments just because I didn't want to see all the crap.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I posted so much I was available.
[SPEAKER_19]: This was when I was working at GNC.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was available all the time and posted all the time.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I had pretty good people skills, so I got offered the position.
[SPEAKER_19]: Right as my cable went down.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, but it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: I still like doing it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I kind of...
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and I do remember the boards were green and I remember a lot of people that were posting were all in the Bay Area and they were talking about the songs they were playing and passing and the freestyle stuff and I was just kind of like these guys are sick, obsessive little freaks which is really funny in retrospect that I thought that
[SPEAKER_03]: But then I lurked for a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I lurked for probably a good two months.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember when I was lurking, they were not using a PHP board.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were using some other type of web board when I first was looking at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was lurking at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then when they did the PHP board, I think that's when I finally signed up.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's not the same one that we know now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, there was another board in between.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's when I signed up and stopped lurking.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was probably about the same time as that Sacramentals thread.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I remember us all taking that trip to the Bay Area to play Parapara for the first time.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was really fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that was my first DDR Freak experience.
[SPEAKER_03]: Angel, do you remember?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Unfortunately, I was the late bloomer out of all of you guys.
[SPEAKER_17]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually I'll blame it on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, probably around 2002 or so, so, you know, like I said, I was a late bloomer out of all of you guys, but, uh, it's pretty cool, I still pretty, I don't do the forums, you know, as far as posting is concerned, because someone took my name, so, you know, and I can't think of anything else that's cool, so, um, you know, because my handle's my handle.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, I just, you know, look and, uh, read stuff, but other than that, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Happy birthday to you folks there at DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're turning five years old.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now you all can be placed in kindergarten.
[SPEAKER_03]: So maybe you'll learn something.
[SPEAKER_03]: But man, that just kind of shows how long DDR itself has been around.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very interesting too to go to DDR Freak and look at the headlines and they're all about in the groove.
[SPEAKER_03]: It kind of shows you where this thing's going.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's take another quick break, and when we come back from this break, we're going to get into the Orange Launch Radio Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe we'll do ourselves a list list tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: We haven't done one of those in a while, and I have a good idea for a topic.
[SPEAKER_19]: That sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll do that, and we'll also open up the Skype line for those of you guys that want to call in.
[SPEAKER_03]: So in this break, you get some Bomani Potpourri.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's really no rhyme or reason why we're playing these songs, we just want to hear them.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dream a dream together, a dream that is real
One, two, three, four!
I love you
Come on, come on!
[SPEAKER_24]: Easier to Dance To Than That Freaking Catch-Up Song Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_03]: www.orangeofficer.com
[SPEAKER_03]: House of Wax
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_19]: Which I will not see.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got a call already, so we don't have to worry about Paris Hilton chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Siggy here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm doing... I fell asleep.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just woke up.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you fell asleep and you missed the first part of Orange Lawns Radio?
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, just only, you know, just the first 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know about the best thing that you missed so far?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I didn't miss that, really.
[SPEAKER_20]: I didn't miss that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well then, I guess you really didn't miss anything that good then.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I'm actually kind of glad you called in.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what you called in to talk about, but I got a question for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything new on Night Style?
[SPEAKER_03]: Any new news going on there?
[SPEAKER_20]: I was about to say that, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_20]: We're like-minded.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, we got the latest as of today.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: There was a Tokyo demo held yesterday in Japan.
[SPEAKER_20]: This is what they've said so far about a demo of the Night Style.
[SPEAKER_20]: There was no revival song information was revealed because the demo only had 32 songs and no old songs were revealed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting, so they're trying to keep things secret then.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did any word get out about the timing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you remember when Night Stalk came out in the arcades, people bitched about the timing issues in it, so I'm wondering how that's going to affect the home version.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, according to people who went there, the timing seems to be fine, though a few people have mentioned that it seems tighter than previous versions.
[SPEAKER_20]: Whether it was just due to the environment, like the controller, TV positioning, etc., or was an actual timing difference is unknown.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's true, because if you're playing it at a loud expo, it's probably going to be hard to nail the timing like you usually do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I'd be okay with that if they were tightening up the timing windows a little bit, but just... You know how Night Style in the arcade had this whole different feel to it, probably because of rumors that they had changed some hardware and things like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else going on with Night Style that you know of?
[SPEAKER_20]: Um...
[SPEAKER_20]: Random Plus is said to be there.
[SPEAKER_20]: High Speed 4 is there, so if anybody's worried.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very interesting that we don't know any of the consumer songs yet, considering we're only about, what, two weeks away from release?
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't really know a whole lot about those consumer tracks, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_20]: Speaking of consumer tracks, there are five CS-exclusive songs that have been released recently.
[SPEAKER_20]: Here they are, the genre, and I'll mention the genre, the song, and the artist.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, so these are for Night Style?
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, cool, okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: The genre here is Dance Pop, and it's Usual Days Remix by Otatu.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's 4-star on Light 7, 7-star on 7 Keys.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: And then Ragged Jungle, 5PM Eternal by Garoovee, featuring Nochiin.
[SPEAKER_20]: 5 Star on Light 7, Flashing 7 on 7 Keys.
[SPEAKER_20]: Is that LED and Groovy or just Groovy?
[SPEAKER_20]: Just Groovy.
[SPEAKER_20]: Interesting, okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: And then the genre is Discotheque, 80s Capsule by Megumi Upper Slope, 3 Star on Light 7, 4 Star on 7 Keys.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hmm, okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: Club Jazz, Paramnesia by Ushiroda Shinji, 4 Star on Light 7, 6 Star on 7 Keys.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_20]: And then the fifth song...
[SPEAKER_20]: Which, you know, genre is drum and bass Photogenic by LED featuring Horisawa Maiko
[SPEAKER_20]: Six Star and Light Seven, Seven Star and Seven Keys.
[SPEAKER_20]: Those are the only five songs that have been announced so far.
[SPEAKER_20]: So there are two more.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's more than I knew about already, so that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's good that LED's going to have one in there, because I always like his stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though it all kind of sounds similar, I'm excited to see that's going to be there.
[SPEAKER_20]: Let me send you this link on the website, which is actually a screenshot of the menu select interface of 2DX Nightstyle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's you posting in the chatroom there as DarkLionXVI for those that want to click on that link.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm pulling it up here on my end here on the computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, it pretty much looks like the arcade did a little bit, a little bit condensed down, but I like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a good look.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just like Night Style a whole bunch.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's going to be the one that gets me back into 2DX.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know I said that about 7th and 8th and it didn't work, but Night Style will be the one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will.
[SPEAKER_20]: In case you notice on the picture that there are clear lamps are in there.
[SPEAKER_20]: You know, like the colored markers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you got this song finished.
[SPEAKER_20]: Good.
[SPEAKER_20]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright, anything else?
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_20]: On 9thStyleCS, for those who have played it, Quasar was supposed to have the 10thStyle video in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, right on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you know how Quasar didn't really have, like, it had a generic video on 9thStyle.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, it's a generic video from the background.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope they do give a 10thStyle video.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope that we get a 10thStyle or a Red song in there that crosses over as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be kind of nice, but I guess we don't know anything yet, huh?
[SPEAKER_20]: No, so... Yeah, they still have the folder sorting, you know, like by folders, like by letter, by the level of the difficulty of the song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_20]: They have it, or supposedly have it in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm sure the next two weeks will be busy two weeks for Night Style News, so hopefully we'll have more stuff next week and the week after, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you, as always, for the update, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: Anything else you want to share with the listeners?
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, nothing much to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, thanks for calling in and giving us this update.
[SPEAKER_20]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_20]: Later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Later.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, a bunch of people hammering us trying to get in tonight, so we'll just kind of take the calls as we see them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey Sky, it's El Mullet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello my friend, how are you?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm doing good, how about yourself?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm pretty good, I'm actually kind of glad you called in.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really, how so?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a bone to pick with Inside Pulse.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, now what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was reading the review of Tekken 5 over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, for crying out loud, not this.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the guy was totally dogging on the music, and I'm like, oh my gosh, Tekken 5 has great music in it, I think.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be his opinion.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know it wasn't you.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's all about the moonlight stage.
[SPEAKER_03]: But since you're the closest thing I have to being able to yell at Inside Pulse, I'm yelling at you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, there always is the email link to the person who wrote the review.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sure he would like another flame to add to his collection.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to flame this guy via email.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd rather he call in so I can yell at him in person.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you supposed to say when you argue about somebody with music?
[SPEAKER_03]: Arguing with people about music is something I never understood because it's like, this song sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, what can you, how can you say, you know, people's perception of music, it is totally and purely opinion, really.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, what sounds good to me may not sound good to you, you know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I completely agree with you there, Sky.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like, but if we don't have arguments about music, we wouldn't have any song pack discussion.
[SPEAKER_03]: But one thing we can all agree on is that Forever Sunshine sucks balls.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, I can't agree with you there.
[SPEAKER_12]: I cannot agree with you that it sucks balls.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can tolerate it and enjoy it when I'm in the right mood.
[SPEAKER_12]: I will take forever sunshine on this song pack.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_12]: That needs to be played on every episode of Orange Lounge from here to eternity.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be the new inside joke.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be the new cake pie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so to what do we owe the call?
[SPEAKER_03]: I got you sidetracked there because I wanted to yell at you, but to what do we owe this call tonight, El Mullet?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, we owe this call to, well, song pack discussion.
[SPEAKER_12]: I find it just very interesting to see everybody's dog in Forever Sunshine, whether you like it or not.
[SPEAKER_12]: Everyone's dog in it, and it's like, oh, now this song pack's going to suck because Forever Sunshine's in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well, a song pack doesn't suck if one bad song is in it, because one good song can make a song pack very good, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Exactly, exactly.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's what I'm trying to get across.
[SPEAKER_12]: There are people out there who have labeled the song pack as bad thanks to one song.
[SPEAKER_01]: Worst song pack ever!
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, people labeled song pack 3 bad because as soon as they heard Dynamite Rave was going to be on it before it was even released, Oh no, it's Dynamite Rave!
[SPEAKER_12]: Everyone's played it already!
[SPEAKER_12]: Go away!
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true, and I was one of those people.
[SPEAKER_03]: But at the same time, there were things on Sompac 3 that I was looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_03]: And to be honest, it's not a big surprise either.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, way back in the day when USA Mix was all there was.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, you remember this.
[SPEAKER_03]: How many people would play Dynamite Rave at Golf Land?
[SPEAKER_12]: Everyone.
[SPEAKER_12]: Exactly, exactly.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I'm personally looking forward to this song pack.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm definitely looking forward to the new songs.
[SPEAKER_12]: Jelly Kiss, most definitely.
[SPEAKER_12]: I put together a list a long, long, long time ago that I never released to anybody of what songs I'd like to see on song packs.
[SPEAKER_12]: I put down 19 November, that ended up being on the mix, and Jelly Kiss was the only one so far that actually made it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You got a Santa thing going on there?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or Sana?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sana?
[SPEAKER_12]: I like Sana.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sana's a good group.
[SPEAKER_03]: I totally just did the white boy pronunciation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Santa?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Santa.
[SPEAKER_03]: That Santa Moleste song, what is that about?
[SPEAKER_19]: That's pervy.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's pervy, just wait until Jelly Kiss comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just glad that Ultramix 2 kind of lives on this way through these songpacks still coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I am a little upset that it took so darn long to start getting these songpacks to roll out regularly because there was that hold up with the whole Canadian thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm glad to see the songpacks coming and keeping Ultramix 2 going.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it was all Microsoft's fault here, and as soon as SP8 came out, I'm sure people were dancing in the streets.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, if they were fanboys enough to do so.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I was actually playing Ultramix 2 online today.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was actually playing another Xbox game, and I got an invite over to Ultramix 2 from somebody who is...
[SPEAKER_03]: I think she's the number one Ultramix player and she's like in the top five of Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she's really, really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So she sent me a challenge thing because, you know, we have fun when we play on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I actually played against her and it was cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were just going down the list alphabetically.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was just, you know, we were just going down the list alphabetically and there's so many good songs in Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, I do love that mix.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish I'd played it more.
[SPEAKER_03]: It makes me excited for Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know nothing official has been announced with Ultramix 3, but come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's got to be an Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what else, speaking of Ultramix, I was actually at Best Buy yesterday, and I was looking for a new game to pick up, and I noticed that DDR Ultramix was in Xbox Platinum Hits now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, I saw that the other day.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't even realize that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, that totally came out of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, has that been that way for a long time?
[SPEAKER_19]: I think it's more recent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it more recent?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, just so you guys know, Ultramix is only $20 now because it's a Platinum hit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can get the Platinum hits cover, too, because the cover looks a little different when you're Platinum hits games.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was kind of neat to see.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, so we can now say, no matter what you think of the first Ultramix, guess what?
[SPEAKER_12]: It was successful enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Ultramix 2 is probably destined for the Platinum hits soon enough as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_12]: If Ultramix 1 can make it, then Ultramix 2 should be Platinum by the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, you know, it was interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been really into this website lately for video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's 1up.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if you guys have heard of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1up.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they have a lot of the... It's very fan-oriented where you can have your own blogger and you can have a club.
[SPEAKER_03]: We actually have an Orange Lounge Radio Club over on 1UP.com that Rice Princess started.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'll have to put the link in the chatroom for that for those guys who haven't seen it yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Orange Lounge Radio Club.
[SPEAKER_03]: They also show how games are ranked.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, the ranking for various games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was surprised because I have in every Xbox title that I own and Ultramix 2 was like the lowest ranked one on the list.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was kind of like, that's so sad because it's such a great game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really a gem of a title.
[SPEAKER_12]: It is, but then again, you know, a place like that, when fans come to congregate, it's going to be a lot of the casual fans.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, of course, games like Halo and Gran Turismo and Grand Theft Auto and Metal Gear, they're all going to be in the top ranks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you look at the top three right now, it's Grand Theft Auto San Andreas, Halo 2, and The Legend of Zelda, the brand new one, because of that, you know, trailer that came out this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Legend of Zelda shocked me, but...
[SPEAKER_12]: I saw that.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was a very good trailer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, remember the trailer that came out this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_03]: How many of you guys saw the Zelda trailer this week?
[SPEAKER_19]: I haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to show it to you.
[SPEAKER_19]: I've been busy.
[SPEAKER_03]: After the show tonight, I have to show it to you.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will just make you tingle in places you didn't know could tingle.
[SPEAKER_12]: Two words can describe the trailer.
[SPEAKER_12]: Holy and what's the other one?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, crap.
[SPEAKER_12]: Holy crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: or other various explicitives that you might be able to get.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, of course.
[SPEAKER_12]: Including the omission of bodily functions that I think I'll just stop there on.
[SPEAKER_03]: What, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_19]: Explicitives?
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't you mean expletives?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, expletives.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to add that to the dictionary of Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is why I'm on internet radio, boys and girls, because, you know, these things, I can't get into real radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can never break into real radio because of my pronunciation problems.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, that was a new song by Britney Spears that was toxic here on... You put the wrong emphasis on the wrong syllables, guy.
[SPEAKER_12]: You need to work on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, I'm learning.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else you want to share with us, El Mullet?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, if you see a piece a little down the line on In The Groove on our site, I'll be responsible for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, I can't wait to see that.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's all I'm going to say on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Knowing that you wrote it makes me very excited.
[SPEAKER_12]: What it is and in what capacity, I'm not at liberty to say at this point.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll be looking for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Talk to you later, Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good one, Mullet.
[SPEAKER_03]: You too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, hey, hey, it's Ranma from New York.
[SPEAKER_03]: How you guys doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm doing pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Glad to hear you guys one more time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been telling DarkSakura for a while I had a little surprise for her.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm posting the links now in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to bring them up on the computer over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can get them on your laptop over there, right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I'm looking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I'm putting them in, too, because I want to see what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: So DJ Ranma S is posting this in our chat room over at OrangeLoungeRadio.com, clicking on chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, is that a picture of you, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: And you're kicking an old arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you don't mind, we want to put that in our Orange Lounge Radio photo gallery.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go right ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is rad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we need to start a photo gallery on OrangeLoungeRadio.com of people kicking Ultracade machines.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll even set up an email where you can email your picks.
[SPEAKER_19]: That is awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you'll be the first one in there, buddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, no fair.
[SPEAKER_19]: You have an Alpine Racer 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: I miss that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you ever come to New York, I'll bring it to the arcade where you can play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I have that plane ticket, please?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, actually, that arcade reminds me of Miggle, kind of, for some reason.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's another... So there's a picture of him kicking the top and a picture of him kicking the coin slot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is so rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was trying to go for a better kick, but manager came by.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just kind of hightailed out of there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, everybody out there, before I encourage you to run out there and kick all the Ultra Kade machines in the planet...
[SPEAKER_03]: Be careful, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't actually damage the machine because you can get in trouble for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't want to get sued because somebody, you know, we had recommended that you kick an Ultracade machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you get in trouble for kicking an Ultracade machine, I will say that I knew nothing about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we never told you to do anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: So don't get in trouble.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got the disclaimer up and running.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else you wanted to share with us?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's great, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more thing, I went out and bought a Donald J. Trump doll Friday night.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only in New York.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is this about?
[SPEAKER_03]: What made you decide to get a Donald J. Trump doll?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, me and my friends, we went out for dinner, and before we decided to play DDR, there's a big Toys R Us in Times Square.
[SPEAKER_04]: We went over, walked around, we found some great stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a picture in my gallery of Toys R Us misspelling Gundam with an H.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that Toys R Us, the one that was in an episode of The Apprentice as well?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's a famous Toys R Us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, we got dragged over to the Barbie section.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're walking around.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the guys was like, check this out.
[SPEAKER_04]: He picked up the doll, and I was like, I bought it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a picture of me in the gallery worshipping the doll because it was like the best thing in the Barbie section.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, so they had the Donald Trump doll in the Barbie section?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is that all about?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it does have this one interesting quote.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you guys can hear it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I couldn't hear it.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was it saying?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no choice to tell you, but you're fired.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, beautiful.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to answer the question in the chat room, that is Laser Park in New York City.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay, very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, Ranma, thank you very much for the pictures, and I think you've started a new trend here on Orange Lounge, so we're going to get on that after tonight's show, doing the Ultracade Kicking Gallery.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm here to help any way possible.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, so get your friends to do it and take pictures of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I plan on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got to get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, take care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Later.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, one more call, you guys, and we're going to get into the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, a couple of things.
[SPEAKER_06]: One, let me see, a tournament I went to this weekend and just basically drama, drama, and damage and drama.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a local tournament in the Bronx, you know, where I'm from.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently...
[SPEAKER_06]: The locals in the arcade there basically got pissed off at, you know, the people out, you know, the outside players for basically being good at them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, beating the crap out of them in, you know, the tournament.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they got so childish that they brought like six or seven people that, you know, they were about to beat the shit out of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how bad... Well, you're breaking up a little bit there, buddy, but... Right now, you'll see the locked thread that resulted in this.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you're breaking up a little bit, but clarify this for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think he might be a little bit delayed here.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, clarify this for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some folks beat some other folks up over DDR, is what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think he's delayed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, these people, the people here...
[SPEAKER_03]: He's really breaking up there.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're really, really breaking up there, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: They take DDR too seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: They take DDR too seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR is nothing to want to even think about beating somebody up over.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I would say that serving people over a DDR tournament, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can serve people, but don't beat them up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, but they take...
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but the thing is that they took it seriously as they compared, they almost made it, you know, compared it as to like a sporting event.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they were just basically, you know, distracting, embarrassing the other players and not the regulars there.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's kind of like, that's where the drama erupted from.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, the regular good players had to like, you know, show them their place by basically showing off in order to show them how it felt like.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what, all I have to say... They basically ignored it, you know, in the past couple of tournaments there...
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: As you can see the post from DDR Freak that I gave you, Sketch, you know, who's basically almost like a household name within the community because, you know, he's one of the best in the city, if not the state or the east coast.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was there in attendance yesterday and he pointed out, he basically, he told them politely that he just, you know, he finds those people rude.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, they basically went on rampage by insulting his group.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Buddy, you're... My friend, you're breaking up over there, so I'm gonna... Zaku, I know you're still trying to talk, but we can't understand you because you're breaking up, buddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm gonna have to go ahead and let you go, but we'll talk a little bit more about this, so keep listening, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_03]: I appreciate the update on the tournament, okay, bud?
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel bad that I had to let him go, but he was just breaking up really bad there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would you want to do this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously, if you go to a DDR tournament...
[SPEAKER_03]: It is going to be a... And I explicit, by the way, walked in during that phone call, so he's kind of picked up most of that call, and he's run a lot of tournaments and has had to deal with some of this drama.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I know you've got something you want to share on this.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you go to a DDR tournament, you should expect that there are going to be people there who are better than you.
[SPEAKER_03]: So why would you want to beat them up because they're better than you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the thing is, I understand this is a human nature that people do not want to lose.
[SPEAKER_05]: or people looking out over some other dude's girlfriend or so forth.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a lot of nonsense, but I mean, I've been through numerous tournaments myself, maybe like 18 tournaments so far total, and never have I seen anybody fight physically in a tournament, but if this were true...
[SPEAKER_05]: I just had to tell people that just grow up, basically.
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't actually do the physical fight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I clarified that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't actually get into a fight, but, you know, get in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember there was one time that I saw a fight over DER.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the CCO like two years ago in July.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's so lame.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's so lame.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what was the honest reason?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my God, you got one more perfect than me, bastard.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, because...
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the thing is, at the time I was there, well, the person who was playing, like, Demon Road got to Max Unlimited.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then some guy was just, you know, messing around, thinking it would be okay to screw his game up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then, of course, the fight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spilled coke over the DDR pads in the group.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, now the in-the-group pads.
[SPEAKER_21]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was two years ago, so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Horrible.
[SPEAKER_21]: Horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, you guys that are going to DDR tournaments, don't start drama.
[SPEAKER_03]: You give the rest of us a bad name, and we will find you and beat you up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I set your ass on fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, your mic's off there, I think.
[SPEAKER_19]: You start drama, I set your ass on fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_19]: So you can start drama if you want to die.
[SPEAKER_19]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: I need an excuse to set people on fire, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well said.
[SPEAKER_03]: You like the fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know that.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to get into the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match now, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those of you guys that didn't get through on the Skype line, try again a little later.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll hopefully open that up again a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_03]: After Listless as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll have to fill you in on tonight's Listless topic because we're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And your DS is here as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make sure it's yours because there's like three of them around here somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says explicit with three X's.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, you're in just under the 30-day rule because if something's here for 30 days, we keep it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have PM to Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to get into the Orange Lounge Radio cage match right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: The way the cage match works, you've got to be in our chat room to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: www.orangeloungeradio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the way the cage match works, we play three songs for you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Last week's winner, we play a clip of that song, and then we play two new songs for you guys, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're going to do that, and you guys are going to vote on your favorite, and the winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio's Bomani Music & More program.
[SPEAKER_03]: Last week in the Orange Launch Radio Cage Match, Ayumi Hamasaki was the winner with a System F remix of a song called Kanaria.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so that's the song that DarkSakura picked.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, sounds like Gonorrhea, but it's Kanaria.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, but it's actually, this song is much, much better than Gonorrhea could ever be.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're going to get into that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here it is, a clip of song number one.
[SPEAKER_03]: You only get to hear a clip because it was last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_03]: So here it is, a clip, Ayumi Hamasaki, song number one.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, that was a clip of song number one.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can vote for it tonight, Ayumi Hamasaki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Song number two is Loki's pick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, what did you pick for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's another song.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a remix of Xenon.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Xenon the halogen mix and it's done by G-Drop.
[SPEAKER_02]: I found it on some video game mix site or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: A remix of Xenon is song number two tonight in the cage match.
[SPEAKER_03]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: All righty, that was song number two in tonight's cage match, Beat Drop with Xenon, the Halogen Mix.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now we're going to go around in our really bad impersonation of American Idol and tell you guys what we thought of that, although we're not the ones who get to choose.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's you guys in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_19]: It sounded like someone took Xenon, which was by itself a really good song, and dropped it and beat it.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_19]: I didn't like the sampling at all.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sounded like it was done through a telephone or a Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_19]: There were parts of it I thought were okay, but honestly I just couldn't get past it sounding like it was done through like a phonograph speaker underwater.
[SPEAKER_19]: So it gets a two.
[SPEAKER_03]: Explicit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's a pretty good song, I mean, there's some, like DarkSakura said, there's some parts I just don't feel would be necessary, which is like, I'll give it a 6, but since it's not a Max Remix, I'll give it, I'll give it a plus 1 point, a 7.
[SPEAKER_17]: Angel It was okay, I still like the original better, 6.5 Loki
[SPEAKER_02]: Me,
[SPEAKER_03]: Hated it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Three.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, but I'm going to give it a bonus point for not being a Max Remix as well, so it gets a four.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's get to my song tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: My song is actually an old-ass song, but they did, like, this new remix of it last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm going to pick this song, because this song was rad, and I kind of like this new remix.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, it really grew on me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been listening to it a lot in my car.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, and everybody out here knows this song.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a group called Hadaway.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is love?
[SPEAKER_14]: Baby, don't hurt me, don't hurt me no more Baby, don't hurt me, don't hurt me no more
What is love?
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura.com
Don't hurt me, don't hurt me, no more
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, that was song number three in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hadaway with What Is Love, Reloaded.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see what the folks in the room thought of that one, starting off with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sorry, but even remixed, that song still gets on my nerves just because it was so damn overplayed.
[SPEAKER_19]: Where I would give the original a five, that one was slightly better, so I would give it a six and a half.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just because I heard it way too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: Explicit!
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to agree with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's a little overplayed.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this remix, I don't know, it just sounds just the same as the original for some reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really much has been done, just because of the reloaded sign-in to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll give it a 6.8.
6.8.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on, give it an extra .1 so we can have a 6.9 explicit.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you say?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'll give it the .1.
[SPEAKER_05]: Man, what is this going to have to do?
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Angel.
[SPEAKER_17]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, because it's 80s and stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: It kind of had an extra little beat to it.
[SPEAKER_17]: God, this mic is loud.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: A new bass, you know, a stronger bass drum and a stronger synth line does not a new... It's just, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not a remix, it's just crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the same damn song all over again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the original, and they fucked it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: They went and made it into a Hard House track, and it's not supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: It lost everything I liked about the original, and it just sounds like a really shitty cover of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it gets a 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, you know what, I kind of like it because that song's been kind of gone for a little while now that Night at the Roxbury isn't on Saturday Night Live anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, you know, so I kind of think it was time for that song to come back.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what I really like about that remix is that it's under three minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So whilst the beat in the background is a little repetitive, the song knows when to quit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I kind of like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I like that song, so I will give it an eight.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: But however, remember, it is not up to us, it's up to you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys get the final say, so here it is, a reminder of the three songs you get to vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Song number one, Ayumi Hamasaki, Kanaria.
[SPEAKER_03]: And song number two you can vote for tonight, Beat Drop with a Zenon Remix.
[SPEAKER_03]: And song number three you can vote for tonight, Hataway, What Is Love, Reloaded.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, place vote now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote for song number one, song number two, or song number three.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll tally them up over the next break and let you guys know the winner very soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: What I've been plugging a little bit tonight, and I'm going to post it one more time in the chat room for those of you guys that haven't had a chance to look at it yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm posting a link to our LiveJournal community, and it's actually a post in that LiveJournal community, and you do not have to be a member of the community to read it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't even have to be a LiveJournal member.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just go ahead and click on that link, because what is in that is instructions on how to vote for us in the Best of Live 365 competition that's going on right now, how to get us nominated.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I know what some of you guys are thinking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why does Orange Lounge Radio want to get nominated for one of those silly award shows?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, because we like attention.
[SPEAKER_03]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, DarkSakura, can you disagree with me there?
[SPEAKER_03]: Attention's great.
[SPEAKER_19]: We are whores for attention.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_19]: We will totally just make utter sluts of ourselves for attention.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where is the link right there for the Podcast Alley vote thing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yes, we'll post that as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll post that a little later.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want people to do this first, but we'll do the Podcast Alley thing later because we're trying to get our
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I think really in doing this, because you have to remember there is all sorts of stations on Live365.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's what, like 60,000?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's incredible the amount of stations that are on Live365.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for a DDR talk video game music station to get nominated, that's really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think it shows that there is an audience for this type of video game programming, where we're not talking about Madden, we're talking about Halo all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're talking about other video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: and you're going to kind of notice that as the year goes on and Orange Lounge kind of slowly does this shift from just being a Bomani to Bomani and more.
[SPEAKER_03]: We just kind of want to show that there is a demand out there for this kind of niche.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of Strictly, if you want to talk a Strictly Bomani-based radio station, our buddies over at DDR Freak, we're trying to help them out get a nomination as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they've been really good to us this year, especially with the whole syndication and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'd like to see them get a nod as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that is all detailed for you guys in the live journal post.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, our grandfather station, Understation Live, we're trying to get them a nod as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Without Understation Live, we would not be here, I do not think.
[SPEAKER_03]: All of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I hope you guys will consider taking a second.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys already have to have a Live365 account to listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you've already got everything you need.
[SPEAKER_03]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those of you guys that are too shy to join our chat room, just go to our LiveJournal community.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's www.livejournal.com slash community slash orange lounge.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's a link right there on orangelounge.com that says community.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's like what, the fourth post down?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just scroll down until you see the best of Live365 post.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we appreciate your support.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so that's that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk about a little bit of SimScene news, and usually this has kind of been a joke lately with all the sites being down, but I know, Loki, I know there's big news you're very excited about this week, so you've got to tell us about this in the SimScene update.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, just like a lot of fan stuff out there that's being worked on, most of the stuff, of course, you'll always find is in Japan, and you really need to watch the Japanese sites, because that's where all the stuff's happening nowadays, since all the American stuff's down.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, the one site whenever we're talking about Japanese Step Mania, the one thing you have to bring up is Food Mix.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yes, it was announced this week that Food Mix 2 Advanced Edition will be coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: When?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a good question.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they have a few screenshots up on their site.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a link on our front page to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And go check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks good as ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tons of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know they're going to have stuff from diverse systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's always a great package once it's put together.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some other things that I might point out.
[SPEAKER_02]: In our forums, in the Orange Lodge Radio, I do have a link to...
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a theme called Pop Candy.
[SPEAKER_02]: The website that had it up originally went down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Luckily, I downloaded it a long-ass time ago, so I hosted it for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can go download that on OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just check in the forums.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'll find it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And other than that, there was the Siberia theme.
[SPEAKER_02]: 2.1 got released, and for those who don't know what that is, that's the Stepmania theme that looks sort of like
[SPEAKER_02]: Techno Fiend, it's the Japanese one, it does look very good, and I've actually switched this to my default theme, I like it a lot, and so definitely check that out as well, other than that, really, there's a whole thread on Belmonte Style, basically it's the fan mix,
[SPEAKER_02]: WatchThread
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I liked Food Mix a whole heck of a lot, so I'm really excited about Food Mix too.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sounds like a good addition.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's kind of neat because...
[SPEAKER_03]: When you hear all this news about, you know, In the Groove, and Neon FM, and what is that other one, Dance Tracks, or whatever, and all these kind of DDR knockoffs that are spawning from the Sim scene, and you know what, I realize In the Groove is getting a lot of credit now, but let's face it, it started as a Sim scene knockoff game, because it is Step Mania, basically, in a box.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very interesting to see that Foon Mix...
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I believe to be the king of all this stuff is not an arcade thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, if it were ever to make it to the arcade scene, if they actually were to do something similar to what they're doing here within the groove over in Japan with Food Mix, I think it would wipe the floor within the groove.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would simply just topple it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just better songs, better everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Better graphics.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just so much, so better, you know, done than In The Groove, it's not even funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, you can't even compare them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely, check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you haven't already downloaded FoonMix 1 and FoonMix Plus, I think you can still do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely download those, it's a huge download, so if you're on dial-up, probably not going to be able to play that, but if you're not, check it out if you haven't already.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think in our next break, maybe if we can round up some songs, we'll do some Foon Mix music and maybe some other stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually... We haven't played any In the Groove songs in a while, so I think there's actually a couple songs that are worth playing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, Jamie's frowning of disapproval.
[SPEAKER_19]: My poor ears.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are some songs I like in In the Groove, so I'm going to play one of those.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's hear about the winner of tonight's cage match, shall we?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys voted, and there was a pretty clear winner tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got to say, I was kind of surprised by it.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a brand new winner tonight, and it's Hadaway.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is love?
[SPEAKER_03]: Reloaded.
[SPEAKER_19]: The chatroom has no taste.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they're just nostalgia whores, kind of like I am, because I think when that song started playing, a lot of them were like, I remember this song, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I remember the scene from... Was it Night of the Roxbury?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Night of the Roxbury.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, I think that, you know, that song, you heard it a lot, apparently, and that song was pretty damn horrid when that movie was out, but it's been a while, I think most people have forgotten it.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's a station in Mobile, I'll go ahead and name it, it's W-A-B-B, who, when that song came out, it literally played once every 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_19]: I kid you not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, I would totally listen to a station that played that kind of stuff, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, they've also played a bunch of crap, because...
[SPEAKER_19]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, stop.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we got that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know what else I wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanted to kind of give a shout-out to one of our buddies.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know her as Rice Princess from Thursday Nights Outside the Box.
[SPEAKER_03]: She goes by a ton of other names, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mojiko, Irene.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's a woman of many different names out there, but I'm sure you guys are familiar with her.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't usually talk about big commercial gaming sites, but there's one in particular that I've grown quite fond of lately, and that's 1up.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually really like them quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would endorse them.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're a great site.
[SPEAKER_03]: We even have our own club over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will post the URL to that club in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's what, like orangeloungeradioclub or something like that, .1up.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's a dash in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here, I got the link.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll just post that for you guys in the chat room if you want to join the orangeloungeradioclub.1up.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Back to Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not only did she start that club on our behalf over there, but she was actually named Blog of the Day.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't know if that was today or yesterday, but her 1up.com blog was named Blog of the Day because she made this really big post about the Dear Friends concert that she went to Monday night in San Francisco, and somebody noticed and shared a little love.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we just want to say congratulations to our buddy Rice Princess on being to Blog of the Day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you know me?
[SPEAKER_03]: I am so famous.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, I guess on that note, we're going to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we got the cage match winner.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess we're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when we come back from this break, we'll finally get to that list list we talked about.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the FUs of the week, we still got that as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some Ask Orange Lounge if we have time.
[SPEAKER_03]: In this break, some Food Mix and whatever else I can dig up.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Started off with a little bit of Evergreen from Food Mix.
Evergreen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Feel the touch of my hands He's the group operator Hypnotized by the look in your eyes Hit the coast
[SPEAKER_11]: Feel you.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hiho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter V, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi guys, we're back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hope you enjoyed that set of mix there from some various sim file scene.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how to kind of loop all that together, but what can you do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Beat Drop, or not Beat Drop, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was the song from the Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_03]: Starting us off was Evergreen from Food Mix, then Zodiac from In the Groove, Mirrorball, and P8107 after that, both from Food Mix as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki is obsessed with this new show called Robot Chicken, which I actually watched last Sunday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I've been watching it every week because I think it's pretty damn funny too.
[SPEAKER_03]: But last Sunday was especially funny because they made fun of Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not really made fun, but they totally paid homage to Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll let Loki explain it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, basically Robot Chicken, for those who don't know, it's this 15 minute long show that's on Cartoon Network, Sundays at 11.30, and I think they also have it repeating throughout the entire week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it repeats at
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know if anyone's going to be awake, but Monday at 2.30 a.m., Fridays at midnight and 3 a.m.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can check them out then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Their last night's, basically, anyway, so 15-minute show, it's all stop animation with toys and claymation.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, for example, week one, we had...
[SPEAKER_02]: They did a parody of, like, the, what was it, the Rachel Lee Cooks public service announcement, you know, where this is your brain on drugs, you know, but it doesn't stop there, you know, this is your family.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she's hitting stuff with, you know, a frying pan, and it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just need to say right now, although it is 1130 right now on the East Coast, that doesn't give you permission to stop listening to us and go watch this.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can download it on BitTorrent later, and also they replay it a ton, so get that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for you West Coast folks, you'll be able to listen to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Octimus Prime, Prostate Cancer Awareness
[SPEAKER_02]: And then last week, they did a parody of Cannonball Run.
[SPEAKER_02]: For those who don't remember, Cannonball Run was the Burt Reynolds movie based on the actual cannonball races where you race across the country and it's like a no-holds-barred thing and they have all the weird teams of people and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they have all these icons from the 80s and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had Vin Diesel, supposedly, as a character.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had the Ecto-1, Speed Racer, Batman and Robin, the guys from Chips, and just a bunch of other weird people.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Mario, and Luigi, and Wario from Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's one scene in there where they're actually in the race, and they're all...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's time we use the blue tortoiseshell!
[SPEAKER_02]: And so they use the blue tortoiseshell and it hits the guys from... What is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It just knocks one of the cars off the road and it was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, I cannot describe it well enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: You really need to go watch the show tonight to give you a brief preview of what's going to be on.
[SPEAKER_02]: This episode is called The Deep End.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says, find out what happens when seven superheroes are forced to live under one roof in the real world metropolis...
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wasn't this called Drawn Together?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, yes, maybe, but this will be better.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then catch Adam James...
[SPEAKER_02]: James T. Kirk, Khan, Noonien Sing, and Kirk Cameron work in a pizza joint in two Kirks, a Khan, and a pizza place.
[SPEAKER_02]: And someone's on a mission to track down Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny in Kill Bunny.
[SPEAKER_02]: And lastly, go backstage for America's favorite undead reality show, Zombie Idol.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what's great about this show is they actually have a lot of the celebrities doing their own voices and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, for example, last week, Luigi, voiced by Matthew Lillard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Great stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: But really, watch the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you can't watch it, it's on torrentbox.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, we have some folks in the chatroom saying, I'm T-voing it right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I'm looking at our live listener stats to us.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I noticed four people dropped while we were talking about Robot Chicken.
[SPEAKER_03]: So damn you!
[SPEAKER_03]: I told you not to leave to go watch it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop being cheap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Buy a TiVo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care if this show gets weak in its last hour.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of that weak program you've come to know and love here at Orange Launch Radio, it's time to do tonight's listless segment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_03]: So you know we need some theme music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, tonight's list list everybody is going to be, the topic is Slash commands I would like to see in an MMORPG And of course this topic being spawned by the recent news about Slash Pizza being added into Pizza Hut I'm sorry, being added The newest MMORPG, Pizza Hut, where you play as the delivery person
[SPEAKER_19]: You have to avoid obstacles such as dogs chasing you and throwing newspapers, I mean pizzas into, oh wait, that's Paperboy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, smartass.
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't you know it?
[SPEAKER_19]: My ass is this smart, imagine how smart my brain is.
[SPEAKER_03]: slash pizza being added into EverQuest 2 in a partnership with Pizza Hut so you can order pizza directly from your EverQuest 2 game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what other slash commands would we like to see in an MMORPG?
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys in the chatroom can submit your suggestions, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just type them up.
[SPEAKER_03]: No guarantees we're going to use them, though, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do have the chatroom displayed on our in-studio television screen where everybody can see it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tonight on Listless, participating, we have DarkSakura, Loki, myself, and Angel and Explicit are working as one team tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're one mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or no, not anymore?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_03]: They are two separate entities now.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have, uh, they have, I know, that's very, that does sound kind of wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: But really funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's find this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I'm going to kill the background music.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll bring it back later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember, you guys get to vote.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys get to vote on the top three.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're only creating the list.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what's going to happen is we're each going to read off our top three.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the fun part.
[SPEAKER_03]: Each one of us gets to take one off of the list.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, why don't you start us off with your number three pick for a slash command you'd like to see in an MMORPG?
[SPEAKER_19]: My first one is slash window.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what does slash window do?
[SPEAKER_19]: It opens up like a little PIP window where you can like, you know, like if you instead of, because, you know, obviously they're not going to actually window Final Fantasy XI without using something that they consider illegal.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, you should be able to access like the play online site as a window in window.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've actually come up with a practical, good idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's not funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: My other ones are funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't have to be funny.
[SPEAKER_19]: But I was really annoyed, because usually I have to set up my laptop to use a fake use-to-play.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just loving our chatroom right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys, seriously, if you haven't looked at what the chatroom is... Slash all your base.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like slash girls' butts.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sega Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, they need to...
[SPEAKER_19]: Even though I would put, I would have, this would have been like my number four, would have been like slash PSO mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_19]: Where you just walk, run around from room to room.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Explicit, your number three, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: Slash yo mama.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you have a microphone over there, buddy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, listeners in here.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Slash yo mama.
[SPEAKER_03]: Slash yo mama.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what does slash yo mama do?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, they're all saying, ooh, I fucked your mom and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So slash yo mama would actually fuck your mama?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel sorry for yo mama.
[SPEAKER_03]: Angel, you're number three.
[SPEAKER_17]: Slash silly string.
[SPEAKER_03]: Slash silly string.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what would slash silly string do?
[SPEAKER_17]: Enable you with the silly string, kid, so you could, like, have a silly string fight with the rest of your party.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my, let's get messy!
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, Loki, you're number three.
[SPEAKER_02]: Slash Nicole Brown Simpson.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think we know.
[SPEAKER_02]: This would, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: This would link you to the Find the Real Killers website out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because they're out there and loose and OG Simpson is searching for them in every golf course.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, wow, wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: My number three needs a little bit of explaining.
[SPEAKER_03]: My number three choice is Slash Abshock.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, they're anorexic from having the lack of slash pizza.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, you're number two.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let me pull up the file again.
[SPEAKER_19]: I love my laptop.
[SPEAKER_19]: Slash sim.
[SPEAKER_19]: What that does is it creates a simulacrum of yourself to go to your job.
[SPEAKER_19]: Like the Calvin clone machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someday, I hope.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, very nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Slash Sim.
[SPEAKER_03]: Explicit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Slash pubic hairs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this for all the 12 and 13 year olds that play MMOs or what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anybody?
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope that one day... What in the hell is this slash command supposed to do?
What the...
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: What this code does is, well, you know how people fantasize about... It's basically a nude code without the pubic hair.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see, okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Or if a boy wants to... I don't fantasize about that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But some do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of which, how did your 40 days without a boner thing go, speaking of which?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, by the way, I'm surviving.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got a few more days.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Meaning I've not got a morning boner...
[SPEAKER_05]: or I see any attractive tits or porno or strip club.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll never get a boner again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, I'll explain that later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Angel, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, you need a mic, don't you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Bitch slap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, would slash bitch slap bitch slap you or the other player?
[SPEAKER_17]: Right, um, like, let's say you have somebody in your party that you don't like or isn't doing their job yet, right?
[SPEAKER_17]: Just do slash bitch slap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, Loki, you're number two.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the only appropriate thing that we're actually missing from an MMORPG is slash dingo because, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: When someone really pisses you off online, you really wish a dingo would go eat their baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so now you can have that thanks to our brand new dingo technology.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dingoes can and will eat your babies.
[SPEAKER_11]: A dingo ate my baby!
[SPEAKER_03]: My number two pick is slash Fred Durst porn video.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the reason for this is because when you guys are feeling a little bit inadequate because you're staying in the house all day and playing MMORPGs, you can type slash Fred Durst porn video and you can see that you can have it off a lot worse and you'll feel better about yourself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so slash Fred Durst porn video.
[SPEAKER_03]: I typed slash Fred.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Jamie, you're number one.
[SPEAKER_19]: My number one is slash IDBFG.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyone ever play Doom?
[SPEAKER_19]: Imagine going around Final Fantasy XI with the BFG.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Imagine gunning down anything that gets in your way with extreme prejudice.
[SPEAKER_21]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_19]: I could just imagine right now, Battering Ram, fuck you!
[SPEAKER_19]: Button.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So ID BFG, just like the Doom Days.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Explicit, you're number one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Slash Tack Slash Engulf
[SPEAKER_17]: Ah, that made you giggle.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what pray tell does that do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Does it engulf your opponent in flames?
[SPEAKER_17]: Either your opponent or somebody in your party you don't like.
[SPEAKER_03]: So engulf is the number one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, you're number one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I figured this is the most needed thing in the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: Slash real girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because some of those people, they need to realize...
[SPEAKER_02]: They need to find a real girl and not masturbate to fictional women.
[SPEAKER_02]: So slash real girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's what's needed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, and my number one is slash give me a dollar.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: and when you type it, it would give you a dollar.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you can't overuse it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here is the list as it stands currently.
[SPEAKER_03]: Slash window, slash yo mama, slash silly string, slash Nicole Brown Simpson, slash ab shocks, slash sim, slash pubic hairs, slash bitch slap, slash dingo, slash Fred Durst porn video, slash IDBFG, slash taku, slash engulf, slash real girl, slash give me a dollar.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: It does kind of sound like The Sims, although I guess that's kind of the idea behind it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we wouldn't want people to get confused, because Americans do get a little too easily confused.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, Angel, one of these has got to go.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're going to kill me.
[SPEAKER_17]: Porn video.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was the best one on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: She always takes off the best one.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, slash Fred Durst porn video is gone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks to Angel.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to eliminate slash pubic hairs, because I didn't really get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, sorry, explicit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Loki, you're going to pick the last one that's come off this list.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to have to say Slash Window because it's just not funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we need funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Heaven forbid someone come up with a good idea during List List.
[SPEAKER_03]: Heaven forbid, we can't have that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to come up with Slash Poop, but, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: The list that you guys will get to vote for, alright?
[SPEAKER_03]: So, pick your favorite from that list and send me a private message with your vote.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Dark Knight gets a cookie.
[SPEAKER_03]: All army.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk about some of the... Wow, a lot of you guys are participating in this.
[SPEAKER_03]: My gosh, we've just got pages and pages of recommended slash.
[SPEAKER_03]: So here are some honorable mentions I'm reading in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Slash pee in your butt.
[SPEAKER_03]: Slash fatality.
[SPEAKER_03]: Slash tub girl.
[SPEAKER_03]: Slash summon Martha Stewart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: slash OLR, slash Penis Enlargement, slash Forever Sunshine, slash Enzyte, slash Cash for Game Money, slash Pedobear Seal of Approval, slash I Am Not Your Game Boy, slash Pokemon Red Flash Seizure, I like that one, slash
[SPEAKER_03]: Slash... Bathroom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where was... There was one I really... Oh, Slash Jesus Juice.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was my favorite, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Out of the chatroom was Slash Jesus Juice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knew that Zaku could say something funny?
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knew?
[SPEAKER_03]: But that was, I think, my favorite out of the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_03]: So just as one was Slash Jesus Juice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots of good ones there in the chatroom, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_03]: So send us your votes now to sky...
[SPEAKER_03]: in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's great, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the meantime, while we're tallying up the votes, we'll give you guys a couple minutes to send those votes, and we'll do a quick, quick break, and then we're going to come back with the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So in this break, Moonlight Shadow, because that song rocks, and we haven't heard it in a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: So here it is, and we'll be back after this.
and the others.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm in the morning, carried away by a moonlight shed I watch your vision falling, carried away by a moonlight shed Life is a game, jump on the ride Turn on your thing, and let's play tonight
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't you try to run.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't you try to hide.
[SPEAKER_11]: Life is a game.
Let's play tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Life is a game, don't want to lie Turn on your pain, let's play tonight Don't you try to run, don't you try to hide Life is a game, let's play tonight
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio with the Ping Pong Ball.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's one of my favorite promos because it's the only one you can hear Jamie clucking like a chicken.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's my favorite.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, let's hear who won tonight's list list, shall we?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Slash Command, you would most like to see...
[SPEAKER_03]: in an MMORPG.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number three, slash Nicole Brown Simpson.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what the hell you guys are thinking there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can see why it's third.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been to before.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: In second place, slash IDBFG.
[SPEAKER_03]: Score one for the old schoolers.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And in first place, slash give me a dollar.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkDeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, why do we have to get a little bit angry every single week?
[SPEAKER_09]: Grr.
[SPEAKER_08]: Arrgh.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, FD to people who drive while they talk on their cell phones.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_19]: I witnessed an accident nearly happen today because both drivers were on their damn cell phones.
[SPEAKER_19]: So fuck them.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sorry, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't think other people should be on their cell phones, just me.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that wouldn't have happened.
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, you know the law's going to pass this year, so I'm looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's also... Shoot, I was thinking about this earlier today, and I completely forgot what it was.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: F you to people.
[SPEAKER_19]: And this is more of a situational F you.
[SPEAKER_19]: But when people complain about how much their life sucks, yet they don't do anything about it, fuck that.
[SPEAKER_19]: You don't have a right to complain until you are actively working to remedy your situation.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, you can say, oh, well, I'm tired of being fat or something like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't understand that I also have a big SU to people who complain about not having money yet continue to frivolously spend on shit they don't need I've had to break myself of this habit too but I recognize that I don't have money because I spent it on this, this, this and this well now I can actively say
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't have the money to spend on it because I'm saving up to buy a house, which is true.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to be buying a house this year.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um... But it's also... It's just, again, I don't understand the whole mentality of how people can bitch about something yet not do anything to remedy it.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_19]: Um... I also big S you to, uh... Um...
[SPEAKER_19]: the car wash line at Chevron today there were seven people in the damn line and the line wasn't moving so I'm going to have to go back after the show at night and get my car washed where the water will not evaporate as quickly big F you're not having an air conditioner but hey, I'm going to have my air conditioning replaced next week I'm doing something about it that's been my big thing is people who just don't do anything to fix their situation so I'm done here
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Loki's turn!
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, first off, I'd like to say a big fuck you to, um, LRGs, because they've been kicking my ass all week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just now starting to feel a little bit better, um, but I don't think that's gonna last very long, because it's LRG season, and I'm affected by both mold and pollen, so I'm fucked all year round.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty much like I am at work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you to work for being a little boring.
[SPEAKER_02]: I tried making a catapult out of my pen last week, and I got a little bit of ink on my finger, because I guess pens don't like to be turned into catapults.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh well, so much for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, also, fuck you the fact that I need, like, I have this urge for projects, even though I haven't finished other projects, and I really...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's hard, it's like crack, I can't stop, I just gotta build crap, and I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, I don't even use what I build, it's, I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um, yeah, it's just some weird obsession that I have, so I just can't stop.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um, fuck you to Lindsay Lohan for acting, because you suck, and I don't really need you to, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: Why does Disney have to fucking remake every movie that they've made?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know what, all the remakes suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, fuck those.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck, you know, the Son of the Mask, because that sucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's still being made, and I got the damn screener for it, and it's dirty.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, or actually, I didn't get the screener for it, but fuck, I got tickets to it, and I never went and saw it, so it was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: And then finally, fuck you, the family that's suing Michael Jackson, because I believe that they're just seeing him as an easy target to try to get money.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you actually follow the testimony, there's a lot of discrepancies, let's put it that way, in their testimony.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I hope they get sued.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and another thing, I'm not sure if anyone heard about it, there was actually a news report a while back of this guy that sued, I believe it's ABC or whoever the fuck puts out that goddamn show, Fear Factor.
[SPEAKER_02]: He basically got sick and dizzy and fell into a door well from watching the show and so he was suing them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there was justice being done, and the judge said, fuck you, this is a frivolous lawsuit, and threw it right back at him, and didn't award him any money.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, at least there's some justice in this world.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm done.
[SPEAKER_03]: An F you to E!
[SPEAKER_03]: Entertainment Television for having those really addicting Michael Jackson trial wrap-up shows.
[SPEAKER_03]: Would they actually reenact what's going on in the courtroom?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because that shit is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: The guy that they have playing Michael Jackson is very eerie, like, identical.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Except they drew on his nose.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not kidding you.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like his nose is drawn on.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And F you to House Hunting, because it's a pain in the ass, and I've been kind of looking for, like, a new place where the new Orange Lounge studio will be.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: And we found five places on the internet we liked.
[SPEAKER_03]: We drove by and only liked two of them when we drove by them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And one of them is in the ghetto, so it's kind of a question mark.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although it sucks because that was by far my favorite house.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was such a cute little house and it had a little gate and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I really want it and it's affordable.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's in the ghetto.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, but I kind of want it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, I could get a guard dog.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio, coming to you live from the ghetto.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're coming to you from South Sac.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll figure something out, I always do.
[SPEAKER_03]: But house hunting sucks, so F you to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And F you to just moving in general, because moving sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because can you imagine having to clean this apartment?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: The place I lived in Chico was worse.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I made it somehow, so I'll get through this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's get to our guest F yous.
[SPEAKER_03]: Starting it off with...
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, the marathon man himself, explicit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd like to give an Effie to work for letting me stay in the sun, for having me stay in the sun without getting me a break at work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yesterday was extremely hot and someone who was supposed to be giving breaks because I was working 10 o'clock in the morning until like 6 at night did not give me a break and everybody else got a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well guess what, almost got heat stroke and almost fainted.
[SPEAKER_05]: And AFP goes to a lot of depression towards this and pressure family wise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course some of you know that my dad passed away like two years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and it's been tough, but some people are pushing me to a point where they don't even understand what I'm going through.
[SPEAKER_05]: They think it's, oh, so what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, okay, a person died two years ago, and you're going to talk trash behind his back?
[SPEAKER_05]: That really hurts, especially when I caught somebody in the cemetery trying to steal flowers.
What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love my woman, but this is the only way I can... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's other ways to show your affection, other than stolen flowers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Perhaps he was bringing flowers to his newly found corpse that he was gonna have sex with.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like I give a damn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you steal flowers in the cemetery, then that's hella simple.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another Effie goes to Almost Breaking Lent.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you get a semi-wood or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: Came close, but no wood.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, a friend of mine tested my ability to watch three hours of porn non-stop.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to kill you, but then again, if I win this bet, I actually will get like a hundred bucks off of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are they going to know if you got a boner or not?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, since I'm an honest guy, I could just... That could be a lie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I was a hardcore heroin addict and I quit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I won a hundred dollars.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you guys know I'm a virgin?
[SPEAKER_05]: I did not know about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, anyway, sorry, Explosive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, how much time we have?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to take too long.
[SPEAKER_05]: Three seconds.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, NFU goes to taxes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Someone got one of the numbers wrong that's needed to file taxes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: They come up to me and give me a mail saying that's the wrong number.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I don't get the correct number, then I would have been arrested or fined a shitload of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why is this the wrong number?
[SPEAKER_05]: Either the person who was coding up the... or accounting the tax is either lazy or just being a dick.
[SPEAKER_05]: After he goes to almost being sandwiched by three cars, both...
[SPEAKER_05]: Two of them in an SUV and one a truck behind me.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what happens, like DarkSakura said, about people with the cell phones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I've actually seen that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this time they didn't even signal while heading to the same lane.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which I almost got squashed.
[SPEAKER_05]: People need to learn how to drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: But to make sure this is short, to be continued.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, Angel.
[SPEAKER_17]: As usual.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, okay, to, uh, follow up on Explicit's F.U.s, F.U.
[SPEAKER_17]: to death, because sometimes you lose people that, you know, really shouldn't have been taken away from you, as far as, you know, age or what have you.
[SPEAKER_17]: And F.U.
[SPEAKER_17]: to the grieving process as well, because, uh, it's not easy, it's really not.
[SPEAKER_17]: And, yeah, so, I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Maybe FU the finals this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's get to the chatroom FUs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Legend of Zaku says, FU to the regulars and the arcade and the tourney I went to this weekend for acting like little bitches because other players were better than you.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for having the gall to be, to begging people to fight them.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to having to pay $11 for a cab to leave the campus, all because of a damn bus straight up here in Westchester County in the subs of New York over petty shit that's not even worth the rider who heavily depends on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Change... Oh, change being to bring.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: MPQ says F you to 7 Star Songs and Beatmania 3 for kicking my ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to Disconnected Expert for kicking my ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to Moonlight Shadow Double for kicking my ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: And F you to myself for missing last week's show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't forget you can always catch that on DDR Freaks Rewinds Friday nights.
[SPEAKER_03]: AgentBuddyPaul says, F you to my school for sitting me in a dark auditorium and showing me a presentation on drunk drivers, mangled bodies, zombie-like people, it was horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to drunk drivers for filling up an hour and 30 minutes worth of tragedy and gore in school.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds like red asphalt to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: They made us all watch that shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkKnight, a big F you to people that never come to work on time and relieve you for the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Allusion says, F you to douchebags.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was this guy behind me kicking a bottle, a faux gangster, who told me to kick the bottle too, which I did playing along, and he said, yeah, you a gangsta in all seriousness.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guess what, buddy?
[SPEAKER_03]: You ain't a gangsta.
[SPEAKER_03]: You live in the suburbs.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have a two-story house and a car that your mommy and daddy bought you, you spoiled ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to rap for making the word ghetto used at least 30 times a day by every, and then it says blank, something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to the word ignorant and being used by people that are ignorant to the meaning of the word ignorant.
[SPEAKER_03]: The irony.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mikotov says, First FU goes to Sony for getting me all hyped up about the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just lucky they have Lumines.
[SPEAKER_03]: Second FU goes to getting the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: in at the store supposedly early this coming week and not being able to take it home despite having it fully paid.
[SPEAKER_03]: And lastly, FU to having to put a code in for Monkey Fingers on Pump Exceed.
[SPEAKER_03]: That song is too cool for a code.
[SPEAKER_03]: LemonLimeJump says, FU non-native palm trees up and down McGregor Boulevard.
[SPEAKER_03]: They hurt the native plants, create terrible blind spots, and they're ugly!
[SPEAKER_03]: SSJ100Matt says, FU to the skater kid trying to start a fight with me for being a noob at Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Thinking I Wasn't Letting Him Play Before Golf Line Closed.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to my double date canceling.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, F you to Hootie selling out to do Burger King commercials.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sephiroth1215 says, F you to annoying ex-girlfriends.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S says, and F you to life.
[SPEAKER_03]: My friend's grandmother passed away and she's really upset.
[SPEAKER_03]: Life sucks like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkTetsuya says, F you to coke with lime.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's addicting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Dork says, F you to school because I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm an attention whore.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a good note to end on, is the attention whore note there.
[SPEAKER_17]: I forgot one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yes, Angel.
[SPEAKER_17]: F you to not one, but two deaths in one weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, yeah, that's all that has to be said.
[SPEAKER_17]: Unless you want me to do a short but sweet explanation of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will leave it up to you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want you to have to get into it if you don't want to.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, you know, that one friend that I talked about at the beginning of the show passing away.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then we had a staff meeting for Herschel Radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: And right before the meeting ended, the manager got really, really quiet.
[SPEAKER_17]: And he's like, I just got a phone call.
[SPEAKER_17]: And everybody goes, what's wrong?
[SPEAKER_17]: My friend just got stabbed and he passed away.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's too bad.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was just craptacular.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyway, I'll shut up now and give you back the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's alright, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so, on a completely different note, and when I say completely, I mean completely different note, Loki is looking up images on, I guess it's Bomani Styles image boards, and he's pulled up Poppin' Porn.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's back in their not-work-safe section.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just figured I'd take a look and see what's in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they've got a lot of not-work-safe stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know who the fuck draws this shit, honestly.
[SPEAKER_02]: But apparently there's a lot of it out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got some really graphic pictures.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, for example, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have this one right here.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's Japanese people that actually draw those pictures.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get a life!
[SPEAKER_02]: You can have a life in Japan as well, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure, if you're Japanese, I say F you to having a Resident Evil 4 censored game.
[SPEAKER_05]: For those who haven't noticed, the Resident Evil 4 in Japan has no head cuts like Leon's head cut off or the zombies.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a weird game, but without the heads cut off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stupid censorship.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's funny that they have more inappropriate stuff for other children compared to the ones we have in America.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sucks to be in Japan for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, we're going to go to a quick break, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: When we come back, some Ask Orange Lounge, because we haven't done it in a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you have a question for us, send it over private message in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we're also going to wrap things up, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we will be back after this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Came in from a rainy Thursday on the avenue Thought I heard you talking so slowly I turned on the lights, the TV, and the radio Still I can't escape the ghost of you What is happening?
Thank you for watching
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_23]: please listen to Orange Lounge Radio because real radio makes Captain Jack cry
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_03]: What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_03]: Will Loki ever find the Tekken 5 soundtrack?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or will Jamie be forced to taunt him because she has it already?
[SPEAKER_03]: Now you can see what we talk about in the studio on breaks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's start it off with a question from MPQ.
[SPEAKER_03]: My sister thinks all Taku songs sound the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously, this is unacceptable.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do I do to fix this?
[SPEAKER_19]: Chain her to a chair.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was thinking the exact same thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: and put her in one of those sensory deprivation things except that all it plays is Taku music and she'll learn the subtle differences.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what you should do?
[SPEAKER_03]: If she listens to CDs in the car, I don't know how old your sister is, assuming she's of drivable age, if she listens to CDs in the car or even the CDs in her CD player, switch out for Bounce Connected or other Taku albums.
[SPEAKER_03]: She'll thank you later for the great music you're providing her, trust me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, next up.
[SPEAKER_03]: RPGKing7 says, Question for all who use Stepmania.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was wondering if you have any tips for someone who has just started getting into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: A little bit vague because we're not sure if you're talking about making step files or downloading.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm assuming you're going to mean you just are getting into it for the first time and downloading.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can probably explain this since I am a sim artist myself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, make it quick though, explicit, because we've only got about 10 minutes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, the tips on sim files is one, select a good song that you feel like people would enjoy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And two, use programs like Acid or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: As long as you cut the track correctly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Perfectly.
[SPEAKER_05]: And three, try to also use DWI.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure if other dudes' DWI tutorial is online, but if you need that, I can probably send it to you via AOL Instant Messenger for those who are interested in sim file making.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you're into sim file making, those are some good resources for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're into sim file playing, my advice would be go and get some of those big pack songs, like Food Mix.
[SPEAKER_03]: and things like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go get some of those really, really well done sim files.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look for the high rated stuff on Bomani Style.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look for artists who have done a lot of songs because artists, you know, folks that have done, you know, when I say artists, I mean like step file background and so forth, artists, folks who have made a lot of songs have probably learned from their past mistakes so they start producing really quality stuff so look for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it makes this, they have like, you can get the label either keyboard or pad so people do not like
[SPEAKER_05]: How did Orange Lounge Radio come about?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you want to tell it or should I?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why don't you?
[SPEAKER_19]: We were on the BART.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bay Area Rapid Transit.
[SPEAKER_19]: Coming back from San Francisco, I thought.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, we first discussed it going to San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then we finalized it on the way back.
[SPEAKER_19]: But we wanted to do the station for some time because I had a lot of fun subbing on Under Sedation.
[SPEAKER_19]: And Kay basically came up with the idea, everything that day.
[SPEAKER_19]: And we were broadcasting, what, in a couple weeks?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, didn't take long.
[SPEAKER_03]: So basically it's just, you know, we were having fun with Under Station Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know personally I was dying to sit behind the control panel for another show because Travis always sat behind the control panel for that show.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I kind of wanted to do one where I could sit behind the control panel just because I'd done it when I was doing college radio and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it worked out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Jamie I knew was, you know, somebody I would want to do the radio show with because she had all that experience on Under Station.
[SPEAKER_03]: and also a vast knowledge of Bomani and video games in general.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's because I have no life.
[SPEAKER_03]: She made a good partner for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Loki just kind of showed up, but it worked out really good.
[SPEAKER_19]: He won a host spot for perfect attendance.
[SPEAKER_03]: He did.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's a question for Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you think that Nintendo DS's online gimmick will be worth it?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to talk about this on the podcast this week, but the online gimmick.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkTetsuya says, Here's what I meant to ask.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was everyone's first cata?
[SPEAKER_02]: So in DDR, your first catastrophic song that you beat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_19]: My favorite one?
[SPEAKER_03]: Your first.
[SPEAKER_19]: My first?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_19]: My first was Hypnotic Crisis.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was my first as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anybody else care to share?
[SPEAKER_05]: I would say the same thing back then with Hypnotic Crisis.
[SPEAKER_02]: Paranoia Eternal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fucking easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or if you count Paranoia K-Set and Dropout before it became Switch as a 9, or Burn the Floor in Max 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell's up with that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Burn in the floor?
[SPEAKER_03]: Give me a break.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember talking about that before, a long time ago on this show.
[SPEAKER_17]: I can express one I'm working on, although it probably wasn't the best choice.
[SPEAKER_17]: My Summer Love from, like, Fourth Mix.
[SPEAKER_03]: My Summer Love, I think, was my second one.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's not a bad one to be trying, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: In my opinion.
[SPEAKER_17]: Or like, um, no wait, that's like an eight, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_17]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was going to say Spin the Disc, but I don't remember what number that is.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, that's an eight.
[SPEAKER_17]: Never mind!
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, we're going to burn through some of these other questions real fast because we've got to wrap up the show here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mikulatov, Dear AskOrangeLounge, seeing as how Sony doesn't seem to have as many ads out for its PSP but it's got so much hype behind it, do you think that it will be as huge of a hit as the PS2?
[SPEAKER_03]: When you phrase the question that way, will it be a bigger hit than the PS2, I have to say no.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the PS2 is just untoppable in that regard.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it'll be a hit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think the PSP is going to be a failure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Legend of Zaku says, What was the worst Bomani-related drama you have ever seen?
[SPEAKER_03]: MGL2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember MGL2?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was pretty bad when we had the guy who smashed food all over the stage and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, weeks and weeks of web board posts after that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I just remember the local drama with certain people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, come to think of it, a lot of the big Bomani drama that I remember, I was directly involved with.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, I'm not just saying that, I'm referring to other people too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I know, when I think about Bomani drama, unfortunately, I think about the stuff that impacted me the most, which, you know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Of course, the two, I think, who were the greatest causes, I would say, are no longer in the scene.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, true.
[SPEAKER_03]: LemonLimeJump says, What do you guys think of an Orange Lounge Radio Winamp skin?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, if somebody wants to do one, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I unfortunately have no artistic skill whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have no time.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if somebody wants to make one, and we approve of it, and we're pretty easily win-over-able, we'll put it up in our download section on the website.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that would be kind of a neat thing to have, because I know a lot of people use WAMP.
[SPEAKER_17]: As long as it works with the newest version or whatever, I'm cool with it, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it can work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Most of them do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any prospective artists out there that want to try that, hey, we will totally support you in that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never thought of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a good thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: And lastly, Illusion wants to know, why are people so lame?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, WTF.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why are people so lame?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's their parents.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: They were raised badly.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to do it for Ask Orange Lounge tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll do it again in future weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember, you can always ask us questions over on our forums, www.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_03]: and just check out the forums over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's time to wrap up the show, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been a fun three hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next week on the show, more of what you've come to know and love.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully we have more news on Night Style we can share with you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully Song Pack 9 makes its debut so we can give you guys our review on that and who knows what else.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're going to have a lost guest.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_03]: There might be that thingy on Saturday, which I need to... Yeah, thank you for reminding me about that, because I want to talk to these two about it after the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'll tell you after the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, final thought time!
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes I wish there was a delay button that I could hit that would dump the stream so I could just say it and then dump it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, someday when we're real radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Angel, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, Nintendo DS is going to be cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: Err.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, Explicit, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: 33 days and still counting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Jesus Christ.
[SPEAKER_03]: my final thought is yes chat room there will be some outside the box this week because we've got Lanky Style and Rice Princess back and they're going to be reviewing the Dear Friends concert from this last Monday which is why they weren't able to make it this week and there was some other stuff going on which really exciting news Orange Lounge Radio is going to get some nice exposure I can't say much more than that we'll know more as the week goes on Loki I better not hear any crap about next week not this week
[SPEAKER_02]: Robot Chicken, which will feature a segment called A Day in the Life of Mary-Kate and Ashley Olsen.
[SPEAKER_02]: No crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just when I thought we were going to get through one week without it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The final word of the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki has his handout, which means I guess he has an idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you know, you have another thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just going to say, Jamie's being such a dumb-o, Beth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Jamie, in response to that, I will give you the final word of the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: See you next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, the final word of the day.
[SPEAKER_19]: So?
[SPEAKER_26]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_26]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_26]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_16]: I grew up in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_16]: I grew up in the midst of Polk Street, hanky code, poppers, San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_16]: So that's my childhood.
[SPEAKER_16]: So I feel really comfortable in talking about it.
[SPEAKER_16]: My parents owned a bookstore on Polk Street, and my mother was in charge of the gay porn, which is crazy.
[SPEAKER_16]: She would pull out these books and show me to talk about it.
[SPEAKER_16]: This book, this book, it's called Ace Master.
[SPEAKER_11]: What is an Ace Master?
[SPEAKER_11]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what an Ace Master is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why do you need an Ace Master?
[SPEAKER_16]: This book is an Ace Master.
[SPEAKER_16]: I thought this is a gay, the book for gay, because mommy know about the gay.
[SPEAKER_16]: The gay, they like ass.
[SPEAKER_16]: They do.
[SPEAKER_16]: They like ass so much, you know.
[SPEAKER_16]: They like ass and...
[SPEAKER_16]: But they like AIDS too much, you know that?
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to have AIDS in moderation You cannot have AIDS all the time Because if you have AIDS all the time
[SPEAKER_16]: There is a boy and his name is Paul and the mommy like Paul you know he's a nice nice boy but he's gay and he only like to sing you know
[SPEAKER_16]: He's like an ace and Judy Garland, and that's all.
[SPEAKER_15]: And what kind of life is he like that?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know, there's an ace and an ace over the rainbow, and that's all.
[SPEAKER_11]: What kind of life?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know why they do this.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, I have to look at this book as an ace, mister.
[SPEAKER_15]: That mommy gonna look at this book.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm gonna look at it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Mommy, look at mommy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Gonna look at Ace Mister now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Mommy gonna look at Ace Mister now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Look at mommy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, look at mommy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ace Mister.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought I was shocked, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was so shocked.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was just ass right away, you know.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was a radical shock.
[SPEAKER_15]: I thought there would be table of contents, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you very much everybody.
[SPEAKER_26]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, that's going to do it for Orange Lounge Radio tonight, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks so, so much for tuning in and listening and supporting us and voting for us in different places when we ask you guys to and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: We love the OL Army.
[SPEAKER_03]: We keep doing this for you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: You help make this interactive show what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we appreciate that, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a great night, which is going to happen now as you are going to get disconnected from the stream, but just reconnect in like 15 to 20 seconds, and you will resume hearing a bunch of DDR, 2DX, and Dance Media favorites.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good one, everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good night.