[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of March 21st, 2005.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your internet radio home for discussion on rhythm and music gaming and all the news on video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, everybody out there in podcast subscribing land.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you very much for deciding to check us out.
[SPEAKER_02]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we are, the Orange Lounge Radio podcast, dedicated to what gamers really want to know out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, my name is Sky, Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Join me as always.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say hello to DarkSakura, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yo, what up, my homies?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, and also say hello to Loki, Matt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: Silent Hill 3, all day
[SPEAKER_03]: I've actually been cheating.
[SPEAKER_02]: What part of Silent Hill have you been in?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm still in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_03]: Silent Hill 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does this have anything to do with the recent thunderstorms we've been having in the area here in Sacramento?
[SPEAKER_02]: You call that a storm?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, but you know, for this area, it's a pretty big storm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Weather wind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, no, it was... It had really nothing to do with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just we were playing with the... Trying to see if we were going to sell our Pro Action replay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we just put in a bunch of codes and I was playing on Silent Hill 4 with the Heather beam.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, with the sexy beam.
[SPEAKER_03]: And with her magical transformation into Super Magical Girl Heather.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get this wand, and when you equip it, you get a transformation sequence on top of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't played... Silent Hill 3 is like... I played a lot of Silent Hill 2 and I played a lot of Silent Hill 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: I somehow completely skipped over 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how that happened, so... I need to give you back your 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: I found it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, you do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Give it back.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know it's in good hands.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, is that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just Silent Hill 3?
[SPEAKER_03]: Some Final Fantasy XI, though hardly any.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I just thought I'd ask.
[SPEAKER_03]: I usually sleep when it starts raining.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's two things that are guaranteed to put me to sleep.
[SPEAKER_03]: One is being a passenger in a car.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the other is rain, especially rain on metal.
[SPEAKER_03]: So when it rains when I'm in a car, it's an instant coma.
[SPEAKER_03]: But thunder, rain, it puts me to sleep.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't sleep in the thunder.
[SPEAKER_02]: I grew up in that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wake up too quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Loki, what have you been up to?
[SPEAKER_02]: What have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been playing actually some different games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Other than Final Fantasy XI, I picked up Gran Turismo 4 and a game called Dog's Life.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is Dog's Life?
[SPEAKER_02]: Now this is different than Nintendogs, which we've talked about previously.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's Dog's Life?
[SPEAKER_01]: Dog's Life is basically this game where you play a dog and you run around and do what dogs do, like sniff smells and, you know,
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, so there's actually a button to crap?
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, it's a trick you have to learn.
[SPEAKER_01]: To crap and fart.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's great about the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like learning how to throw a fireball in Street Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just down towards punch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But this game, it's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's more kind of a collection game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really kind of meant for little kids.
[SPEAKER_01]: But what's weird, though, is even though it's meant for little kids, there's a lot of this really crude humor that's in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a little odd.
[SPEAKER_01]: but um the plot line is kind of seems like it's ripped from 101 Dalmatians a dog's been kidnapped by some woman named Mrs. Peach that makes dog food or something I don't know what exactly that's about but anyways um so she's kidnapping the dog and I haven't even really gotten that all I've been doing is running around in smell-o-vision which you can actually see the smells which is kind of neat you collect smells or whatever and then you get a bone or whatever and then
[SPEAKER_01]: Or you can, you know, collect smells and race a dog and then you get to become this small little dog and run around.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just interesting, but one of the things I've been passing my time with is shitting, grabbing my shit, and then flinging it at people.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's quite fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, for example, I jumped on top of a van and took a crap and then just ran away and then, like...
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, just like small stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, taking this out of context, like if we were to clip up the audio of this, and so you wouldn't know he was talking about a dog video game, that'd be quite hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very incriminating.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll have to save it for a promo.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, how's Gran Turismo?
[SPEAKER_01]: Gran Turismo I played for about five minutes, just I played a couple of the arcade stuff, because I've been kind of mainly playing this dog game.
[SPEAKER_01]: But anyways, Gran Turismo...
[SPEAKER_02]: He's more into crapping on vans than driving them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, so I was playing Gran Turismo, and I had to remind myself why I sucked at Gran Turismo.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's maybe because I can't steer for shit in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: But anyways, you start it up, and it starts playing this really opera-sounding music, and it's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, the graphics are really good, except the background and the audience, they're still 2D.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're still flat and not moving.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yet the game boasts on the back that the audience reacts to...
[SPEAKER_01]: like what you do and the only guys that are like a ooh ah type of thing or i saw camera flashes and that's about it i didn't see the audience moving they're just kind of looking like like um jerry blank's dad in strangers of candy that's a reference nobody's gonna get whatever that's why they have to watch the movie when it comes out all right but um so that's what happened there um
[SPEAKER_01]: But it was really good.
[SPEAKER_01]: The second race I did was on an off-road course.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I have to mention beforehand, they recreated all the tracks from the first game.
[SPEAKER_01]: In this game.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's really cool, first off.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's like, I forget, 100 tracks, 600 cars.
[SPEAKER_01]: You start off with 240.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's like a ton to unlock.
[SPEAKER_01]: And there's a ton of cars there.
[SPEAKER_01]: The first car I played as was a Ford Focus, because that's what I drive.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I decided to see how well of a race car that is.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's not.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then I tried playing...
[SPEAKER_01]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: So, um, but I like it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I gotta, you know, get into playing it more, and if I get frustrated, let's cheat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to hearing more about what you think about that game in the future.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, myself, I'm still on the same games I was last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been playing Phantasy Star Online and Zelda Minish Cap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been making a little bit of progress in both.
[SPEAKER_02]: I now have two characters at level 10 in Phantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: It's insane.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, pretty much just been playing those same games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Haven't had a whole lot of time to play any new stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Besides the fact I went to the arcade and I played, you know, some In the Groove, which is that new dance game that's kind of trying to take DDR's throne.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, what is on everybody's mind this week is the PSP is coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I'm too broke to get one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bah humbug.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do you say bah humbug?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just to be contrary, I'm actually getting one.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, you're the lucky one that can actually get one of these.
[SPEAKER_02]: I, unfortunately, am too poor to get one right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody should send me a free one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, somebody should.
[SPEAKER_02]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's nice to want.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to get your hands on a PSP, if you want to be one of the first, well, you have to live in San Francisco because actually at the Sony Metreon, they're going to have a midnight sale today.
[SPEAKER_02]: 12.01am on the dot Thursday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the other part of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: For those of you guys that are too lazy to pre-order, reserve, that kind of stuff, the Metron is going to sell them on a first-come, first-served basis.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it'll be interesting to see what kind of people end up camping out this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's also Best Buy is doing the exact same thing as far as... But not the 12.01 thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're one of those people, you have to be the first to own it.
[SPEAKER_02]: More power to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get your ass on down to the Metreon and do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, they've definitely given you more to look forward to getting it first day because there's actually games out for it, whereas the DS, we're still waiting for games to come out for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of which, this was another news story I wanted to mention about.
[SPEAKER_02]: The official launch of the PSP isn't happening until Thursday, but retailers are already selling the software.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing, there's a restriction on the street date for the PSP, but there's no rules against distributing the software before the hardware street date.
[SPEAKER_02]: People are out there and they are buying the games before the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're at Fry's, I was there.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had Wipeout, they had Metal Gear, they were there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And for those who don't know, Fry's is a major chain on the West Coast here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fry's Electronics.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of places I'm hearing are getting the game, so I don't understand why you would want to buy the game when you don't have the system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe you want to oogle over the instruction manual, or you just want to hold the disc in your hand.
[SPEAKER_02]: and confirm that it's not going to play in a normal CD player?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a smart way to build the hype, though, to go ahead and start making some money on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess, to have the display boxes out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I did think that they should have done like how they did with the Dreamcast, what Blockbuster did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blockbuster had a deal where you could rent Japanese Dreamcasts and play Sonic Adventure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, they had to send them all back, but you could actually rent just those two.
[SPEAKER_03]: They should do something like that with the PSP, I thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: you know that would be a way to
[SPEAKER_03]: Let people see what it was like.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they have the kiosks and stores now, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: A few, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've heard some folks have played the PSP hands-on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some places have got demo units for the staff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the PSP is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure there'll be plenty of news all over the internet about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're just kind of waiting to get our hands on one, and we'll definitely give you our feedback.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will all have to share Jamie's PSP if she's willing to share next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that's actually Dan's PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm going to bring him next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, steal it from Dan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whenever we have it, I'll bring him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan can live without it for 30 minutes while we tape this podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reminder, guys, if you ever have any feedback on the Orange Lounge Radio To Go edition, you can send us an email.
[SPEAKER_02]: The email address is togo, T-O-G-O, at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Since we talked about the PSP, let's talk about the competitor, the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: DS just rolled out recently in the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, okay, you know what though?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's weird for me to call the DS the PSP competitor.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that a lot of folks want to say, DS, PSP, DS, and it's like a big fight, but honestly, to me, and that's the way I felt about the two systems at first, especially at E3, but to me now...
[SPEAKER_02]: Both systems really are incredibly different, and they really both have different things to offer, such as the PSP actually has games on launch date.
[SPEAKER_02]: DS has, you know, the innovation touchscreen and all that other stuff, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's hard for me to compare the two.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, is there a comparison for you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a difference between your DS and the great game launcher.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder if you can still shoot games out.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to twist it pretty hard, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I'm curious about, if the PSP is still going to be a great game launcher.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remind us again about what was going on in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a failsafe built in so that you wouldn't hurt the games or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Something or the other.
[SPEAKER_03]: that if you got too aggressive with the system and twisted it you know sometimes, you know I used to do it all the time with the old game gear and everything with the Nomad sometimes you get so into the game that you twist it just a bit like if you're doing a racing game or something but if you twist it in that manner it would shoot the game out you'll shoot somebody's eye out with that thing
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, sorry, I just wanted to get that out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get to the DS story.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually just launched in the UK recently, and it sold 87,000 units in the first two days.
[SPEAKER_02]: That makes the DS the biggest hardware launch in the UK to date.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are calling this over Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: The general manager of Nintendo UK, David Yarrington, says, "...an unprecedented success, breaking all expected sales figures."
[SPEAKER_02]: and even exceeding our expectations.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good news for the Nintendo folks in the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now if we could just get some damn games!
[SPEAKER_02]: Where's my Animal Crossing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Where's my Castlevania?
[SPEAKER_02]: Give it to me now!
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, in DS news, this was a really big thing that was going around this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, if you look in the recent issue of Nintendo Power, that's what I'm hearing,
[SPEAKER_02]: Under Namco's planned DS titles, you can actually see Katamari Damacy DS is being planned.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is so cool to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I'm kind of wondering how you're going to control this, but you have any thoughts on this, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you're a big Katamari Damacy fan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like that Pac-Man Marble Madness game that they had at E3, trackball.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do a trackball style with the stylus.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting thoughts, like a little trackball.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_01]: That was my thought, too, as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Either that, or you'd use the directional pad as one analog, and the four buttons on the other side as the other analog, sort of.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was kind of wondering how the whole two-screen thing is going to work in Katamari Damacy DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, is the top screen strictly for the King's package, or how's that going to work?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, probably be just, you know, stretched out, maybe a map on the bottom or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's typical for DS games, have your little map on the bottom.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then again, Kanamari Namashi, you know, I kind of would have liked a nicer map in that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would be kind of neat, though, that if you are using the buttons and everything on the normal screen, and then on the lower screen, as your ball gets bigger, you know how your field of vision gets bigger, your map expands.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, that'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some good ideas there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll see what the future brings for Katamari Namashi DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very excited about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very happy about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also in DS news, I have one other story about the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a quick one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Majesco has announced that they're going to bring two new DS games out later this year, one of them being ATV Quad Frenzy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's, you know, four-wheel in action on your DS, 40 different tracks, and you can upgrade your ride using the stylus system.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's got Wi-Fi support.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the other game is Texas Hold'em Poker.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm just kind of going, do we need another poker game?
[SPEAKER_03]: To quote the best line ever from Mystery Science Theater 3000, the movie, well, whoop-de-shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is with the popularity of all these poker games?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I keep seeing all these cheap Game Boy and PlayStation poker games for sale at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it just because of the show?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not just that.
[SPEAKER_03]: When I was at Fry's last night, they were selling poker tables, poker sets, just everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it seriously the popularity of that celebrity poker or what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Poker is the new bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's funny you should bring up Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_02]: Banning Solitaire from computers and Minesweeper as well I'm not saying from every computer, you can do what you want in your house But from state computers and state offices like at the DMV, state insurance companies, things like that That's smart, disgruntled the DMV workers more But they're joking around calling this the country's first anti-solitaire legislation
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm just kind of thinking...
[SPEAKER_02]: This has really become the new age time sink here.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know, I see it happen at my company where I work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I walk around and when people are feeling unproductive, I see Bejeweled and what are all those other games they have on like Yahoo and PopCap?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Insaniquarium I've seen, the Zuma is the other one.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't need to be working my job.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't have time to be working.
[SPEAKER_03]: When you're, you know, handling... When I handle something anywhere between...
[SPEAKER_03]: 15 to 20 bankruptcy desk girl accounts doing their analyses by hand.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: They should have all of that locked out.
[SPEAKER_02]: People that work in construction and jobs like that where you're not necessarily behind a desk probably get pissed off at these kind of stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially in North Carolina where it's like, damn right my tax dollars shouldn't be going to people playing solitaire all day.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, doing it on your breaks, one thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And to folks at works credit, a lot of folks play Bejeweled on their breaks and that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just glad that I can still check my school stuff during my lunch.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I miss checking my live journal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, did you have something you wanted to share?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to mention that Tuesday, or at least this last Tuesday, the Matrix beta has ended.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I had to say they did it in a really interesting way.
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently, the...
[SPEAKER_01]: The Matrix was being cleansed by a fire virus, so people started bursting into flames.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I actually, I have some other crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: The sky turned into a bunch of eyeballs.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I actually have a video here for Rob to see real quick.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is creepy as fucking hell.
[SPEAKER_01]: And basically, you know, eyes floating around, the sky turns bright red and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, I guess at the very end of the game, once it was done, the
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: It says, jack out now, discomfort will be extreme.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: There are signs in the club, like, time is running out, you are in violation, you are in violation, you know, you cannot hide, and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And apparently gigantic brawls were happening, where, like, some of the actual people from the game, or the movies, like Seraph and stuff, were fighting agents, and just nuts stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_01]: They've got, like, you know, there was... That is crazy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fire virus people catching on fire, it's just...
[SPEAKER_01]: It was really interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Matrix Online folks got pretty clever with how they're going to end their beta.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you imagine you're playing World of Warcraft and then suddenly your character just bursts into flames?
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't really play the beta that much.
[SPEAKER_01]: If I actually jacked in and saw this, I'd be like, what the hell is going on?
[SPEAKER_01]: There's beams of light shooting down from the sky and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, your character literally just gets bent over backwards.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sort of looks like the T-1000 getting shot with shotgun shells.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nuts.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that's a really good sign, at least, of how the actual game's going to be.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because if they're putting this much detail into the beta to bring up all the hype from this, you've got to wonder what the actual game's going to be like.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that, I think, will be pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got to give my hands off to them.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a pretty clever idea there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope this doesn't become a trend in MMOs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like on April Fool's Day, can you imagine some different MMOs doing that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Final Fantasy XI suddenly turned the behemoths loose in the middle of the city.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, that sounds like something they would have done on Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, I had five wanderers come by and axe me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, in another time, I was lucky enough that I was high enough level.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was left with...
[SPEAKER_03]: Six hit points after taking one hit from Wanderer and my ass ran like hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of World of Warcraft, you guys, just because I was talking about MMOs and stuff and we were talking about the various ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: World of Warcraft hit 1.5 million users this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's really all there is to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game just keeps getting bigger.
[SPEAKER_02]: Won't stop going.
[SPEAKER_02]: Meanwhile, I'm all getting back into PSO.
[SPEAKER_02]: Am I behind the times or what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm still apparently paying for it, I'll play Well you know there's some news coming out on the new PSO We'll be talking about that in upcoming weeks as more news comes out Alright, and of course we here at Orange Lounge Radio on the to-go edition We are not only interested in bringing you the gaming news you really want to know But we want to better your life And who better to better your life with some advice Than our very own DarkSakura with her advice column
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, what are you going to share with us tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Today's tip is how to cross a piranha-infested river.
[SPEAKER_02]: And how would one cross the river?
[SPEAKER_03]: Number one, do not cross if you have an open wound.
[SPEAKER_03]: Piranhas are attracted to blood.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number two, avoid areas with netted fish, docks where fish are cleaned, and areas around bird rookeries.
[SPEAKER_03]: Piranhas may become habituated to feeding in these areas and may be more aggressive there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number three,
[SPEAKER_03]: Stay out of the water when piranhas are feeding.
[SPEAKER_03]: When large numbers of piranhas are attacking prey, a true feeding frenzy, they may snap a bite at anything around them.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you see them feeding, stay away or well upriver.
4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cross the river at night.
[SPEAKER_03]: Virtually every species of piranha rests at night, and when awakened they will swim away rather than attack.
[SPEAKER_03]: Piranhas are more active at dawn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some large adults may hunt in the evening.
5.
[SPEAKER_03]: Swim or walk across quickly and quietly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do not try to create a large disturbance in the water that might awaken piranhas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Be aware.
[SPEAKER_03]: Piranhas are freshwater tropical fish.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the wild, they only exist in South America.
[SPEAKER_03]: and slow-moving rivers, backwaters, or floodplain lakes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Piranhas generally do not live in either mountain lakes or streams.
[SPEAKER_03]: The water is too cold and flows too fast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Piranhas generally do not attack humans or large animals unless they are already dead or injured.
[SPEAKER_03]: During the dry season, however, when food is scarce, piranhas can be more aggressive.
[SPEAKER_03]: When driving cattle across a river suspected of containing piranhas, farmers will sometimes sacrifice a sick or injured animal downstream before letting the herd enter the water.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, the final piece of advice, Matt?
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't cross the river in South America.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't go near the piranhas.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you have to, bring a gun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, dynamite.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dynamite.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for that helpful piece of advice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just in case I should ever find myself in a piranha-infested river.
[SPEAKER_02]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll keep them coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: From piranhas to turtles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles Mutant Melee is coming out on Xbox, GameCube, and PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually, it isn't coming out, it just came out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is by the same folks, by the way, who did Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix, the folks in Konami, Hawaii actually put this game together.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is kind of, I guess if you really wanted to roughly describe this game, it's Mario Party with Ninja Turtles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not just the Ninja Turtles though, 16 other playable characters, Casey Jones, Shredder, etc, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rated T for teens, it's a budget game, $19.99.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would make me happy if it has Usagi Yojimbo in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have the list of characters, so no idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know, I think it's weird that there's all these Mario Party knockoffs, yet I have yet to play one as good as Mario Party.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they have Mario Party Advance now too.
[SPEAKER_01]: I saw that store.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all about Mario Party 6, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played the Sonic one, which I didn't really care for.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played the Crash Bandicoot one, which I really, really didn't care for.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played the Namco one a little bit, which was eh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just leave it to the folks who do it best.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lastly, a little story on Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this is interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: On a Korean Xbox website, the official Korean Xbox website, it says, coming soon, and it calls this game the X-Pack, which is a Halo 2 expansion pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: No comment officially yet as to what this might mean for American audiences.
[SPEAKER_03]: That means that Canada will get it first.
[SPEAKER_02]: But wouldn't that be interesting?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, you get all these people to buy this game, and a lot of people were saying that the ending to Halo 2 was a little lacking, unfinal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Geez, surprise!
[SPEAKER_02]: Now you gotta spend another $20 on the expansion pack to really finish the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tell you, Canada's gonna have it before we do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because remember, they got the Crystal X-Box.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: We didn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: They get all their neat stuff there first.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Their Christmas bundle came with Halo 2 and some other really big game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where we got, what, two off-road games?
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: FIFA, soccer, and some other thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tennis.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, is this something that... I know you guys aren't really huge on Halo, but what do you think of this whole expansion pack?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sucker America into buying the game and then release the expansion pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: More fodder for my motion sickness.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't think of any other companies that do that, Maxis.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess it's just part of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Halo 2, bust it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I always assumed they were setting up for Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be interesting if it's an expansion pack.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're setting up for Halo 3, alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wouldn't doubt it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'd be like Halo 2K.
[SPEAKER_01]: See, they're worried.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're worried about one game coming out in that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Timesplayers 3, Future Perfect.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, okay, that game has the oddest characters ever.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're the only fan of that game I've ever met.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also like Twisted Metal a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do love Twisted Metal.
[SPEAKER_01]: That game rocks.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love the giant eyeball game where, you know, the sky eyeballs.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think you're thinking of Matrix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to do it for this podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you guys for subscribing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final thoughts, Loki?
[SPEAKER_01]: I wish all MMOs had giant red skies with eyeballs and lasers flying out of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what's really missing from Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_02]: Laser beams on their freaking heads?
[SPEAKER_01]: Laser beams and floating eyeballs.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the floating eyeballs...
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got to say, that's almost a ripoff of Lord of the Rings.
[SPEAKER_01]: Almost.
[SPEAKER_01]: Getting close.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought is I'm very sad to hear that all my friends who saw The Ring 2 said it sucked, because I was looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dead puppies aren't much fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not.
[SPEAKER_01]: And remember, folks, Robot Chicken, check your local listings, 11.30 on Sundays.
[SPEAKER_01]: and I know it's being replayed throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, have a good one you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for subscribing.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for subscribing to our podcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next update.