[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of March 7th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your internet radio home for discussion on rhythm and music gaming, and all the news on video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody, welcome back to our podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks so much for subscribing.
[SPEAKER_02]: and support in our little talk program we got here dedicated to video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, we're just a sideshow to the website www.orangeloungeradio.com where we actually have a 24-hour-a-day, 7-day-a-week station where we play a lot of video game music, especially stuff from Konami's Beatmania series, or Bomani series, I should say, as well as DDR, etc., etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of good stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then other video game stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not just limited to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then our live programs we do throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joining me as always is my awesome co-host.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say hello to DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_01]: I have diseased lungs.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've kind of got the 80-year-old grandma thing going on right now because of your infection.
[SPEAKER_01]: I sound like a broken-necked ghost.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I hope you feel better.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Loki is here as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hello, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eating my five pounds of gummy bears.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gummy bears.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stronger than the average bear.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, these things are like crack.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, honestly, I gotta put them down, because otherwise I will feel sick.
[SPEAKER_03]: And because, for some reason, your body does not like five pounds of gelatin inside of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Throwing up gummy is no fun, either.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I've heard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, let's get into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to get to some gaming news, but let's talk about what's going on in our gaming world lately.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, what kind of games have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Tekken 5, Tekken 5, Tekken 5, and Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_02]: How's Tekken 5 going?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's awesome, but Mishima Jinpachi is a bastard.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, really quickly, tell me the best thing about Tekken 5 and the worst thing about Tekken 5.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's always been Jin.
[SPEAKER_01]: The worst thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Jinpachi And his stupid gut fireball And then Julia is like sucky to dodge it
[SPEAKER_02]: Devil Jin has his old moves.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm very happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you played a lot of the arcade mode where you earn the points so you can customize your character?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what we've been doing because we've got Eddie Gordo, we have Panda.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you like though how they have, have you played a lot of one player arcade because it has like the made up names that you play against and some of them are really funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think we did that, no we just were doing story mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check it out because if you play one player arcade you get to play against like fake personalities like it's a real arcade, it's really funny some of the names, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do like seeing the Roger Jr.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mokujin conversation.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Mokujin.
[SPEAKER_02]: I miss that guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is he?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I just haven't unlocked him yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've only unlocked a couple characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been playing a lot of Tekken 5 this week as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: He talks in woodblock language.
[SPEAKER_01]: You ever hear woodblocks like in Marching Band?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what he sounds like.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cool because in Tekken they all have their native languages.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's funny that Mokujin has a... And, of course, Roger Jr.
[SPEAKER_01]: is hanging out in Mommy's pouch speaking kangaroo.
[SPEAKER_02]: What does kangaroo sound like?
[SPEAKER_02]: Care to demonstrate?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Loki, what have you been up to this week in the game world?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been playing Final Fantasy XI, and I've been playing, well, I tried playing some Neo Contra, but for some reason it wasn't working.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I played some, actually, some arcade stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Alien vs. Predator all the way through, and I also played the guy game again.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're just determined to see as many boobs as possible, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ran a porn!
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not about the fact that there's boobs in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not really the point.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a fun party game, and the trivia is a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like Trivial Pursuit with boobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mario Party is a fun party game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The guy game is boobs.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a good trivia game, honestly, because there hasn't been a good You Don't Know Jack game for the home console system in a while, so this will have to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Besides it has boobies in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I was looking for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: As for me, this week I've been playing, well, Tekken 5 as well, but Jamie already mentioned that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I will mention I've been playing a lot of Final Fantasy Dawn of Souls, specifically Final Fantasy 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been trying to just get further along in that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I decided I was going to force myself to take a break from Final Fantasy 11 this week because, you know, I'm just, I'm ODing on it, honestly, and it's getting stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I need to take a minute to play some other games.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Final Fantasy 2, which, yeah, I go from one Final Fantasy to another, I know, big
[SPEAKER_02]: Big wow, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: But I figure, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I spent the money on Dawn of Souls.
[SPEAKER_02]: I ought to, you know, check it out and play it a little more.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, because I kind of gave up on Final Fantasy 1 because I was like, I already know this from the NES.
[SPEAKER_02]: I already know this story.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, the graphics, okay, I'm done with that now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Final Fantasy 2, it's still very fresh to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never really got into it, even when it was translated and out in ROM form on the internet years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never really got into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now I'm kind of getting into it and it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So,
[SPEAKER_03]: I also forgot to mention in the guy game, I got one point at the end of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got zero points because I bet on the wrong girl to win the guy challenge, I guess is what it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where basically they have to do something stupid topless or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I got it wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they reward you with some crew member, some big fat hairy guy that's doing like sultry stuff and I thought that was very hilarious.
Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's get into some video game news, some stuff that's actually going on out there this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Big news, Metal Gear Solid 4 is confirmed.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is going to be happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a press event in Berlin to celebrate the release of Metal Gear Solid 3 Snake Eater in Europe.
[SPEAKER_02]: The next game in the Metal Gear Solid series was confirmed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although Hideo Kojima always said that Metal Gear was kind of going to be a trilogy, of course these games sell very well and they're going to live on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just that Hideo Kojima is going to step aside in this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's just going to be executive producer.
[SPEAKER_02]: This time, Kenichiro Imezumi is going to be taking over as the title's producer.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we can expect some new things to come out of Metal Gear.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a Metal Gear fan, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: So what do you think about Hideo Kojima stepping aside?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think it's going to be a fresh look for the series?
[SPEAKER_01]: He's still going to have control over the basic elements.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's not going to let anything go outside his vision.
[SPEAKER_01]: As long as he's executive producer, I don't feel like producing your stupid ideas.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think things will be okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were talking about this on Outside the Box on Thursday night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kojima, he's been threatening to do it for a while, so it's not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, a perfect example would be the Silent Hill series.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember the original creator of it, but then you have Akira Yamaoka stepping up to actually write the series 3 and 4, whereas someone else is doing 1 and 2, and he was just doing the music for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it could be a good thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it is a good thing, actually, because...
[SPEAKER_03]: He's probably run out of, not really run out of ideas, but, you know, having some, you know, actual, someone else helping to create this, it'll be a little bit better because, you know, some fresh new ideas can come from it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, obviously, since he's still the executive producer of it, you know, it's not going to just turn into something awful like that you might see in, I don't know, a video game movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so we'll see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to seeing more stuff on Metal Gear Solid 4.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just think it needs to have Dave Snake again.
[SPEAKER_01]: I always call Solid Snake Dave Snake if you ever played through the first Metal Gear Solid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Metal Gear Solid are games I've watched and not played a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've played them a little bit, but not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Metal Gear Solid 3 was all about Big Boss.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing will trump the original Metal Gear for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: The truck have started to move.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, did they mention which console this is going to come out?
[SPEAKER_03]: Next Gen, probably?
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe it was Next Gen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have the story in front of me anymore, but I think it was Next Gen.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I'm wrong, I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you ever want to give feedback, by the way, if you want to yell at us for being wrong or whatever, you just want to say, hello, hi, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Our email address, togo, T-O-G-O, at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'd love to answer some viewer mail in the podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: We haven't gotten anything really appropriate for that yet, so something to think about.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have a question you'd like us to address on the podcast, send it over to go at orangelaunchradio.com ESRB, the Entertainment Software Rating Board, they have introduced a brand new rating.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how games are rated, very similar to movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have ratings such as Childhood, EC, Everyone, E, Teen, T, Mature, M, Very Rare, Adults Only, but you probably see that in the guy game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, but now they've got a brand new rating.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just unveiled a new rating.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called E10+.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to categorize those games that may not be necessarily family friendly, but they're not quite really worthy of a T rating as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Donkey Kong Jungle Beat would be an example of a game that would get like an E10 plus rating because it's kind of not really for everybody per se, but it's not really a game that needs to be teen rated either.
[SPEAKER_02]: So thoughts on that?
[SPEAKER_01]: is called They Should Rate It.
[SPEAKER_01]: Parents, do your research.
[SPEAKER_01]: Parents, do your job.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think the rating system does its job?
[SPEAKER_01]: The only good that comes of it is giving an overall indicator so that if a parent actually feels like doing their job, they can look at the game and get an idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: So where's the rating that's, um, if you're under 17 and you buy this, we're going to, um, sue the pants off you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or, or like, um,
[SPEAKER_03]: This game may cause you to go murder someone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Retarded idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a way for them to make money.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, um... First of all...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not necessarily going to be the store's fault.
[SPEAKER_01]: Having gone into my fiancé's store plenty of times, I see where someone will pick up a game, walk around the store with it, and put it on the bottom shelf.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, there shouldn't be any reason that the store should be held accountable for some other poor idiots, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, this is retarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: For example, Sir, I cannot reach that game on the high shelf.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you please get it down for me?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, there you go, got the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That doesn't stop anyone.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's discrimination against short people.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's midget discrimination.
[SPEAKER_02]: Poor midgets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is no one thinking of the midget gamer?
[SPEAKER_02]: Midgets want Grand Theft Auto 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_03]: What does it matter that they can reach the game?
[SPEAKER_03]: The person that's behind the counter shouldn't be selling the mature game to them anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's it matter?
[SPEAKER_02]: The parents shouldn't be giving the kids the money to buy the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: When I was in 6th grade, I was just under 5 feet.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I could reach up
[SPEAKER_01]: and grab something.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is retarded.
[SPEAKER_01]: How old is this senator?
[SPEAKER_02]: No idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be honest here, okay, violent games, I don't even see how these can be, you know, even close to being equal to like violent movies or violent TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just completely like two different things.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'd be like depicting a piece of art with blood in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just really sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it doesn't stop there, you guys, because also coming out on the Newswire this week, three Washington State representatives, Jim McCune, Jim McDermott, and Mary Lou Dickerson, they co-authored a bill that will hold game companies responsible if a minor commits a violent act that is seemingly inspired by a video game they played.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's even more stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's, yeah, that's not fair.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just straight up not fair.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's called...
[SPEAKER_01]: They're trying to find a scapegoat because parents don't want to take any responsibility for what their children do.
[SPEAKER_01]: The reason why their children are acting this way is because it's their own damn fault.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I would freaking pay to have a press conference to announce to all these parents that they're idiots.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you got the podcast.
[SPEAKER_01]: Parents of America, do your goddamn job.
[SPEAKER_01]: If your child is a little hellion, spank them!
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what's wrong with this whole United States?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is the goddamn balls have left the judicial system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where are the judges out there that go when these people go, Yeah, my kid killed this kid and he learned it in Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe he learned it because you're a bad parent.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll tell you what, she's on TV every night at 7 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_02]: Judge Judy, thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know...
[SPEAKER_01]: Watch the news.
[SPEAKER_01]: Watch the fucking news.
[SPEAKER_01]: Watch fucking CNN.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so-and-so killed so-and-so.
[SPEAKER_01]: And kids thinking, huh.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have violent tendencies.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to be on the news.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Next thing you're going to have Al-Qaeda suing Microsoft because they learned to fly airplanes in the buildings from Microsoft Flight Simulator.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all Microsoft's fault.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's always Microsoft's fault, but that's another story
[SPEAKER_02]: 60 Minutes was going to be airing a segment and it has to do with the battle between the families of a slain Alabama police officer I'm sorry, actually multiple Alabama police officers and the makers and the sellers of the Grand Theft Auto franchise because there was a lawsuit that was sparked by the deaths of three Alabama police officers who were killed by a teen who said he was inspired by Grand Theft Auto
[SPEAKER_02]: Talk about scapegoat.
[SPEAKER_01]: The game made me do it, Mommy!
[SPEAKER_01]: That's because Mommy facilitated him having the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: There were plenty of times I wanted games, and my mama wouldn't buy them for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: The arrest of Devin Moore, who is allegedly responsible for the crime, 18 years old.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's hangable.
[SPEAKER_02]: More allegedly said, life's like a video game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've gotta die sometime.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Games like Grand Theft Auto do not teach you how to kill.
[SPEAKER_03]: Games like Area 51 teach you how to kill.
[SPEAKER_03]: That gives you fucking, you know, hand-eye coordination and you get better aim playing some games like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the type of games that'll teach you how to kill is a game like Time Crisis or a gun game like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Grand Theft Auto, I push a button and it fires a gun.
[SPEAKER_03]: That David Chappelle skit
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, Ridge Racer taught me how to drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I'm playing Star Wars, I can't fly a space shuttle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Playing DDR doesn't teach me how to dance.
[SPEAKER_03]: Playing Karaoke Revolution doesn't make me any better at singing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, maybe a little bit, but not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the whole point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Games do not teach you much.
[SPEAKER_03]: They help you improve hand-eye coordination, but you don't really learn much from them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to sue the makers of Monopoly because I got a bad real estate deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's because of Monopoly.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to sue Parker Brothers for the game of life.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because you suck at it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not married and have six children.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I didn't start my life with $20,000.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm gonna sue the game of life for not allowing me to have two blue pegs in the front of the car, per the instruction manual.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I get called on that too, and that makes me upset.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, the Game of Life came out a long time ago when that was, like, not hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not okay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because it's old doesn't make it right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'm just, I'm serious, I'm not being serious here.
[SPEAKER_03]: You gotta play by Monopoly rules, you know, where you make up your own rules.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm being a little silly here, but honestly, if we can sue the video game, why can't I sue...
[SPEAKER_03]: Metal Gear Solid 3, Snake Eater.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just because I play the game does not mean I can survive in Vietnam.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, it does not work that way.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not in Vietnam, it's in Russia.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever, it's a jungle, they're all the same.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you sometimes dine on a tree frog?
[SPEAKER_02]: It also does not mean that I can eat snakes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or tree frogs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or alligators.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a lovely way to follow this up, since DarkSakura is talking about, you know, parents...
[SPEAKER_02]: Be responsible for your kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here is a segment for us to give back to the community.
[SPEAKER_02]: And DarkSakura is going to let you know how to better your life.
[SPEAKER_02]: We call this segment DarkSakura's Advice Column.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what are you going to be giving us advice on tonight, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_01]: Today's advice is how to escape if trapped in a lion cage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, this is good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number one, do not run.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, where would you run to?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're in a cage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lion cage is a big...
[SPEAKER_01]: 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Watch for signs of an attack.
[SPEAKER_01]: A low staccato growl combined with eye contact and a lashing tail usually indicate when an attack is likely.
3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Find a defensive tool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Moving very slowly, picking up anything within reach, a water bowl, bench, or anything else that may be used to fend off a charge.
4.
[SPEAKER_01]: Back away slowly.
5.
[SPEAKER_01]: Watch for mock charges.
[SPEAKER_01]: A lion may make several mock charges before actually attacking.
[SPEAKER_01]: It will run forward, then stop.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mock charging shows that a real attack is imminent.
6.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yell.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yell as loudly as you can.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lions are sensitive to noise.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yelling may discourage further charges.
7.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fend off the attack.
[SPEAKER_01]: Push its paws and head away from you with a nearby object.
8.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keep screaming as loudly as possible.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what my thing is?
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't fucking get caught in the cage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just because I played the Lion King game does not mean I can survive a lion attack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because I played Zookeeper does not mean I can... Moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we definitely need to get to a different topic.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's talk about another industry that ruins people's lives.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about Hollywood for a minute here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And when asked if the WWE wrestler played a creature, The Rock responded, no, I'm the one.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Jet Li's the one.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, Keanu Reeves is the one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm confused.
[SPEAKER_01]: Too many ones.
[SPEAKER_01]: Can't he be the, like, 11?
[SPEAKER_01]: Then he's 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm the 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, who knows if he is the main guy or not, because supposedly some sites are saying that he's playing this character that says Sarge, and The Rock was quoted earlier by Empire Online by saying, Without giving the movie away, I play the ultimate blank.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be great, but you don't know I'm blank.
[SPEAKER_02]: The blank part's being censored.
[SPEAKER_02]: So who knows what the hell he's doing in this movie, but he's involved with the Doom movie, and it'll be interesting to see if that movie is decent, like the game, or total crap, like Alone in the Dark.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is Ewan Bull attached to this movie?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do not think he's directing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, thank God.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is hope.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's one point to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh man, that guy does not need... I just got Alone in the Dark the other day.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got my screening copy from work.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still have yet to watch it because my friend is borrowing it this weekend to see how bad it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will come back and give my full review on that later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm scared because... Oh man, it's just bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: But honestly, The Rock...
[SPEAKER_03]: I think he's going to be pretty good because he was pretty funny in Be Cool, at least from the trailers I've seen.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's pretty versatile.
[SPEAKER_03]: He wants to go in the acting career, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I could see him as like an action star.
[SPEAKER_03]: He was good in the rundown, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd be willing to give it to him, other than Vin Diesel.
[SPEAKER_02]: He wants to fill Schwarzenegger's shoes so very badly.
[SPEAKER_02]: As long as he never runs for governor.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, actually, if you've ever seen the rundown, there was sort of a passing the torch in that movie where Arnold had a cameo and basically, I don't know, I didn't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never actually seen the rundown, but it looked good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And my dad said it was awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you know...
[SPEAKER_01]: The Rock is related to Rikishi, and both are related to the late Yokozuna.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did not know that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now you do.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know who would be a better role, though, for Doom?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hulk Hogan.
[SPEAKER_01]: He needs to do some things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hulk Hogan's man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Give Hulk Hogan a movie, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hulk Hogan needs work.
[SPEAKER_03]: He needs work more than, you know... His daughter does need work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, like Mr. Nanny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, Hulk Hogan's going to be in a reality show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I heard this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Lord.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be following him around, him and his daughter, and it's going to be like life as a celebrity or after being celebrity.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's supposed to be coming on TV.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just glad he retired from wrestling.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Hulk Hogan, he needs more work.
[SPEAKER_03]: because god damn it he's funny you can put him in like something ridiculous like Suburban Commando and you know that movie is so bad but still you can watch it and enjoy it that's the whole point it's fun it doesn't have to be good to be fun Mr. Nanny fun movies people are losing it they want to concentrate on whether a movie is good or bad just be fun fun movie
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's move on to another story here.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the biggest, duh, not a surprise of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo DS is getting brand new colors in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Granted, right now, but
[SPEAKER_02]: It's only a matter of time, kids, as far as I'm concerned.
[SPEAKER_02]: What colors are going to be happening?
[SPEAKER_02]: Graphite Black, Pure White are going to hit the streets on March 24th.
[SPEAKER_02]: And on April 21st, the DS will come out in Turquoise Blue and Candy Pink.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the Graphite Black one.
[SPEAKER_02]: No price increase for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: It costs the same as the standard colored DS, but Nintendo always does this.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is no surprise.
[SPEAKER_03]: How many times can you buy the Game Boy before you get tired?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I need to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And guess what, folks?
[SPEAKER_03]: Also coming out soon, because the DS is not the replacement for the Game Boy, the Game Boy Advance 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right, they're working on Game Boy Advance 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: The DS is its own little entity.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've got our thing down there for the great game shooter.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what's great, though, is you have the DS with hardly any games, and now when the Game Boy Advance 2 comes out, there won't be any games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just going to die off like the freaking, I don't know, Jaguar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Out of curiosity, is anyone here going to pick up a PSP on our launch day?
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got one reserved.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_01]: The great game launcher.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm on the fence.
[SPEAKER_02]: It kind of depends, because I have things going on in my personal life I have to pay for, and that's quite a bit of an investment.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if I have extra money, I want to get one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or you own an Atari Lynx.
[SPEAKER_02]: This isn't totally about video games, but then I think about, I go around at work, and I constantly see people that should be working playing on Yahoo Games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so it kind of makes me think that Yahoo Games kind of has a pretty decent impact on the gaming world.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or the people around you are slackers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that too.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I thought this was worth mentioning.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yahoo is actually going to be breaking into the mobile game area now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yahoo announced that it has launched its own game development studio because it acquired...
[SPEAKER_02]: Stadium Inc., another development studio, and they're going to have this new studio, Yahoo Games Studio.
[SPEAKER_02]: It already has, of course, the free multiplayer card and board games they have on their site.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now they're going to be working on mobile phone games, so this should be interesting, another way to waste your time.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to admit, Yahoo has some pretty addicting games on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have good games, but you've got to admit, also, mobile phone games are way overpriced.
[SPEAKER_03]: Way overpriced.
[SPEAKER_02]: True.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's interesting to see the mobile game world kind of expanding.
[SPEAKER_02]: And not just the N-Gage, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're still going with the N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_02]: They won't let that go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember the press release.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're still working on the N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're like, we're not done with the N-Gage yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, yes you are.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're all past it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why can't you get past it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Every serious gamer has said bye-bye to the N-Gage a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let it go.
[SPEAKER_01]: There is a time where they need to learn to let go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't wait to see the Engage tent again this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of our favorite companies, Square Enix, Square Enix, however you want to say it, or as we say it, Squeenix, they have, the president, Yoichi Wada, said an interesting quote, I think that over half our income and profit will be based on network content, including games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I-Speed Internet is becoming like cable where everyone has it so why not embrace the future?
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XII, Kingdom Hearts 2, Ergot
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, one more story for you guys tonight, and this one's for Loki, because I saw him post about this game on his live journal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo is letting the dogs out on April 21st Puppy Time
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even know why I'd want this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably because I'm just sad that there's no other games for the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let me tell you what you can do with this.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can use the touchscreen pad.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can call out the puppy's name by yelling in the microphone.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can yell, stay, sit.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's over 150 items that you can use to entertain the dogs with.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll have to get it because my fiance won't let me have a dog because she's...
[SPEAKER_03]: I also have this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, the virtual dogs and everything will work even when the DS is in sleep mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to do it for tonight's podcast, everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks a bunch for subscribing to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any last words, DarkSakura?
Puppy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, it's another long podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Over 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: We rock.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we've just got a lot to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's my final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got big mouths.
[SPEAKER_02]: But thank you for listening to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once again, watch Robot Chicken if you haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: See Appleseed if it's nearby in one of your theaters because it's an awesome movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: And kick an Ultra Kade machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kick an Ultra Kade machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for subscribing, everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for subscribing to our podcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next update.