[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, June 29th, 2008, is the latest game in a popular series going 8-bit, Diablo 3 is finally announced, and we talk on air to Tommy Tallarico from Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are that podcast on the internet dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_03]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_03]: You might know me as Sky if you talk to us online in our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: But also joining us tonight, as always, the one, the only, the lovely, happiest bunny on the farm, one and only, truly, spectacular... Get on with it!
[SPEAKER_03]: Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's just trying to butter me up for something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can I have a dollar?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, because I don't have a dollar.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't have a dollar.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can have some of my Diet Cherry Pepsi.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm in a festive mood tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been busy.
[SPEAKER_00]: A busy boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have been a very busy boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was out of town most of the weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was marching in a big parade this morning, which was fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know what would make you cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: What would make me cry?
[SPEAKER_00]: You'll find out during what I've played this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well we'll get to that in just a sec.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I wouldn't be able to get to How Was Your Gaming Week if I wasn't able to introduce the one and only Tech Master, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to figure out something that I was talking about before we started the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I can't remember the damn name of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's bugging me.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was it that we were talking about before the show?
[SPEAKER_02]: We talk about a lot of things before the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was saying that song should be in a side-scrolling game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, like the new Konami one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember the name of the game though, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: We played a track by Akira Yamaoka.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know him from the dude that does all the music of Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_03]: He also contributes to one of our favorite gaming series ever, Beatmania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that particular track was from Beatmania Gold.
[SPEAKER_03]: Playback Hate You was the name of that song.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Loki was saying it's a pretty awesome song that should be in another game he was thinking of.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well speaking of games, we've got a lot of gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got an interview tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tommy Tallarico is here.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's going to be joining us during Part B. But first, we've got to start the show as we always do with a little bit of how is your gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, what did you play this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: I downloaded the, when we were at Weeby Toys, aka Toys R Us, I downloaded the Iron Man DS game demo.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it kind of sucked, but the controls were really cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, the controls are kind of complicated, but they were pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so what are the controls, kind of?
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you describe it?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you've got your... It actually moves up, left, down, right, you know, just like any regular game doesn't do, like, flight commands.
[SPEAKER_00]: But when you shoot, you touch the touch screen on your little radar pad, and it controls the direction you shoot.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you can actually move your thumb all around and have them circle around and shoot like that and still move in different directions.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that part was cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you pick up bombs and lock on, but it was fairly difficult from the get-go.
[SPEAKER_00]: And honestly...
[SPEAKER_00]: That type of game needs a bigger screen, so that didn't quite fly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, here's the game I was talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Otomedius, which is a shooter game with cleavage-heavy characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of a Gradius spinoff, and it's in arcades in Japan right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's supposed to be coming to the Xbox 360 on September 25th in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, in high def on the 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, comment from our chat room at chat.orangelaunchradio.com SSJ100Matt, going back to Iron Man, says, And I thought Jamie was anti-Tony Stark.
[SPEAKER_00]: Only the... Well, okay, I like the character.
[SPEAKER_00]: I hate what a big dick he's been in the whole, you know, regular Marvel continuity.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I like the character, and the movie was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, the game, not nearly as cool as the movie.
[SPEAKER_00]: Imagine Babies
[SPEAKER_03]: That's Miklatov's peering through the door.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's going back to Kansas, so he's waving goodbye forever.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: Live radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it sucked.
[SPEAKER_00]: I didn't want to wave the rattle at the stupid baby.
[SPEAKER_03]: How does Imagine Babies work?
[SPEAKER_03]: I picture it like Nintendogs, the way you describe it, like instead of shaking the head.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is a stupid game.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's for little children.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's kind of cute, but I'm like, I don't want any real children.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why do I want fake children?
[SPEAKER_00]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: because fake children you can do stuff to and CPS won't get called.
[SPEAKER_00]: They don't let you do crap to them in the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can't pick them up and throw them out the window.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't dangle them out the window all Michael Jackson style in real life because that's wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: But in a video game, you can do anything.
[SPEAKER_00]: At any rate, it sucked ass.
[SPEAKER_00]: And we moved to a new Ragnarok server because our old one has sort of gone to shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm playing on Void RO now.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: A lot cooler, actually.
[SPEAKER_00]: Very cool people run it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, oh, oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you sure you're done?
[SPEAKER_00]: I also laughed my ass off watching Dan play GTA 4.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was so funny that happened?
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: FearTheClaw in chat.orangelandtrader.com says, if Imagine Babies is like Nintendogs, does that mean you can pet them to make them happy?
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be creepy.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can wave a rattle at them.
[SPEAKER_00]: The first thing it has you do is it shows you the baby.
[SPEAKER_00]: And there's this dark background with a patch of light.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you have to wave the rattle in that patch of light as it moves around.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the closer you stay in the middle of it, the happier the baby gets or some shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't go towards the light!
[SPEAKER_02]: Run away, Carol Ann!
[SPEAKER_02]: I won't get paid if you die!
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't get to play as much because I've been working on web pages.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so I played lots of Grand Theft Auto 4, as usual.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still fascinated by the stupid swing set.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what we do during lunch now.
[SPEAKER_02]: That and fire rockets at each other with friendly fire turned off so that we just fly into the air and just take damage from the impact.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, we're easily amused.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I also played over here actually the other day because I got Rob a copy for his birthday and it's odd that I'm playing his copy of the game before I played mine which I bought weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Blastworks and we actually played that a bit and that was funny because people were amused by it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were like, look at your ship, it's like taking up the whole screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, I'm trying to think if I played anything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I checked out that... I don't remember what it's called now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like some cooking guide.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can't decide what to eat or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of a neat concept.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really a game, but just a recipe book.
[SPEAKER_02]: It teaches you how to do different techniques and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's a lot of video and stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And plus, you can make your own shopping lists and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: The recipes were kind of limited.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish you could add your own.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something that needs to be done over here, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although there was that Gourmet Chef game that came out over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what that is, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots of cooking games getting popular over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: which kind of sucks if it's similar to that it should be just like kind of American Idol what American Idol is a karaoke revolution you know where they berate you for sucking that's what should be like Cookie Mama but instead of Mama Will Fix It it's you're fucking lame you suck take this game back to the store because you suck I'm coming to your house and killing you and your family get out of my face fuck off
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how the show is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a very hard shooter at first, but once you get the hang of it, there's a certain delicate balance to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've probably heard this game by now is based on Tamiki Fighters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Imagine Katamari Damacy meets a shooter game.
[SPEAKER_03]: As you destroy ships, you can run over them and attach them to your ship.
[SPEAKER_03]: As you can imagine, the ship gets quite huge.
[SPEAKER_03]: The trick is having to balance using the collapse button.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: I was feeling a little bit retro this week, and it'll probably be explained why when we get into the news a little later, but I decided to go pick up an old GameCube game, the Mega Man Anniversary Collection.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanted to pick up because I was suddenly getting a hankering for playing Mega Man again, and I'm sure as we get into tonight's news, you'll understand why if you haven't already heard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I know there's a lot of people that talk smack about the GameCube version of Mega Man Anniversary Collection because the buttons are switched, and you can't
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't turn them around very easily.
[SPEAKER_03]: But look, let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_03]: It cost me six bucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's hard to complain with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm having fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the old Mega Man games all over again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was playing a little bit of Mega Man 8 because the anime scenes in Mega Man 8 are so crappy and the voiceovers and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I laugh every time.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I want to go back and play the old school Mega Mans too because, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: They're all there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like Mega Man 1 through 8, and then the fighting games you unlock, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the fighting games are kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got my work cut out for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean, I've played them before on MAME, and I think they're on GameTap?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they're on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I've definitely played them before, and they're okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, they're on the... I played them in the arcade, because they're on the Ultracade.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though they were never released here, they were on Ultracade.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, years ago, I played it on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Allgames.com is currently down from what I understand there was a virus something that hit the server computer I don't know the details because I'm not much of a tech person obviously if you're listening live tonight then you figured out that you can go to allgamesradio.com to listen to us or you probably have the URL of the feed saved in iTunes or what have you so it's made it very easy to listen to the show I'm told allgames.com will be back very soon probably by the time most people are hearing this podcast so no worries there
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm really horrible at updating Facebook because every time I log into Facebook, I have like 150 different crappy applications that are trying to say, you know, hey, so-and-so thinks you would be compatible and should go on a date.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then it's like, I already am dating somebody.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or so-and-so wants you to play Scrabble with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or so-and-so wants you to take this quiz.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm so freaking sick of all that shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't ever go to Facebook.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do have a Facebook community.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other things coming soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't talk about them, but we're working on stuff soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: How descriptive, huh?
[SPEAKER_00]: Things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to build excitement.
[SPEAKER_03]: Things are happening at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Penny Arcade Expo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know I'm going.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura might be going.
[SPEAKER_03]: Might.
[SPEAKER_04]: Big might.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, however, will not be going.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because of the wife.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if I could swing that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: So hopefully we'll have some representation.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know at least I will be there come hell or high water.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully two out of three.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I had to swing my company's doing a...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish I could go, but I don't know if I can.
[SPEAKER_00]: And we'll bring cider for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: With alcohol and cider for me and the kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, more details on that as PAX approaches.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bobby Blackwolf says Scott is actually not going to be there because he's at Burning Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's passing up PAX to go run naked in the desert?
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't that sound fun?
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, it does sound kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, blowing stuff up is pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, actually, Burning Man does sound kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's one of the things I want to do at some point before I die is go to Burning Man at least once.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though me plus sun equals not good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I get all gross and my skin doesn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it was a redhead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's say redheads don't do well in sun.
[SPEAKER_03]: He starts to melt.
[SPEAKER_00]: I understand that.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I went to Burning Man, I think I could only go for like a day.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they had some screenshots that leaked out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think scans from the issue.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it looks cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the first female boss robot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did have a list of the different boss men that you'd be fighting.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have Magma Man, Galaxy Man, Plug Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: What does Plug Man plug?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a curiosity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Concrete Man and Splash Woman.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Megan Esplash, the first female boss character.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I think I heard, I don't know, I might be getting mixed up, but I think in Japan one of them was a woman in a prior game and it got somehow switched on the way over here to America.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could be wrong on that, don't quote me on that, but I don't want to say somebody was telling me that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's still, what do you guys think about, this is interesting because Mega Man series is essentially taking a step backwards, but in a way it's a step forwards, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome, I think it's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: They should do that for more stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they kind of are.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, look at Bionic Commando Rearmed.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not exactly as old school as Mega Man as far as the way they're doing it, but same type of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a 2D game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They kind of forget that a lot of times, even though we do have the technology to do 3D games and stuff, you don't always have to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you think, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you excited about this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Fairly so.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hear all the music is going to be 8-bit-ish and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Dark Knight in our chat room might not agree.
[SPEAKER_03]: Worst Mega Man boss names ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: Mega Man 2 and 3
[SPEAKER_03]: were probably the peak of the series, a lot of people would tell you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure there's some hardcore Mega Man people out there that are like, no, 7 or 5 or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think a lot of us fondly, fondly remember 2 and 3, so that's kind of interesting they're going back.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I know I'm going to check it out, because if it's retro, hopefully that means it's cheap.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I like cheap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Defender Castle Awesome WiiWare game
[SPEAKER_03]: Shaoran said in chat, says soon we're going to have Pencil Man and Cloth Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I don't know, Pencil Man might be kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like he shoots erasers at you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's like, okay, they've got to always have a, you know, a villain that's, you know, fire based.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're like running out of different words for fire in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Magma Man and, you know, Fire Man, Heat Man, Hot Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuego Man.
[SPEAKER_00]: Heat Man was cool though.
[SPEAKER_00]: Heat Man was like the coolest of the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Heatman was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm old school.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Fireman.
[SPEAKER_00]: But Heatman's only one game later.
[SPEAKER_02]: I say they make a new Mega Man game, just have all of the different bosses in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, all of them.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mega Man boss rush?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, just have, like, well, not necessarily playing all the bosses, but just have all the levels from all the other games, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what the Anniversary Collection should have been.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can use the weapons from Mega Man 8 and Mega Man 1 and, you know, mix it all up.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Ossifer makes the mandatory Boobie Man reference.
[SPEAKER_03]: J-Rod says Toaster Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: J-Rod says Powdered Toast Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Powdered Toast Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just thinking that.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do not want the chat room filling up with Blank Man or whatever there.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Blank Man was already done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was there a Blank Man really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, there was a Blank Man movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: This place is thick with the stench of ghoul.
[SPEAKER_03]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like Diablo 2 and Diablo 1, but much prettier.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's obvious that this game has evolved quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: This game, of course, was unveiled at Blizzard's recent event over in France, the Worldwide Invitational, and tons of stuff was leaked.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a trailer, there's this 20-minute gameplay clip we're looking at here in studio right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you guys think of Diablo 3?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know you guys don't play a whole lot of PC games, but what do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'd have to check it out.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I never played any of the others, but I tried this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played a little bit of, I think, Diablo, like back in the day when I had the demo and stuff for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was one of those games you could sit there and play for a while and you level up some and then stop and go back to it later.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of like the whole grinding part of World of Warcraft, except you don't actually have any...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, as far as I'm aware, because I only played the demo, like, huge quests you have to go on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just grind, grind, grind, grind, grind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, look, I'm super powerful now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kill, kill, kill.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you do have quests, but part of the really cool thing about the old Diablos is that everything was randomized.
[SPEAKER_01]: You'd like to start today by introducing the Barbarian.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to turn that off, because now the guy is talking about the Barbarian class.
[SPEAKER_03]: All the dungeons were randomized, so it was like you were playing a new game every time.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was kind of one of the cool things about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Guild Wars does that.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's true, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: So, very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Diablo is just different.
[SPEAKER_03]: Diablo is not really an MMO, but it is something you can experience with tons of other people, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do like the four-player co-op that they're going to have in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because didn't Diablo 2 only go up to two-player co-op, I think?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Diablo 3 officially announced this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's stuff all over the internet on this.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want the official word, Diablo3.com is where it's at.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just go to any Blizzard site.
[SPEAKER_03]: That whole splash screen that was being teased all week long was there.
[SPEAKER_03]: As far as when this comes out, who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we still have StarCraft 2 on the list.
[SPEAKER_03]: We still have Wrath of the Lich King.
[SPEAKER_03]: When?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometime.
[SPEAKER_03]: SSJ100Matt says it'll be on my Hanukkah list for 2011.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's probably not a bad bet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say maybe 2010.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we'll get StarCraft 2 next year and probably Diablo 3 the year after.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Diablo 3 will probably come out around the same time as StarCraft 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you may have one in the fall, one in the spring.
[SPEAKER_03]: J-Rod says Diablo was cool until people started cheating to make their own loot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I hear that's a real problem that plagued Diablo 2 on Battle.net.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is why I don't like to play games except with friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, because I know that friends won't cheat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or OLR listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, cheating sometimes, it can be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, like, with Red Alert, Command & Conquer Red Alert...
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that stuff, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially when you found out about the whole rules I and I file and you can make your own units by combining stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: That made the game even more fun for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you and I agree, okay, we're going to play this game or we're going to cheat the hell out of it and just have fun with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's one thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's cool because we're both on the same page.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if I've worked really hard to level this character and then some stranger pops in my room and dumps all this shit in my thing that he's cheated to get or shown off or whatever, that's just dumb.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you trying to prove?
[SPEAKER_00]: that's sort of the problem that we had I guess with the last Ragnarok server we were on that people were sort of exploiting a little problem in there duplicating items and things and messing up the economy and as a result all of us suffered for it you know so yeah cheaters suck
[SPEAKER_00]: I think that there's such a thing as appropriate cheating.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, what Matt's talking about, you know, like, you know, what they do at work and everything, when they're, you know, whatever, that's one thing, because you all agree you're going to cheat, and the whole point, you're having fun with the exploits, but, you know, these other a-holes that come on and try to ruin other people's, you know, legit experiences suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I would say it's less of a cheat, more of a mod, because you're just modifying the game, and in order to play someone, because this was back in the day when I was playing someone Red Alert over, you know, a fucking modem.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, we would share the same file back and forth and then basically play this, you know, kind of hacked version on both computers, which was pretty fun, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially with...
[SPEAKER_02]: I made the super fast tanks and Einstein that shot lightning and the suicide bombers and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looking in chat here, Hitstun says, Funny, I play with OLR listeners because they hack just as much as I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, again, if you all agree you're going to hack, then that's one thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's just when you try to kind of cross the line there where you're an ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're trying to ruin other people's experience.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's... Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Diablo 3 is definitely... You think it's going to break the Diablo 2 record?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to say, if I remember right, Diablo 2 has the best PC game launch ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even above World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Diablo 2 sold like a million copies in its first week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is Diablo 3 going to top that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or is PC gaming dead?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've read enough fan-gasming on LiveJournal to make me think that if that's just a small portion of the community, I think that it would be big.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's definitely going to give Diablo 2 a run for its money.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think PC gaming is dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there's enough people... PC gaming is napping.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even think it's necessarily... There's certainly a hardcore audience very into PC gaming, but I'll tell you what, love them or hate them, whoever you are in the PC gaming community, Blizzard gets people to the PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Diablo 3 coming soon.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, going back to other Blizzard news, there were some people who were afraid that Diablo 3 would steal World of Warcraft players, but Blizzard really isn't worried about that because...
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, the thing is they're actually just not concerned about losing the revenue because if they go from one of their projects to another of their projects, they're still getting money from it.
[SPEAKER_00]: But they said that it's not going to be as big of a crossover between the communities because they're different types of game.
[SPEAKER_00]: But they do hope that plenty of the World of Warcraft players would be interested in Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_00]: No, probably not.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't because Irene might call me and be all, Rob, Kara, and I'm going to have to drop Diablo 3 to go run Karazhan again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Curtis in chat is addressing the whole issue about PC gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: He says, I have Portal on my PC because unfortunately I'm still stuck with a PS2 and can't afford next gen.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there's a lot of people still doing PC gaming because of that, but I've got to be honest.
[SPEAKER_03]: I look at a game like Diablo 3 and I'm going...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm probably going to have to upgrade my computer in order to be able to play that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blizzard's sometimes pretty good at getting the tech requirements pretty low, but I'm a little worried I'm going to have to upgrade the computer to be able to play that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you have to upgrade the computer, isn't that just like, you know, might as well buy a system?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like buying a few systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but I understand that, you know, some people want to put it all in one, you know, then invest all the money in your best machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's a big reason why there are a lot of people really into PC gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, kind of the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the same thing, yet opposite for me, because...
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I've upgraded my system, I have to buy more PC games because what's the point in upgrading it that much to play games if you're not going to play games on it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think Blizzard is really going to be losing any WoW players to Diablo I don't think Blizzard will really start losing WoW players until other MMOs come out that really step up to challenge them which Age of Conan is probably done better than most so far and there's others I think Warhammer is going to be coming soon I've heard a lot of buzz about that and eventually WoW 2 or World of Starcraft which in 5 years is probably inevitable so we'll see what they need is like World of Dead or Alive keep on dreamin
[SPEAKER_02]: Itagaki, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: He can do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: One thing that's going to be coming hopefully pretty soon here, and we've been hearing about this for a while now, is the trophy system for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of their answer to the achievements that are on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there are some pictures that have leaked out, supposedly, of this trophy system.
[SPEAKER_02]: They show that you're actually not going to have gamer points.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: So, basically, it sounds like the achievement system, I don't know, it kind of reminds me of, like, Burnout.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, where, like, if you get a certain time, you get a gold.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you get a certain, you know, higher time, it's a silver, and so on, for a bronze.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to have that type of system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I think what's going to be the difficulty for each trophy, it's not going to be like, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess, sort of like that, but you wouldn't be able to, like, say, get gold and then get all the trophies below it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be just, like, different things, like, finish level one, bronze trophy, finish the game, you know, gold trophy or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_03]: Reading some more comments from chat, chat.orangelunchradio.com, live on this Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_03]: J-Rod says, trophies and achievements, god no, I can't juggle that between two systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: Achievement whore!
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't Conan equal World of Dead or Alive?
[SPEAKER_03]: Parts.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know it's inevitable that God of War 3 is going to come out sometime for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: But were you guys thinking that it might be this soon?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, apparently one of the Eurogamer affiliates, Eurogamer.pt, has run a report that God of War 3 is going to be shown at E3 this next month.
[SPEAKER_03]: This was from a Sony rep at the Interactive Digital Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of see this, if a trailer is unveiled, which I don't see why it wouldn't be because this is one of Sony's biggest franchises, it's going to be in the vein of the early, early Halo 3 trailers where it's going to show you like, you know, there's going to be some epic music and then, you know, some girl talking like, you know, in a land far away.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need your help.
[SPEAKER_03]: And whatever shit they're going to talk in the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then you'll see suddenly at the very end of the trailer, Kratos' face in HD.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's going to be like, oh my god, fangasm!
[SPEAKER_03]: And then God of War 3, 2009.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's going to be it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's kind of predictable at this point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or then again, if it is Sony, they could say it's coming out this Christmas and then just keep pushing it back until it gets to Christmas 2009.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is the Sony way, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you hear about the other rumor that they're saying that Kratos is going to be a hidden character in Soul Calibur 4 on the PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_03]: I had heard that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was on the lineup for tonight, but it got cut because we're going to be long otherwise.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I'd heard about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that weird?
[SPEAKER_02]: It'd be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'd be something that they could probably slip in there for E3 or whatever since the game comes out a few weeks after that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I would think, if that is true, wouldn't a word of that already slip out somehow?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've been announcing stuff each week, like little tidbits, doing different screens.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were talking about the tag system that's supposedly in there now.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's another thing I saw the other day for the character creator, where you can basically create... Someone made a solid snake, or old snake, basically, and Ryu...
[SPEAKER_02]: Ryu from Ninja Gaiden.
[SPEAKER_03]: FearTheClaw in chat says that's three games in three years.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like Tony Hawk or Madden.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I'm thinking, wait a minute, there's the PSP one, but J-Rod jumps in and says, yeah, but the PSP one doesn't count for most people.
[SPEAKER_03]: I heard the PSP one was actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't play it myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not really in the God of War, but... I can see them probably will port the PSP one to the PlayStation 2 before the third one comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: because they've been doing that quite often.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I think it's inevitable God of War 3 at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll just see if we get a teaser at E3 or not.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, there is some other news that should probably be pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm actually kind of excited about this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nintendo Power put up an image of a photo taken of the Castlevania game for Wii and it looks like a fighting game.
[SPEAKER_00]: and not a platformer but it said so far you should be able to well at least it's rumored that you should be able to play Simon, Alucard, Shanoa, Marie Renard and Dracula it better have Richter in it that's all I'm saying
[SPEAKER_03]: But doesn't it look like a fighting game?
[SPEAKER_00]: It looks like a fighting game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's like Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_03]: So is this Konami's response to Soul Calibur?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: GS68 calls it Fightervania and then facepalms in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Castlevania Judgment, I think was the name of the name.
[SPEAKER_00]: I want to play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's my quandary with this is that this looks like one of those things that could be really, really, really freaking awesome or really, really, really terrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm just kind of worried it's going to be terrible, but I'm hopeful because these are some great characters in a great franchise.
[SPEAKER_00]: Simon's got pretty hair and shapely legs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't most of the Castlevania characters play kind of similar?
[SPEAKER_03]: What's going to differentiate all these different characters?
[SPEAKER_00]: Richter had different moves.
[SPEAKER_00]: Remember he had the backwards double jump?
[SPEAKER_00]: If you go by Symphony of the Night, he had the double jump, and then the one where he leaps up, and then the backflip that would let you go an extra space and a half.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you put Maria in it, I don't know if she'd have her crybaby attack from when she was a little girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did see a screenshot that they had Maria in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a second screenshot that was floating around out there also.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what would be kind of cool is if certain boss characters were kind of downgraded to, you know, the playable fighters in this.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you could like play as the Grim Reaper or you could play as, I don't know, the Vampire Bat, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or Medusa or, you know, some of those like old school Castlevania bosses.
[SPEAKER_03]: That might be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it just me?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that would be fun to play as like the Grim Reaper as a character.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well... Or Dracula.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would think that if Dracula is in it, Dracula is in it as a boss.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bosses are always playable once you unlock them, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: They should have Shaft.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Dark Priest Shaft.
[SPEAKER_00]: And their little text exchange should be like, he's like, yeah, we hear you're one bad, and then he says, shut your mouth.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope that they have horrendous voice acting, like the old school PlayStation Symphony of the Night game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would rock.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just think that Simon had pretty hair in that one picture.
[SPEAKER_03]: I imagine this is something that we'll get a trailer of at E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: So hopefully we'll get a little more feeling about if this is going to suck or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Again, I'm hopeful, but it's one of those things where it's like, boy, they could really screw this up if they wanted to.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I hope they took the time to get it right.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and unfortunately I can't see that the track record for spin-off games have been that great, especially on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: What was the Tekken game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, God, there was the spinoff with Nina, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: It was Death by Degrees.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guilty Gear 2 Overture.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's alright, but it's kind of like 99 Nights a bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to think if there's another one there.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkTetsuya says, I want to play as Grant from Castlevania 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: He can climb on the freaking walls and ceiling.
[SPEAKER_00]: In the Japanese version, instead of just stabbing with the knife, he actually threw knives.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, this... That would have been a lot better.
[SPEAKER_03]: These are the kind of characters that need to be in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, and I say, you know, we might be talking negatively about this game already because we're very cautious, but by all means, please, Konami, prove us wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make us eat our words, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please feel free.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: The graphics don't look that bad, so if they wanted to do, say, another 2D Castlevania game for the Wii...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: So, basically, today you have Guitar Hero Aerosmith, which I'm sure a lot of people picked up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other than today, there's really a whole lot of nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Elements on PC, which is some puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Supreme Ruler 2020, also another PC game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a strategy title.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see...
[SPEAKER_02]: The Immortals of Terra I have no idea what that is Journey to the Center of the Earth for the DS which is based on the new movie that's coming out here they keep trailering like crazy 1 vs 100 the only game with Bob Saget in it it's for the DS until they make a full house game
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, which will never happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rugu on PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whoops, sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking at a banner ad.
[SPEAKER_03]: God damn these banner ads that make noise.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, Rugu on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool little independent game, so that's worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_02]: PurrPals on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, another cat raising sim or cats raising you sim.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gears of War, the refresh as they're calling it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically the re-release of Gears of War with some extra content and a new price point of $39.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's on the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dekatimoto on the DS, a motorcycle racing game.
[SPEAKER_02]: AMF Bullying Pinbusters, that's on the DS as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hail to the Chimp on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only game that's actually cool this week, Trauma Center Under the Knife 2, coming out for the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kdog96 asks, hasn't 1 vs. 100 been cancelled?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I think the show was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, the show?
[SPEAKER_03]: The TV show was, but if they made the game, I think they're kind of stuck releasing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the game's been pushed back a while now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some comments on Guitar Hero Aerosmith.
[SPEAKER_03]: DeadmanWalking in chat says, Guitar Hero Aerosmith is awful.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jrod says, Guitar Hero Aerosmith has a great track list, but I can't get myself to support Activision milking that franchise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a large part of me that really wants to get Guitar Hero Aerosmith, but I cannot justify $60 on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just can't.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm hoping it comes down in price soon.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can come play it at my house.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's right, because Dan's going to get it, huh?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's a good thing that they're releasing music games and stuff like that, but I think more than one release a year is too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even with DDR, if they were releasing two or three games a year, that would be overkill, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's head on.
[SPEAKER_03]: D-Extreme Stage
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's check out some of the other systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know there's nothing coming out on the Xbox 360 this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the Wii, Akodepan Ikisama Horoyuki is coming out, and Jawa Mammoth Tohitsumu no Ishii is also coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have no idea what either of those games are, but I imagine Akodepan is probably some type of puzzle game, if I'm not mistaken.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it looks like... Oh, it's a board game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, board game translation for the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably not a game we really play here on this side of the ocean.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking at the handheld system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, quickly looking at PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some other price reductions there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, El Nokitsu 2 Invisible Memories comes out on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has a limited edition as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's an adventure game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can't tell much about this, but it has schoolgirls in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that could be anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: That could be anything, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looking at the handhelds, because there's usually stuff on the Nintendo DS, even in a slow news week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't see a lot of big game names here, but I do show a game called Nanashi no Game from Square Enix is coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Trying to figure out what that game is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Action adventure game.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: with a touch panel on one side for the game and the other side showing a full body view of your dancer and her competition.
[SPEAKER_03]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's like a dance music game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And lastly, on the PSP in Japan this week, looking to see if there's anything new.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Bleach, Heat the Soul 4 gets a price reduction and moves into best hits.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the Namco Museum Battle Collection expands into an Asia-wide release this week, not just Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, more Bleach.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, I have a friend who's touring around in Japan right now, and he asked me if I wanted anything from Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was going to have him pick me up a copy on PlayStation 3 of Battle Fantasia, which is that really cool-looking fighting game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I wanted to play that.
[SPEAKER_00]: One of my other friends is planning on importing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So hopefully I get that and I can bring it in and we can do it on JustinTV or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, in two weeks in Japan, since we were talking about God of War earlier, God of War Chains of Olympus finally comes out in Japan on July 10th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Something to look forward to there.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Japan release dates.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, for the UK, there's a few things.
[SPEAKER_00]: On the 30th, actually, GoView is coming out for PSP, and then with the start of the month, we've got on the 2nd, Dance Dance Revolution Hottest Party on Wii, Wolf of the Battlefield Commando 3 for PlayStation 3 on the 3rd, and then on the 4th is Arkanoid DS, Space Invaders Extreme for DS and PSP, The Incredible Hulk on Wii, and Wall-E on damn near everything else, and we love golf!
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, it's not Dancing Stage Hottest Party?
[SPEAKER_00]: It says Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of strange.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I thought they called it Dancing Stage over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why is it that they call it Dancing Stage over there anyways?
[SPEAKER_00]: Because Revolution is a taboo term to use in marketing from what I understand.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know why.
[SPEAKER_00]: And if I'm right, also back in the 80s you actually couldn't use Ninja.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like for example, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles was Teenage Mutant Hero Turtles.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got weird stuff over here too.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, like, you know, fag is a cigarette over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But over here it means something much different.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_00]: There's little things.
[SPEAKER_00]: And a bundle of sticks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wario Land Shake It
[SPEAKER_02]: Super Paper Mario Kirby Super Star Ultra DS Remake Super Nintendo Game
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that the one with all the minigames in it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's also got minigames in it, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's also... I had that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mystery Case Files Millionaire.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, error as in, you know, errors.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, and that is a mystery game that I guess is a PC franchise that they're now bringing to the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: So those, let's see, I believe...
[SPEAKER_02]: September 25th for Kirby Superstar Ultra and September 29th for Mystery Case Files Millionaire and I want to say that Wario...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: So their November and December releases are still a question mark.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there might be some big bombshell in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it doesn't really even end in October.
[SPEAKER_02]: It ends basically at October.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's all September stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wario sounds kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kirby sure has a lot of diehard fans.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's not really that OMG title in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's also weird?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, this is weird for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Nintendo usually releases their games on Sundays.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're switching to Tuesdays now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're finally getting normal like everybody else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, switching over to the Xbox 360 for a minute, it's been speculated for a while that one of the things that they are going to announce at E3, along with all that news that got leaked last month, or no, it was about two weeks ago, was the price drop.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Xbox 360, any day now, should be getting some type of price drop, and it looks like
[SPEAKER_03]: It might happen at E3 that they might walk out there on stage and they're going to say we are dropping the price of the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's what happened to make us all think that is that apparently a Kmart ad has leaked.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a Kmart ad that is actually supposed to hit on July 6th.
[SPEAKER_03]: and this ad shows that there is an Xbox 360 20 gig console, meaning it comes with the hard drive, $299.99 and it's being advertised as a new low price.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also supporting the fact that this ad is for the week of July 6th, you see a little box art for Civilization Revolution, it's a game that's coming out that week, that is a game that's scheduled to be out that week, so very interesting that this could be seeing a $50 price drop from the current $349 that folks are paying for this system.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't know if it's
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_00]: But did nobody shop at Kmart?
[SPEAKER_03]: I understand that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if this is true, then people are going to price match and what have you.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not going to all of a sudden drop their systems down for whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it says new low price.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not saying on sale.
[SPEAKER_03]: SSJ100 Matt says, Rob, do we get a Rock Us Dukakis t-shirt with our purchase of a 360 at Kmart?
[SPEAKER_03]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_00]: I want one of those shirts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: You might be able to buy some mold.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want a moldy Xbox 360, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: If Kmart ends up selling these, it better be for an old skewer.
[SPEAKER_03]: How's Kmart going to get rid of all the 360s that have been sitting on their shelves since launch?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because nobody shops at Kmart.
[SPEAKER_03]: They get price matched.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_03]: They get all that stuff on the back end.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: If you look, and I don't even know why I looked at this when I was looking at this ad here, they have a high-res scan on Joystick.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you look at the very bottom left-hand corner, it says job number 713, so that's when the ad is supposed to hit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a feeling somebody else, another retailer, will leak a very similar thing this week, and that's when you know it's the real deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm already on board saying it's the real deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, look at what was it last year with the whole, I think the first price drop, and also there was the PlayStation 3 stuff too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think there was some sort of price drop or SKU announcement or something like that that was leaked by that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was the 80 gig or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: A price drop coming soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you haven't bought an Xbox 360 yet and you want to, and I say this because we've had some mailbag people write us recently wondering if they should take the plunge and get one now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe you should wait now a couple weeks before this price drop unless you go to a store that's going to honor.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because sometimes stores, like if the price changes within a month, they will give you a refund.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would rather just not risk it and just buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just wait a few more days.
[SPEAKER_03]: Weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just wait a couple more weeks and I think you will be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then you might have a reason to shop at Kmart.
[SPEAKER_00]: A reason to shop at Kmart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pick up some of that hip 80s fashion while you're there.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have bought something at Kmart a year ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought something at Kmart once in the past three years and that's because they were the only place open on Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_00]: I bought cereal there.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: You're nasty!
[SPEAKER_02]: and you know we went in there buying okay we only need aluminum foil and like you know a snack and then that's it we ended up walking out with like aluminum or not even aluminum foil because we forgot to get that obviously but we walked out with like bagel bites and like clothes and like all sorts of random shit it's like what the hell what is wrong with this I did buy something important there what I bought flannel sheets for my massage class
[SPEAKER_03]: I almost live literally next door to a freaking Walmart and I don't go there unless I have to because it's scary.
[SPEAKER_03]: That Walmart is scary.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Walmart by my house is cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, did you see this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Right over there by the freeway they are opening up a Hooters right by my house.
[SPEAKER_00]: We need to go!
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, we should do our OLR 300th episode live at Hooters.
Let's do it!
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh my god, let's do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we'll have to look into it.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I'm not eating hot wings because their hot wings taste like shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll have to see if they have the facilities for that and if they're not going to charge us too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: But otherwise, I kind of like that idea of doing our 300th episode live from Hooters.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_03]: PKJr92 asks, How is it scary, Rob?
[SPEAKER_03]: The Walmart over here just said...
[SPEAKER_03]: There's always people outside asking for money.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a good way to describe it.
[SPEAKER_03]: When you walk in there, it smells like formaldehyde.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have a good way to describe it.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_00]: Think of the oldest Walmart in the South.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then transpose it to California.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not quite as bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: The floors are at least white.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the quality of consumer...
[SPEAKER_03]: Sadly, I think the Kmart locally here is a little bit more ahead of the times than the Walmart next door.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really, the only difference between Walmarts and Kmarts is Kmart, you have to step on the pad to open the door instead of, you know, the infrared.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Enough Kmart chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Back to gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: We gotta.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tommy is waiting to come on our show.
[SPEAKER_03]: We gotta get to him.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, well, hey, we've got some other stuff that's pretty crap news for our friends in the UK.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're supposed to introduce a dual rating system for rating games.
[SPEAKER_00]: One that's the, if I'm right, it's the PEGI, and the other one then to go with the BBFC.
[SPEAKER_00]: And...
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway, they were talking about the games that were rated 12 plus or above by the PEGI should also be rated by the BBFC, the British Board of Film Classification to also include that, which right now they only rate the 15 and 18.
[SPEAKER_00]: But Microsoft is actually saying that it's going to make the games more expensive because they have to submit them through both rating systems as well as delay their releases.
[SPEAKER_00]: because they have to be approved by both.
[SPEAKER_00]: In fact, to pretty much quote, it was actually said by Neil Thompson, who was one of the executives there, that, quote, we're concerned with any measures that would mean this process is made more unwieldy or incurs additional costs which have to be shared with the consumer.
[SPEAKER_00]: So... So...
[SPEAKER_00]: That's kind of crap, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it kind of sucks that they have to do two.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't understand why you just can't stick with one rating system.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically like, well, we need to rate it too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then just have them rate everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get rid of the Peggy system.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't see why we can't do this in America and why they can't do it everywhere else.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wherever has a movie rating system, apply it to the games.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't need an ESRB.
[SPEAKER_00]: If people can understand what movie ratings are about, then apply it to video games as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But people are even dumber than that, so they won't understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yet another Microsoft rumor we've got here.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then again, the source is not entirely credible.
[SPEAKER_02]: So take this with a huge grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, this was apparently found from the 4chan forums, which I know they probably already... Wow, that's the most respectable news source I've ever heard on this show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But just...
[SPEAKER_02]: Just reporting it, that's all.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are two screenshots that supposedly leaked from 4chan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: With MyGamerPad.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's basically kind of like Microsoft's version of Home, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got the avatars.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one screenshot shows that you can invite friends, change your wardrobe, furnishings, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then...
[SPEAKER_02]: The logo for it looks like it's drawn in crayon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, big grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Big grain of salt with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think there's really an... Excuse me, I'm choking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it could be very well photoshopped, but with these kind of announcements that we've been hearing and leaks and stuff about their avatar system and stuff like that, I could definitely see them doing something like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I think the minute you said, and I'm trying to think of the nicest way to say this, but I can't really think of anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: The minute you said this news comes to us from the 4chan forums, the biggest grain of salt fell from the heavens.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dumped here in studio When you said that When I think news I think CNN MSNBC I don't think 4chan Just saying In case it actually becomes true Exactly I love this comment from Jrod in chat 4chan?
[SPEAKER_02]: Photoshop?
[SPEAKER_02]: Never I know, I know
[SPEAKER_02]: Just in case it's true, you heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_00]: If it's not true, you heard it on the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kidding, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_03]: That should be a new commercial for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's time for us to do something here on OLR we haven't done in a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's dance, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a stupid award giveaway tonight, and tonight it's not because of any hideous shooting or anything, thankfully.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this is just no plain stupidity.
[SPEAKER_03]: The news comes to us from the New Haven Advocate, and it is about the Connecticut State Senator Gail Schlossberg.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gail Schlossberg is looking for the rape scene in Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: And going to the actual news article here on NewHavenAdvocate.com She wants confirmation of the rumored rape scene in Grand Theft Auto 4 She is unable, though, to reach that level of the game Hmm, could it possibly be because, I don't know, it doesn't exist?
[SPEAKER_03]: But she's not willing to believe that But she just doesn't believe it Surely, this is a Grand Theft, surely there must be rape
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, she was putting out a request that someone proved to her that it's not in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: What kind of fucked up logic is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Prove your innocence!
[SPEAKER_03]: Prove that there is no rape in your game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Need I say more?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're an idiot.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is why politicians suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not all, but most.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like this one.
[SPEAKER_00]: They suck once they get to a certain level.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, let us know when you find that scene.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, but the funny thing is that she's going to be going around forever and ever trying to find that scene and she never will.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, heaven forbid she actually gets some work done.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, speaking of Grand Theft Auto 4 though, I did see the most hilarious thing in that.
[SPEAKER_00]: The lap dances.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_00]: They're hilarious.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're so badly animated.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, she's going to find the lost city of gold before she finds that rape scene in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe she can find a balanced budget for the state of Connecticut.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if they have the budget problems we do in California.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if this were coming from a California senator, I would be going through the freaking roof.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they cannot balance a fucking budget in this state.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would be in the middle of the roof right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Listen, Connecticut, do you really need to lower yourself to Delaware's level?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: News like this makes us... You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to me for using the wrong music tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh well, a bit of retroness for you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_00]: FU, Rob.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have a few, so I'll try to get through them as quickly as possible.
[SPEAKER_00]: FU to me for...
[SPEAKER_00]: Being so out of it that I made an error in the email.
[SPEAKER_00]: I won't elaborate more.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, F you to my body.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because I got really sick on Thursday night.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, technically Friday morning.
[SPEAKER_00]: With some pretty nasty pain in my stomach.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, really bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm not going to go into details because it was fairly disgusting.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I ended up going into the doctor on Friday.
[SPEAKER_00]: and being tested for a peptic ulcer and a few other stomach related problems and got put on quite a number of drugs to help with digestive issues.
[SPEAKER_00]: And one of them is addictive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fun!
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I know, so I have to be very careful.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, um, and then I'm also being treated for sinus infection.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because we've had smoke!
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pretty bad, awful smoke from the fire.
[SPEAKER_00]: Was it up in Placer County?
[SPEAKER_03]: Fires are, like, all over.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's surrounding.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's fires up in the mountains to Reno, there's fires up in the mountains to the bay, there's fires up north in Chico.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there's no fires to the south.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's the only safe place.
[SPEAKER_00]: Head south.
[SPEAKER_00]: We haven't had any true blue skies in a while.
[SPEAKER_00]: We've had sort of a dusty brown color.
[SPEAKER_03]: True story, if you go onto the Wii forecast channel, at least yesterday, it actually said haze.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it showed that disgusting brown colored cloud for our weather.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's the first time I've ever seen that in this area.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was just nasty.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the thing is, is that basically we've all been, you know, inhaling, you know, very fine soot, you know, in our air.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm not the only one.
[SPEAKER_00]: A lot of people have developed sinus infections just from the damage, you know, caused from inhaling this day in and day out.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, um, F you to fires.
[SPEAKER_00]: Even though I normally like fire, F you to fires on that scale.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, Frisbee activated in our Justin.TV chat the weather function, because you can type weather and where we're at.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the official weather on Justin.TV says it's currently 83 degrees Fahrenheit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Conditions?
[SPEAKER_03]: Smoke.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, and today's actually a lot prettier than it has been.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Today is a lot nicer, but on top of that, though, we've had cooler weather because of the haze.
[SPEAKER_00]: However, though, at the hottest part of the day, it has trapped plenty of heat.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, and our hottest part of the day is like, what is it, 3, 4 o'clock?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, about 4.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right when the show starts, about 5.
[SPEAKER_00]: so it's it's been on the not fun level and people have been getting sick from it so big F you goes to the the fires and good luck to the people who actually live in those areas yeah definitely um i used to live up in chico where a lot of those fires are happening in that area and i know
[SPEAKER_03]: Friends of friends that have been affected.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it just sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no real other way to put it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_00]: I remember going to Julian, which is right outside San Diego, up in the mountains.
[SPEAKER_00]: After they had the big bad forest fires there in the mountains.
[SPEAKER_00]: And seeing what happened to one of the mountain towns.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was just gone.
[SPEAKER_00]: You could see foundations.
[SPEAKER_00]: The whole place was gone.
[SPEAKER_00]: So having seen what happens right after the fire, I just hope that everyone comes through it okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well that is it for your FUs.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll go to Loki.
[SPEAKER_00]: Today's forecast is noobs I bought.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess FU, this is not a really big FU because I'm not buying them this year, but FU is the safe and sane fireworks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Each year they get worse and worse.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's safe and lame.
[SPEAKER_02]: Safe and lame, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm shipping me some Roman cans.
[SPEAKER_02]: This year, Arnold is basically saying, don't buy them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so, no one's supposed to buy them because apparently, according to him, anyone that sets off fireworks immediately sets off forest fires.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're like, don't fire!
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, you've seen these people.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen these people.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are people that are like, don't fire!
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to listen to Arnold because they're going to be like, I ain't listening to that European.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll do what I want.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm American.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right Bear Firearms!
[SPEAKER_02]: And fire is part of that, so... I'm gonna set my arm on fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just go fire a gun for the 4th of July.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, fire guns in the air instead.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, um... No, don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's really dangerous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, no one can get killed by that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did it in Mythbusters.
[SPEAKER_02]: It happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so, um... Yeah, F you that because those suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: So instead, we're gonna play video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that it for you, FU's of the Week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I'll make mine fast, because this is almost over.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to the fact that when I went to Great America, the best ride at all of Great America was fucking closed on my birthday, and that would be Top Gun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, excuse me, Flight Deck, because they lost all the licensing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I would like to point out the Survivor ride is still cool, and I rode Invertigo for the first time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know why they call that ride Invertigo?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it inverts your stomach by the time you're off of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought I was going to hurl.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then you have to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, yeah, then I thought I was going to, like, tinkle.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, my pants.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I got to raid the Demon, like, three times in a row, because there was no lines on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Demon is, like, the best ride ever, next to Top Gun, Flight Deck, whatever the fuck ever it's called.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the other FU would go to the Fires here, which suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's all I can think of for right now, so that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to do it for the FU's of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: We almost ran out of music.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had to cut it short.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we have some other music right now we have to get to.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, LLR.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, hi, Sky, because this question is for him.
[SPEAKER_03]: Goodie.
[SPEAKER_00]: Rob, you said that you only have two songs that you like in In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_00]: What songs are they?
[SPEAKER_00]: Personally, my favorite song from that game is Do You Love Me.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks, Osfer.
[SPEAKER_03]: My two favorite songs in In the Groove, actually, there would be three, because I kind of like Lemmings on the Run, and then outside of that, I like the Banzai songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Zodiac, and I like Anubis.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like the Gen Z with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just not big in the groove music.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like MC Front a lot though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of it's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like I like the Shusha song because it makes me think of Telemundo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, that's really it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dun-dun-dun!
[SPEAKER_00]: and then addressed to me a classic game of the week and it's from Richard.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I love the 19XX series and I would love to see an updated one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_00]: That would be so sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Am I crazy?
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought I saw one was in planning.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a remake of 1942 coming out to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought I had heard something about one of the 19 something something games being remade or something was happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you might get your wish sooner than you thought.
[SPEAKER_00]: Next up.
[SPEAKER_00]: Would a takeover by EA of Take-Two be good for the gaming industry?
[SPEAKER_00]: Consider 2K Sports and the GTA franchise.
[SPEAKER_00]: A lot is at stake.
[SPEAKER_00]: I personally prefer a takeover than for EA to spin off Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_03]: I, I, this, you know, even though I'm not much of a sports game player, I don't think it's a good idea to have 2K Sports and EA, your two biggest sports game makers, in the same roof.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just think that's kind of a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_00]: That'd monopolize the market.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, as far as the rest of it goes, you know, I don't know enough about the inner workings of the game industry and how, you know, how much freedom the current teams would have to continue to develop their products if this happened.
[SPEAKER_00]: but that would be my number one concern would be the monopoly of the sports games and that there's really no one else who is wanting to step up and challenge that monopoly of course the fact that EA holds that whole exclusive license thing doesn't help next up and this comes from Ben I cannot believe that you guys didn't jump on this show 284, 6 year anniversary show at 1 hour 7 minutes and 40 second mark Guitar Hero Tool
[SPEAKER_00]: Comic Freakin' Gold, no one jumped on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: My ears are just burning for one of you to jump on this zinger.
[SPEAKER_00]: Was it Loki that said this to your guest?
[SPEAKER_00]: Regardless, you should all have been all over this one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh well, peace guys, keep up the great work, and congrats on six years.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was Andrew that said it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was someone in chat that had said it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just said Tool would be cool, but... But I think the joke there is that you're kind of a tool if you keep buying all these Guitar Hero games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, yeah, we missed it.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I just said that I actually wouldn't mind a Tool edition, because I like Tool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow, we did get a couple of different long ones.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway, this one comes from...
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's signed Rickchard, so I'm just going to go with that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Happy Friday, OLR.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's Friday when I write this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hope you have a good weekend.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh Lord, Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_00]: is out in the UK.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why has it taken so long to come out here?
[SPEAKER_00]: We always get screwed over with releases.
[SPEAKER_00]: What the fuck, Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_00]: Seriously, you need to pull your thumb out of your arse and get some decent games out soon.
[SPEAKER_00]: I recently completed Metroid on the Wii, and I do believe it was a superb game.
[SPEAKER_00]: However, I can't help but think that there were some areas that could have been improved so easily.
[SPEAKER_00]: It could have been incredible.
[SPEAKER_00]: The story and writing could have been more immersive and compelling.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's face it, you didn't really care about why you were shooting at those spiky space pirates.
[SPEAKER_00]: You just wanted to get to the next pretty stage with a new and bigger gun.
[SPEAKER_00]: The cutscenes in this day and age were pretty poor.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't tell me it's because the Wii is underpowered, the PS2 could pull off cinematic and exciting cutscenes for God's sake.
[SPEAKER_00]: Take a look at Eternal Darkness Retro.
[SPEAKER_00]: One last thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love being in Samus' ship.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was so cool pressing all of those buttons.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, did I miss something or does the best button do nothing at all?
[SPEAKER_00]: You know which one I mean.
[SPEAKER_00]: The one that makes the big gun appear.
[SPEAKER_00]: It could have been a fantastic bonus to fly off into space and shoot baddies from this fresh perspective.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, bitching over.
[SPEAKER_00]: You don't have to read this out as I know you hate long emails.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't hate long emails.
[SPEAKER_00]: And may have nominated myself for an FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh shit, I just realized that I'm making it longer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh shit, I did it again.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh fuck, go balls.
[SPEAKER_00]: Shit, fuck ours.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's just trying to get me to say that.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: It worked.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you later.
[SPEAKER_00]: This email brought to you by Chardin is never ending.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wait for some kind of goddamn RTS Command & Conquer game for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was... Funny email.
[SPEAKER_00]: Quite.
[SPEAKER_00]: Next up.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dun-dun-dun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, everyone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have a few questions for the three of you.
[SPEAKER_00]: One.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
42.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_00]: I hear the answer's 42.
[SPEAKER_00]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have you ever had what could be termed as holy crap moments as they relate to gaming?
[SPEAKER_00]: An example may be like when you've seen your first video game or arcade as a youngster, or maybe seen a game that was light years ahead of its contemporaries in some regards.
[SPEAKER_00]: Final Fantasy VII, anyone?
[SPEAKER_00]: Furthermore, how heavily do these holy crap moments factor into your decision to stay with gaming?
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want a recent example, play Lost Odyssey, and the first time one of those text-only stories comes up on the screen, the memories, that was kind of one of those, holy crap, type moments.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think that was exactly like the way I said it, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: As far as, what was the second half of the question?
[SPEAKER_00]: How does it play into... And your decision to stick with gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like to say holy crap at movies, but sometimes I like to laugh at movies, sometimes I like to cry at movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not that I really cry at video games, but I like to have fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it doesn't necessarily have to be a holy crap moment, but they help.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think that my last holy crap moment... I remember one of my early holy crap moments was when you're doing the train cart ride in Final Fantasy VI.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was like, oh my god, it's like Indiana Jones!
[SPEAKER_00]: I've got a headache!
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, you know, every so often I run into a game that gives me those happy moments like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I think I keep playing to, you know, find more of those happy times.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought of one other one.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about Symphony of the Night when you get the real ending, quote unquote, and then you go into the upside down castle and you realize you have to play the whole fucking game all over again.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's harder.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was kind of one of those.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or how long it took me to freaking get a jewel sword.
[SPEAKER_00]: That sucked.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I'll tell you what took even longer was getting the freaking Yatatsuna.
[SPEAKER_00]: Having to fight the werewolf.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was a pain in the butt.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway, number two.
[SPEAKER_00]: A few episodes back, Rob mentioned that he was interested in the HD remake of Commando 3 for the 360.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm interested in his opinion on it, assuming that he's played it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's on my to-do list.
[SPEAKER_03]: Naughty me.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, number three then.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have the three of you considered making up some goofy as all hell sounding catchphrases or words to use on air?
[SPEAKER_00]: I found that using such things can be quite fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: My personal favorite is snot puppy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't ask, I don't know what it means either.
[SPEAKER_00]: I made it up a few years ago after having way too much Crown Royal and Labat Blue.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like twat waffle myself, but I didn't make that up, so I can't really claim that I made that up.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I like twat waffle.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know what, those types of things, you can't force, like, you can't make fetch happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop trying to make fetch happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those types of things have to happen naturally.
[SPEAKER_00]: Next.
[SPEAKER_03]: You twat waffle.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do you know of any places where I can buy video game soundtracks, preferably on CD?
[SPEAKER_00]: I know of sites where I can get them less than honestly.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I want to support video game music with my hard-earned money.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kino Kuniya?
[SPEAKER_03]: CD Japan?
[SPEAKER_03]: Amazon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Amazon has a lot of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've got everything.
[SPEAKER_00]: and actually they're releasing legitimate ones in the US plenty of times now.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you don't prefer shopping online, you like to walk into a store and look at the real thing, try like comic book stores locally because I know one of the ones here has them.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it depends where this guy lives.
[SPEAKER_03]: Try like comic book stores and other nerdy type stores.
[SPEAKER_03]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It might be a small selection but they'll probably have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like the local comic book store here has the Final Fantasies, the DDRs, you know, the big stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, last question.
[SPEAKER_00]: On a similar note, once I move, I'll be considering buying one to two, three arcade machines.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've never bought any before in my life.
[SPEAKER_00]: With that being said, what advice as pointers can you give me?
[SPEAKER_00]: If it helps at all, all the games I'll consider were made between 1978 and 1998 and span across virtually every genre.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll tell you probably the best thing you're going to be able to do for your money is to get an EOGO AVS machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once in a while you see those Ultra Kade-ish things pop up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember Target was running one like two Christmases ago and I think Costco once in a while has one too.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to really keep your eye out for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: They usually show up around the holidays but another multi-game in one system and very, very classic stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: We built a MAME cabinet out of a pole position stand-up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you could do that too.
[SPEAKER_00]: MAME is fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry for the somewhat lengthy email and thank you for taking the time to read it as well as answer my questions.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll be a dollar.
[SPEAKER_00]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is the long one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought that was the long one.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Last one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hello and good show to everyone.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is... It's Rini, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: A very long time since I've written in.
[SPEAKER_00]: To begin, I'd like to touch on Knuckles Chaotix as featured on DarkSakura's Classic Game of the Week from a couple episodes ago.
[SPEAKER_00]: A correction, the characters were not rendered in 3D, they were sprite-based.
[SPEAKER_00]: What was in 3D were the special stages.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry, they looked rendered.
[SPEAKER_00]: An interesting note on said special stages, you can complete them all to get an obligatory set of jewels that need to be acquired.
[SPEAKER_00]: However, as an extra challenge, players could compete in special stages again, only this time the stages were drawn in wireframes.
[SPEAKER_00]: To make it even more devious, the wireframe versions, you only had flickering verticals of the polygons to go by to avoid the holes as best as possible.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura also touched on Sonic Crackers, the presumed prototype for Chaotix.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not necessarily a tip, but for anyone who's played the old side-scrolling Sonic games, should go online and read up on the analyses for earlier ROM dumps that were meant for developers' eyes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Interesting bits include tiny nuances such as the pixel-perfect placement of the score, ring...
[SPEAKER_00]: and Life Indicators on screen to the creepy sounding Genocide City Zone, an alternative stage that was supposed to be a meltdown version of the Chemical Plant Zone in Sonic 2 that players would reach later in the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a nice way to kill an afternoon.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love prototypes, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love looking for prototype games.
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually have a couple of prototypes that were released for Atari 5200, like Millipede.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know it is hot.
[SPEAKER_00]: And Ms.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_00]: For the other half of this email, it's not quite half, it's more like a third.
[SPEAKER_00]: I listened to your anniversary shows, Ask Orange Knowledge, Radio Segment, and Bobby Blackwolf asked how Konami could improve the American Bimani situation.
[SPEAKER_00]: Very briefly, was poppin' music mentioned as to how it could be brought over, which it should.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is the obvious issue of localizing it, but there's another problem, content.
[SPEAKER_00]: Correct me if I'm wrong, but poppin' has a lot of songs unfit for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was mulling over this for a while and thought of a different...
[SPEAKER_00]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_00]: Absolutely agree.
[SPEAKER_00]: They don't have to just copy the same damn game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you want my take on this, Konami should have a video game themed song list.
[SPEAKER_00]: In optimal situation, the US song list would consist of part KOs, part licenses, and part songs from video games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not just Konami either, here's why.
[SPEAKER_00]: In my personal preference...
[SPEAKER_00]: We should get a poppin' Wii and take Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_00]: Brawl approach, because the Wii is selling downloads, etc.
[SPEAKER_00]: Imagine Konami being able not only to access music from every Nintendo console release, but also from any console services on the Virtual Console, aka anything before PS1 in any sort of relevance, although technically you can have access to an entirety of Sega's offerings, too.
[SPEAKER_00]: Imagine playing the goddamn hardcore remix of Gourmet Race from Kirby Superstars that's on Brawl on Poppin'.
[SPEAKER_00]: It says, holy shit, shut up, sexy ferret, OMG.
[SPEAKER_00]: Seriously, imagine Konami having access to those vast assets and putting select songs into Poppin' earlier in their original chiptune form or gloriously remixed from Modernization.
[SPEAKER_00]: They had an Anamelo version, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Guitar Hero, Rock Music, DDR, Dance Music
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, the last third of the email.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, and it'd be a double as filler for Japanese releases, but no one cares for that.
[SPEAKER_00]: This email has run too long, so I'd like to give a chance for another listener to give their input.
[SPEAKER_00]: Before I finish, however, I'd like to chastise the OLR host, Minkletov, and the Andrew Junami, the Zephyr, is that how it's pronounced?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, Zephyr.
[SPEAKER_00]: For the listless selections for the best Mimani songs on the 6th anniversary show.
[SPEAKER_00]: How could you neglect Scorpion Fire from 2DX Red?
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm talking about the epic 8-minute long version 1-2.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're...
[SPEAKER_00]: You're all mean, but points to Loki for canceling out Zephyr.
[SPEAKER_00]: This message was brought to you by the Metallic Rose DS Lite, because baiting and switching target for your coral pink light for Metallic Rose just feels right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, I really did do this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shame on you, but that's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was an epic email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Epic email is very epic.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's get back to the news.
[SPEAKER_03]: We still got Tommy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's some interesting patents filed by Sony here.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, people are speculating it's for the next PSP or whatever system they're going to be calling it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, the patent was granted for a handheld device with touchscreen and digital tactile pixels.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I have no idea what they claim digital tactile pixels are.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says, as for digital tactile pixels, claims 19 through 30 of the patent suggests that vibration acts as a tactile response.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what, a PSP with a touch screen?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, like you would touch it and it would vibrate or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tickling game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, it might be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: well who knows what that's going to be but something's in the works which is not surprising very interesting um
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, and I apologize because this link here on our roll is broken.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully, maybe Loki can help me out a little bit here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kingdom Hearts 3 apparently was rumored to be in the next Nintendo Power.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is up with that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we already kind of talked about that, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kingdom Hearts 3?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we only talked about some of the other stuff in the Nintendo Power League, but apparently they're saying something about Kingdom Hearts 3?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it was a thing that was rumored.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a sword in the new... I remember Jamie talked about it, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: KingHeart3
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I see, because that happens in the comments to this little news story here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't think... They've already got two Kingdom Hearts games in the pipeline that aren't even out yet, so you're full of crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm full of crap?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not you.
[SPEAKER_03]: The people who are trying to say Kingdom Hearts 3 is coming out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: I totally doubt that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we'll see you next month.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's true.
[SPEAKER_00]: There is some news regarding Crave and the ESA, as in Crave said bye to the ESA, which is the Entertainment Software Association.
[SPEAKER_00]: They actually sent a report into... They actually confirmed, sorry, a report on Game Politics that Crave Entertainment was basically splitting, that they decided not to renew their membership, and they're off to, I guess...
[SPEAKER_00]: Do their own thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: The other departures that left were the Vendy Activision, LucasArts.
[SPEAKER_03]: A bunch of those other things you were talking about previously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting that one more has now joined them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then again, I try to think, what has Crave done lately?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing I can think of.
[SPEAKER_00]: World Championship Poker.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yippee.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I guess this isn't exactly, it's not nearly as big as Activision Vivendi not going, but it is interesting that the exodus continues nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, one thing that's been gone for a while that's actually just come back is Nestor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, Nestor from Nintendo Power.
[SPEAKER_02]: You remember Nestor and Howard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Howard and Nestor, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: And their exploits and, you know, chronicled in Nintendo Power.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now, after a, you know, hiatus of quite a long time, he's back and grown up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's interesting because now he's...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Losing at Mario Kart apparently from the picture.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: I told everyone I'm going to give everybody a hard time because they kept ragging on me for Saturn games and for Sega love.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I picked a Sega Saturn game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: I picked Astal, which is known as... Oh, awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's what it's known as?
[SPEAKER_00]: It is awesome, I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's... Kisui Shodensetsu Astaru.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game is the fucking shit, is what it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a 2D side-scroller, and listen to this music, isn't it pretty?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just one of those gorgeous 2D games that came out fairly early in the Saturn's life.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it really is just a beautiful game that really shows just the amazing 2D capabilities that the Saturn had.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sorry, the PlayStation would not have been able to make this game look this gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: It had the 2D capability of...
[SPEAKER_00]: A Snotty Nose
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, as you go through the game, you actually get a little partner that goes with you called Lita.
[SPEAKER_00]: That you'd be able to...
[SPEAKER_00]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, but you could also, um, you know, punch things and jump things and you could, you know, stun your enemies by punching them and you can throw objects and lift humongous things.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you also had this sort of super breath attack that you would inhale and then just blow it all out and blow all the enemies away.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's just a really, really, really cool game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, just to mention, if anyone read the Sonic the Hedgehog comic books that Archie Comics did, Astall shows up a whole bunch in the background.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you can find a YouTube of there's a volcano level, it's fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Best music in the game, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the first level of the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's actually another couple of neat trivia things about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_00]: The US release of the game has it where the title does not appear on the side of the case.
[SPEAKER_00]: All you get is the Sega Saturn logo.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it also has music hidden in the game, which is basically the music from the intro, where you can just put it in a CD player and listen to it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It has lyrics in the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_00]: Instrumental in the US one.
[SPEAKER_00]: And there's also in the game's graphic files is a sprite of Mario.
[SPEAKER_00]: So there's your trivia.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: So check that out on the Sega Saturn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it a pretty easy game to find or kind of hard at this point?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hard at this point, but if you can find it, definitely go for it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know there are images of it available.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, we're finally going to take a break here.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're pretty long this segment here, over an hour and a half.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're going to take a break here.
[SPEAKER_03]: When we come back, more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a whole lot in our next segment news-wise because we're going to have a nice long interview with Tommy Tallarico.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's going to be here to talk about Video Games Live, the gang audio network guild that's going to be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so much more when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: So stay tuned.