[SPEAKER_07]: And welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio for this live Part B that we're taping on June 1st of 2008.
[SPEAKER_07]: And for those of you guys that listen to us on the podcast feed, you're probably going, hey, wait a minute, I'm not hearing you guys live.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you can always join us.
[SPEAKER_07]: We tape live on allgames.com, that's All Games Radio, every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time, 9 o'clock Eastern.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right after the Bobby Blackwolf show, the man in Atlanta, Georgia tapes his show live on Sunday nights as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you haven't heard his show, you really should check that out in iTunes.
[SPEAKER_07]: We make appearances on the show every week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bobby's kind enough to have us on the show to do a little cross-promotion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of taping the show live, you guys in the podcast didn't get to hear this, but we were actually listening to some of the tracks from the Metal Gear Solid 4 soundtrack during the break there.
[SPEAKER_07]: What did you guys think of it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought some of it sounded pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice help.
[SPEAKER_02]: Epic soundtrack is epic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, epic soundtrack is very epic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, I know you were watching some more scenes from Postal there during the break.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm an hour 11 into it, and it's an hour 47 minute movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Out of curiosity, those of you guys in chat, chat.orangellingerie.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you guys enjoy that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let us know in chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Meanwhile, we are going to get back into some gaming news here on this Part B. There's plenty of stuff to talk about.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think we mentioned the Wii at all in Part A. I got, by the way, I got a game this week, Boom Blocks.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of my friends kind of hooked me up with a copy of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Completely legitimate.
[SPEAKER_07]: He just had some inside connections, got me a pretty cheap copy of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm looking forward to checking it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll have a review on that next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're not going to talk about Boom Blocks right away, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Portal, Still Alive DS
[SPEAKER_06]: You remember the Flash game that they had out there that was kind of similar to Portal?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this is kind of similar to that Flash game, a little bit more cartoony.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you own a Flash card or a means of putting Homebrew on your DS, you can download this game for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it looks pretty awesome, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: Download it now before lawsuits.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually going to because I have a Ninja Pass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It uses the touch screen as well as some of the face buttons on there for launching different portals and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will have to play DarkSakura's copy because I don't think I'll be getting to check this out otherwise.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll hire a portal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm definitely going to download that because, you know, me and my minor portal obsession, so I'll have to
[SPEAKER_07]: Folks in chat are playing it right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo Maniac 64 says, ironically, I'm playing still live DS right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's have T says, it's rather hard to control.
[SPEAKER_07]: How the hell do I shoot the orange one?
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe you guys can put your heads together.
[SPEAKER_06]: The orange one is by pushing down on the directional pad or I want to say A. Or see if there's instructions and read them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Down or A and the two shoulder buttons are the blue portals.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's how you do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're like a Nintendo game counselor all of a sudden.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they have the screenshots of, or I guess artwork shots of the controls, so they're all over the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, well, the latest issue of Japan's Famitsu magazine has given us some insight as to what's going on with the SimCity series.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: SimCity Creator is going to be a new game in the SimCity vein, and it's going to be coming out for the Wii and the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be coming out September 22nd of 2008 for North America and September 19th, a little bit earlier, for Europe and the Japan and other Asia regions.
[SPEAKER_07]: And here's the interesting thing is that the Wii game, what you can do, you can draw your own rivers or tracks using the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can actually change the different styles of your buildings as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can do like a Chinese style building, an Indian design.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can also make buildings made out of candy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: or Christian.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie got so excited she dropped the mic.
[SPEAKER_02]: On my laptop.
[SPEAKER_07]: She was like, ooh, a candy palace.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like saying, you know, you can do like a gingerbread house.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it makes me think of the opening scene or one of the opening scenes in Charlie and the Chocolate Factory, the newer one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you see the newer one with Johnny Depp?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, it's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all I'll say.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a scene with a chocolate Indian palace.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, also, it uses the Wi-Fi connection feature so you can show off the game to friends.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of cool, especially when you draw those rivers shaped like penises.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Blade3 in chat got very excited.
[SPEAKER_07]: He says, awesome, candy rules.
[SPEAKER_07]: Candy does rule.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can have Candyland.
[SPEAKER_07]: It does depend.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you could actually make Candyland.
That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could actually make Willy Wonka's Chocolate Factory.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be so awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want a river of chocolate.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I want a wall that tastes like snozzleberry.
[SPEAKER_02]: there's no such thing okay anyway for people interested in other culinary related games that are actually related to food there's going to be another Cooking Mama World Kitchen to be released later this year around October-ish they actually have Majesco has a coming soon with a release date of October 30th
[SPEAKER_06]: It's also replacing Dinner with Friends.
[SPEAKER_06]: As you remember, there was Cooking Moment 2 on the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: This was going to be Cooking Moment 2 on the Wii, but I don't know if they changed the title or are actually going to change the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was supposed to be coming out in June, now it's in October.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need to have Redneck Cookin' Mama.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look, I'm... They have a game... We make fish sticks.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a game called Order Up.
[SPEAKER_07]: My roommate just ate that for dinner.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you smell that inside the house or something?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, actually... This is also Redneck Foods.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fish sticks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Funny you should mention that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I walked in the house and I'm like, it smells good in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: What'd you make for dinner?
[SPEAKER_02]: What is it about fish sticks?
[SPEAKER_07]: He said fish sticks.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I said... Funny that you should mention like a Redneck Cooking game because they're going to have Order Up, which is basically like Cooking Mama, but you're working at like a fast food restaurant.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need to have truck stop diner.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't they have diner dash?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, same thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look, I just hope Cooking Mama Wii kind of blew chunks compared to the DS version, so I really hope they do a better DS to Wii port this time.
[SPEAKER_02]: The closer you are to the screen, the more tight the control would be.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all I say.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did not enjoy Cooking Mama on the Wii, although I own it, and I'm kind of upset I do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, now the Wii was... The Virtual Console was supposed to be getting MSX games for quite a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: Finally, Japan has had their first MSX game release, and it's a game called Aleste.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what's kind of interesting, though, is that there's been some additional options to this game that no other Virtual Console game has, including the...
[SPEAKER_06]: MSX option menu which allows you to select between the MSX hardware based music and the more advanced FM music that back when the MSX was actually a console was in add-on card.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's pretty cool that you can actually do this in the game by pressing the minus button.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually just think that it's cool that they're getting that game because it's a really freaking good game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you can also do, I guess, there's some button change options as well thrown in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of neat that they're adding all these options almost like an actual emulator for this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why they don't do that with any of the other games that come out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope we get Gartic with the deluxe treatment.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know!
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, Toki Tori is a game that is coming to the North American virtual console, WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess it's not really a virtual console, but you know WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a 2D puzzle game, and it's going to cost you 1,000 points or 10 bucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, this game's been fairly well-reviewed.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a little puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You didn't like it?
[SPEAKER_07]: You played it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you describe it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I don't know much about this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I look at screenshots and I go, it looks a little Lode Runner-ish to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_06]: You collect the eggs, basically, and then that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you can hop around, jump different platforms with motion controls and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It might be cool later on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't give it that much time, but it wasn't something that I was interested in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it like Time Bird?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, it's very basic, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, how about something different?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure, different.
[SPEAKER_02]: Virtual Console!
[SPEAKER_02]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_02]: At least in the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: Games out this time around are... We have Hello Pokemon Puzzle League.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, why did I say hello?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm reading from the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says Pokemon Puzzle League has come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's also...
[SPEAKER_02]: Samurai Shodown, which makes me perfectly happy because it's the actual Neo Geo versions for their Neo Geo virtual console stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually it's going to be out for 900 Wii points, which is 630.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and before I forget to mention, Pokemon Puzzle League is 1,000 points.
[SPEAKER_02]: Burning Fight is also the other one that's out today.
[SPEAKER_02]: for 800 points, which is sort of like a Streets of Rage type brawler.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would download these games if I had room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that does suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't like having to delete stuff to make room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Room sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a game coming out in the US actually that Japan's had for a while now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a game called Tornado.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a lot of you may not be familiar with this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually very similar to Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the game entails you playing a creature that basically becomes a tornado and you have to
[SPEAKER_06]: Much like Katamari, suck up smaller objects and make your tornado bigger and then you can suck up larger objects and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tasmanian Devil?
[SPEAKER_06]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we'll be coming out on the DS in the fall.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say September, I thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought I saw this in September.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could be wrong though.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, it's kind of neat and kind of a little quirky game that will be coming out here a little bit later on.
[SPEAKER_06]: So keep an eye out for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this something you've actually played?
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't played it, but I've just seen screenshots and video of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Could this be the next big thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's going to be a big thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be a quirky little game though.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be like worth checking out at least.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alan Carr's Novel, The Easy Way to Stop Smoking
[SPEAKER_07]: And what the game will do, this game's coming out in November, what you do, you pick a coach, I guess, in this game, and you create a program based on your smoking habit.
[SPEAKER_07]: And basically what the easy way method does is that you educate smokers about how addiction happens, convince them that whatever type of great feelings you get from smoking, you get from...
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess you can curb that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you try to stop the emotional dependency.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's kind of strange, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is all coming out as a video game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this is, I don't know, interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really strange for Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to know, though, are there Rabbids in this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, that would be funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to stop smoking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's interesting that the DS is branching out like this, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, brain draining has kind of led to a lot of these outside-the-box type games.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm going to tell you what.
[SPEAKER_07]: I used to be a smoker, and I quit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Granted, I was not a very heavy smoker, but enough where I was addicted.
[SPEAKER_07]: In my mind, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: This might be a personal opinion.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll probably get hate mail over this.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the only way you can quit is to, when you say, I'm going to quit, quit, and then do it cold turkey.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's one of those things where when you say it, mean it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I didn't have that huge dependency either.
[SPEAKER_06]: So maybe that's how I was able to get away with the patch.
[SPEAKER_06]: What this game does, though, is when you have the urge to buy cigarettes, it gives you different Ubisoft game options that you could purchase.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's like, instead of buying a pack of cigarettes, how about you buy quick yoga?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or Far Cry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Far Cry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or how about purchase the My Weight Loss Coach?
[SPEAKER_06]: It comes with a pedometer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how this game's gonna work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Frisbee says, can't wait till Alcoholic Hero comes out for the TS.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you think, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think this will be an effective game?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that any tool is effective if someone believes in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a lot of it has to do with willpower and whatever... And I hate to use this term, but if the crutch works for you, then use it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kind of iffy about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just anyone who says that anything is easy is usually trying to... I mean, they are trying to sell you something.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're trying to feed you crap when all you need to do is just
[SPEAKER_02]: It's willpower.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know not a lot of people have a lot of willpower, and I know that it is a physical addiction.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a drug, and people are addicted to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, it's one that withdrawing from will not kill you.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just have to ride it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Listen, has anyone learned anything from Metal Gear?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can eat tree frogs.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at what happened to Snake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because he smokes cigarettes, he has to fight this crazy war, fight giant mechs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you really want to fight giant mechs?
[SPEAKER_02]: He smuggled his smokes in his stomach.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is why...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, I have nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But really, this game is stupid, and if you're suckered into buying it, then I'm sure Nintendo has a few other training programs that they can send your way, including vision training.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure they're going to have hearing training coming up soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Poop training.
[SPEAKER_06]: Consumer horror training.
[SPEAKER_02]: And how.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, and again, I'm going to stick by this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything is possible if you're willing to work for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything worth having is worth putting effort into, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just depends on how much you want it.
[SPEAKER_07]: My whole thing is that if you really, really, really want to quit smoking, if you really want to do it, you don't need a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'll just do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: A game might help, but you don't need it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not like heroin, you know, where you could, you know, I guess have a bunch of complications from withdrawal, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: If you need to buy a book to tell you how to quit something, that's retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: How do I quit something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop doing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you really need to buy a book for that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to say this because I will freely admit that there's lots of things that I have kind of poor willpower about.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think that if you just sort of say, nothing changes until you are ready to make it change and then do what you need to do to make it change, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think that you just have to want it bad enough to put the effort into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want it bad enough, you'll do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, well, we'll see how this game does and what type of floodgates it'll open if it does really well.
[SPEAKER_07]: In the meantime, let's talk about smoking.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, I have no pity for people who say, I can't stop smoking and hold a cigarette in their hand.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish my mom would quit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, guess what is coming out in Japan?
[SPEAKER_02]: A bunch of stuff, including the gardening game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Poop training?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is poop training coming out in Japan?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they actually have toilet training cartoons.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry I asked.
[SPEAKER_02]: With a toilet that sings to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: And poop that laughs as it exits the body.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm really sorry I asked.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're funny, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, they're getting a Fatal Frame 4...
[SPEAKER_02]: If you like your gory ghost games, then that one is definitely going to be the one to go for.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's by Tecmo Grasshopper Manufacturer Collaboration putting this out together.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Fatal Frame 4 can be also called Poltergeist Snap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Poltergeist Snap?
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a good name for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But basically you go around and shoot pictures of dead people.
[SPEAKER_02]: The end.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does your character at any point go, I see dead people?
[SPEAKER_02]: I develop film of dead people.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's only porn if you tape it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Instead of Fatal Frame, they should have Fatal Cam where you videotape certain places and then have to run it through a spectral analysis to have everything show up on film.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm still waiting for WhatTheyPlay.com Snap because that was the picture-taking game I was looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Raving Rabbids
[SPEAKER_06]: TV Party and you sit on the balance board and use your ass to play different mini games in Rayman's Raving Rabbids.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're kind of a party game sort of situation there.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the games they show is actually sliding down a hill on what looks like an upside down moose and you are using your ass to balance yourself as you go down the hill.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moose.
[SPEAKER_06]: Other options they're going to have in the game, too, are other minigames.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to have a dancing minigame where you have to do different things, different poses and stuff, which will also use the balance board.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it looks kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, of course, the raving rabbits are very funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: This needs to become a sitcom.
[SPEAKER_06]: The rabbits, just in ordinary life, kind of like a Garfield thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Should do like Joe's Apartment, but with... Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like where you're going there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if it's like Garfield, will there be a Nermal?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know I had to go back and read that again, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Garfield minus Garfield is excellent.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan and I had a discussion about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've decided that just looking at that either John Arbuckle, the main guy, is either really, really, really sad or mad, like Looney Tunes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe a little of both.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you know what makes me really, really sad and then really, really mad is the fact that I can't find Wii Fit anywhere because the game sold out as fast as it came out and that is not yet back on shelves.
[SPEAKER_07]: And one of those crazy game industry analysts, Michael Patcher, talked to the LA Times about the Wii Fit supply and how it's so short.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's very interesting what he says is the reason for this.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's because of the value of the dollar.
[SPEAKER_07]: The shortage demonstrates one consequence of the weak dollar.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're seeing companies ignore their largest market simply because they can make greater profit elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: They know that Americans will be just as fat a few months from now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even though there has been about half a million copies of Wii Fit shipped to the US, there have already been about 2 million in Europe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those things are going at really crazy prices on eBay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like $180 and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's dumb.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like Wii's when they first came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Same thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alpha Canogram in chat says, Sky should have pre-ordered it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the thing, I didn't know if the game would be any good.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a lot of money to drop on a game you don't know that much about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then honestly, though, I think they're giving... They kind of blame everything on the weak US dollar now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, there's a shortage.
[SPEAKER_06]: Must be the weak US dollar.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really think they put that much thought into it, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's just... They fucked up yet again, and so... I mean, because what would be the point of releasing... Like, for example, Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a shortage...
[SPEAKER_06]: The week it came out, and then there was a lot more later on next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you're telling me that the dollar turned around within that week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I somehow doubt that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Much like I doubt that once these stores get replenished with more product, that, oh, it's because the dollar turned around.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I think it's just because they're retard and poor planning.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Akuma JP is one of our listeners in Japan and he says there's fit everywhere here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Granted, the game's been out a lot longer there, but what I thought was interesting that he said is a lot of used here, so I think it's not that good.
[SPEAKER_07]: So apparently a lot of them are being turned right around in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can ship one to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can we play it on the American Wiis though?
[SPEAKER_07]: They're region locked, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you can.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can get the... Can you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't they figure out the... It's just the weight limit's not as high.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they patched the freeloader.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the Freeloader should work now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, remember that homebrew channel that we were talking about last week?
[SPEAKER_06]: They have the Gecko Freeloader that you can use on there, which is a basically region-free player for your Wii games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's homebrew.
[SPEAKER_07]: And free.
[SPEAKER_07]: SSJ100Matt says, I can't get my porn.
[SPEAKER_07]: It must be the weak US dollar.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't get his porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, if that were the case, then we wouldn't be able to buy any games because everyone would be selling them in different regions.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, they say porn is rescission-proof.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: CrunkyBoyJr says, I'm sure Nintendo does this on purpose to create a demand.
[SPEAKER_07]: They do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is retarded now.
[SPEAKER_06]: They want this to be the big Christmas item, and that's what they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to make this just like the Wii system, and it's going to be a shortage for like a year and a half.
[SPEAKER_07]: You watch.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, let's see what you, the listener, have to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can always email us every week, mailbag at orangelaundrader.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: And every week, DarkSakura picks out a few of her favorite emails and reads them to you in a little segment we call the OLR Mailbag.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, DarkSakura, dive in to mailbag at orangelaundrader.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pull out a few of your favorites and read them.
[SPEAKER_02]: None of them were my favorites, so the end.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice try.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, this one comes from Cheeseburger.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm finally reading one of your emails, so leave me alone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey guys, I'm going to get an Xbox 360 Pro soon and I want some recommendations.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, I got my first BSOD after playing six hours of StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never found out what the problem was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, you're playing six hours of StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably heat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, StarCraft's pretty awesome though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or your computer's like, stop playing StarCraft!
[SPEAKER_07]: Play something else.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck!
[SPEAKER_07]: It's such a broad question though about the whole Xbox 360 recommendations.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you like?
[SPEAKER_07]: It really depends.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell us some games that you do like and that'll be good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess otherwise games that everybody seems to like, at least if you're listening to this show, I can kind of already tell you probably must like the RPG.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're not as into sports games, let's say, because we don't talk a lot about those unless it's like Tecmo Bowl.
[SPEAKER_07]: Geometry Wars Marvel Ultimate Alliance
[SPEAKER_07]: You can get that on multiple systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but I still go back and play that all the time.
[SPEAKER_07]: What if you're a racing game fan?
[SPEAKER_07]: What's one of the better racing games on Xbox 360, you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: I still like the last Burnout game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Project Gotham 3 was okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I guess it depends.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Box suggests Actdeft, which is definitely Portal and other great shooter games if you like first-person shooters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tiger Claw, Samus is not in Marvel Ultimate Alliance, it's Iron Man.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Samus is in Marvel Ultimate Alliance, or was going to be in Marvel Ultimate Alliance, but got cut out for the Wii version.
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone found it in the PlayStation 2 version, because you know the code that they just edit out or whatever, or comment out.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'm going to have to find this then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a video out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think Kotaku ran it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to see maybe even Joystick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's some suggestions.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want more, I guess, tell us what kind of games you do like and that'll give us some places to start.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, next email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I read it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I?
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: This comes from Lycan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just thought that I would say hi and keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just wondering if any of you have seen the video of using the Wii with WoW and if not, I'll send it to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: He did send a link to it, but I'm not going to watch it.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said he thinks it's going to like our comments, but why don't we watch it and comment back on it next week?
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess so, because I've heard of it, but I haven't really watched it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Jamie, it'll be your responsibility to make sure we watch it for next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I have hiccups now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next email!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been listening to your awesome show for some time now, and I was just wondering what kinds of places you get your news-slash-release dates from.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you can't read it on air or don't feel like revealing them, it's no big deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just curious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Breadsticks are brought to you by this email home of the never-ending Olive Gardens by Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_07]: Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_07]: Between the three of us, we probably look at like a hundred different gaming news sites and blogs out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'll tell you a little bit about how it works behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Behind the scenes, we keep a little thread in a private forum that nobody but the hosts and some of the other OLR people who've worked with us for many years can see.
[SPEAKER_07]: And basically, when stories are interesting, we put them in this post and then we
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I will say, though, where I get my release dates from, since it's come up on the show as a question before, is that I do actually get my release dates from Eurogamer, which is just great overall.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I get my Japanese release dates from import game stores.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although sometimes I will use, just on my own, I will actually use some of the video game retailers in the UK to verify a few dates.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now, on the other hand, Loki sometimes has insider info on the US release dates thanks to, you know, the stuff that he does, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: GS68 says, What is OLR?
[SPEAKER_07]: A miserable little pile of secrets.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to point out there's other people that contribute to the stories you hear on the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkTetsuya also posts in our thread.
[SPEAKER_07]: And once in a while, Travis Donovan and DMN poke their head in there when they see something really interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's not just the three of us that contribute the stories, but just everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have our eyes everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: The terrorist story from Part A was actually a link given to me last night by my friend who's busy doing a programming test applying for Namco.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she's like, I'm tired of doing this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here, look at these links.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I get them from people.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other week I actually got from Ranma, so that was cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So next email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dun, dun, dun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's Amplitude with a Y, so I'm saying Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, this comes from Kevin.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kevin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, Kevin.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's in San Jose and you can read all the info at www.caexpo.com or just California Extreme into Google and Firefox, your rail bar, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be my first time going and it would be a kick to see what anyone else thinks of it from their first time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep up the good work and join the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hit the fair by accident.
[SPEAKER_02]: And join the show as I'm typing from work, huh, Kevin?
[SPEAKER_02]: We won't tell your boss, Kevin, because I do this all the time too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have never been to California Extreme, but I want to go this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: We actually ran into Mel and Melody there last year.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a hotel, and they live there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sometimes you want to get away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last year, in what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Where everyone knows your name?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, last year was my second California Extreme, and it's just a freaking blast.
[SPEAKER_02]: First of all, it's air-conditioned, which gives it major, major points over Pentagogo right then and there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like you go up to the desk, you pay your money, you walk in, PINBALL!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's not just pinball too, it's old classic games, like they had the Journey game there, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why I'm fucking sold on this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played a full game of Space Harrier.
[SPEAKER_02]: I beat Space Harrier, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's all on free play, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, we're definitely going.
[SPEAKER_07]: Definitely go on.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had... Oh, God, what else was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: They had that game where you slide a pole back and forth and you're sort of like a tug-of-war game where you... Oh, I thought it was Incredible Maze or whatever that game was.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's where you have to either run them into or push it from the other side.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's whoever's stronger, but you win matches out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I actually... I beat...
[SPEAKER_02]: Who did I beat?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember who I beat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I beat Will.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was who I beat.
[SPEAKER_07]: So look, there's your long answer to the short answer of yes, we're going.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's more.
[SPEAKER_02]: We asked for opinions of whoever had their first time.
[SPEAKER_02]: They also, it is an Ultracade sort of show-off type place.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they do have Ultra Pin there.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did last year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Ultra Pin is a plasma TV the size of a pinball table with LEDs and everything up and it emulates different tables.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's just really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: and they also have room with machines for sale.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you want to take home a bit of classic joy, you can nab a machine for cheap.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had Alpine Racing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're like, who's going to take that home?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, no one has room for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'll tell you what, if you want to meet up, because I'm definitely going to go, shoot another email and we'll make arrangements for meeting up there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do they do panels there or anything?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do believe they do panels.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe we ought to look into that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_02]: But California Extreme is just tons of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tons of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh god, really long email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Long email is long.
[SPEAKER_02]: Long email is long.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, but, but, but, but, this is from Katamari's Forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm going to read it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's watching that movie while you're reading emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm watching something else.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Now you gotta tell.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ferret porn?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a cat battle bot.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a battle bot that is controlled by a cat.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it rides in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that is the coolest thing ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_06]: I posted a link already in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, can I read this okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Good evening, OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: I trust you have had a pleasant weekend so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, since I didn't write a letter for the past couple of weeks, I wanted to put out a few things out of the open.
[SPEAKER_02]: With the school year ending in a couple of weeks for me, and the raging sense of boredom I feel I'm going to get, I decided to stock up on summer games!
[SPEAKER_02]: Since the titles coming out in the June, July, August months are slim pickings, I've got more than enough games to hold me over from the A-list Wii titles to Lost via Domus.
[SPEAKER_02]: While I live close to the border to Canada, I frequently shop there, and Canadian EB Games already has a game day sale out late June.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't wait for the summer sales here, and I hope I can find a copy of Rez, PS2 version, I don't have a 360, or, excuse me, Guitar Man for dirt cheap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything you're looking forward to playing other than WoW, Ragnarok, and GTA 4?
[SPEAKER_02]: I want the world to end with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I want the Iron Man game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm being denied.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guys?
[SPEAKER_07]: Games we want?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're looking forward to playing in the summer.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to be honest, not a lot I can think of right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wii Fit, whenever I can get my hands on it, I think will be fun to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially after the little demo I had the other week.
[SPEAKER_07]: But as far as games I'm really looking forward to, I can't think of a lot right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you going to hula hoop in your underwear?
[SPEAKER_07]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: I just might.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should get you some underoos.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Matt, were you looking forward to anything?
[SPEAKER_06]: I was looking forward to Saints Row 2, but I can't now because...
[SPEAKER_07]: later news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy 4 DS, if that ever comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think that's coming out this summer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it this summer?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's the end of July.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and the Civilization game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm looking forward to... I thought I might be looking forward to Grid.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure if I'm going to pick that up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the next game I have on order is... Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was Good to Heart Hero on DS, but I don't think I want that anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I may just get one of those DS R4s or R6s or wherever they are now and just homebrew.
[SPEAKER_06]: I might buy Guitar Hero Aerosmith for laughs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to continue because I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please do.
[SPEAKER_02]: What I'm still waiting for is my Okami covers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: I ordered one the week of when you said how to get one and I'm still waiting for it a month after.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you gotten your cover yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: And does it look cool?
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll find out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks cool on the website.
[SPEAKER_02]: And well, after reading some rave reviews and some really odd statistics, I picked up a copy of Grand Theft Childhood from my local library.
[SPEAKER_02]: While I haven't read a whole lot of it, finals week soon, have to cram, I have to say I'm quite impressed.
[SPEAKER_02]: They somehow debunk all of the gaming myths such as violence and sex and shed some light on the hot topics like what girls actually play and how violent video games reduce stress.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't wait to finish it as well as my newly acquired copy of Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to say I was...
[SPEAKER_02]: I was a little five-year-old boy again after hearing the news about DDRX and DDR Hottest Party 2 last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: While I know most of the world has moved on with other lavish music games, I'm still anticipating the release of one of the best franchises Japan has ever given birth to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I must be the only one in Michigan who cares about this now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of Konami, are they... What, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're grabbing the mic.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it for support?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, just getting ready in case I think of a witty comment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of Konami, are they really serious in releasing Rock Revolution in its current form?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they should just change the engine to Unreal 3.1 and put arrows instead of colored cues.
[SPEAKER_02]: But really, Konami and Bemani should just release a guitar-slash-drum-freakish type game and ditch the rock-and-roll-is-in vibe that just makes them sing like copycats of their own concept.
[SPEAKER_02]: and hopefully the DLC in Hottest Party 2 will be one unlockable key that unlocks everything and more for just 200 points or less.
[SPEAKER_02]: We could hope, but will they?
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Three more things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for giving us a countdown.
[SPEAKER_02]: How's Dr. Mario online?
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you really send Wii friends a demo?
[SPEAKER_07]: From what I understand, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Somebody has sent me a demo, but I haven't bought the game myself yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we don't get copies because we're not special.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we have to buy them just like you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, are you going to Penny Arcade Expo?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the plan.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will know for sure in a couple weeks, but I am planning on going.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Ferret, are you really going to be in a horror movie as the slasher that kills everyone?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we should let the ferret answer that, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think you should give... Oh, you shouldn't give so much plot details away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ferret's... You know what, Ferret?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, that's good enough, baby.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like the other one that made the different noises.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know the wolfy looking one.
[SPEAKER_02]: That one's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I regret that this letter is very super long.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just that I had to say was on my mind and I really didn't have the time until now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Until then, your favorite emailer freeway shuffling to the next DVR iteration.
[SPEAKER_02]: Katamari's forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: This message should be brought to you by the Olive Garden, but instead it's currently asking permission to be endorsed by Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, as Katamari's Forever wrote, Boobie Blackwell.
[SPEAKER_02]: Best typo ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe that's his cousin.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a typo, but it's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Two more emails and they're little.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, are they short?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: J-Rod.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, J-Rod.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a quick comment.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just listening to episode 279 at work the other day when Loki started his rant about Wii Fit and how Nintendo is just trying to find a new market of soccer moms and people who watch Oprah.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the end of his rant, I found myself almost clapping with my headphones on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, Loki echoes my thoughts around the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: This email is sponsored by the Olive Garden, home of never-ending salads and breadsticks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't encourage him.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't say anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Heart.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know he likes it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I was just wondering if you were going to do a show on a Saturday on a long weekend like you talked about a while back.
[SPEAKER_02]: OLR goes past midnight where I live and I have to get up at 5 in the morning.
[SPEAKER_02]: The show is comedy gold and I will listen until it is long dead like DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for putting on such a good show week after week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's BHK667.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know so much about Saturday, but we did talk about doing a show around noontime, so we should still make sure that happens at some point.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sometime over the summer.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what we should do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Although it would probably kill us.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do an all-night marathon.
[SPEAKER_06]: No way we'd die.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you know I'm not...
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I remember what happened when we did a marathon show at the tournament we had at Scandia.
[SPEAKER_06]: That wasn't fun, because you run out of things to talk about.
[SPEAKER_07]: If we found something, though, to keep things interesting, like maybe rotating out old classic video games for a night or something, or we did it for charity or something, there might be a reason to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe Labor Day weekend.
[SPEAKER_07]: But don't hold your breath.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so that's it for emails?
[SPEAKER_07]: if you would like to contribute, mailbag at orangelaundry.com is the place to go for now, more gaming news so as I kind of hinted when we were talking about games for the summer sorry, hold on, Black Wolf reminded me Labor Day weekend is the same as PAX for some reason I thought it was the weekend before so what's the next three day weekend after Labor Day weekend?
[SPEAKER_07]: maybe Thanksgiving that's not a three day weekend, Rob it's a four day weekend it's a four day pre-weekend whatever
[SPEAKER_02]: I probably won't be here.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's make up our own holiday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll make up a holiday.
[SPEAKER_07]: OLR day.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have OLR day.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we can all take off from work.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: Saints Row 2 has been deleted to October 14th.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, because I would imagine that Grand Theft Auto 4 is so awesome, so, you know, they have to spend the extra time making sure that Saints Row 2 doesn't suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, apparently, they're saying, you know, of course, marketing issues and product quality is the reasons for the... Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Product quality?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's just making sure that the game's not so glitchy.
[SPEAKER_06]: After all, we don't want another musical detailing the glitches in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I do, but no one else does.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's kind of cool that they're putting it out so late because that gives me enough time to be done with Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not that I'll ever be done with Grand Theft Auto 4, but to the point where I can play another game.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Play games I already have.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rugu is coming out from South Peak and it's a puzzle game coming out for 800 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's $10.
[SPEAKER_07]: And apparently it's a four-player game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't have to be.
[SPEAKER_07]: But what you do, you slide pegs of different shapes into appropriate holes while you're trying to save an alien race.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it sounds like the game Perfection, but a little different.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds bizarro.
[SPEAKER_07]: and it's also an 800 point price tag and it's coming out from Artec and we have a screenshot so it looks like a space game hence Galaxy but that's about it so you'll have to check that out when the demo comes out but if you've been for whatever reason secretly following Aces of the Galaxy and no more information than we do well then the payoff is this week there you have it payoff hey hmm hey hey listen what
[SPEAKER_02]: Galaga!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a listing up for Galaga Legions for Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually put up by the USK, which is the German version of the ESRB, and I would so try to pronounce it if I didn't suck completely at German, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, actually, that did remind me of something funny I found in GTA 4, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'll talk about that later.
[SPEAKER_07]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, they have a billboard for something called Passwasser.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pisswater.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, basically, it's a shooter.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's about all we know.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, but it's Galaga.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're not sprightly.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, and pixely.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: you know what though the weird thing about this is that it makes me think maybe it's an upgrade thing like pac-man versus was or not versus pac-man well i mean that was an upgrade but you know i'm thinking a pac-man championship edition kind of like that although pac-man championship edition is pretty awesome so if they are making a game like that but out of galaga that could be kind of cool because i actually like galaga so i don't know
[SPEAKER_02]: I like Galaga a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually have a little charm thing that's the ship somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if I care for Galaga that much, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: PENNY ARCADE was the highest grossing Xbox Live Arcade debut ever, earning $330,000 in its first three days.
[SPEAKER_06]: The prior record holder was Worms HD.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I guess in term of units sold on the Rainslake Precipice of Darkness was the third highest performer of 2008.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, good for them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still have not bought the game, but I think I'm going to because I had a lot of fun with the demo.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the Penny Arcade game, good for them.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a funny game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Mario RPG Legend of the Seven Stars
[SPEAKER_07]: is apparently making its way to Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be in June.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's made its way to the June release calendar.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know, games that tend to show up in the Japanese calendar usually end up over here eventually.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: which we already have here, Neketsu, Coco, Dodgeball, Boo, for the Sega Master System, Rambo, for the Genesis, Phantasy Star 4, for PC Engine, which over here was TurboGrafx-16, Power Tennis, Days of Thunder, Paranoia, and Blazing Lasers, and for the Neo Geo, King of Monsters, Ninja Commando, and Art of Fighting 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you know the Art of Fighting?
[SPEAKER_07]: I know there's a character named after me in Art of Fighting.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I spent about 30 minutes today reading the Wikipedia article about Dan from the Street Fighter Alpha series and how he's a big parody of Rio and Robert Garcia with Yuri's taunts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I don't know, are you excited about Super Mario RPG on Virtual Console, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: I am pretty excited about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just have to wait for it to come out over here.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be waiting, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're sitting here waiting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then why don't you read a story or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I will then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guess what else is going to be on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Beer Pong Game No, you have to guess though because I'm not going to read the story Well, I know the answer Tecmo Bowl Not the virtual console releases we've already got but we'll have Tecmo Bowl Kickoff which is a new football game that is going to be on the Wii so it's going to be on the Wii and we'll probably use a Wiimote
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's football, that's about all that we've got details on But I'm sort of agreeing with this article that it has the stench of WiiWare about it Will it have the awesome halftime cutscenes that the NES version had?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I'm hoping for I believe it's going to be on Wii and be about football Should cover about everything I know about that game Fine
[SPEAKER_07]: Be that way.
[SPEAKER_07]: See if I care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, our Skype line is going to be open very soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1-877-GAME-OLR if you want to get in on the fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have a couple more stories to read for you first.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say also one thing too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going back to the Tecmo Bowl, it's interesting this here.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can customize your teams, everything down to the logos, to the player stats, names, etc.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how they're getting around not having the license.
[SPEAKER_06]: because you can make your own teams.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Smart.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, something else that's coming to consoles, well, not anytime soon, but eventually, Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: And one of the cool things about Street Fighter 4 is other than online play, you'll be getting some new characters from the arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: And two of the characters that they showed concept art for, Fei Long and Dan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's also supposedly more characters beyond just those two, but two's a start.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it's kind of interesting to see that they're adding characters from you know Street Fighter Turbo and stuff like that plus it's Dan and I'm sure that makes Jamie kind of happy yeah it's just because he cracks me up because I love that his one of his attacks is it translates to taunting legend and um uh shiny fist I love all of his attacks they're just hilarious I actually kind of like playing as Fei Long in the Street Fighter super game so I'm excited to hear he's in Street Fighter 4
[SPEAKER_07]: Sound he always made.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, we'll be checking that out when Street Fighter 4 comes out here in America.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully sooner rather than later.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, Steam.
[SPEAKER_07]: I talked about Steam earlier when I was talking about AudioSurf, which I was reviewing earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Valve has announced that there will be a new edition coming to Steam.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Steam Clash.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cloud.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a service that was announced this past week.
[SPEAKER_07]: What it's going to do, it's going to store your Steam player data online and the cool thing about that is that you can access your saved games, keyboard configurations, all the games that you purchased through Steam from any computer anywhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that was something that was announced earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Valve is very committed to PC gaming and saying that PC retail is not doomed, even though they sometimes have these free weekend games on Steam.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just in turn supports stronger sales at retail.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, some people just don't want to buy their games online.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we'll have to see how this turns out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sounds pretty cool in theory, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we'll see how that works.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, in theory.
[SPEAKER_07]: You never know how that's going to work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, the Skype line is now open.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we're going to go to the Skype line right now and take a call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, it's GS68.
[SPEAKER_01]: Huzzah!
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, Huzzah.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: So, California Extreme.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think I'm going to go check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cool, then we'll see you there, and hopefully we'll be able to do something there, although I don't know if it's last minute or what, but we'll do an OLR lunch or something, if nothing else.
[SPEAKER_01]: If I decide to go, that might throw me what little chance I have of going to Comic-Con this year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, decisions, decisions.
[SPEAKER_07]: Comic-Con I hear is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've never been myself, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: If we go to California Extreme, we're probably only going to go for the day.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know about Jamie, but I see it as more of a day trip than a weekend trip, personally.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think it's something I want to stay the night for.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I'm actually going to go for both days.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's dedicated.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mainly because I'm in the area.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, Santa Clara specifically.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, gosh, it's right in your backyard.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: You should go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like six miles from my house.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well then you got nothing, you got nothing to worry about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of Santa Clara, you said you live in Santa Clara?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: I, uh, I might be going to Santa Clara around the time of my birthday.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm thinking of taking the day off work to go with, uh, my, uh, boyfriend and we can go ride some rides, so it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, I've only been there once.
[SPEAKER_01]: What critical thing you learned out of my Fanime report last week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Swap meet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, how was the swap meet at Fanime?
[SPEAKER_01]: Best deals ever.
[SPEAKER_01]: How so?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, if you go to Kingdom Kingdom, for example, and buy a year beat CD, it's like $40.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, this guy over at the swap meet was selling those for only $10 each.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now to get some other games that are cheap, Contra 4 for $18 and Amplitude for $3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like bargains.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's one thing I missed about going down to... I almost called it out of my expo.
[SPEAKER_07]: One thing I missed about going to Faname this year was getting to go to the dealer's room and the swap meet and all that good stuff and trying to get some good deals on shirts and stuffed animals and other chibi things.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did something cool happen when I was like getting Contra 4.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had a $100 bill and I offered to get only $80 and change back and to make it for a difference, you throw in an Ultramix 3 slash Extreme 2 sample CD.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, hey.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, little deals are pretty awesome sometimes.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, cool, cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, so to anyone listening, if you go to Anime Convention and don't go to swap meets, you're missing out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Swap meets are great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've looked into lots of good stuff at swap meets.
[SPEAKER_01]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well, GS6TO, we've got to let you go take some more calls, but it sounds like we'll be running into you at some Bay Area event in the near future, so take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, what's up, guys?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Toshin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, Toshin.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanted to know, Rob, if you've got picked up Super Dodgeball for the DS this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I forgot it came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you get it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I actually played my friend's copy and he loaned it to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell us about this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it faithful to the original or what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say it's pretty faithful.
[SPEAKER_03]: I only got to play a multiplayer brawl, but you can apparently level up your players and there's like 14 or 15 different teams you can pick.
[SPEAKER_03]: And your super shots are apparently picked on your birth date that you enter whenever they ask you for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so I don't know all the combinations of like the super shots, but my friend's is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of like the one where, you know, when you run and it was like one of the slider ones that goes back and forth like a vertical ball.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: He had that one set up, which was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: 8-Man Brawl 8-Man Brawl
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else you wanted to share with our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: Any other games you've been playing or what have you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't been playing a lot because I've been working a lot, but I probably won't make use of the 600 or 800 Microsoft points you're going to give me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I finally got that over to you, so definitely check that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you're supposed to be getting ResHD with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was the deal, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh no, I'll make use of the points.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will definitely make use of the points and me and you are going to have to play like Rock Band or something soon or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well I want full reviews on whatever you get later on, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: You got it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, take care Toshin, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep, thanks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for the reminder about that DS, Super Dodgeball DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had no idea it was coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, the phone's ringing off the hook tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're already into another call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yo, this is Jammer J. Hello, Jammer J. What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't believe I've heard you call before.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you called before?
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Just to solely play an arcade version of DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, good question.
[SPEAKER_07]: Farthest we've ever traveled to solely play an arcade version of DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, do you have any answer for this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's pretty much just like three hours, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: We drove from here to San Jose or Milpitas to play some Japanese stuff there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember also we drove to Stockton Golf Land to play...
[SPEAKER_06]: Extreme, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was Max 2 when it first came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Max 2 when it first came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: They only had it stocked in Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do tournaments count?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because we drove all the way to San Diego once to go to a tournament at Raze, and San Diego's like a 10-hour drive from here.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that was pretty, that's like one of the farthest I can think of.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or if you guys drove to like, was it the Japanese arcades?
[SPEAKER_06]: Arcade Infinity.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was thinking, I didn't drive all this way to play DDR, but I have driven that whole way to play Beatmania 2DX would be Arcade Infinity, which is in LA, which is about a six and a half hour drive from here.
[SPEAKER_07]: So how about you?
[SPEAKER_07]: What's the furthest you've ever driven?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think about six hours, but sometimes when I go on trips, I make it a highlight to hit up any DDR in the area.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I think...
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_07]: DDR tournament in Biloxi when I went back to visit
[SPEAKER_07]: I know you were out for a moment when the caller first called in, but he was wondering what's the furthest you've ever gone just to play DDR?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to play DDR?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I was saying, okay, Beatmania 2DX at least.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's been Arcade Infinity, but that's a close thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I went to San Diego.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to San Diego anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: But one of the things I intended on doing was playing the DDR Max when it was new.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, because Raise was like the first place anywhere that had that, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I went and played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: and that's when I realized that the hold arrows hurt really bad because I've got a little bit of a weakness in my ankles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other than that, the farthest distance I've traveled and then played DDR was going back to Alabama from here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that Biloxi tournament at Boomtown?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do believe it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a few years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was definitely before Katrina.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was when we had a max, they were just getting a fifth mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, yeah, I think I remember that, because my buddy was working at that arcade there in Boomtown.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't Boomtown, now that I think about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Small world.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it was that, the arcade was sort of off to the side, if I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was a shiny, brand new machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I got up there, and I think I played, when did I play Superstar?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that was, no, it wasn't that, it was when I was, I had this thing about doing, what was it that I used to always play in Hidden?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: but there's a within two hours is Supernova 2 arcade so that's not too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently there's a Supernova 2 in Roseville but I have yet to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love being from the south but I don't miss living there.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know the reason I don't play the home version so much is up here I don't have a good, since I live in an apartment complex, I can't use my Cobalt Flux.
[SPEAKER_05]: It depends on what you play at home on the actual platforms.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had that problem when I lived with Extifer is that we lived upstairs and when I played DDR it wasn't fun for the downstairs people so I couldn't do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but other than that, some people in the home version they have just as much fun on it but I would need to really play in the arcade because I hit pretty hard on the pads.
[SPEAKER_07]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well Jammer J, we gotta let you go to get some more calls, so thanks for the call, and I hope we call you in again sometime, we like hearing from new folks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Peace out, and triple A. Peace out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Peace out!
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: What was the other thing you said?
[SPEAKER_07]: Triple A?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like car insurance?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or maybe, you know, high score?
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR, triple A?
[SPEAKER_02]: Where you make the machine go, oh!
[SPEAKER_07]: One more call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, hey, hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, you always get through.
[SPEAKER_07]: You got the miracle dialing finger.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We like you, at least.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm recovering from Wizard World Philly, which was this weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: From what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wizard World.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wizard World Philly.
[SPEAKER_04]: How is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Want me to be honest?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why did it suck?
[SPEAKER_04]: As much as they really said this would be a big comic book convention, I could tell you it looked like no more than 10,000 people showed up at least.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just quiet.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just like bleh.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: 10,000 sounds like a lot to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, there's no Comic Con, but still.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus, the tournaments were kind of crappy too.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another thing that really pissed me off was the fact that somebody was there selling ROMs and emulators and ROMs for between $30 and $50.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you can get really busted for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean it's kind of illegal to begin with, but when you're selling it for profit, that's when they really go all out of the way to get you.
[SPEAKER_07]: You got to be careful.
[SPEAKER_07]: Turn them in.
[SPEAKER_07]: The funny thing is with  I said turn them in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well, interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell me a little more about this con.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was comics and games and anime and all of that all rolled into one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's more comic books than they add in a touch of science fiction and anime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of like Comic Con.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that's what Comic Con does.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, Comic Con is supposed to be about comic books, but hello, the Battlestar Galactica people show up every year and it's turned into this big, big thing, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Even with Starbuck being there, it still wasn't that big, big, big thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aw, too bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Starbuck was there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, my roommate was online for two hours to get her autograph.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've finally been catching up on Battlestar Galactica.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm in the third season right now, so good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, overall, I don't think we're going back next year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aw, that's too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, well, Ranma, anything else you want to share with our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Quick story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: About two weeks ago, I went to GameStop to pick up a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought Rumble Roses XX.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah, I know, I know, but I wanted the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sucker.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I paid $12.99 for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't complain.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I do want that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, quite a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good music, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boobs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, finish your story, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: We gotta finish sometime tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, no problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: So as I'm picking up the game, there's a guy there who flat out says, turn-based RPGs suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I looked at him, I'm like, what was that?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's like, yeah, turn-based RPGs suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: And me and my roommate look at him, and I'm like, you've never played the classic games like Dragon Warrior or Final Fantasy?
[SPEAKER_04]: He looks at me and my roommate and goes, oh, you guys must be in your 30s or your 40s.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would have slapped him right there in the store if I could.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bastard, you should have.
[SPEAKER_07]: Teach the kid a lesson.
[SPEAKER_07]: Respect your elders, you little shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, my roommate goes, yeah, you're right.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're absolutely correct.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell you what, I'm going to go home and have sex with my hot Asian girlfriend while you're fat with your five fingers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_04]: and Alina if you looked a little bit like Rossio UT oh stop it I'm sorry I had to get that in just for the chat room I'm so glad that you're coming to hang out with me Ranma what's the weekend you're going to be here 4th of July weekend I'll be touching down in Sacramento at 11.06am so you're just going to miss the anniversary show well I can't get that time off no it's fine better late than never right
[SPEAKER_04]: of course, we'll make up for it for lots of alcohol look, we're gonna have a great Independence Day Ranma, think of it this way fire explosions at my house exactly dude, okay, we pull a couch out in front of the street and burn shit that's the best and then at the end they burn the couch firecrackers at broken toilets, okay I don't know where they find it every day, they find a toilet, they get the firecrackers they just start launching them out of there I'm like, where the hell do you find this?
[SPEAKER_04]: you don't know
[SPEAKER_07]: BlackWolf in chat sums it up perfectly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our old buddy Bobby BlackWolf.
[SPEAKER_07]: The 4th of July, the day where you celebrate the birth of our nation by blowing a part of it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Works for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, Ranma, we've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: See you soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bring fire.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, don't bring fire on the plane.
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like fire.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I didn't mind doing it, but still.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob was in a really bad way last year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it was bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, let's not talk about my crappy life.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's talk about last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, do you have anything tonight for us?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo actually had released some dates for Japanese game releases, and there's some new games on there that a lot of people might not know about, including, well, this one they showed off before, Mario Super Sluggers for the Wii, which is coming out June 19th there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Band Brothers DX Resident Evil Zero Wario Land Shake Wario Land Shake
[SPEAKER_06]: Super Paper Mario Type Game July 31st, Fatal Frame 4, The Mask of the Lunar Eclipse Rhythm Tengoku Gold
[SPEAKER_06]: another rhythm music game, and Fire Emblem DS on August 7th.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they have a screenshot, or not really, well, a scan, I guess, of some of the stuff for Wario Land Shake.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like a platforming game and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, there's a new tournament going on for Mario Kart Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: This one's a little different.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not just like a race and times and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're actually doing a boss battle and you're battling...
[SPEAKER_06]: the spiky top man from Super Mario Galaxy so that's kind of neat that they actually have almost kind of like download content for this game that you're fighting a new boss or something I don't know why they include something like this in the game like maybe a story mode or something like that but at the very least though you can check it out for free and the exclusive tournament and content ends June 9th so if you want to check that out
[SPEAKER_06]: Do it now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, there's that game next week, Grid, that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Xbox 360 version is apparently freezing up on people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Codemasters is rushing to fix the game already, which I believe has been released in the UK already.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it will be coming out soon, maybe a day one patch or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They say we're getting close through the problem and we will be including a fix and a backup workaround option just in case in our forthcoming patch due within the next few weeks or sooner.
[SPEAKER_06]: We think the issue is due to a specific drive hardware and possibly with bad blocks or sectors on your hard drive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently Nintendo of America has 100 WiiWare titles in development.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wonder how many of those are going to be crap So that's interesting And let's see here
[SPEAKER_06]: There's some mobile games that have been selling pretty well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sonic Mobile has hit 8 million downloads, which is pretty amazing for a mobile game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Guitar Hero 3 Mobile has made 1 million downloads.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're interested in watching some original content from G4, or stuff that they used to have on their station, you can check out both...
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they have episodes of X-Play on there now, or Attack of the Show and stuff like that, as well as Code Monkeys, and I want to say there was a Block, I guess, which is a snowboard documentary series that never really debuted on the network.
[SPEAKER_07]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't they just put this stuff on their own network instead of, I don't know, cops, marathons, and cheaters?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's beyond me, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura I like fire
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, thank you guys so much for tuning into and supporting independent podcasting by supporting Orange Lounge Radio and All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, if you like what you hear, all you gotta do, tell two friends, you know, about our show because you slowly tell your friends and they tell other friends and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Eventually...
[SPEAKER_07]: We take over the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just this really easy plot.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like a pyramid scheme, but you don't have to pay for it because it is free here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or you could leave us a real nice review on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_07]: We appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or any site where you can rank podcasts and spread the word that way on the internets.
[SPEAKER_07]: So thank you guys very much for tuning in to another week.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be back next week with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a good week, everybody.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you for listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Thanks for watching!