[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_03]: To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_04]: and tonight for your entertainment Tommy Tallarico is going to be here on Orange Laundry to talk about video games live very shortly but first we're going to talk about some gaming news and I thought since you know we are going to be talking about music and video games how about some music news you have some music game news for us Loki you could share
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I do actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some pretty interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've been kind of hoping for this to actually happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: But apparently a box shot of Samba de Amigo, a bundle with Maraca controller add-ons, has been seen at UK retailer HMV's website.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I hope they aren't the cheapy, crappy little plastic snap-on things like you've seen for Wii Golf and Wii Tennis, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, they need to make the shaky maraca noise.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like that they have maracas on top of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if they make the shaky noise, but I don't see why they wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're going to do maraca controllers, do them right, or don't do them at all, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's right now on there for €34.99, which is about $70.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we always like to read comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: The ever-present fourth guest on our show at chat.orangeloungeradio.com live on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_04]: And J-Rod says simply, Maracas equals win.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maracas do equal win.
[SPEAKER_04]: What other games could be made better by Maracas?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, you think of anything?
[SPEAKER_07]: Games that could be made better with Maracas?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um... Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Soul Calibur?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, Maraca Calibur.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because remember, I did Rod Calibur.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you do Rod Calibur on the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Simply be Maraca Calibur.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got Maraca's controllers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me too, on Dreamcast, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's try Maraca's Calibur.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, any game can be played with the Maraca's...
[SPEAKER_05]: 3rdBullet suggests Gears of Maracas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gears of Maracas?
[SPEAKER_05]: Miso suggests Cooking Mama is better with Maracas.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only thing that's kind of weird about the Maraca controller, though, I noticed, is that... Where's the infrared going to come out?
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless it goes all the way through the middle there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it looks like the top's covered by the Maracas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, one game that will not be made better by Maracas is a game near and dear to our hearts here at Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Beatmania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, this series has been around forever, a long, long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I remember when we first started this show, probably like Six Style was the hot new thing that was out on the block, I think, when this show started.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Beatmania 2DX16
[SPEAKER_04]: That is incredibly gay looking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it really is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a pink Sailor Moon looking logo with a butterfly.
[SPEAKER_04]: 2DX16 Empress.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a little butterfly hanging off the S and it's pink.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is very, very, very pink.
[SPEAKER_04]: V2
[SPEAKER_04]: is supposed to be in this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: A sequel to V by Taka.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the most horrid songs in Beatmania 2DX history.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you've ever walked by a Beatmania or a DDR machine, you've probably heard this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: It actually is a V final from that Taka album that came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Beatmania 2DX Empress location testing right now, which means they'll probably be out in Japan in a couple months, and you'll probably see the home version in Japan only, sadly, early next year because they tried to release Beatmania here, and unfortunately it didn't do too well because people thought it was a Guitar Hero ripoff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shame on Konami for sitting on what could have been a gold mine for far, far, far too long.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, another potential goldmine, and this is one that was sent to us by the lovely and talented Sauce, is a Rumor of Guitar Hero Beatles edition, which actually I think would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that more of the young whippersnappers need to hear some Beatles music.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the Sony ATV CEO, Marty Bondier, I guess, said that they've actually talked about putting Beatles songs in a Guitar Hero game as something that you'd like to pursue, and that's a quote.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, maybe it could happen?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're getting booted from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Watch me do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is not a democracy here at OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a Jamieocracy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who is it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Third Bullet?
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to read.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamocracy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamocracy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamocracy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Revolution!
[SPEAKER_04]: Off with her head.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, um... I don't know if we're gonna... We'll probably be getting this before we'll see Beatles on any sort of system for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Rock Band is getting, um... I guess some tracks from Crew Fest, which is the Motley Crue tour, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: They've got a few tracks on here, including a free one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Part of the CrewFest pack, which is going to be 240 Microsoft points, or $3.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got Down at the Whiskey by Motley Crue.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got Time is Running Out by Papa Roach.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's Going Home With You Tonight by Trapped.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also the free track, Promised Land by...
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: G4's Judgment Day
[SPEAKER_04]: So we reached out to Tommy to come on the show to talk about the upcoming tour As well as respond to some of the recent emails we've gotten about Video Games Live So let's head on over to the Skype line Alright, hey Tommy, are you there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yo, I am here Hey Tommy Tallarico, how are you doing this fine evening?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing great, working as always You must be a very, very busy man traveling to all these new places on the Video Games Live tour Do you actually go to all the shows yourself?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh yeah, every single show aside from creating and producing the show every night.
[SPEAKER_00]: I also host the show and even play guitar with the symphony towards the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you've got to be pretty exhausted because not only are you balancing video games live, but video games live isn't the only thing you do either.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I mean, aside from still working on a few smaller game projects here and there, because VGL definitely takes up most of 95% of my time, but working on a couple DS and Wii and PC products, as well as also the chairman of the Game Audio Network Guild.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I definitely want to ask you about the Game Audio Network Guild, but I know the listeners want to hear about Video Games Live, absolutely, because we've gotten emails and calls about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me ask you this about Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to so many new places on this 50-day city tour you just announced.
[SPEAKER_04]: What can someone who has never been to Video Games Live before expect to experience?
[SPEAKER_00]: Video Games Live is all the greatest video game music of all time played by a full symphony and choir but what makes it really unique is that everything is completely synchronized with video and rock and roll lighting and special effects and interactivity with the crowd and stage show production and we have a whole pre-show festival with gaming competitions and prize giveaways and
[SPEAKER_00]: Costume Contest, Post Show, Meet & Greet It really is a complete celebration of the entire video game industry.
[SPEAKER_00]: In fact, I like to describe it as all of the power and emotion of a symphony orchestra combined with the excitement and energy of a rock concert
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: We really wanted to create an event.
[SPEAKER_00]: We wanted to create a show.
[SPEAKER_00]: We didn't want to just create a concert or, oh yeah, here's a bunch of classical people in tuxedos up on a stage playing video game music.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's great as well, but people have been doing that in Japan for almost 20 years now.
[SPEAKER_00]: We wanted to do something completely new, completely unique.
[SPEAKER_00]: And really, our goal from the beginning was to create this show for...
[SPEAKER_00]: The Non-Gamer as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: We wanted to create something that had mass appeal and that you don't have to know a darn thing at all about video games in order to come to the show and really be blown away and entertained.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that's why Video Games Live has grown so quickly and as big as it has.
[SPEAKER_00]: We did three shows in 2005.
[SPEAKER_00]: 11 shows in 2006, 29 last year in 2007.
[SPEAKER_00]: This year we have over 50 shows.
[SPEAKER_00]: Next year we have over 80 shows.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the goal is to build it by 2010 up to 100 and to 120 shows a year.
[SPEAKER_00]: So by having all these visuals and by creating a performance and a production and an event and a show,
[SPEAKER_00]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_00]: And again, that's not to downplay what all of the amazing concerts in the past have done and continue to do, but ours is a little different.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me go off of that a little bit, because you talk about making this concert accessible to even those that are non-gamers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know we have a lot of listeners that are a little bit younger, 15, 16, 17.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little harder for them to just kind of get up and go get a concert ticket.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would you say would be the best way to sell a night at Video Games Live to my parents?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, oh, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I mean, of course, there's a website, videogameslive.com, and we have a bunch of trailers on there.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you'll see parents in their 40s and 50s.
[SPEAKER_00]: You'll see grandmas in their 60s and 70s.
[SPEAKER_00]: You'll see little girls, 7, 8, 9 years old, all saying,
[SPEAKER_00]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_00]: Why I created this in the beginning was to prove to the world how culturally significant and artistic video games and of course their music have become.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so the best letters and emails that we get after a performance, they come pouring in.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're all from non-gamers.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're all from the people who are blown away going, oh my gosh, I never knew that video games were this incredible and the music was so powerful and the characters and the storylines were so
[SPEAKER_00]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll put in these comments and we'll put in, we show all of the reviews that we've gotten for the show and all of the comments and letters from people and non-gamers.
[SPEAKER_00]: And in those reviews, they all kind of, you know, follow the same thing going, well, you know what, I wasn't into video games, I didn't know what to expect, but wow, you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's word of mouth that really is, I kind of compare us a little bit in that respect to Cirque du Soleil in that, you know, the first time people had
[SPEAKER_00]: I've heard of Cirque du Soleil.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know I was one of them.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was kind of like, what the hell is it?
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it circus animals running around?
[SPEAKER_00]: Clowns?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was only until you saw it with your own two eyes or somebody really close to you explained it in great detail where you start to go, oh, I get it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, I mean, yeah, you could watch the 1,500 plus YouTube videos that are on there right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: You do a search for video games live and they'll all come up.
[SPEAKER_00]: But a lot of people always tell us, you know, I watched all the YouTube videos, but until you're there, until you're experiencing that magic of being in a room with 3, 4, 5,000 people all experiencing it at once, there's some magic that goes on.
[SPEAKER_04]: YouTube is never a substitution for anything like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever you guys are doing, however the word is getting out there, obviously it's working.
[SPEAKER_04]: Video Games Live is coming up on its three-year anniversary pretty soon, if I'm not mistaken.
[SPEAKER_04]: Based on what you're saying, ramping up to 120 shows in 2010, it's not slowing down anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would you say, Tommy, is the biggest accomplishment, the biggest thing you've accomplished from Video Games Live in its three-year history so far?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you know, I think that...
[SPEAKER_00]: I had a dream.
[SPEAKER_00]: Myself and my fellow video game composer, Jack Wall, who also conducts video games live, and we kind of created the show together.
[SPEAKER_00]: It took us three years to create the show.
[SPEAKER_00]: And in the beginning, we started this in 2002, and everyone thought we were completely insane and completely crazy.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I would say that our biggest... Show them.
[SPEAKER_00]: is getting this thing up and running to the point where... I could point to certain singular things that happened.
[SPEAKER_00]: For example, our first show ever was at the Hollywood Bowl on July 6, 2005 with the LA Phil.
[SPEAKER_00]: Over 11,000 people showed up to that show.
[SPEAKER_00]: People thought 2,000 or 3,000 people were going to show up or whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: What an accomplishment to say that
[SPEAKER_00]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_00]: The First to Play in Brazil and places like Spain and London, England, New Zealand, things like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can point to a lot of those things, but I just think the idea that this is surviving and growing at the rate it is, I think when everyone in the beginning told us we were insane and crazy and it would never work, that's the greatest accomplishment for us.
[SPEAKER_04]: And kind of building on that, because you've talked about all these places you've been, and that you're kind of the first video game concert in Canada, and the first concert in Asia, and things kind of keep growing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, through these latest tour dates, you guys are going to Germany, China, Thailand, Portugal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, your passport is probably very impressive.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got to wonder, how do you select the places that you're going to go?
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you decide, we're going to do this in Asia, or we're going to go to Portugal?
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you pick where you're going?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a great question.
[SPEAKER_00]: A number of different ways, actually.
[SPEAKER_00]: We've now grown to a point where people are now knocking our doors down, trying to get us.
[SPEAKER_00]: The people in China...
[SPEAKER_00]: Contacted us.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're doing Beijing and Hong Kong, multiple dates.
[SPEAKER_00]: The people from Singapore contacted us.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a great thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: In terms of all the places in the United States, we had a really important show at the end of April where it was our debut on Broadway in New York City.
[SPEAKER_00]: A very important thing for any actor performance is
[SPEAKER_00]: and we sold out the show three months in advance and so that was a huge accomplishment.
[SPEAKER_00]: What that does is that sends messages to all of the other promoters and cities and symphonies and buyers of this material.
[SPEAKER_00]: It sends out a strong message and so they start knocking down our doors so at this point for us
[SPEAKER_00]: All we're trying to do is take all of these things and make some kind of sensible routing or sensible order and figuring out, okay, which ones do we pick?
[SPEAKER_00]: For example, if the San Diego Symphony contacts us, oh, hey, let's do it during Comic-Con in San Diego.
[SPEAKER_00]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_00]: I would like to get a petition going to bring video games live to Taiwan.
[SPEAKER_00]: It would be the very first video game concert ever in Taiwan.
[SPEAKER_00]: She asked if she could use our logo and things.
[SPEAKER_00]: to start a petition.
[SPEAKER_00]: She wanted to make up flyers and pass them out.
[SPEAKER_00]: I said, sure, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_00]: I thought it was kind of cool and adorable.
[SPEAKER_00]: Two weeks later, she contacts me and she has an Excel spreadsheet and a link that I could follow.
[SPEAKER_00]: She says, hey, look, been working really hard.
[SPEAKER_00]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_00]: Dave Matthews Vans
[SPEAKER_00]: might be super popular in America and they might sell out 20,000 seat stadiums.
[SPEAKER_00]: But when they go to Germany, maybe not so much.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or when they go to Spain, no one knows who they are.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or Korea, no one's heard of them, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: And the reverse is true.
[SPEAKER_04]: European bands try to break you here all the time and people have no idea who they are.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just never really catch on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Exactly, and the same with Japan as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Whereas video games, music, what a universal thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, although the game popularity might
[SPEAKER_00]: might change from region to region.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_00]: here, we might play Halo as our big grand finale, but maybe down in Brazil, where the PlayStation is a lot more predominant and not so many Xboxes, maybe a game like Castlevania or Nintendo is big down there as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: So maybe it's Mario or Castlevania down in Brazil.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so...
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_00]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_00]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_00]: than I've seen and experienced in other parts of the world.
[SPEAKER_00]: Even down in Mexico, we played a smaller town in Mexico a couple months ago.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was at the end of March.
[SPEAKER_00]: We played a 7,000-seat bullring in Mexico, Mexicali, Mexico.
[SPEAKER_00]: It wasn't Mexico City, which is the biggest city in the world, which people may not be aware of.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: There were 5,000, 6,000, 7,000 gamers who showed up.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what's funny, Tommy?
[SPEAKER_04]: One of those people that were there at that concert in Mexicali actually called us that next weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, he's one of our listeners, Actdeft, and he said he had a great time at the show, can't wait to go back.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was going to kind of lead into my next question, which I think you might have already answered.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talk about the girl from Taipei, but if there's somebody who wants this event to come to their city or come back to their city, what do you think is the best way for them to go about doing this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you want to get a petition from every city, but what do you think would be the best way for somebody to get this back to their town?
[SPEAKER_00]: We actually put this in the FAQ on our website as well because we get asked that same question by so many people.
[SPEAKER_00]: and the other question that's asked a lot is how do you pick which music to play for different cities or countries that you go to?
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's really a two-part answer.
[SPEAKER_00]: The first question is we have a mailing list on the front page.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's Video Games Live mailing list and we don't spam people.
[SPEAKER_00]: We send out something maybe once every couple of months or if it's coming to your area, we'll geotarget your area to let you know that
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_00]: for that area so I can geo-target like a 200 mile radius around the city that we're going to and it will show me out of all the people who signed up for the mailing list what they want to hear most.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, you know, each show we do we have our
[SPEAKER_00]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then when you start to, we play about 20 segments in an evening.
[SPEAKER_00]: That constitutes about a two and a half hour presentation.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, you know, so one night we might, you know, if we're in France, for example, and, you know, the game Beyond Good and Evil was created by my good friend Michelle Ancel at Ubisoft in France, we're going to play
[SPEAKER_00]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, you know, we have, you know, in Asia, you know, stuff like StarCraft II and WarCraft, and StarCraft II hasn't even come out, but we're still, we're already playing the music and the video.
[SPEAKER_00]: And games like WarCraft and StarCraft are super huge over in Asia.
[SPEAKER_00]: But not so much down in Brazil, because a lot of people are less about PC gaming and more about Nintendo and Sony.
[SPEAKER_00]: So down in Brazil, stuff like Metroid and Castlevania is huge down there.
[SPEAKER_00]: So we vary, but we really listen to the fans from that area to decide.
[SPEAKER_00]: And if people want to...
[SPEAKER_00]: bring our show to their city.
[SPEAKER_00]: We also have an email address info at videogameslive.com and we collect all those emails and normally someone will get back to you within 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, excellent.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope not only Actdeft, but all of our listeners who are hoping to get video games live in their backyard are successful with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of listeners going to this show, I have to bring this up.
[SPEAKER_04]: This might be a little silly, but I gotta ask it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of our listeners, DJ Jani, wrote us on a previous show, and he was talking about the Video Games Live tour stop in Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Raved about the show, said he had a great time, but one part that kind of cracked me up is he specifically mentioned that you change outfits quite a bit during the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you...
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you coordinating your wardrobe to match the games, or what's up?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll tell you exactly, and I'll explain it, and it's, again, a great question.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I'm Cher up in this motherfucker.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I'm like Cher.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've got to change everyone.
[SPEAKER_00]: Madonna, you know, Britney.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, there's three times.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have a two-and-a-half-hour performance.
[SPEAKER_00]: I host the show, of course, as I mentioned, and...
[SPEAKER_00]: I want to be respectful to the symphony and the people on stage.
[SPEAKER_00]: But by the same token, I've been a video game composer for 18 years.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I might come out in an Armani suit, but I might be wearing Nike sneakers and a Spider-Man shirt underneath or a Mickey Mouse shirt underneath or whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I don't know what you'd call it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Casual whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Casual tux or something.
[SPEAKER_00]: But at the beginning, I kind of do that.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then we have a 20-minute intermission, and I come back, and now the shirt's on buttons.
[SPEAKER_00]: The coattails might be off.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're going to turn down the lights a little bit for this segment.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then at the end, I come out with a guitar, and it would look silly of me to be wearing a suit and playing guitar, so...
[SPEAKER_00]: by The Encore.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm kind of in, you know, a little bit more rock and roll gear, if you will.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so, yeah, so I changed three times.
[SPEAKER_00]: Once at the beginning to be kind of more formal, and then it kind of evolves into not so formal.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for helping to explain that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a very important question about being in his life.
[SPEAKER_00]: No worries.
[SPEAKER_04]: This really is an important question about Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people are wondering, is there a CD at some point in the future?
[SPEAKER_04]: Some type of digital distribution?
[SPEAKER_04]: iTunes?
[SPEAKER_04]: Question mark?
[SPEAKER_00]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_00]: In fact, it's something that was supposed to come out last fall.
[SPEAKER_00]: The record company made the decision that they didn't want it to come out during Christmas season because they didn't want it to get lost in all the great games that always come out around that time.
[SPEAKER_00]: So then we're going to delay it to the first quarter of this year.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, we're thinking, oh, maybe come out like around, you know, February or March instead.
[SPEAKER_00]: After all the Christmas hype had subsided.
[SPEAKER_00]: But then we're working on some new great pieces.
[SPEAKER_00]: At the time I was working on, because a lot of people also, they email us.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_00]: and so I was working on this Castlevania thing and I was just like man I really want to get this on the album so I asked EMI who's one of the biggest record companies in the world who's putting the album out I kind of begged and pleaded I said hey can we
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm talking about all over Europe all over Asia it's the first time ever that a video game compilation album is being released by a major record company around the world it's never happened before and the licensing if you can imagine the licensing you know going through companies like Halo and I mean Microsoft for Halo and Ubisoft for Myst and you know Konami for Castlevania I mean it got to be you know it was a bit of a
[SPEAKER_00]: Nightmare at first because no one had ever really done anything like this before.
[SPEAKER_00]: Same thing we encountered.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's why it took us three years to get the first concert in order because no one had ever done it to the scale and size that we were doing.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to be released all over the world.
[SPEAKER_00]: July 22nd is the release date here in America, which we're coinciding.
[SPEAKER_00]: Another reason we wanted to delay it
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_00]: Outside Show, San Diego Symphony, so many special guests.
[SPEAKER_00]: But we're also having synchronized fireworks as well for that show.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so this is all in celebration as well of our album being released that week.
[SPEAKER_00]: So we wanted to wait for something big, and that was the one.
[SPEAKER_00]: In terms of our European release, we're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're playing a 7,000-seat stadium in Leipzig.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the Leipzig Arena.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right there during the Games Convention in August.
[SPEAKER_00]: So we're going to wait to release the album in August in Europe.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have it be around a big press and marketing event and things like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then in Asia, we're going to be releasing it right around the time of the Olympics where we're playing in Taipei in the beginning of August.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that's when we're going to do the big release there, the very first video game concert ever in Asia.
[SPEAKER_00]: China, Taiwan, etc.
[SPEAKER_00]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we here at OLR, I think we can all agree we're very comfortable with you delaying the CD to incorporate Castlevania because that game is incredible and the music is awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like when Miyamoto – I worked with Miyamoto on Metroid Prime and I've known him for many years.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's such a great guy and he once told me –
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't you wish all game companies and game makers and game developers had that same sense about them?
[SPEAKER_00]: Why is Halo Halo and Half-Life Half-Life and why any Miyamoto product is what it is?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's because they refuse to let anything out that's not perfect.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or the best it could possibly be at that time.
[SPEAKER_00]: We feel the same way.
[SPEAKER_00]: We don't want to just rush out an album and
[SPEAKER_00]: We were making Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like, man, I got to get this on.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a really popular track that we love to perform.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're absolutely right.
[SPEAKER_04]: In gaming, a lot of people get very frustrated with these delays sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes it's for a good reason.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you know the funny thing about that, too, is that you'll notice people will bitch and moan like crazy when it keeps getting delayed.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then the second those games come out – I worked on Metroid Prime.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think we were working on it for five freaking years or something –
[SPEAKER_00]: with Miyamoto, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: But the thing you'll notice though is when the game comes out and it's freaking perfect.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you for having me.
[SPEAKER_00]: I remember that, Tommy.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was in L.A.
[SPEAKER_00]: and I wanted to go to the show.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was stuck doing work.
[SPEAKER_00]: I couldn't do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was so mad.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe just the theme from the very first game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That really haunting little melody in the beginning and the kind of upbeat as it goes through.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just the classic.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of partial to the soundtrack for Silent Hill 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what my co-host would say about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they're all about Silent Hill 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know the tough part?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's something to think about too from my end is that
[SPEAKER_00]: The music from Silent Hill is a perfect example where certain games, it's very hard to translate to a live performance, especially when you're talking about a symphony on stage.
[SPEAKER_00]: Silent Hill is one of those games.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll tell you the other game that was very, very challenging and I didn't want to put in the show until I...
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: What we did with Metroid is we decided to, let's try to create that beginning that everyone knows and loves so much.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's try to kind of recreate those electronics and bleeps and bloops with the symphony.
[SPEAKER_00]: And add in the electronics, add in the original...
[SPEAKER_00]: Sounds from the game and play those live with the symphony as well to kind of give it this really super duper retro feel because if you try to just do it with instruments, it sometimes doesn't translate, you know, so we're really happy with with
[SPEAKER_00]: I can't wait to see it myself, hopefully in San Jose.
[SPEAKER_04]: One thing, I want to kind of ask you about some of the other stuff outside of Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know we're kind of longer than we anticipated in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're having a good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to ask you about some of your other stuff besides just Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me take another listener question here.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of our listeners, DarkTetsuya, wanted to know, do you have a favorite piece that you've ever worked on for the video game music that you've composed?
[SPEAKER_00]: Sure, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to go with two, actually.
[SPEAKER_00]: The stuff that I did for Earthworm Jim is some of my favorite stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: And more so, not necessarily even from a composing standpoint, but from a...
[SPEAKER_00]: Just a silliness standpoint in terms of like when we were working on Earthworm Jim, there was like 10 guys in a room all trying to make each other laugh.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was Earthworm Jim.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's what we did.
[SPEAKER_00]: We had a year to make each other laugh.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you totally can't tell from the way it turned out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: And so that was such a great experience and just doing it so, so differently.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, that team had been together for a long time.
[SPEAKER_00]: We worked on –
[SPEAKER_00]: The original Terminator game.
[SPEAKER_00]: We did Global Gladiators for the Genesis.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then we did Cool Spot.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then we did Disney's Aladdin.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then we did Earthworm Jim 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then MDK after that before everyone kind of started their own companies.
[SPEAKER_00]: But that was such a great experience.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I would say if I had a personal favorite, that would be it.
[SPEAKER_00]: But in terms of composition, though...
[SPEAKER_00]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_00]: but I was really happy with the way the music composition turned out in that and it was something I've always wanted to do my whole life and so I really put my heart and soul into that score.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hopefully people will get a second chance to check that out if it ever makes its way to the Xbox Originals.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Game Audio Network Guild or GANG What's GANG up to this year?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, the biggest thing, the biggest thing that the gang has just done last week, in fact, was launched the version 3.0 of our website, which is a complete networking mass.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it really, you know, the third word in gang, network, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: The Game Audio Network Guild.
[SPEAKER_00]: This was always our dream to have this kind of portal and website available.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, think of like, you know, MySpace meets, you know, the Game Developers Association, you know, or the IGDA or, you know, Gamasutra.com or any of those great websites out there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Networking is so important in our industry.
[SPEAKER_00]: When I talk to people about people trying to get in the industry or give speeches at schools or whatever, I always say that the creative aspect of what you do is only about 50% of it.
[SPEAKER_00]: The other 50% is networking.
[SPEAKER_00]: I say that to any...
[SPEAKER_00]: Musician.
[SPEAKER_00]: Instead of practicing piano for 10 hours a day, if you practice that for 5 hours a day and then you take the other 5 hours and use that to network and to get to know people or to send emails or to help better yourself or your personality or whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: People have to
[SPEAKER_00]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_00]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_00]: Game Audio Curriculum for Colleges and Universities
[SPEAKER_00]: And by the way, some of these colleges and universities are places like Berklee School of Music in Boston, places like UCLA and USC.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, some of the finest schools in the world.
[SPEAKER_00]: and even some specialized colleges, accredited colleges, you know, places like Full Sail in Florida, for example, or Guild Hall in Texas or Expressions in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, you know, working, it's been a passion of mine from the beginning to really, you know, help the game audio industry have more respect and to educate not only each other as composers and sound designers but
[SPEAKER_00]: But also to educate the developers and the publishers as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because when I first got in this industry almost 20 years ago, they didn't care.
[SPEAKER_00]: They didn't give a crap about video game audio.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was so like – I mean a typical day in the office back in the early 90s would be somebody walking in my office saying, okay –
[SPEAKER_00]: The game's done, we don't have any music, we don't have any money or budget, we don't have any space left on the cartridge, and oh yeah, we gotta submit this in two days, so we don't have any time either.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_00]: and music go through the roof.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that's not just because of the technology.
[SPEAKER_00]: Gang should take a lot of credit for that, for educating all those things, for educating them about
[SPEAKER_00]: 5.1 Audio
[SPEAKER_00]: Sound designers and composers to do what we need to do.
[SPEAKER_00]: These are all things that gang does on a constant basis behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Some of our sponsors are EA and Dolby and some of these colleges and schools and THX and all these DTS and all these amazing companies, Microsoft and Intel and AMD and
[SPEAKER_00]: Chip manufacturers and things so everybody believes in the message it was just a matter of everyone banding together to get that and coming together as one to get that message out there as a group of people and that's really
[SPEAKER_00]: And of course we have our gang awards as well each year where we have about 25 different categories.
[SPEAKER_00]: Everything from best sound design of the year to best music of the year or best song written for a video game, best licensed music for a game.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's best cinematic sound in a game, so there's all sorts of different categories.
[SPEAKER_00]: AudioGang.org
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, Tommy, I got one more question for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: And thank you so much for spending the time here with us tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we always ask this, all of our guests we bring on the program.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the way we start off our show every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We always talk about our gaming weeks and the types of games we've been playing this week and what we've been enjoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Tommy, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of video games you've been into lately?
[SPEAKER_00]: Fantastic.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, it's funny because yesterday I played.
[SPEAKER_00]: Father's Day, Buzz,
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: I played a little rock band this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: But also, this might get people a little jealous, I've been playing Metal Gear Solid 4, of course.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been playing that for a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_00]: Guitar Hero Aerosmith
[SPEAKER_00]: Which hasn't hit the shelves yet, but I've been playing a lot of that lately as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So something Guitar Hero related is coming to Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_00]: An interactive segment with Guitar Hero and Stephen Tyler from Aerosmith.
[SPEAKER_00]: His real name is Stephen Tallarico.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's my cousin.
[SPEAKER_00]: We've been always talking about doing something together and ended up getting them hooked up with Activision to get that product on the market the first time ever.
[SPEAKER_00]: A band has its own music video game with Guitar Hero, so we're all really proud of that Wouldn't it be cool if somebody could come up on stage and play a song from Guitar Hero Aerosmith While playing along on the big screen with the orchestra And with some live musicians on stage as well, wouldn't that be cool?
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be awesome, and thankfully it's Aerosmith and not that Dragon Force song from Guitar Hero 3, because then I'd be, I think we'd all like, you know, I would want to lose in front of all those people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aerosmith I think I could probably handle, I know those songs pretty well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Tommy Tallarico, the man behind Video Games Live, the man behind Gang, and the soundtrack to so many video games, thank you so much for spending the time tonight here on Orange Launch Radio, talking about everything, and best of luck to you through the next few dates of your tour.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you, and I really appreciate you taking the time to help spread the word because I think what you guys are doing are so important to us and the growth of this thing, and talking about it really helps us out in helping to spread the word.
[SPEAKER_00]: So thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: No problem, Tommy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Best of luck to you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you so much to Tommy for taking the time to talk to us here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's pretty chatty, but a lot of really insightful information about how the whole process works.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's funny because I didn't believe it when he said it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Steven Tyler's last name is actually Tallarico.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I kind of thought it was a joke when I first heard it too.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I didn't follow up on that at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, it is true.
[SPEAKER_04]: He is actually related to Steven Tyler, which means he's also related to Liv Tyler.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can be related.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's just kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of thought he was joking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, oh yeah, he's my bro, he's my cousin, you know, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just very surprised.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's so funny because, you know, Loki exclaims something like, if it's not on Wikipedia, it's not true.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then he went to Wikipedia and I just heard, oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it is true.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyhow, we got some more gaming news to cover.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you guys on Skype are eager to call in, so we want to get to you guys as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have a few more stories for you guys quick, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll start off with Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well, last week, you know, the PSP got firmware 4.0.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, of course, they couldn't leave it just like that, so they put out 4.01, which, you know, is just, I guess, to make sure that 4.0 was working correctly and updates as far as...
[SPEAKER_05]: They improved some of the search features, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I don't know if they were trying to stop the homebrew stuff, but pretty much the very next day, the custom firmware 4.01 was released.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, PKJr92 in chat says, 4.01 is a joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like 9-1-1 is a joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: 4.01 is a joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that could be a hit new song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole annoying digital rights management thing on the Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: They have finally fixed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a new DRM tool, digital rights management tool, that is available on Xbox site, on the Microsoft site.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is originally going to be a part of the next patch or the next release, but it's actually available now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's available on Xbox.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can manage the digital rights contents of arcade titles that you've downloaded and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't used this myself, but I should because my original Xbox 360 died of the Red Rings of Death.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I have this awkward digital management thing with Geometry Wars and Joust, which were the first two arcade titles I ever bought.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I should go in and try to fix that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now you don't have to go through this whole mess of getting the points credited back to you and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, you can see the three-step process here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make sure you've signed into Xbox Live with this account, or whatever your name is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go to the Xbox Live Marketplace and select Account Management, Download History.
[SPEAKER_04]: Select an item and then select Download Again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Repeat Step 3 for each item in your download history.
[SPEAKER_04]: I win.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you win?
[SPEAKER_04]: I win a story.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what would this story be about?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, everyone knows that one of the coolest voice actors in the world, in my opinion anyway, is David Hayter.
[SPEAKER_07]: He has written movies, done a fairly good job with the first X-Men movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, with the first two X-Men movies since he did the screenplays.
[SPEAKER_07]: But he is actually looking for a petition out to get all of the fans to sign so that he writes the Metal Gear movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, honestly, I would have to think that he would know Snake better than just about anybody except maybe Kojima.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or some of the other people on Kojima's team.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think, though, that when you're the person who puts the personality into the character, I think that you would have a bit of insight into how to properly write for that character.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I think it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of writing creds does he have?
[SPEAKER_07]: He wrote the screenplays for the first two X-Men movies.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's doing an adaptation of Watchmen.
[SPEAKER_07]: But he's actually looking to have everyone actually email a rep at Sony Pictures.
[SPEAKER_07]: The address is, and I'm going to go ahead and say it on the air because honestly I would love for him to write the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: He does a good job.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's Matt, M-A-T-T underscore T-O-L-M-A-C-H at S-P-E dot Sony dot com.
[SPEAKER_07]: So send those emails in.
[SPEAKER_07]: And actually use good grammar, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: Spell check for the win.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a really good opportunity for us to try and get David Hayter on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to email.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to see if I can get an email.
[SPEAKER_07]: You realize I'm going to be sitting in the corner fangasming the whole time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fanning yourself.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's actually really good looking, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll have to see what we can do about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: In a reference to the video that we saw the other day, and no one else will get, Blurred Fluids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody's going to understand that.
[SPEAKER_04]: YouTube joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was I going to say here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Some comments here in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Dark Knight says as long as he plays him.
[SPEAKER_04]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_05]: but iTunes has a similar policy I think you can reset your iTunes digital rights management like once a year as well but of course then again you can also install the music on like four different computers something like that awesome well remember there was a big to do about the whole hot coffee crap in Grand Theft Auto San Andreas and then there was a settlement where people could possibly get money for not even having purchased Grand Theft Auto but you know
[SPEAKER_05]: You just have to pretend that you did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the response to the whole thing was really only 2,676 claims.
[SPEAKER_05]: You didn't say 26,000, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: You said 2,000.
2,676.
[SPEAKER_05]: And how many people bought Grand Theft Auto?
[SPEAKER_05]: Approximately 12 million.
[SPEAKER_05]: 11 billion?
[SPEAKER_05]: So that apparently is approximately 0.022% of the consumers that actually were offended and upset from the content in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: In other words, people looking for a free lunch, courtesy of Take-Two from McDonald's.
[SPEAKER_05]: And essentially that...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, just wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I had the stupid award music still queued, I'd probably play it right about now.
[SPEAKER_05]: But unfortunately, I left that in Part A. Everyone was complaining that it was such a big deal and everyone was making a big deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know who that .22% or .022% was?
[SPEAKER_05]: Jack Thompson and his family.
[SPEAKER_05]: And just people blowing the shit out of proportion.
[SPEAKER_04]: People wanted to see if it worked or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, out of those 2,000, how many just wanted to see if it would work?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I'm curious about.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they got money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did anybody in our chat room do it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Einhander and Xenogears are now going to be on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like Einhander.
[SPEAKER_04]: We still need Zweihander.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm surprised Xenogears is on there since I think it's a multiple disc game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hey, you know, they've got a lot of storage space on that PlayStation 3, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So anyhow, you can now download these songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can download these games on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're being sold right now in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, you can't do it here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's being sold for 600 yen apiece.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's about $5.56.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Money Talks, people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Money Talks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Ranma, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey everyone!
[SPEAKER_07]: I know what you were doing last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know what you were doing last night too, tell us about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know what you did last night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, besides getting drunk with Freeze Pop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, so when you say that, you don't mean you were actually getting drunk at a Freeze Pop concert, although that is probably true as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: You actually went out and got drunk with Freeze Pop the band.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, this is what actually happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please tell the story.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was at a room party having a good time, and I left, you know, to bring some more alcohol up, and I was going up the stairs, and I saw them, and the girl, I think her name was Elizabeth, she said, is there a party going on?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, yeah, follow me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Follow me right into the party, and we've been partying ever since, and right now I'm actually downloading all the pictures from the party with them as we speak.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you remind them that OLR loves them muchly?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes I did, in between shots.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I doubt they even remember us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Only one of them came on the show, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's where you just list?
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole band or what?
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole band.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doing shots with the band.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did they happen to let slip any things they might have coming up in the game world?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I read recently one of their emails that went out to everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a little bit of freeze pop controversy about the fact that their song I Am Not Your Game Boy is on Guitar Hero DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's actually not by Harmonix anymore, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: And so
[SPEAKER_04]: They wanted to kind of clear the air that, hey, they're loaning their songs out to, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, no, the deal was that, I think if I remember right reading on their site, they don't get paid when they're in the Harmonix games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do it just, you know, for the love of Harmonix, for the love of those games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they were getting paid by Konami when it was in DDR, by Sony, you know, branded games, and by, you know, the folks who did Guitar Hero on tour.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, a little freeze-pop controversy I thought I'd clear up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they really are talented.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, after seeing them a second time, it was really awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: They really deserve more, you know what I'm saying?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they're destined for stardom eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody knows some of their songs from Rock Band and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they did a new song at the concert.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they covered a popular song from the 80s as an encore song.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Final Countdown.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice!
[SPEAKER_07]: That's definitely keytar friendly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, you never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock Band 2, maybe?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next time you go drinking with Liz, since now you have her number in your black book or whatever, tell them that OLR would love a new theme song.
[SPEAKER_04]: No disrespect to Middie Head, but we've been using the opening song now for like two years, so we're looking for something new.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: I may be able to do something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know somebody that knows somebody, so I may be able to cash in a favor or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I would love you forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, what else is going on in your world?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you want to update our listeners on real quick?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, are you ready to drink this weekend?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, that's right, you're coming to town.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I can't drink.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can drink cider and milk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I'll drink cider with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, your cider will probably be special cider.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll get the Blackthorn for us.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm looking forward to you being in town, and I'm looking forward to the Fourth of July party when we're going to set things on fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a surprise for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay, I like surprises.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to present it next week if I can be on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course you can be on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought you were already coming to the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just wanted to make sure, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Ranma will be here in studio next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so until then, I'm hanging up on you because you have all next week to talk to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is next week, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: God, time flies.
[SPEAKER_07]: That means I have to do... I'm going to be busy this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's time to clean the house.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I already... My house is pretty clean.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just got to change the cat litter.
[SPEAKER_04]: You okay over there, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I'm just frustrated getting this working.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's J-Rod.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, J-Rod.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just asking you guys, what are you looking forward to for E3 the most?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's right around the corner.
[SPEAKER_04]: What am I looking forward to E3 the most?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, me personally, I'm looking forward to seeing how much of Microsoft's press conference really did get spoiled.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm looking forward to all the press conferences.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love sitting there not working and reading the press conferences.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really am looking forward to seeing if Animal Crossing MMO or Wii or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking forward to seeing if it is true that Animal Crossing is coming back to Nintendo and what they're doing with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so freaking curious it's killing me and of course I want Nintendo to address the space issues so I gotta say Nintendo's press conference I'm definitely looking forward to Sony I don't know what I'm looking forward to hearing from Sony but sometimes they really surprise you out of left field so I don't think you can predict Sony Microsoft if the rumors are true they're gonna have an interesting press conference ahead of them I'm also looking forward to seeing how the absence of these companies is gonna play into the E3 reports this year with all these companies dropping out
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, DarkSakura, anything you want to add?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they'll just have pretty much Activision, so since they're not going to be there, they'll probably have their own little press conference that'll take place at the same time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it'll pretty much be the same damn coverage.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, true.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still think that they made a mistake with cutting out the fanfare.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just think that they should have been a bit more discerning as to invitations.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very disappointing, but have you looked at the Penny Arcade exhibitor list?
[SPEAKER_07]: Now that I'm happy about.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's doing it right.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want to hear something that really would piss you off?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so my company got one invite to E3, and they said, oh, forget it, we're not going.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, you fuckers.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, you fucking whores.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, J-Rod, I'm turning the tables a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you looking forward to seeing at E3?
[SPEAKER_01]: I am looking forward to Gears of War 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is my main game for this year, is Gears of War 2, and I want to see how the new Silent Hill is turning out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm kind of iffy about that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, and I haven't seen this myself, but a buddy was telling me about this, that apparently the first 10 minutes of the game are out there on the internet, and it looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I don't want to spoil anything.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to have to pass on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, J-Rod, thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you want to share really quickly?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, well, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_01]: This phone call is brought to you by the Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go to the Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had Italian today.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I had Mary's Pizza Shack.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought you couldn't have pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I can't, but they have pasta dishes there, and there was a pasta dish with marinara, because I can usually have light marinara pastas.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it was good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, I better hang up on J-Rod.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you really want to hear us talk about Italian food the whole time?
[SPEAKER_04]: Osfer says, I saw a trailer for the new Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looked really scary.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not that many games I'm excited about right now, but that Silent Hill 5 is one of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that game is supposed to be out sooner rather than later.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we shall see very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to do one more call?
[SPEAKER_04]: One more quick call?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawn Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hola, bienvenidos a Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Echo 1, 2, 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it that hard?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're closing the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't deal with the lack of Echo 1, 2, 3 tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to go around and wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: First, we've got to get some last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, you have a last-minute story?
[SPEAKER_04]: I see you giggling over there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just in a giggle mood.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't be happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not allowed.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can be as happy as I want to be, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm going to whine so that you have to put up with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Neener.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you have any last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_04]: I did have a story.
[SPEAKER_04]: You did?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, then read it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop your bitching.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a story that Sauce gave me like an hour ago or so.
[SPEAKER_07]: That AppleCore has given the okay for a computer game to be released based on the Beatles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Since they own the master recordings.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: and they are trying to decide who's going to get it and they are between Activision and MTV Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that for real?
[SPEAKER_04]: That is crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, have any last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, well, I haven't been looking at last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been working on other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, Catwoman's going to be in Marvel vs. DC Universe, and she has a lot of cleavage, apparently.
[SPEAKER_04]: Surprise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tigerclaw mentions in chatroom, by the way, Sky, you know that Bill Gates officially retired?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: But he'll still always be kind of like a mascot of sorts to that company, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, he's gone, but he's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't he drop out of high school and start his own company?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just takes dedication.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: He dropped out of college.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, so did I. And look at me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm on the internet with a radio program with my friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: Winners don't use drugs.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what's your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: I fucking hate PHP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, my final thought is I really want another piece of ice cream cake because the one I cheated with on my birthday and had was really, really, really fucking good.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really want some creme brulee right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my fucking god, creme brulee is the shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm gonna go get some creme brulee ice cream, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Since we are Orange Lounge Foodio, I have to mention real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is our first mention of food tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we did have Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you know that Claim Jumper now has a healthy menu?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do they?
[SPEAKER_04]: Food under 600 calories a dish or something?
[SPEAKER_07]: Under 600 calories a dish.
[SPEAKER_07]: Half a day food, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: For them, that's really good.
[SPEAKER_07]: A bowl of soup and some of their garlic toast is under 600.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but now they have salads and stuff that are really good and under 600 calories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, but they're really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, they have the creme brulee.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have like a new dessert dish that's three of different flavors of creme brulee.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the green tea and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the little tiny dishes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do kind of want, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, I probably should be good after massively cheating on my birthday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I don't want to die.
[SPEAKER_05]: This isn't really a last minute story, but it's interesting nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_05]: But apparently there was a price drop on a cat skin for your Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it's a cute little kitten that you can put on your Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will post it in chat
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm not DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's the ferret.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's going to do it for another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will see you next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same bat time, same bat channel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.