Orange Lounge Radio
With your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and the Loco King
Tonight, June 8th, 2008
Could Microsoft really be going Blu-ray?
Another Star Wars character comes to Soul Calibur
And which former Supreme Court judge is getting into gaming?
Orange Lounge Radio
With your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and the Loco King
Tonight, June 8th, 2008
Could Microsoft really be going Blu-ray?
Another Star Wars character comes to Soul Calibur
And which former Supreme Court judge is getting into gaming?
Orange Lounge Radio
The only thing about Defend Your Castle is it gets a little bit old
Especially if you're playing by yourself
But it's a neat party game
Who doesn't love flinging people to their deaths?
I'm surprised DarkSakura isn't all over this game
She could be flinging helpless bad guys to their deaths
Defend Your Castle, it's a WiiWare game
I haven't played much Wii lately
I'll have to show it to you at some point, it's fun
It's based on an old, old Flash game
I think it's called the same thing
Defend Your Castle, it's very similar
But it was much bloodier in the Flash version
They had to, you know, Wii-itize it or whatever you want to call it
They had to tone it down, but I like the style
And if you notice also, just like that Gummy Car game or whatever they had
It's all done with the guy's voice
Yes, I love it, his voice is great
That's like the music in the game, it's great
Games I played this week, lots and lots of World of Warcraft
Because I'm kind of addicted
But I did check out a couple of the new arcade games on Xbox Live
These are demos only, so I'm really basing my opinion on demos
Just kind of a disclaimer there
Ace of the Galaxy, I don't know
I played it for a little while, it was kind of interesting
The shooting style of it reminded me a little bit of Rez
Where you could lock on to things and let all your bullets go off at once
But then I go, you know, I'm kind of playing it, and I'm just like, I just want to play Rez
Play a game like this
But it was okay, but I don't know
I can't justify spending little nickels and dimes here and there
Games got to really wow me
Back in the old days of Xbox Live, I was buying everything and everything
I have so much crap on Xbox Live, I can't even stand it
But now a game's got to really wow me, and it just didn't have that for me
I also played Rugu, that new puzzle-y game
But I didn't exactly see where the puzzle was in it
Because it was more of a reaction game
Now granted, I only played the demo of this
And the game made it sound like there was a lot more to be unveiled after the demo
But if that's the case, then the game didn't really sell me
Because all I really saw in the demo was
Turn these little disks as fast as you can
To make sure the shapes, as they fall, fall through the right shape
You remember that old, old game like we had in elementary school called Perfection
Where you had to put those little shapes in the right holes before pop
They all pop out, like before the board explodes
Right, you ever played that game? Am I the one that played that?
I used to play it
I think it was awesome, okay, thank god
Alright, it's kind of like that
You want to make sure you turn the disk
So that a star shape throws to the star hole repeatedly
Or else the galaxy blows up
Basically
In a nutshell
But I couldn't figure out, like, how is this game gonna
I mean, granted as it was going along, it added more shapes
And it got a little harder
And you had to, like, squash these aliens by speeding the bricks up
But it was still about reaction time
I was kind of like, where is the puzzle game in this?
If there's a puzzle game here, the demo totally neglected to show it to me
You have to understand, if there's objects falling down on a screen, it's a puzzle game
I guess, but not to me
So I wasn't very impressed
Which is a darn shame
Because the graphics and previews for the future levels made it look like more exciting things were to come
But I don't know
Maybe I'll have to look it up on the internet and see if there's videos of future levels that make the game more interesting
Because, I mean, it did hold my attention
I was like, whee, rotating disks is fun, this game is easy, I bet it could get lots of achievement points
But then, like, when the demo was over, I was like, that's it?
That's it?
So
Those are the two new games I played this week
Otherwise I've been playing more audio surf as well, that game's pretty rad, I talked about that on last week's show
If you missed that
Alright, we're going to get into some gaming news here shortly
But I also want to introduce the one and only chat room
It's chat.orangeloungeradio.com
Gerardimo in chat says, Rugoo equals the baby toy for adults
Kinda
Gerardimo also says, Rugoo equals boring, a lot
AJ Mix has been playing a lot of Wii in his week
He's been playing Dr. Mario on WiiWare, Battalion Wars Wii, Bomberman Live on Wii, and Mario Paint on the Super Nintendo
That's old school
Anybody checked out Dr. Mario on WiiWare yet?
That's one of those games I keep like, I need to get it, but I have no space
No, this is just like, remember how Nintendo said, oh we have a hundred WiiWare games in development
Yeah, they're all gonna be fucking old clones of shit
And then they're gonna put Dr. Mario out there
Just put Dr. Mario out there
But, hold on, to be fair, Nintendo is the master
No one does it better
Nintendo is the master of making old shit new again
Case in point, Mario All-Stars on Super Nintendo
Who didn't love that game?
Because it was like the upgraded versions of the old Mario games
Nintendo is the master of making old shit new again
And they do a good job of it
Maybe that was a little fanboyish statement, but they do
Now, I have to ask about this before we get into housekeeping tonight
And tonight at housekeeping I'm gonna address why there's been changes on Justin.tv
We'll get to that in a minute
But, first I wanna ask Loki. Loki ran through the door
Like, during the Bobby Black Wolf call
He calls in right before we go live
Because, you know, we tape live on AllGames.com every Sunday night
And if you haven't joined us yet, you ought to
And the show before us is the Bobby Black Wolf show
And, you know, we've been buddy shows for years
So, you know, this is awesome that we follow his show
But he always does this little tease when he calls our program right at the end of the show
And Loki ran in right during that statement
But I got a call right before saying
Rob, I'm gonna be late, there's food problems
So I have to ask
What the hell is the...
How did food drama make you late tonight?
Because the pizza place I ordered these breadsticks from said
It would take 10 minutes
So I went down there, 10 minutes
And took another 20 minutes after I got there
Apparently it was a stupid, stupid employee night
You know, where they're like
Oh, I forgot to put the breadsticks in
Okay, so they put them in
But they only put in half my order
Oh, I forgot to put the other half in
So, you know, I'm just sitting there
Nice
And the guy, you know, up front
Working cash register
Had his mouth open
Kind of drooling there
And some guy's like
Is my pizza ready?
I called it in, he said it's gonna be 20 minutes
And it's been 25
So, can you check on it?
Well, she said that it's gonna be
It was, you know, gonna be about 5 minutes once you've ordered it
What do you mean?
What?
He's like
Oh, well, they just put it in
Can you go check on that?
He's just like stupid and just standing there
I love how food emergencies are a valid excuse
Here at Orange Lounge Radio for making you personally late
I had plenty of time, you know, if my food
Even with like a slight delay
I would have still been here on time
But it was like fucking 40 minutes for breadsticks
That shit takes like 2 minutes to make
Alright
Let's talk about Justin TV at Housekeeping tonight
We've changed a little bit over on Justin TV
Here's what happened
We used to run through an iSight webcam
And my little Mac laptop
We used to run the webcam that way
But the iSight got broken due to my stupidness
And it no longer runs audio through it
So what happened is that this past week
I actually got a video camera
Because I've been wanting a video camera anyway
So I just figured two birds with one stone
I'm gonna get a video camera
We're gonna use it for Justin TV as well
So that's what you see hooked up tonight
We actually have now a video camera
Running on Justin TV
However, here's why the resolution is crappy
Because for some reason
Even though the old Justin TV broadcaster
Used to support 640x480 on the USB capture device
It no longer does that
So we have to use like 160
But it's some really tiny tiny resolution
So the picture's not great
I apologize for that
I will contact Justin TV
And the people who make my card
Try to figure out what's up with that
But then the other thing is that the audio
We were so close
We were gonna have it running through the microphones
But that didn't work out this week
Because with Loki running late
We didn't have enough time to run all the wires
To the places they need to go
So c'est la vie
We're running as the audio through the actual camera tonight
I still think it'll actually be better quality
Than the iSight was
Because as an actual video camera
I think it has better quality
But here's the other cool thing about what we have set up
And what we hope to bring in the future
Is that on Justin TV
All we would have to do
Is make a little switch
Just like this
And you guys won't hear this on the podcast
But they'll see it on Justin TV
You can actually go to live video of gameplay
And playing right now on Justin TV
Is our old favorite 8-bit classic
The Guardian Legend
A little screenshot from there
And you'll be able to see us kinda switch back and forth
So we can actually like
If we talk about games
And we happen to have them up
We can switch just that easily
Now here's the other problem
Is that on Justin TV
Just then
Their audio completely cut out
They only got the audio of the game
They didn't hear us talking over that
So that's the other thing we gotta fix
But we're working on it
Exciting things to come on Justin TV
But since you guys have been crying the past few weeks
Like where's the webcam gone
I wanna show you we've made some progress
We're trying
We are a non-profit organization here at Orange Lounge Radio
K?
Alright
So anyhow
Let's get into tonight's gaming news, shall we?
If there's no other housekeeping tonight
The only other thing I can think of is
The old plugs for our communities
We love to add people on MySpace at Orange Lounge Radio
On LiveJournal at Orange Lounge
Or our Facebook community
The O.L. Army
Let's get to tonight's gaming news, Loki
There's also the Orange Lounge Wiki
At Wikia
Oh that thing is awesome too
This is how awesome our community is
I put out a call on the forums this week
I'm like, hi
I don't know anything about editing Wikis
Like I'm not very good at it at all
I don't know the Wiki language
I think Wiki's a wonderful concept
I need to take my lazy ass
And sit it down for a while and learn Wiki
But the front page on the Wiki right now isn't working for me
Like I can't find things
Can someone please clean up the front page
Within 24 hours
It looks great
You go there now and it actually has all these articles
Linked from the front page
It's awesome
So if you haven't checked out the Wiki yet
Orangeloungeradio.wikia.com
A true product of our community
They are awesome for doing that
Alright
Well this is a rumor that never seems to die
CrunchGear, a tech blog, is actually reporting
That an inside source at Microsoft
Who was a former member of the company's
HD DVD department
Has confirmed that the company will announce
That the Xbox 360 will get Blu-ray
Before Christmas via a press release
That's set to go out tomorrow morning
Around 9-10ish
Apparently the system
They don't really have any info on it right now
But it says it will cost less than an Elite system
So
I don't know
This still seems far fetched
But I guess we'll just have to wait until tomorrow morning
Now won't we
Well which will be today
By the time this show goes out
So either we were really smart
In saying this in advance
Or we're dumb
But it seems like this rumor is always going around
That Microsoft is going to be announcing Blu-ray
What makes this special
All I think that they're going to be doing with this
Is just releasing another external thing
That's going to have
Just like the HD DVD player
I mean that would be the only way to do it
That's kind of fair to everybody
Because if you think about it
If you put this in the system
Then you're going to have problems with the drive being too slow
Because that's what the problem is with the PS3
And why you have to install all this shit on there
Is because the drive reads too slow
So if they had it as an external device
That way it puts everybody on level playing field
If you don't want it
You don't have to buy it
If you don't want it it's not going to cost you
As much as the system
I think that's what they're probably going to have to do with this
If they do include it inside of a 360
I think it's going to be a dumb move
Hopefully
I hope they tested all this stuff
To make sure that the access times are the same
Because otherwise you're going to have a lot of problems reading games
What is it about this particular report though
Why I should believe it
I don't know
I think those people are just
Because I think that instead of just saying
Oh it's coming
It's saying hey there's going to be a
Press release tomorrow
That says duh duh duh duh
At this time so it's a lot easier to say
Okay well this is going to be true or false
Instead of speculating whether it's true or not
Now GK128 in our chat makes an interesting observation
He says the new iPhone
Is supposed to be tomorrow as well
That's half speculation
Half Apple fanboys
Always speak about this stuff in advance
So they're probably right
Well here's the thing
Tomorrow is the worldwide developers conference
So is this Microsoft's answer to Apple
In a way like hey Apple's making this big unveiling
And we're going to unveil Blu-ray in the home
Is that what maybe gives us a little weight
Maybe I don't know it'd just be weird
Unless you know Microsoft
I mean they're always kind of butting heads with Apple
And stuff maybe they're trying to
Get people on board with
Their video download service and stuff like that
I don't know
And you put the nail on the head there
When they have their download service
Alright they had the HD DVD player
And to be honest
I guess when I hear about Microsoft putting out a Blu-ray player
You remember in the old Charlie Brown
Comics when a character would get really upset
There'd be a little scribble drawn over their head
That's what I look like
When I keep thinking about how my HD DVD player
Pretty much I only have five movies
I'll ever be able to watch on it now
We can still find movies all over the place though
Usually really cheap
But to know that there's no more
Ever coming out on some of these newer movies
I might want to get
Well we found out they were clearing out
We went out and bought our player
But I bought my player full price
That's why I have angry
Angry face
Well there are always positives and negatives
To adopting early
I know I know
It just sucks
Keep in mind
Blu-ray being now the
Preferred method
Of high definition
Media
I'm expecting now to start seeing
More of the
Less expensive models coming out
Over the next year or so
So you'll have an easier
Time getting one in your hands
All the more reason not to buy this
I don't know
Well I'm not going to buy the Blu-ray player because I know
Eventually I'm going to get a PS3
I realize I'm the only OLR host without a PS3
And eventually I'm going to crack it
Well right now
I'm not but Final Fantasy 13
Is going to come out someday
I am a Final Fantasy
Fanboy I will be the first to admit
When it comes out I have no choice
I must upgrade to PS3
Even if the game sucks it's Final Fantasy
I have to get it
I did the same thing for Final Fantasy 7
I held out on getting a Sony
PlayStation for the longest time until Final Fantasy 7
Came out and then I finally caved and bought
One and I'm glad I did because you guys all know
Tons and tons of classic games on the PlayStation
I hope the PlayStation 3 has
A similar legacy but I don't know
We'll see
Rama and Chad agrees, Rob you're not missing anything
Hey before we get to the next story
I missed one housekeeping thing, I'm such a jerk
But it's because we were
In a hurry tonight with trying to set up all the new
Fancy stuff for Justin TV which didn't
Even end up working anyway, I forgot to script out
What's going on for housekeeping tonight but I wanted to mention this
Because I saw his name mentioned earlier
DJ, I'm sorry
Mark Tetsuya says
DJ Tetsuya
Maybe for tonight he's DJ Tetsuya
DJ Tetsuya said
That SSJ 100 Matt is to
Thank for a large part of how the
Wiki got reorganized so thank you SSJ 100 Matt
I also wanted to say as far as
SSJ 100 Matt goes that
The Grand Theft Auto 4
Contest was finally finished over
Allgames.com this week, all the votes came in
Sadly SSJ 100
Matt did not win the contest
I'm sure as you read
They sent me the console instead because they knew
I was the appropriate owner
Of such a console
But I do have some good news
SSJ 100 Matt did tie for third place
So he does get something so that does kind of rock
So congratulations
The winner of the Grand Theft Auto 4
Contest was the Bobby Black Wolf show
And their little spoof on the Cheers ad that the guy made
And so he walked away with the
Limited edition
Xbox 360 and I got to admit
It was pretty funny
It was definitely worthy
We ended up voting for the Allgames Interactive one
Which tied for second place
Apparently, funny enough
Only one vote got
SSJ 100 Matt tied for third place
Because Bobby's show got like four votes
It was a runaway
But do you know which show voted for us?
Out of everybody?
Bobby
Because Bobby's the only one that probably
Understood all the in-jokes
That's great
So the winning show voted for us
I don't know what that says
But something to think about
Something to think about
Let's move on to more news
Something else we like to think about
Are music based games
Lately music based games have been all about
Guitar Hero and Rock Band
A brand new Guitar Hero game is coming out
If you haven't heard, it's Guitar Hero Aerosmith
Guitar Hero Aerosmith is scheduled to come out very soon
And there are some songs
That have been announced for the game
I'm disappointed
Well let me tell the songs first
I want Fog Hat edition
Tell your frustration
We'll just give it a couple more years
I'm sure that one of the billion releases will be the Fog Hat edition
You get to play in such places as Nipmuc High School
Maxis, Kansas City
The Orpheum Theater, Halftime Show
And Moscow
Which is kind of cool that you get to play at places
You know, like
Aerosmith kind of played in, that's cute
Some of the Aerosmith songs you can look forward to playing
Sweet Emotion
Livin' on the Edge, Lovin' an Elevator
Dream On, Walk This Way
And that is the version featuring Run DMC
That's pretty rad
And there's some other bands in the game too
Funny enough, there's not a lot of the other bands
Well I guess in a game called Guitar Hero Aerosmith
It shouldn't be that surprising
It usually breaks down that there's three Aerosmith songs in the stage
And two other band songs
And some of the other bands you'll see
Cheap Trick with Dream Police
Joan Jett, I Hate Myself for Lovin' You
The Clash, Complete Control
Lenny Kravitz, Always on the Run
And Run DMC with King of Rock
So
That's some of the stuff you have to look forward to
In Guitar Hero Aerosmith
Which is coming out for the Playstation 3, 360
And Playstation 2
And if just the game wasn't enough, once you know it
Bundles coming out as well
So no excuses to say
You can't play this game unless you just don't like Guitar Hero
Or Aerosmith
I like Aerosmith
Or if you're not a consumer whore and realize
Hey guess what?
You can just wait a few more months and get an actual sequel to the game
Oh Loki
Achievements
A thousand points worth
I'm not fucking playing that
I do like Aerosmith though
But I will
I don't know
Not buying a game just with Aerosmith
Cause that's almost like buying an album
I don't wanna buy albums anymore
That's a lot of album though
That's like 15 songs
Well I guess that's a normal album, nevermind
See what they're doing?
Now we're charging you $50 for an album
They will never know what's actually happening
You don't get to actually play your album
Then again it's not real guitar
I'm not making a good case here
Help Chat Room
Guitar Hero Fans
Justify Guitar Hero Aerosmith
Ready? Go!
The next story has to do with something that rather excites me
One of my favorite game series ever
And I'm not saying Metal Slug
But it's Samurai Showdown
They actually said
Well from the ESRB
That Xbox Live Arcade
Would be getting Samurai Showdown 2
And also now they're saying they should be getting Samurai Showdown
I suppose they mean they're getting them separately
But
There's no news beyond what
There's been on the ESRB
So we can hope
That they'll be all jazzed up and pretty
Are we gonna get like all the Samurai Showdown games?
Cause that's kind of a lot
What's so special about 5?
5 is the last cartridge that was released
On the Neo Geo cartridge system
And I've never played it
And I want it
I want Samurai Showdown HD Remix
You can do Samurai Showdown 5 HD Remix
I want Samurai Showdown 2 though
Most of all cause that one was like the best
Huh
They had caffeine nicotine
Nice
Going back to the question that we asked earlier
Justify Guitar Hero Aerosmith
Let's see, Kitsune says
I'm not too thrilled about the new Guitar Hero
AJ Mix says it's not Guitar Hero Blink 182
Kitsune follows up and says
I think my husband might get it for the 360
Robert M says
I still can't find many of the Aerosmith songs on iTunes
Gerardo says
Guitar Hero Aerosmith, why?
Because Guitar Hero makes it money
Let's see, GS68 is hoping for
Guitar Hero Loki Fusion
I don't know about that one
Well here's the thing
Activision is starting to get like
Before people were saying, oh you're really hoarding this franchise
Well now they're just
Not even trying to pretend that they're not
They are just coming out with
Oh by the way, hey if you don't want this
Guitar Hero game, don't worry cause there's like four
Other ones coming out within the foreseeable future
Last couple comments
GK128 says Guitar Hero
Insert band name here will always be a rental
Unless it's something badass like Pixies or
Dinosaur Jr. which you must be fanboys of
Frisbee says
Make Aerosmith a download pack
And AZHP says
It'll only be worth it if you actually like Aerosmith
Aerosmith's kinda cool though
I think what I'm talking about is
Rockband has it figured out with the download packs
Problem they're gonna run into with that though
Is what they do for Rockband 2
Because now you have like
Rockband with all these songs
And you can't
Here, make all the old songs that you've already downloaded compatible
Hopefully they do
Just like they did with EDR
And that's how they could sell more Guitar Hero Aerosmiths
Is by saying, okay well all those download songs
That you had will be compatible with this game
Or you can download more
And have them compatible with both games
That would be smart
Which is why they're not gonna do it
Nintendo Maniac 64 says
This is what we need, Guitar Hero F-Zero
I'm not sure how that would work
But it sounds good in theory
It would be just like
You know, the Rockband commercial where they're
On top of the bus, you know, playing their music
But on top of an F-Zero
That's the intro to the game, isn't it?
What's that? That's the intro to the game
I know, I know
But still, that would be Guitar Hero F-Zero
It's playing music really fast
On a really, really, really fast car
Flying through the air
Or maybe instead of that normal note track you have
You're actually on a car that's racing down
One of those super fast F-Zero tracks
Doing loops and stuff
And you have to read the notes off that
That'd be kind of fun
You know what would be cool?
Is to actually combine
The play levels for frequency
With Rockband
Wouldn't that be fun?
And so
As you play through it, you twist up
The path that they take and
Form new designs and
Get new effects that way
Or if you really want an obscure reference
You can just make a Guitar Hero
Action game that's based off of
Macross 7
Yeah, that would be great!
You get more points if you scream out
Listen to my song, dammit
For those of us who are familiar
With Macross 7
All the mechs were based around music
Rob, one of the biggest
Points in Macross was that music
Had a lot of power, which was how
In the very first series, spoiler!
You know, 20 years later
How in the first series they defeated the enemies
That came by was because of stupid butt-head
Mid-may
And so Macross 7 is sort of a big play-off
Of the whole music is power thing
I gotta tell you though
Going back to F-Zero for a minute
I wanted to actually put in F-Zero GX
And play it a little bit because it's still one of my favorite racers
And I think I said this over on Bobby's show
When we were doing the tees tonight
There aren't a lot of racing games I really like outside
Of F-Zero because F-Zero is fast
And it's horrifically simple
Like, that's what I like in a racing game
I like Burnout because Burnout is fast too
And it has explosions
There's not a lot of racing games I really, really love
If they made a Burnout arcade game that would be pretty awesome
That would be pretty awesome
Alright, let's move on with more news
So, of course
Me being a huge fan of Grand Theft Auto
Was a little bit disappointed to hear
That the Grand Theft Auto
Download content that's been promised for me
Has been delayed to Fiscal Quarter 1 2009
What's that mean?
Well, that means
That it's due between November 1, 2008
And January 31, 2009
Which when you look at it
It's not really that bad anyways
But hey, still though
I wish it was out a little bit sooner
Because, you know
Because sooner is better!
Exactly! And because you know
I'm almost done with the game
I need more achievements
And also I need more stuff to do
I hope they add tanks
What about multiplayer?
Multiplayer is fun
Having some lag issues
Well, not really lag issues
But like disconnect issues
But still love it
Love the multiplayer
We want to do instead of just killing each other
We want to do like a team of four
And go against another team of four
You know, because our office would kick ass
But so far it has
Cock blocked this from doing such
It's like, nope, sorry
You can't connect to anything
Fuck you, bye
I don't know
That's a really in depth message
Yeah, hey
I was surprised to see that pop up too
But you know, that's just how they roll
How they roll
Yeah, it's alright though
Because if the download content comes out later
That gives me time to play Saints Row 2
In the middle, and oh god I want that game too
You know, I don't think Saints Row 2
Came up on our show roll at all tonight
Maybe it's because we talked a little bit about the delay last week
But I guess a new trailer came out this week
And it caused somebody, and I apologize I'm not crediting this
But I don't have our forums up right now
Somebody went to the forums and actually posted
Dude, this looks like Loki the game
I didn't watch the new trailer
What's so great about it?
What they were doing, the whole trailer was comparing
Grand Theft Auto 4 with Saints Row 2
And mainly it was a trailer highlighting
The side missions you can do in the game
Because the side stuff you can do in Grand Theft Auto 4
You know, they have like
Bowling and playing pool and darts
And stuff like that
Well, they were showing
Oh hey, you can go and spray sewage
On people, you know
Or you can do insurance fraud
With co-op and throw people in front of trains
Or you can streak through the neighborhood
Or you can rob stores
And do all sorts of crazy stuff like that
Hey, you know what
Me being a fan of both games
Both are great in their own aspects
They're just different
It's like Star Wars and Spaceballs
So competition is healthy
Exactly, you know, I'm glad to see
Because a lot of the stuff that came from Saints Row
Ended up making it into
Grand Theft Auto 4
The whole
Their navigation systems
Pretty much the same as Saints Row
Using the cell phone for all the cheats
And stuff like that
A lot from Saints Row
Just, you know, the multiplayer
Probably pushed them a little bit more
To do multiplayer on the platform, which is good
So, you know,
Competition is good, I like to see that
And also because Grand Theft Auto came out
That pushed Saints Row to add flying vehicles
And stuff like that, so
I don't care, they're both awesome
You don't have to pick one
Alright, if you want to check out the Saints Row 2 trailer
11 million copies sold to retailers
So yes, that means about 2.5 million
Are sitting on store shelves right now
Waiting to be scooped up through the holiday season
That was all reported in Take 2's
Second Quarter Financials reported earlier this week
So, not too shabby
11 million units sold to retailers
Take 2
Very happy campers right now
Extremely happy campers
I wish I could sell 11 million
Units of one of my dream games
I'd be rich, I'd never have to work again
Although we all know, I'm telling you, if Laser Cats the game came out
That's like 25 million
25 billion
Units
I don't care, there's not that many people in the world
But everybody would buy like 5 copies because it would be that awesome
Don't you think?
I smell another ET
Uh oh
You know, speaking of ET
This is going to sound so random
But I don't care, I'm in a mood tonight
I was on Wikipedia this week
Reading about old school Atari games
Like ET and Pac-Man
And like why they failed
And it was fascinating
I don't know, just kind of reading up on my video game history
I think it's good to brush up on your video game history once in a while
Because you played ET and you're like
How does anything like the movie?
I don't get this
I didn't get it when I was 5
I don't get it now
Forget it
Can I do my story?
Um, more Xbox Live
Arcade news is
Uh, Commando 3
That's Wolf of the Battlefield
Is going to be on
Xbox Live Arcade as of I believe next Wednesday
And will be 800 points
And it also has an
Invite to Super Street Fighter 2
Turbo HD Remix beta
So
So I wonder how many percentage of the purchasers
Of Commando 3 are actually trying to get the beta
Like what happened with
Crackdown and the Halo 3 beta
Crackdown was pretty awesome
But Crackdown was a pretty good game
So hopefully Commando 3 is a pretty good game as well
That would make it very worth it
But I'm not a big fan of all these 800
Price points lately
Whatever happened to the $5 games?
When was the last time we got a $5 game?
Oh wait, we had like Warlords and stuff
I guess that wasn't really worth it though
Well now that Penny Arcade came out for 1600 points
Everyone's like, Hey!
That game sells really well, it's $20
Do anybody think there's a reason?
Ah forget it
They won't put 2 and 2 together
Well we'll see
If you don't want to download that
There are some other things you can download
Especially if you own Guitar Hero 3
We're going to have some new Motorhead
Tracks coming out
It's going to be part of
A series of tracks that they're going to have
Coming out in June
So the Motorhead Track Pack
Which will be available June 5th
I guess that's already come out then
Includes, We Are The Road Crew
Stay Clean and of course
Motorhead
And is available for 500 Microsoft points
Or $6.25
In real money
The track that's coming out next week
Which is the Isle of Wight
That is coming out June 12th
The price has been unconfirmed
But it's probably going to be also 500 Microsoft points
Includes, Shoot The Runner by
Cosbian
I Predict The Riot by Kaiser Chiefs
And Problems by the Sex Pistols
So that's pretty awesome
Alright
Well also speaking of ever expanding
Games, Soul Calibur 4
The roster of players just keeps
Growing and growing
And interestingly enough
When we got Darth Vader and Yoda
Announced for Soul Calibur 4
People were kind of like, oh haha that's cute
We're going to have these Star Wars characters
In the game that's going to be
Kind of random
But here's the weird thing
Another Star Wars character
Has been added to the Soul Calibur 4
Roster
So this is suddenly starting to feel like Star Wars
Versus Soul Calibur or something weird
Which I would not disapprove of
I guess that's true
It's kind of neat in a weird way
It's just weird
I'll say it again
After I've played the game, we'll see
But here's the deal
The Secret Apprentice
Is going to be in both versions of
Soul Calibur 4
Darth Vader is only going to be in the PS3
However the Secret Apprentice
Now the Secret Apprentice comes from
Star Wars The Force Unleashed
This guy is actually going to be
In Soul Calibur 4
So check that out
When that game comes out a little later this year
You know they need to put Bob Barker
Into a fighting game
Uh huh
Bob Barker needs to be in a fighting game
I mean that would be pretty badass
Immortalize him, put him in another Soul Calibur game
Soul Calibur versus Happy Gilmore
I don't know about that
No, just like TV show hosts
Just throw them in, random, it doesn't have to make any sense
The Star Wars stuff doesn't make any sense
Just throw it in
So if it's TV show hosts, can he like beat up Rosie O'Donnell
And Barbara Walters
Yeah sure, anything can happen
Bob Barker, don't you know that he's held together by Clay
And that formula from Death Becomes Her
Celebrity Death Match
That already was a game, wasn't it?
Speaking of characters held together by Clay
I know, really
Maybe they just need Celebrity Death Match 2
That would be great
But you know what they should have if they did something like that
Is have download characters
And have it, you know, where you could
Customize, you know
They have like, you know, like they do in the wrestling games
So you can make different, you know
People, you know, mimic them
In wrestling games, you should have something like that
Like Celebrity Death Match
Could be, make your own celebrity
See what they need to do, they need to have more games
I'm a celebrity, dammit
I want to put myself in the game
I'm an internet celebrity, I have a pen that says so
What they need to do is have more games that have that kind of same humor
As like Kung Fu Hustle, kind of like God Hand
Where it's just ridiculous
And more of like an anime style, you know
That was more of a brawling game
But, you know, more of like a fighting game
With some like funny characters that are just really exaggerated
And stuff like that
Star Wars vs. Soul Calibur gets a lot of reaction from chat
Let's check this out, Gerardo says
Star Wars GTFO of my Soul Calibur
Go get your own fighting game
No, they already did that
And that didn't turn out too well either
The Terrace
Then let Namco do it
Well, actually though, they're going to be doing something
With the Force Unleashed on the Wii
Is going to have like a fighting game portion of it
Why don't they just put a Star Wars game
That's based off the Soul Calibur engine
GS68 says this is Soul Calibur
Not fucking Star Wars Calibur
Cheeseburger says Chuck Norris in Soul Calibur
Will roundhouse kick everyone
I dig that, he doesn't have a sword
He just has his roundhouse kicks
Why not, GS68 says
Luckily if anyone picks a Star Wars character
I'll pick Ivy and suffocate them to death
Sounds like fun
I'd be like Boob Smash
Exactly, chat.ornisontraday.com
Is it my turn now, is it, is it, is it?
It is
Yay, um, well
I'm sure people who've listened to this show
For quite a while now know that I have an interest in law
I love
What
But you are the law
Rob
What?
You know, I think that's an unhealthy obsession
That you have there with Tekken
I was just waiting for her to go
I am the law
I do have a Judge Dredd pinball machine
In my house, thank you very much
But um
One of the former Supreme Court judges
Sandra Day O'Connor
Is wanting to make a game
That teaches court lessons
It's called Our Courts
It's a free game for kids between 12 and 15
And it basically
Lets you learn how
Courtrooms work, what the system is like
And learn
You know, actual legal issues
When I was in school
We used to do
Court simulations
Using modern day
I guess
The modern day courtroom system
To judge
Historical acts, like I got to be Marie Antoinette
So I had to be really
Awesome
Did they behead you?
First and foremost
Don't get me started on the French Revolution
Because
No one wants to hear about that
Keep in mind
I'm a history buff
I love my history
Look, here, I'll retard the conversation
A little bit
You know what we did in our school to practice courtroom?
What?
We watched Nickelodeon Kids Court hosted by Paul Provenza
That's what we did
Oh
The other thing that we also did at my school
Was model United Nations
And I got to be on the Security Council my senior year
And that was freaking badass
Because I had to tell both China and the US to shut up
What country did you represent?
Hungary
It was great
Hungary was on the Security Council that year
Considering that your life has evolved into
A food podcast
That sometimes talks about video games
That's really funny that you represented
Hungary
Oh come on
Home of the Habsburgs
Anyway
You can't write this shit you guys
It's all true
So anyway
It's basically
An educational game
Supposed to be put out so that children
Have a better understanding of how
The government works without having to
You know see the
Sort of farcical side of
Law enforcement with Grand Theft Auto
And those types of things
You know to actually see
Where your duties come in
I guess as far as
Participating in the system
I think it's a neat idea
And honestly it's something that I myself
Look into because I have
An interest in it
I've taken a number of law classes
Through my various majors
Didn't you say it was only for kids 12-15?
It's targeted
It's actually to be
Offered free to children
12-15 years old
I know some people 25 years old that could benefit
From that game
I want to give it a try
She's actually quoted saying
It will allow students to engage in
Real legal issues
And it gives an example of
A debate by someone
Wearing a controversial t-shirt
So I guess freedom of speech versus
You know how
Stupidly offended everybody in this
Country gets over people
Sneezing the wrong way
Sorry
Robert M. makes the mandatory Phoenix Wright reference
By saying hold it
Yes hold it
Anyways
So
This is kind of interesting
There's been a couple stories
That have come out recently about
Different gaming surveys
And oh my god what it means and stuff like that
Yeah I have never seen anything about this
And this just totally slipped under the radar
For everybody I think
Anyways
There was a survey that went out to
Select people in the
Microsoft game studio
And it was a survey
Talking about different
Characters and what you thought about them
And stuff like that
Now the survey was for
What they describe basically
Here's their description of it
This game will be a game creator
And will provide a simple way to make
Your own games on the Xbox
Using just the Xbox controller
You can build worlds, populate
Them with characters and give the characters
Unique behaviors
You can easily build racing games
Platformers and adventure games without
Touching a keyboard or leaving your couch
So this is either XNA for dummies
Or little big planet thing
Exactly
Well what this is
Through the process of
Deduction I should say
It's a game called
Or not even really a game
A programming language called Boku
And Boku which you'll find out
There actually are stories out there on the internet
I'm not exactly breaking any news here
Boku is a programming
Environment for children that runs on
Windows and the Xbox 360
And basically what makes it
Kind of different is it
Uses basically
Symbols like you have different objects
For each symbol and you have
Kind of actions
And then other objects
So you kind of tie them all together without any programming language
So say you have a creature that looks like
Pac-Man or something like that
The Pac-Man character
Eat dots
And so that character will now seek out
The dots and try to eat them or something like that
It's basically simple like that
But here's what I see
Happening with this
Sure they can make it just for children
But why not expand it to be a little bit more
Full featured and make it something that
Can compete with say
XNA, well not even really compete with
But compete along with
I was going to say you don't want to compete against yourself
With XNA or even say
Like a little big planet
There's a bunch of screenshots of
You know characters and stuff that they had out there
And there's some other like
Links and stories and stuff showing
The programming environment
And the characters look interesting
It's like everything from Pokemon looking characters
To I don't know
Just some strange looking shit
One of those things there looks like a pregnant Pac-Man ghost
I don't know what that is
Can you link that picture to our chat?
Looks like a pregnant Pac-Man ghost
But I just think it's really interesting
Now Dr. Seuss says
It sounds neat I wish there was a PC version
But this is something being developed across both platforms
It is going to be Windows and
For the 360
No idea though when it's going to be released
Or anything of that sense
But it looks like they're still working on it
If they're sending out surveys about this thing
Why has this only been a blip on the gaming radar?
I don't know
Do people think there's not going to be interest in this?
Or what is it?
The stuff that was covered here wasn't really in
It might have been just under the radar
Because there's no gaming related stuff
Kind of covered where this stuff was
It was basically at
The Microsoft Research Tech Fest
This came out in 2007
The Tech Fest 2007
So March of last year
Is when this
Originally was shown
And they only had it demoing
It was covered by WIRED
They actually had a
Little piece on it
But that's about it
I don't know
It's very very interesting
It could be something that's coming soon
Something maybe they'll show at E3
But if they are working on it
I think it could be pretty big
Because a lot of this stuff
The whole game 3.0 crap that they're trying to push
Where it's all user created content
Why not make it like a game creator?
What, click and play?
This old Maxis PC
Game making software is actually pretty cool
Vaguely, I actually do remember that
It was pretty cool, but make something like that
Maybe like LittleBigPlanet almost
But you can make your own games
Using this software and then distribute them
To your friends or post them on
Some sort of integrated message board
Or something like that
They're going to do the same thing with Blastworks
Which is coming out this week
That game is going to be pretty awesome
This is the way
Things are going
I'll link that picture in chat
While you're waiting for more
Information on Boku
You can get some games a little bit sooner
Across the world, we like to cover release dates
We're going to start off in Japan tonight
Not a lot sadly coming out on the Xbox 360
This week, but if we look at the Playstation 3
Hello, Metal Gear Solid 4
Guns of the Patriots
It's this week in Japan, June 12
Is when you can get that
The Japanese language version
You can get over there, there's a premium pack
A special edition
You know all the goodies
Because people in Japan love their limited edition stuff
So that is all coming out for Metal Gear Solid 4
And honestly because of it
There's not a lot out there
That really wants to compete with it this week
Nintendo Wii has nothing coming out
Playstation 2 has nothing coming out
Now the Nintendo DS has a little bit
Coming out, but not a lot
A game called Breath
Oua Akaneiro is coming out on June 12th
As well as another Pachinko game
That has to do with Neon Genesis Evangelion
Is coming out
Just because we didn't have enough Evangelion
Games on the DS
But I'm looking at what this Breath game is all about
And trying to figure out what this is
It looks like an adventure game
I'm trying to figure out if it's another dating sim
Because it definitely looks like you have
Cute girls on the top screen
And text on the bottom screen
That's usually a good sign of a dating sim
And also coming out in Japan
Othello de Othello DS
Which I'm assuming is just the classic game
You might know as Reversi
Yeah, it is
Othello
The old school game
And also coming out on the Nintendo DS
Sekai wa Atashi de Mowateru
Is coming out
Which is a
RPG game
From Global A Entertainment
And quickly glancing to see
If there's anything on the PSP of note
Or if Metal Gear is just dominating
The Sony universe this week
Medical 91 for portable
Is listed for the Sony PSP
That is a game
It's not Trauma Center, I'll tell you that
It's an adventure game
There's no screenshots, I couldn't tell you more about that
But looks like there's one lone game
On the PSP this week, but otherwise
Not a lot wanting to compete with Metal Gear Solid 4
This week over in Japan
Well we do have our UK releases
If anyone is interested
We have on the 12th
Metal Gear Solid Online and
Metal Gear Solid 4 Guns of the Patriots
Don King presents Prize Fighter
Whatever, that's on the 13th
More on the 13th is Doodle Hex
On DS
Emergency Heroes, Family Ski
Okami on Wii
Pro Cycling Manager 2008
And Sid Meier's Civilization Revolution
On Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3
Alright
The US, there's actually
Quite a bit coming out
Of course this week, you know, Metal Gear Solid 4
That's obviously going to be the biggest one
On PS3
Also coming out, NASCAR 09
On PlayStation 3, PlayStation 2
And the Xbox 360
We've got
Backyard Baseball 09
On PlayStation 2 and the Wii
8 Hunter Detective Chronicles
On the DS
Looney Tunes Cartoon Conductor
That's the one if you may remember
That's a rip-off of
Elite Beat Agents
That will be coming out on the DS
My Fashion Studio, also on the DS
And
Dragon Ball Z Burst Limit
On PlayStation 3 and
Xbox 360
And let's see here, Don King presents
Prize Fighter
And finally, Blastworks
Build, Trade, and Destroy on the Wii
If you own a Wii, you must buy this game
I'm telling you right now, buy this fucking game
Huh
It's an awesome shooter game
Everything's customizable in it
You can build your own levels
I'm thinking we should run a contest based on it
But, you know
I don't know, it looks awesome
I plan on picking it up when it comes out
Alright
Tomiki Fighters, you mean?
Well yes, it's basic, well it's not exactly
Tomiki Fighters, they do have Tomiki Fighters
in there as an unlockable game
But it is completely rebuilt
And it's a lot more than just
Tomiki Fighters, it's not just a rip-off
It's got a lot of stuff to offer
So, definitely check it out
Did the company pay you to plug them?
No, the company does not pay me to plug it
I think it looks really good
And they're gonna have this whole Blastworks Depot
thing where you can upload and download objects
created by other people
For example, you can take this and make your own
Star Fox game
You can take this and make another Guardian Legends game
if you wanted to
Stuff like that
I think it has a lot of
Especially, everybody's into the whole customizing stuff
Making custom levels for Smash Brothers
That was pretty simple
Look at this, this thing, people should run with this
Alright
Well, hey, if you want to get something a little sooner
as in right now, the PlayStation Network
was created on Thursday and they added quite a bit
of new things
They added something called Core, which we're gonna talk a little more about in Part B
But they also added some new downloadable games
Wolf of the Battlefield, Commando 3
came out this week, $10
As well as Nova Strike
Some new things came out for Guitar Hero 3
including the new God of War song
we talked about a few weeks ago
It did finally come out this week
Some new demos for you guys, including Civilization Revolution
Battlefield Bad Company MP
and NASCAR 09
for some varying games
Hail to the Chimp
which I'm sure you're all downloading right now
Lego Indiana Jones, slightly cooler
and very cool, Resident Evil 5
The trailer is up for that
if you're interested in checking that out
Also some new themes, a retro theme
has come out for the PlayStation 3
I'm not sure what type of retro that is
How retro could that be?
Maybe PS1 graphics
It's all Betamax
That should be kind of rad
It comes up with the beta logo
and then a bunch of
SOCOM, Fireteam Bravo 2
stuff in the PC
PlayStation Store
TV spots, wallpaper
and the whole freaking game
itself, if you want that
So check that out, PlayStation Network
updates this week
Another thing that's been updated
is Sega's calendar
It looks like Sonic Unleashed
is going to be out in November
but other things people might have been
waiting on like Aliens
Colonial Marines
and Empire Total War
are both going to be out in 2009
But the Beijing
Olympics game is going to be out on the 27th
of June and on August 27th
is a
game called Space Siege which is by
GasPowered Games
Other things that are set to be out
is the Golden Axe
I guess a revamp
of it, Sonic Chronicles Bioware
Role Playing Game
and Picto Image DS
also
a sequel to
Yakuza
I hate to say this because I know Sega
is near and dear to your heart and I don't know how you feel
about this series but Golden Axe
was something that was way cooler when I was a kid
I love Golden Axe
I love Golden Axe the Duel a whole lot too
I went and I downloaded
the Genesis version on Virtual Console
and I was just kind of like
oh my god this game is like repetitive and boring
it was so much better when I was a kid
I don't know what it is
but somehow the charm, the magic was lost
maybe it was because I wasn't playing with friends
at a pizza joint
you know what I mean? Games like that are always much funner with friends
because couldn't you like hit each other in that game
like if you're on that little purple bird
looking thing you could hit your friends over
that was always pretty rad
yeah and that purple bird thing would be something that you're riding
like in
Golden Axe Beast Rider
well I do still think
you know what I always loved about Golden Axe
I would check out a revamped version of it
because you know what I always loved about Golden Axe
was the ending, wasn't the ending
the best thing ever in Golden Axe
where they actually came out of the arcade game
spoilers, sorry
I was gonna say
one of the games she forgot mentioning there
of course
we're gonna like this game on the Wii
uh
Someday Amigo, that's out this summer
nice
but only if there's like fake maracas
I love maracas
you know someone's gonna release
a maracas attachment
they will, they've talked about the little
plastic sleeves and silly things
and besides, if they don't
what a difference duct tape
and maracas can make
all you need to do is order more free
condoms for your controller
seriously, we should do
okay, you know what we should do?
the Orange Jones Radio edition maracas
I love it
and we make them out of paper mache
like you used to do in kindergarten
we'll get all the supplies at Michael's
we will, you can actually just buy gourds
and duct tape a gourd to it, that'd be fantastic
if you don't live
Michael's is all across the US, right?
I think so
it's a craft store, if you live abroad
even though you've visited a Michael's
let me just put it that way
it's a great little craft store
anyway, forget it
dude, okay, I've been spending so much time
with stuff I have to get at Michael's
that, okay
I'm gonna make maracas
just you watch, I'll make them
put it on YouTube and all that stuff
we have a YouTube channel we don't use for anything
your hands can be, right?
yeah, I've actually thought about buying
a tub of the fondant there one time
cause that stuff tastes like those animal cookies
but it's really not good for you
alright, forget it, move on, move on
so something that has nothing to do
with Michael's
unfortunately
it's, you know, sad to see
that Itagagi has
left Tecmo
so you're not gonna see
him helming anymore Ninja Gaiden
or Dead or Alive games
at least not with Team Ninja
I
I don't know why he left
but I guess just
you know
emotional distress
I guess
worsening personal relationships
and work environment
if I remember right, wasn't there something about unpaid overtime
too, or something that factored into it?
I'm sure there is
basically he's a very disgruntled employee right now
he's a rock star, he can't be like, you know, tied down
with a job and stuff, he has to be trashing hotel rooms
Itagaki is a fucking rock star
you don't see a lot of
gaming rock stars
Itagaki is a rock star
they need him to hang out with
say the guy that does the
Castlevania games
just like make this really kick ass
guitar wolf
programming team that just
fucking says, they come in
they kick over the microphone and they're like fuck this
you're buying our fucking game and everyone's like
hell yeah I am!
so that's how they need to do it
just like scare the crap
out of the press, that'd be awesome
just come in, set something on fire
throw it into the crowd
just like, that's how you
sell your game
women coming out and wearing
nothing but you know
skippy ass clothing, they don't fucking
care if it's offensive, they're just like
whatever man, just some fabric
they bought at Michael's, that's all
whip cream, that's it
just whip cream
barbecue condiments
Itagaki is a rock star
so he'll go on to doing something
I'm sure
just hopefully he doesn't decide to go
develop playground equipment
like a certain other people
unless the playground equipment
electrocutes children
that I can see
and has fake boobs that are on it
yeah yeah
that's what he does in the middle of the presentation
just a motorboat right there
busts out with that
buy our game
how come you never see someone like him
busted for destroying hotel rooms?
that's what I want to know
just wait for this year's E3
you know, that could be the rock band sequel
no, keep in mind
instead of
I don't know
but keep in mind
you have rock band the RPG
where you know, you go and you trash
hotel rooms and have groupies
and you know, that type of thing
wouldn't that be awesome?
how about video game rock band or something
because you could play as Itagaki
alright, maybe not
you know, Itagaki's got his own thing going on
he's cool
he wants to have champagne
and only green M&M's
if anyone gets that reference
that's awesome
by the way, if you get that reference
you're awesome
because that's a true rock star right there
somebody who fucking demands
only green M&M's
just to see if someone will do it
more points to somebody who gets that joke
alright, anyhow
what?
Africa
onto things less cool
actually, I take that back
because this game was kind of like the running joke
of E3 a couple years ago
because they didn't tell us anything about the game
there was nothing told about the game
well guess what, finally
finally with this game just around the corner
for release in Japan very soon
some details have come out about the game
Africa, you're going to be a photo journalist
and you can take pictures on foot
in a car or by air balloon
which is kind of rad, because you don't see hot air balloons
make many gaming appearances
and you can unlock
non-CG pictures
and actual research footage
of animals as you encounter animals
in-game
and it comes out on August 28th
you build up this animal library
well great, I would like to know as much as possible
about the things I'm running over in my jeep
I don't think
you can do that in the game
dammit
so basically it's Africa Snap
but it doesn't sound like it's on a track
it sounds kind of a whole lot cooler
it's going to be a trailer for the game
and with the graphics and all
I've got to say, it does look like
potentially, it's going to be a very kick-ass
I don't even know if you really call it a game
like a kick-ass thing
it looks really neat
I've got to say
so maybe we'll all end up eating crow
about making fun of this game at E3
a few years ago
but it actually looks kind of neat
so I want to check this out
right, and then Aya Judgment is going to be awesome too
oh wait, no, I mean you really got to check out the preview
it kind of, like the graphics look gorgeous
absolutely gorgeous
yeah, they do look gorgeous
great, what does it say about the gameplay?
nothing, exactly, and the gameplay could suck
and this game could still suck
but I'm just saying, there's hope
there is hope, before we had no hope
Africa was just the running joke
but now that we're finding out a little bit about it
it sounds interesting
exactly, just like Frisbee says in the chatroom
Africa equals Endless Ocean
yes, pretty much
and how did Endless Ocean do?
not very well, how did
there was another Safari game that was on the Wii
that sucked
that's the only Safari game that did any
and this is not even really a Safari game
but a similar game that did
you know, really well was Pokemon Snap
I'm going to guess that's because it had Pokemon in it
have we ever had like a really kick-ass
Safari game, like Jumbo Safari
of course, but
that's just an arcade game, people like that game
eat moves and you're going really fast
and you're catching animals
and you can throw harpoons
harpoons make every game better
add that to the list of things
that make games better
1 Dragonforce, 2 harpoons
3 Pokemon
who didn't love Scorpion in the first Mortal Kombat
Pokemon does not make things better
stop that
that is wrong
Pokemon has flavor
eating Pokemon would make a game better
number 1 thing that makes games better
Dragonforce
by the way, they have a new album coming out
do what?
number 2, things that make games better
harpoons
3, the other things that make games better
fire, shooting hookers
we need to get them on the show promoting their album
I will send them an email
right after the show, I will
alright
however we have some other business to take care of
real quick
Tigerclaw says in chat
the real question is
will Africa show animals doing it?
yes!
since it's supposed to stimulate
stimulate the wildlife
well we know where my brain is
since it's supposed to simulate
wildlife, what do wildlife often do?
Frisbee says
Africa, rated M for strong sexual content
2 things, 1, animals fuck
2, monkeys throw poo
the end
did you see that, someone says
and it had the pester ball
did you see that
there's a little robotic camera
that you can drive around
and take pictures with
in Africa?
yeah, it looked like a Mars lander
I can't wait to annoy things with that
that's it
Darktessia's got it
instead of doing Africa, they should do
Jurassic Park
with a cam
and you could drop lawyers in there
and watch them eat people
were you trying to avoid getting eaten by a
velociraptor?
no, you have a robot camera
dude, taking a trip down memory lane
for a minute, and we're about to get into the
classic game a week, so this is okay
I don't know if you remember this game
the original Jurassic Park game that was on
Super Nintendo, it boasted
it was one of the first games that used surround sound
and all this stuff, now here's the thing
the game was kind of split into two parts
there was an overworld thing
that was kind of generic, like it was your basic
3D
ISO type view, where you go
around the world collecting things, whatever
but then you went into this mode, which was like
first person, Doom type thing
and I'll tell you what, if you played that game with all the lights
out and everything back in the game
that mode was scary as hell
because you would be walking around
and suddenly a velociraptor comes out of nowhere
and crawls your eyeballs out and it's over
and it was scary
did you ever play that game?
it was freaky, and then Hitler comes out
in the robotic machine
but I was at just two lanes one time
back when they had an arcade and not a pro shop
and they had
for some reason their Jurassic Park
shooter game was broken
and so I got to play on free play
the whole time, so I had beaten the arcade one
you know what, I'm very disappointed in him
this is totally off topic, but that's fine
off topic, us, who?
this show, off topic?
it has to do with games
where the hell is the fucking Silent Hill arcade game
locally?
hey, that's a very good question, what the hell ever happened to that game?
no one has imported that shit
that is a damn good question
let's buy one
we could put it in the corner right there, that works
I'm down, we could just liquidate the funds
Loki will be very happy at this news
guess what the OLR studio is getting next week?
a couch
we are getting a couch, and I'm thinking we're gonna put it right there
where Loki usually sits
by the way, I'm going to
buy us an air conditioner
sweet
with the funds that were donated to us
hooray
and we're going to put it in that window
and we're not gonna burn our asses off
here in the studio
it's not that bad
not right now, but wait until August, hello
well we could get more fans, I don't know, we'll get the damn air conditioner
you know what, we need
a game called beat the heat
where you actually take like, pockets of heat
and beat them to death
one other quick thing about Jurassic Park, wasn't it weird
that the Genesis version of Jurassic Park was like
a completely fucking different game
it was like, it was more of a side scroller
it was better
he could play as the velociraptor and kill people
true, alright, there you go
just about everything was different
you know, for games that would come out on one system
versus the other
look, nostalgia is awesome
and all, but we have another segment we do
here on Orange Lounge Radio
it's a chance for us to
it's nostalgic too?
it is, very nostalgic, it's a chance for us to pay tribute
if you will, to the elders
of gaming, what?
I had a list of two
and thanks to Sauce
I had a list of one
well you'll just use the other one next week, won't you?
I'll probably forget
and I had to go in the vault to pick this again too
look, look
this is the last video game of the week
for you kids to dig up and play
and Dark Sakura
is dug through the archives with Sauce
the archives?
what is wrong with me tonight? I'm broken, malfunction, malfunction
alright, uh
exterminate
exterminate, what is the classic game
the kids should be playing this week?
Space Channel 5
cheeseball, cheeseball, cheeseball
play some music!
oh did I miss it?
you want me to go back to it?
Space Channel 5
And this one is obviously from the Japanese version, but her voice actor in America was
Apollo Smile, who was supposed to be like the blooming anime girl who's actually kind
of a big hoe.
But with this one though, it is technically a music slash puzzle game.
And so the whole point of this is that you run into these little aliens called Melodians.
And it's funny when you have your load screen that says Now Meloding, which I felt was pretty
good.
Anyway, they'll name out a direction and then maybe a shoot button, and you have to mimic
it when it's your turn.
And it has to be perfectly in time with the same rhythm that they did.
So you have to have a really good sense of rhythm and keep up with it.
As you go through, you also have like a little heart blast where you can rescue people.
And so as you're going through the game, if you rescue people, they join your little entourage
that walks behind you.
And like in the last level, you can actually get Space Michael, as in Michael Jackson.
There's also a Game Boy Advance one that I didn't play because I refused to.
And Rez had a Merolian in it as one of the evolutions for the characters.
So that was pretty cool.
There's also the Space Channel 5 minigame in Sega Superstars.
There's a Sonic, uh, the, the, um, Ulala is a hidden character in Sonic Riders.
Um, there's actually a girl who looks like Ulala in Phantasy Star Universe around Chapter
10.
She's the news reporter for Gerhal Channel 5 News.
And it's her theme song.
I've seen that.
She's in the, she's in the add-ons too.
Um, Ulala and Pudding are playable characters in, uh, Sega Superstars Tennis.
Pudding is like her rival.
Um, Pudding is also one of the best video game characters ever.
Um, there's also, um, Space Channel 5 Part 2 and, um, something actually Rob, do you
like D-Lite?
The group D-Lite?
I, I like the one song that everybody knows by D-Lite.
Quick name two D-Lite songs.
Those grooves in the heart that everyone knows.
And I have like, um, their, uh, one of their, uh, their later albums.
I thought it was really good.
But, um, Lady Miss Keir, who is their, their singer, actually, um, opened a lawsuit against
Sega for, uh, basing Ulala off of her without her permission.
And, uh, Hippolytus is in chat right now and knows quite a bit about, uh, D-Lite.
Apparently they split up years ago and Keir Kirby and DJ Dimitri married.
And, uh, Talate was in that group too and he does remixes for like everybody.
They were confusing.
But, um, anyway, the way that that went is that, um, Sega, um, offered her $16,000 for
licensing and to use their songs.
And she refused and they went ahead and made the game anyway, but she lost the lawsuit
and had to pay, um, Sega's regal worth of, uh, $608,000.
So, um, and actually that was Michael Jackson doing his own voice acting in the game, by
the way.
Because Michael Jackson loves Sega.
Didn't he only say, like, two things in the game, though?
He said, thank you, Ulala, and- Sega made that frickin' Moonwalker game, which was all
kinds of badass.
I know.
He had a whole big- in Space Channel 5 Part 2, there's a whole part of the game that's
doing nothing but buy the Jackson dances.
Yeah, it's pretty rad.
It's freakin' cool.
And I really love Space Channel 5 too, but, um, but this, um, this was, like, the game
for me.
Space Channel 5.
I love this game.
Let's get to the, um, boss music, because it's really awesome.
This is the other big thing, is the great music in the game.
I remember this stage.
Gerardo mode, boops, he says, the first level of my favorite song is the same.
This is my favorite music in the game, because it's all shit, shit, shit.
It gets stuck in your head.
So easily.
That's the crazy thing about this game.
Well, it's better to- it's easier to tell it in the American version, because it's either
chew or shoot, or, uh, or heart or something, no, it's- what is the other thing she said
if it- she says chew and she shoots them, and it's something else when, you know, when,
uh, she saves people.
Hey, I think is what they say.
But anyway, um, Space Channel 5 too, though, had, like, um, my favorite bad guy in any
game ever, though.
And that was the three robots that had the speakers coming out of their head that would
sing, like, to the, uh, barbershop quartet.
I think I remember that.
They were awesome.
But, um, we need- we need more Space Channel 5, we need more Lala.
It'll be awesome.
All right, Space Channel 5 is your classic game of the week, available on the Dreamcast,
um, also- And PlayStation 2.
Repackaged for PlayStation 2, that's right.
So check it out on either of those systems- would you say they're both good, or you need
to actually check it out?
Dreamcast!
Yeah, that's what I figured.
Actually- You always pick Dreamcast games.
Actually, actually, actually, Rob.
What?
I have to say that I do have, um, Space Channel 5 2 on PlayStation 2, and it was really good.
And I have played Space Channel 5 on PlayStation 2, and it was also very good.
It was a very good port.
All right.
Very cool.
All right, I have a request.
Next week, I'm going to challenge you to pick something not Sega.
But- I haven't done Sega- I don't- what was- okay, last week was Sega.
The week before that- oh, the week before that was Sega.
Yeah, exactly.
The week before that.
Go check the wiki.
I'm just giving you a hard time.
Pick whatever the hell you want.
But- but Sega's awesome.
Sega is awesome.
I want to hear something creepy.
What?
And not related to Sega in any way.
Okay.
They're making another Barbie Horse Adventures game.
The fuck?
Okay.
Chat room.
People who update our wiki.
I need someone who has, um, elite skills in Excel or Access to, um, uh, put everything
into a spreadsheet and see what the percentage of games that I have picked that are Sega.
All right.
Thank you.
It's in Excel.
It's freaking easy.
AJ Mix says eight Sega games.
Okay.
Overall.
I guess.
That's not that bad.
All right.
Look, I'm just giving her a hard time.
That's what I do here on the program.
That's what they pay me to do.
But I have to give a hard time back by having no sense of humor.
All right.
Rob?
What?
We're going to take a well-deserved break here on Orange Lounge Radio.
When we come back, more of Orange Lounge Radio, including the taping of part B, will be back
right after this here on Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcasted to the world twice
a week.
Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.