[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_12]: To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: And welcome back to more of Orange Lounge Radio here on All Games Radio where we broadcast live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time immediately following the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_15]: So sometimes it's a couple minutes early, sometimes it's a couple minutes late as it was tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: But that's alright because we have some great shows that we play with here on All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not just Bobby on Sunday nights but a whole sort of assortment of different podcasts and other live shows that air throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_15]: So if you haven't checked it out yet you definitely should.
[SPEAKER_15]: www.allgames.com Meanwhile
[SPEAKER_15]: We've got some other gaming news to get into, and we're going to get into that in just a minute.
[SPEAKER_15]: But we've got to follow up with some of that hilarity from the Part A. Or I guess I shouldn't say hilarity, because somebody is going to get yelled at over all those game news things getting leaked out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, you were doing some poking around on the website.
[SPEAKER_15]: What kind of stuff were you looking at there during the break?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I was just trying to pull up a bunch of... What's the name of these guys again?
[SPEAKER_02]: Intellisponse?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, Intellisponse.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was funny though because there was a section on the NeoGAF forum that someone had highlighted their privacy policy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all the policy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Protecting your privacy and your information is a top priority.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have taken careful measures to secure your information.
[SPEAKER_02]: We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from PC to our servers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our secure server software encrypts information, ensuring that all internet transactions remain private.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's got to be so embarrassing, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's got to be so embarrassing.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's so stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it is secure, and it will prompt for a password and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, if you remove part of the URL on that, it won't.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it's broken.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, somebody's going to get screamed at.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of stuff, and we'll talk about it a little bit more later on.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd be curious to see if this company makes a statement, or if they just try to pretend it didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they're just going to pretend it didn't happen, and let Microsoft and Activision kind of
[SPEAKER_02]: And all the other marketing research companies today are going, Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_15]: New business is going to be coming soon.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's stop kicking sand in these guys' faces and go back to gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's some interesting things coming out this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really know what you'd call this press event, but it was basically the event where Microsoft says, Hey, look at all the Japanese RPGs that are coming our way.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess apparently the game was announced back in 2007 at the Square Enix party.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was funny too because originally it was supposed to be a PS3 exclusive.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no word yet on when it's going to arrive on the PS3 or if it will.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tales of Vesperia Tales of Vesperia
[SPEAKER_15]: Is it coming out of the U.S.
[SPEAKER_15]: at the same time?
[SPEAKER_02]: Around the same time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Around the same time, but we don't have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll also be mid-August.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So far.
[SPEAKER_02]: That wasn't part of this press release.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you know something I don't?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that's coming out mid-August.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember the exact date, but it's coming out mid-August.
[SPEAKER_15]: It still looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a Namco Bandai RPG, which I believe Eternal Sonata was by them as well.
[SPEAKER_15]: That game was kind of one of those games that slipped under some people's radars, but it's great.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a great game.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I'm hoping this game follows in that.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's going to be 37,800 yen for the bundle.
[SPEAKER_15]: because the game is actually going to get its own Xbox 360 bundle over in Japan to try and tap into that market that just won't pick up on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_15]: The Japanese are really resistant to Xbox 360, but trying to use some of these upcoming role-playing games, which all look pretty rad, to try and woo some of the Japanese players over to Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_15]: It hasn't worked so far.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I have a feeling they're all too busy playing Metal Gear Solid 4 to care this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'll buy it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Another game that Squenix published is actually developed by TriAce for Xbox 360 Infinite Undiscovery has ship dates for North America and Europe being 9.2 and 9.5 respectively and proposed in-store dates of September 11th for Japan and Asia You can read about it if you read Japanese on Famitsu
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, this was like my favorite out of all those role-playing games I saw, this Infinite Undiscovery.
[SPEAKER_15]: This was pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_09]: The name is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's really weird that we're getting it before Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's shipping on that day.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's still going to be there the next day.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll still be able to walk into a store and get it before a Japanese listener or person, which is strange, because with role-playing games, I can't think of many times that happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, but that's, I mean, it's not that much.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's only like a week.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I think it's pretty cool they at least obviously developed the games at the same time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the last game, of course, which we've seen a little bit of trailers on, I think during E3, and maybe the Tokyo Game Show, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the last title, of course, The Last Remnant, will be getting an Xbox 360 release.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the one that's using the Unreal 3 engine that I'm...
[SPEAKER_02]: was first announced in 2007.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the game is supposed to be, I guess, supposed to be launching simultaneously on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 in Japan, North America, and Europe, I guess, a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now it looks like they're going to get a simultaneous worldwide launch in all three territories.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's supposed to come sometime this winter.
[SPEAKER_15]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: So coming soon is basically what they've said.
[SPEAKER_15]: The fall.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, I'm actually curious, because I know a lot of our listeners are into these RPG-type games, because we are.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm kind of curious, chat room, out of these games we just talked about, Star Ocean, Tales of Vesperia, Infinite Undiscovery, Last Remnant, is there any that, and kind of including other RPGs we know are in the tailpipe for Xbox 360, such as Blue Dragon 2, I think's been confirmed, as well as the Lost Odyssey sequel.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm kind of curious, those of you guys in chat, are any of these catching your interest?
[SPEAKER_15]: And if so, which one and why?
[SPEAKER_15]: Which one do you think you're more interested in over the others?
[SPEAKER_02]: I already have Infinite Undiscovery on order, same with Tales.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there's also the PS3 Sega one that's coming out that I can't remember the name off the top of my head right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that one I also have on order.
[SPEAKER_15]: chat.orangelongeradio.com if you want to join in on the instant discussion there if you're listening live to us on this Sunday evening as well as five copies of Saints Row 2 for each one of our Xbox 360s nice we'll move you asked a question of us oh I was asking chat but certainly if you have an opinion too please I'm sort of thinking that Infinite Undiscovery but it depends on if I have time
[SPEAKER_15]: Always depends on time.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll go back to that question in just a minute.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let me address this, though, related to Xbox stories.
[SPEAKER_15]: Super Street Fighter 2 Turbo HD Remix, the Xbox Live Arcade game with the longest freaking title ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know it's going into beta, and the beta was purchased through Commando 3, which just went on Xbox Live Arcade this past week.
[SPEAKER_15]: That beta is going to open up on June 25th.
[SPEAKER_15]: That would be next Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_15]: is when this beta is going to go live now remember about the beta though you only basically get Ken Ryu in one stage so it's not really a whole lot to the game but hey at least you do get to take a peek at what this game is going to look like so again that all starts on June 25th
[SPEAKER_15]: Going to the question that I asked earlier, looking in chat at some of the answers here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Joshi16 says, I don't have the time anymore.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want to try Eternal Sonata.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm so behind.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, sometimes I feel like I'm behind on a lot of these games too.
[SPEAKER_15]: Damn wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: GameGuru says, OLR, not really.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe the Blue Dragon games because Blue Dragon is from Team Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_15]: I got to tell you though, the first Blue Dragon game, not what you would have hoped for.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Imagine a Super Nintendo classic RPG on an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's kind of what Blue Dragon was.
[SPEAKER_15]: But unfortunately the story was a little generic as a lot of RPGs tended to be back then.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was really it.
[SPEAKER_15]: We didn't get a whole lot of comments on that in chat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Osfer says he wants to get Eternal Sonata for PS3.
[SPEAKER_15]: I guess they do have the extra stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wish I hadn't looked at this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really wish I hadn't looked at this.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, what's that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not going to spoil it for anybody else.
[SPEAKER_09]: And actually, this really isn't that bad of a spoiler.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm still not going to say anything about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because there is a voice acting casting callout for a second Portal game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not going to say anything about it.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we don't know what it is or why, it's just out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know why, I know what it is now.
[SPEAKER_15]: But it's a spoilery.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't want to spoil it for anybody.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you want to know, you can actually hunt it down on... I hate most gaming blogs around the story this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm not going to ruin it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I gotta say though that the premise sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: From what I read of it, it sounds very interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: You knew it was coming.
[SPEAKER_15]: You knew a Portal 2 had to happen somehow.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I'm glad they will make it work one way or the other.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: was a new map for Halo 3 called Cold Storage.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what Cold Storage is, is actually a remake, or I guess a map that resembles the Chill Out level from the first Halo game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it's kind of interesting, it kind of falls in line with, you know, the other maps that have been released, kind of a lot of remakes, and that...
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess, inspired by previous game maps and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, no word on when this will be coming to us, but probably something like in the fall or summer.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, another map pack.
[SPEAKER_15]: But pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: Although I'm kind of over Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know about the rest of y'all.
[SPEAKER_15]: It didn't have the lasting power that Halo 2 did, sadly.
[SPEAKER_15]: The Maw is a new game that's going to be coming out on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_15]: The first time I look at this and I see this little creature in a little screenshot from The Maw, I think it's something I see out of Spore or something.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, what Maw is, is that is kind of the little mouth creature on a pet blob that is featured in the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can actually use this little creature to eat a house or...
[SPEAKER_15]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_15]: Twisted Pixel is the people behind the game and they promise that they will have a lengthy single player mode, cut scenes that are described as intense and cutting edge graphics for Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_15]: No word on when this will be out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hopefully a little sooner than Castle Crashers.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Meanwhile, let's take a look at what you guys have to say in our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_15]: Every week we open up our mailbag to you guys to send us your emails and your love and adoration or your hate mail.
[SPEAKER_15]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com is the place to send those emails.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura's going to dive in right now, pick a few of her favorites, read them for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: We got a bunch of them, but they're not that long.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: First one comes from...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just going to say James.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there a date on how long Deoxys is available?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm in Germany and my cartridge is in Texas to get the event item for Darkrai.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I may need to ask someone to take the cartridge to GameStop.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't see.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't remember seeing one either.
[SPEAKER_15]: I will try to find the answer.
[SPEAKER_15]: You may have to get a friend over here to get it for you or something somehow.
[SPEAKER_09]: This one comes from our friend in Kenya.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, OR, I've been listening to tonight's show and I'm thrilled you read my email.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait, no, this guy's fake.
[SPEAKER_15]: I proved it.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's on our Facebook community.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not sure how I'm supposed to prove who I am, but I will try and find a way to get a hold of the camera to take a picture of Samara's Cafe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're in the USA from Kenya, and that's from Taiwan.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just want to know, what the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_15]: Just come clean, I caught you.
[SPEAKER_15]: The name in your email is in our Facebook community.
[SPEAKER_15]: You got caught.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now admit it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, next email.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I still want to see the picture.
[SPEAKER_15]: I kind of want to see what you were going to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: This one comes from the guy with the cool email.
[SPEAKER_09]: Saltech.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just wondering if any of you know whether Sony ever plans to let you play PSP games using your PS3 via remote play.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate the PSP's control, but it seems all the games I like are coming out for it, i.e.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kingdom Hearts 3, God of War 3, Final Fantasy 7.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just seems like it would be smart because it would only take an update to do, and I know personally that a few of my friends would pick up both the PS3 and PSP just to do this, and the others, since they already have a PS3, would just buy the PS3.
[SPEAKER_15]: He means Crisis Core.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I meant.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome Show Never Let It Stop, Salt Tech.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, wait, wait, was the question, should he get the PSP, or?
[SPEAKER_09]: If they're ever going to have the remote play.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, remote play on PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought they already had something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he's talking about in the other direction, where you can play PSP games on your PS3.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, um... Maybe someday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: I can understand that, and maybe Sony will do that whole compatibility in reverse thing, but because of the video out, and because Sony doesn't feel that their controller sucks, don't hold your breath.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: GeekBoy
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, OLR crew, I've been looking unsuccessfully for free lessons in programming languages.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've wanted to learn how to learn programming languages for some time now.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I wanted to know if you knew any good websites and which languages I should learn.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks, Geekboy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you can learn to learn anything, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if you want to start off, you know, easy, try something like, you know,
[SPEAKER_09]: Visual Basic, maybe, because you can use that in Word and all kinds of other programs.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: If he ain't writing in ZZT, you ain't shit.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, you need to learn Fortran.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jeez, Pascal.
[SPEAKER_15]: How about Logo?
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: That game will teach you a lot about programming, even though it's like years old.
[SPEAKER_15]: And a lot of these games that are game maker type games, it's a really good place to start.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because programming and all that is a lot about logic and a way of thinking and debugging your stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's why I don't do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not logical.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, look.
[SPEAKER_15]: When I originally went to college, I was studying originally like computer programming.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I started with a C++ class.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hated it.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I decided this is not for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I quit database management because as soon as I went through the VBasic stuff, I was like, I hate this.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's a lot of people in chat yelling C++, Java, C, Basic.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would say, honestly...
[SPEAKER_15]: Who uses basic anymore?
[SPEAKER_15]: But why not?
[SPEAKER_15]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Start with one of these game maker type programs that teach you how to think logically and debug your games.
[SPEAKER_15]: Then you're ready to start with a programming language.
[SPEAKER_15]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_15]: And seriously, check out ZZT, it rocks Xenocore says, turn him to Game Maker 7 Make a game while you learn coding techniques That's exactly the kind of thing I'm thinking is a good starting point Because if you try to just jump in and learn C You're going to be in over your head, buddy Yeah
[SPEAKER_09]: You've got to have the... You always build up to whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: And Alpha Canogram says TI-83 Basic for the win.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hell yeah!
[SPEAKER_09]: I had one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had the Texas Instruments computer that had the little cartridges that you slid on the side.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I had the Basic book.
[SPEAKER_15]: I will write you a Commodore 64 basic program right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: 10 space print space quote Rob is awesome quote enter.
[SPEAKER_15]: 20 space go to 10 enter.
[SPEAKER_15]: Run.
[SPEAKER_15]: Programming lesson here on OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Make sure you've got plenty of printer paper.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, this one comes from Katamari's Forever.
[SPEAKER_09]: First of all, I want to thank you, OLR, for naming Space Channel 5 your classic game of the week last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was beaming with excitement when Jamie said those words.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, thank Sauce for that, because she's the one who told me to do it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you, Sauce.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you, even though you're not listening to us to watch the Tony Awards.
[SPEAKER_09]: She didn't hear that now because she's watching the Tony Awards.
[SPEAKER_09]: Second, I want to give a shout out to an OL Army, Carizzle.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's nice that I found him on another forum, Red Flag Deals.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you get excited when you see a random OL Army around an event?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and by the way, this reminds me, I finally got around to making a character on the Ragnarok server that you have to guess which one I'm playing on, named DarkSakura with the party OL Army, so if you find me, you get a prize.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not going to tell you where I am, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Only a few people know.
[SPEAKER_09]: And third, remember when someone nuked your article from Wikipedia?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was laughing out loud when I found out that under the beautiful Katamari article was none other than you, OLR, when the article referenced the story you posted about the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess you're in places you think you're not in.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, wanted to say I'm playing Space Channel 5 Part 2 now and talk to you later.
[SPEAKER_09]: Katamari's forever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob!
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember that's still a live parody thread?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I finished the song and put it on this email.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please listen.
[SPEAKER_09]: It would be greatly appreciated.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or maybe put in a bonus segment.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about we make that our fortune cookie?
[SPEAKER_15]: Or, better yet, so the podcast listeners can hear it.
[SPEAKER_15]: We will play it at the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't even remember why, what we had to do with that game.
[SPEAKER_15]: I guess we were... Did we announce it earlier or something?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_15]: Guitar Hero 80s Edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about 80s edition?
[SPEAKER_15]: We're linked from the article in Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, for some reason, we're referenced in the article.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't remember why.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think we may have talked about it earlier.
[SPEAKER_15]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here's my question.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did anyone ever try to recreate the Wiki article?
[SPEAKER_00]: They should.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think so, too.
[SPEAKER_15]: Recreate it.
[SPEAKER_15]: The reason why it got nuked is because they said it wasn't sourced or that it didn't prove its relevance or whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, dude, we're coming up on our sixth birthday.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: Guitar Hero Encore Rocks the 80s was initially announced by EGM in January 2007 as Guitar Hero 1980s Edition.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio claimed that the game would be released in June 2007 based on an Activision announcement, though no other source has cited this announcement.
[SPEAKER_09]: Activision officially revealed the first details of the game as May 11, 2007, in addition to changing the game's title to Guitar Hero Rocks the 80s.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it never came out, though, in that time.
[SPEAKER_15]: I remember what it was, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was some type of sales presentation thing that you had.
[SPEAKER_15]: I remember that's what it was.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's why no one else would have had it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember what it was from.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was from Destination PlayStation because it's retailers only.
[SPEAKER_02]: No press.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_09]: This one goes for the World of Warcraft players.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_09]: From Lord Katakos.
[SPEAKER_09]: What server do you guys play WoW on?
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, my 77 priest I mailed you about two months ago was hacked.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I restarted on a private server called Dagon MS, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm now level 168.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait, you can't be that high in WoW.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you sure this is about WoW or is this RagnarKrak?
[SPEAKER_15]: Horde side, Horde has cookies
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I looked up Dagon MS and it's a freaking MapleStory.
[SPEAKER_15]: MapleStory?
[SPEAKER_15]: Get out of here!
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jamie doesn't play MapleStory.
[SPEAKER_09]: The end.
[SPEAKER_09]: Help me don't play that.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, by the way, the...
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: if anyone wants to find out and it's only going to be a casual guild I'm not going to let anyone else invite anyone unless I trust them but find me on what is that chat thing we use?
[SPEAKER_09]: IRC and I might tell you
[SPEAKER_15]: I want to point out too, because this is in the JustinTV chat, going back to the kid who was asking about the programming languages, wanting to know more about where to start with that.
[SPEAKER_15]: AkumaJP, who works for game companies in Japan, suggests download the iPhone SDK.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: Start from there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not see, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: I didn't even think about that.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's that whole new development kit that iPhone's got.
[SPEAKER_01]: That'd be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good suggestion.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's actually officially supported now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey OLR, Amplitude here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm listening to Part B of this week's show at work, and the whole tangent on how awesome arcades used to be really got me to start thinking.
[SPEAKER_09]: We, or at least those of us from that era, certainly can name some arcades that are on the decline and what happened, but reminiscing will only get us so far.
[SPEAKER_09]: I feel like we never quite found an explanation for this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can we point fingers at corporate America and say that things were bought out and consequently ambushed?
[SPEAKER_09]: But is anyone else looking at it from a different perspective?
[SPEAKER_09]: What about the kids that go to the arcades or lack thereof?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nowadays, if you were spotted at a local arcade, you're pegged as a gamer and all the stereotypes are realized and you begin to accumulate what can only be described as loser points.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry for the long email slash rant amplitude.
[SPEAKER_09]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: This email brought to you by Subject Hometown here, home of the test subject here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I see what you did there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good thought.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't think we ever did get down to the bottom of what happened to arcades.
[SPEAKER_15]: There was money to be made in birthday parties.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe we should do our first investigative story.
[SPEAKER_15]: An OLR, investigative report.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: We should.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie, you head that up because I wouldn't even know where to begin.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jamie goes to college and works full time.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rob works full time and Rob has other things going on too.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't you work full time and is very busy with other things.
[SPEAKER_01]: Junami, get on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a shiny dollar in it for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a Susan B with your name on it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I do want to, one part of the email said people don't go because they're afraid of being a nerd.
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, that can't be true.
[SPEAKER_15]: People are dorks because they go to arcades?
[SPEAKER_15]: by some guy who doesn't know you
[SPEAKER_15]: I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just being a bitch.
[SPEAKER_15]: But seriously, you know, it's like, I don't... The hell with what they think!
[SPEAKER_15]: So what if they think you're a geek?
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, Cheeseburger points out for programming languages, PHP, Python, C++, Java, Ruby, Perl, and if you learn HTML, it will be easier.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: HTML is freaking easy.
[SPEAKER_09]: So... We're almost done.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello OLR, it is Janai from Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_09]: As of typing this email, I have returned from the Video Game Live concert in Henderson, Nevada.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is a must-see event.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wore my Professor Layton costume and gave people gold coins that noticed who I was dressed as.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was backstage for the costume contest and even though I didn't win, I got to see Martin Leung, the famous piano player who played the Super Mario theme blindfolded on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_09]: I quickly said, I love your YouTube videos and he replied with a cool thank you and that made my day.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome lighting, great music selection, both new and classic games, and Tommy Tallarico kept changing his clothes, which was strange.
[SPEAKER_09]: I give this show a solid 100% rating.
[SPEAKER_09]: If it's coming to your town or close by, you must see it, and yes, they have international dates this year.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I'm really glad you read that email.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because it gives me a chance to say we have a guest coming on the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not next week, but the week after.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's going to be on the show on the 29th.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sunday the 29th.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tommy Tallarico is going to be on Orange Lounge Radio to talk about video games live.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I will ask him for you about why the wardrobe changed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, yeah, and we're going to be asking you about the world tour and what people can expect this year and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then all expenses paid tickets to see it overseas.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't push it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But no, Tommy Tallarico will be here in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last one!
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, by the way, just to answer the questions in chat, Tommy will not actually be here in studio because he has this whole Video Games Live thing going on he's also trying to do.
[SPEAKER_15]: But he will take a little time to... We're going to have a seance and channel in.
[SPEAKER_15]: Plug it on our show!
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Last one comes from our very good friend Vandalus.
[SPEAKER_09]: We miss you!
[SPEAKER_15]: Happy Father's Day, Vandalist.
[SPEAKER_09]: Happy Father's Day to you.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's got a small army.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have lost count of how many children Vandalist has.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think five.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's at least five.
[SPEAKER_09]: Happy Father's Day.
[SPEAKER_09]: You've earned it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, you have.
[SPEAKER_09]: Quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Several times over.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we miss you.
[SPEAKER_09]: We really miss you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Come back and visit us soon.
[SPEAKER_15]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey gang, it's Terry slash Vandalist.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope you're all doing well.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wanted to pass on a news story I just blogged about in my weekend news job at www.hardocp.com
[SPEAKER_09]: it's about the US Army's new recruitment tactic Interactive Centers and he sent me a link to it but he continues with full size mockups Apache helicopter simulations look like America's Army was just the beginning and tells us to take care and actually what it is is they're having recruitment centers set up with simulators for full scale mockups of equipment and a gaming arena that uses America's Army and
[SPEAKER_09]: so that instead of doing the whole, having a commercial to show what you might happen, they actually have something that, in fact, it was even quoted from Major Larry Dillard, who's a U.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: Army marketing executive.
[SPEAKER_09]: He said, the modeling command and control systems are like those used in Iraq.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like we said earlier, there's an Apache simulator for pilot and co-pilot that uses the flight and weapon system, a Black Hawk helicopter that has four door gunner positions and an armored Humvee vehicle simulator.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I kind of want to do that myself.
[SPEAKER_15]: Humvee simulator?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, with turrets and that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just makes me think of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: What was that movie?
[SPEAKER_15]: The Army is innovative.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're very innovative at this stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: They do their job well.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's all I can really say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Smart folks there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're using that wonderful America's Army.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, whatever happened to America's Army 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game sucked.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think it's still going.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's got a cult following to it.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: That it for Mailbag?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_15]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's get back to some news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is kind of funny, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, there is a game someone noticed that's reusing Oblivion's graphics.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the game itself is called Limbo of the Lost, which just sounds weird anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it is blatantly ripping off Elder Scrolls Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, they had a screenshot...
[SPEAKER_02]: Comparison, and... Yeah, it's near identical, except for maybe the fire effects are shittier than the other game.
[SPEAKER_02]: No word...
[SPEAKER_02]: No word on what else they may have stolen.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says apparently also... Oh, there are some updates to the story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently also they stole an environment from Thief Deadly Shadows as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently Joystick just heard back from the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: publisher TriSynergy who told them that the similarities between the two are striking...
[SPEAKER_02]: But we were just as shocked as anybody else and we put the line into Majestic.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had no idea that any of this had been happening in the game and things would have been different if we had known.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait, Bethesda is making this game themselves?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, Majestic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Majestic is the company making the game and it's being published by some company called TriSynergy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, Majestic actually made a phone call to Bethesda and this is what they had to say.
[SPEAKER_12]: Except in this case, they actually can't do it that much better.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, they can't.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, uh...
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of funny though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wonder what else they're going to... It says they also think that the game stole some artwork from Diablo 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: A shield called the Wall of Eyeless or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're stealing from everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: Azaku says bullshit who the fuck was producing that game and greenlighted the copyrighted textures without consulting a lawyer
[SPEAKER_15]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is it bullshit?
[SPEAKER_15]: Or is it the real deal?
[SPEAKER_15]: Only time will tell.
[SPEAKER_15]: Meanwhile, let's go back to some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_15]: In the law world, two guys are suing EA.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_15]: And they're saying that because of the NFL license, EA is engaging in, quote, blatantly anti-competitive conduct, and they are seeking, quote, restitution and damages for those who purchased an EA football game since August of 2005, disgorgement of all profits made as a result of anti-competitive actions, and that the infringing agreements be declared null and void.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Not EA, as much as I hate to say that.
[SPEAKER_15]: And for those of you that don't understand legal translation so much, we actually had somebody try to simplify this lawsuit for us, and they translated it for us.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wah, wah, wah, wah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wah, wah, wah, wah, wah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bitch, bitch, bitch.
[SPEAKER_15]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's what this lawsuit's all about.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyhow, stories like this, I don't know about you guys, but whenever I hear about all these type of frivolous lawsuit type things, I get a little bit angsty.
[SPEAKER_15]: and Mad.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that always necessitates some FUs.
[SPEAKER_09]: To myself, I left my laptop at home and had to go back and get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hence my late arrival.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Loki FD is the guy in front of me at Burger King because apparently he didn't know what he wanted to order and then he proceeded to order like half the menu because I was waiting behind him for like 10 minutes while he proceeded to wait for his food to be delivered to his car in about 5 to 6 bags Nice Yes, I love people Oh, and he was smoking right there in front of the window too Nice Which is awesome, he's a winner
[SPEAKER_15]: My FU of the week goes to the root canal I had on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Root canals are not fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: An FU to the fact that I think there's a problem with it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to have to see the dentist next week.
[SPEAKER_15]: FU to dentistry.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's my FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's get back to gaming news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do we gotta?
[SPEAKER_15]: We gotta.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Penny Arcade.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope, I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, did you get ahead of yourself?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I did.
[SPEAKER_15]: Penny Arcade, coming up soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Later in the program.
[SPEAKER_09]: Squeenix!
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: There actually is a trailer up for the new MMO, Concerto Gate, and it's going to be a free MMO RPG, and it's pretty.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's actually the sequel to Crossgate, which was an MMO that was in Japan since 2001.
[SPEAKER_09]: and it's just very cute.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I want to give it a try.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hooray for free and hooray for cute, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: As long as it's not MapleStory.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why all the hate for MapleStory?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've never even played MapleStory.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't look fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, spoiled Ragnarok online.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ragnarok has withstood the test of time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure has.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: One thing Ragnarok does not have that Dungeon Runners does have is a bling gnome.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, a bling gnome.
[SPEAKER_02]: What per se is a bling gnome, you may ask?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm about to tell you.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a gnome with bling?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, sort of.
[SPEAKER_02]: A bling gnome is a pet of sorts that runs around and picks up all gold dropped from bad guys while you also kill other things.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the gnome also will pick up dropped items that aren't rare and eat them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then he poops out gold as a reward.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the best thing ever!
[SPEAKER_08]: I want a gnome that poops gold!
[SPEAKER_02]: and they have screenshots to back it up yes, the bling gnome who either has loot or woot tattooed to his stomach I don't know but it's kind of funny and for those who may not be familiar with Dungeon Runner it is a free MMO where can you check this game out if you want to see this amazing pooping gnome?
[SPEAKER_15]: DungeonRunners.com oh well, I should have been able to figure that one out, huh?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh my god, this is the best thing ever!
[SPEAKER_00]: And he does have woot on him.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's loot.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I thought it was a woot.
[SPEAKER_02]: It could be a little of both.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe woot on the front and loot on the back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's poot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because he poops out, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: SIV4 Colonization
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, here it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: How's that for your tremendous long wait?
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Penny Arcade game is now available on Steam.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's called Penny Arcade Adventures on the Rainslick Precipice of Darkness.
[SPEAKER_09]: Episode 1 is there at www.
[SPEAKER_09]: SteamGames.com and it will also be offering the future episodes there.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there are achievements available for Steam purchasers.
[SPEAKER_09]: So go check it out.
[SPEAKER_15]: And by the way, the game is very funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's our first review.
[SPEAKER_09]: You heard it here.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you haven't heard.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now you have.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: And knowing is half the battle.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate you too.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Neverwinter Nights 2 is getting yet another expansion.
[SPEAKER_02]: The new expansion is being called Storm of Zeher, and it's going to be the second expansion for the game that came out in 2006.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will add a single-player campaign with approximately 15 hours of gameplay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will add new classes, spells, creatures, and a new playable race system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, there is a new Overland map that is being introduced that will allow players to explore the Chultun Peninsula, Sword Coast, and Samarit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And looks like they also have got... Looks like that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's due out, I guess, the fourth quarter of this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, something around Christmas, perhaps.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_15]: One last story tonight, and then we're going to open up the Skype line, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_15]: Click on Interact With Us to see all the different ways you can give us a call.
[SPEAKER_15]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio, or our free 800 number for US and Canada, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_15]: But first, one more story for you guys, and it's a little bit of a retro, some retro goodness.
[SPEAKER_15]: Quick, how do you get 30 lives in Contra?
[SPEAKER_15]: Up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A, start.
[SPEAKER_15]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_15]: Everybody knows the famous Konami code, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, how do you get all of the power-ups in Gradius?
[SPEAKER_15]: You pause the game and then up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A, start.
[SPEAKER_10]: How do you do it in Proteus?
[SPEAKER_15]: Up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A, start.
[SPEAKER_11]: Backwards.
[SPEAKER_15]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: So everybody knows that freaking Konami code.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, what's funny is that you can actually use this code in Google Reader.
[SPEAKER_15]: Seriously, this code works in Google Reader, presented from Google.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you put up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A on your keyboard, and you don't have to hit start because there is no start key on your keyboard, all of your unread items will be reset to 30, and a little ninja will come on the screen to watch you surf RSS feeds.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you might be asking, why?
[SPEAKER_15]: And to that I say, why the hell not?
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: So you think this game is going to come out for Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_03]: So somebody like me who's thinking of taking the plunge to get PlayStation 3 soon to play a game like this ought to just wait?
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_15]: One of the reasons why I think is because of the amount of if they don't pull the certain amount of system that they need that they're going to have to come over.
[SPEAKER_15]: Notice Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_03]: and notice Assassin's Creed that was supposed to be originally for only exclusive Xbox 360 how it goes on the other system.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I just think that maybe they just kept everybody quiet and hopefully it's going to come over to Xbox 360 in order for them to make money.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you see that little thing that was making the rounds around the internet this week about kind of the joke that's inside Metal Gear about having to change discs?
[SPEAKER_15]: And then the guy says, oh wait, no, you don't have to change discs because you're playing a Blu-ray game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you see that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I haven't seen that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I try my best to ignore all my friends that actually bought into the hype.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just really understand because you know how Microsoft is moving over to Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_03]: I understand that part.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it doesn't necessarily need to be on a Blu-ray disc for it to work as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why I'm thinking that it's...
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a good chance it could... They could always revamp it and change it, you know, for it to work with 360.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, but even if Microsoft came out with a Blu-ray player, which, you know, that rumor... We brought that rumor up on last week's show and then Monday came, no announcement.
[SPEAKER_15]: But let's say Microsoft did come out with a Blu-ray player, although at this point I don't think they will until their next system.
[SPEAKER_15]: But let's say they did.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's say they came out with a Blu-ray player.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't think they're going to start putting out games on that player because they're going to want to tap into their existing user base.
[SPEAKER_15]: They don't want to suddenly say games can only be on this... You know, I...
[SPEAKER_15]: I just don't think there'd be enough market for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that the user base is bigger on Xbox 360, and I think they'd rather tap into that user base.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they could be more influenced by Konami, because the game isn't necessarily, it's not like Sony owns Konami in any way.
[SPEAKER_15]: Right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, you know, I would love to see the Xbox 360 port happen as well, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sometimes, for whatever reason, they like to keep these things system exclusive for whatever backdoor deals happen.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Konami will keep denying it, but E3 would be a good time for them to announce it if they wanted to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you're right, and that didn't come up yet as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks a lot.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll be crossing my fingers for you on the Xbox 360 Metal Gear.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Part of me says not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think they've denied it so many times.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think if they were to come out and release on 360 now, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: They'd have to have a lot of extras or something to kind of justify it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Oscar.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, Oscar.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just happy that I managed to get my hands on the Metal Gear Solid 4 Limited Edition this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ah, what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't even reserve the game either.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't even reserve the game either, and I found it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think they did a pretty good job.
[SPEAKER_15]: They knew the demand was going to be pretty high for this, so they made a lot of copies of it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_15]: Surely you've opened it up by now.
[SPEAKER_15]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I've only had time to play about three hours of it so far, and it's pretty great.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like really epic.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like the only word you can describe it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think that's kind of the consensus around here at OLR Studios this evening.
[SPEAKER_15]: The game is epic.
[SPEAKER_15]: What makes it so epic?
[SPEAKER_15]: Is it just the cutscenes epic?
[SPEAKER_15]: What is it that makes the game so epic?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I remember back when Hideo Kojima, he was all talking about how the PS3 was the only system he wanted to be in because he wanted it to be like a movie, basically.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it kind of plays like a movie to me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here's my question because you have, you know, the cutscenes and we've heard a lot about the cutscenes and how they're very long and how they're very epic.
[SPEAKER_15]: How about the game itself?
[SPEAKER_15]: The actual game that you are playing?
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, is the game cool?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what's it considered?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it like a... What kind of game is it even considered?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it like a strategy shooter or something like that?
[SPEAKER_15]: A stealth action strategy game.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, usually the games are kind of like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All I can think of is Rainbow Six maybe, but I got bored with Rainbow Six.
[SPEAKER_04]: This, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm very into it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is it because the story really draws you in in a way that maybe Rainbow Six doesn't really have quite the same epic cutscenes?
[SPEAKER_04]: That has to be it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rainbow Six, the story was...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, board me.
[SPEAKER_15]: As I was saying earlier in the show, Kojima's always been a bit of a storyteller, even in the NES days.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, the very, very first Metal Gear game that was on the NES, or really MSX, if you want to go that far back, kind of had depth and story that not a lot of games of that time had.
[SPEAKER_15]: Queltipo in chat says it's tactical espionage action.
[SPEAKER_15]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_15]: It even says it right there on the box.
[SPEAKER_15]: That would be the genre the game fits into.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that's what I thought it was.
[SPEAKER_15]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: and there's no guard humping in this one I got Mario Kart Wii and I challenge you alright, we'll make it happen we'll have to set up a time I'll try to set up something in the forums this week because Bobby Blackwolf wants to have a go at it too so I'll try to set something up when we're both available alright we'll let you know alright, later buddy alright, see ya see ya
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, if you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR, or use the name on Skype, Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_15]: This is Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, Spazinator, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I just want to kind of comment on like two or three things, if I may.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's for your little rant about Nintendo earlier in Part A. Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boy's next.
[SPEAKER_05]: Only thing I'm going to say is right on.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, I've been more or less boycotting them for the past 10 or 11 years.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I can't speak for everyone out there, but personally, I feel that Nintendo really hasn't been pointing out anything for their systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've really been overly compelling, aside from maybe one or two titles for the past couple systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: and, uh, you know, you know, of course, you know, Super, or Smash Brothers, Brawl, and whatnot, notwithstanding, but, you know, the last really truly system they really had was the Super Nintendo, uh, but, you know, you know, granted, yeah, the N64 did have a, you know, a few good games out there, you know, like GoldenEye and whatnot, but,
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, aside from that, ever since then, they've been going, like, downhill ever since then.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I've cooled off a little bit since I got very hot-headed during Part A. And, you know, I'm a little regretful that the actions of this guy at Nintendo of Europe kind of hurts the company's image as a whole.
[SPEAKER_15]: Right on down, you know, from people, the president, you know, from Reggie Visamay,
[SPEAKER_15]: All the way down to the little people that work at Nintendo, you know, that probably don't deserve a boycott or what have you.
[SPEAKER_15]: But damn it, something has got to give, and we have got to show that this guy is made of suck for making this statement and needs to...
[SPEAKER_15]: Something beyond just a little apology needs to happen.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because here's the thing, and the reason why I said it's part of my boycott, that if Nintendo addresses it, I would be okay with it, and I would end my boycott, is because if Nintendo were to address it, it would invalidate everything this guy said about it being for Geeks and Otaku, and this guy would look like a moron.
[SPEAKER_15]: So that's part of the reason why I said that, you know, I will forgive and forget if Nintendo will say, look, we are going to do something about it, and it's not just for Geeks New Taku.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, well, you know, that guy's comments kind of factors into, like, you know, my opinion that, you know, over the past few years, you know, Nintendo has been
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess it could be termed as an over-inflated ego.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've been kind of like, I don't know if you want to call it Russ and the Laurels or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's definitely prevalent on all sides of Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hold up, since Super Nintendo, after Super Nintendo, Nintendo did not exactly enjoy world success with the Nintendo 64 and the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_15]: Granted, those systems weren't failure per se, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: They still think they're fucking cocky.
[SPEAKER_02]: We see it on the retail side.
[SPEAKER_02]: We see it also on the consumer side.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, it's just their mentality.
[SPEAKER_02]: They control their market with the releasing of their systems and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty sure that there's some sort of shortage going around that's intentional.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, but at the same time, they're doing this stuff with suing third-party peripheral manufacturers.
[SPEAKER_02]: This stuff, they have a schedule of how they're going to release this stuff, and they're going to slowly roll out stuff to keep people interested.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like Wii Fit and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Wii console, people finally have it now, and they're just like...
[SPEAKER_02]: How can we get people interested in this console again like they were at launch?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's release Wii Fit now and make that fucking hard to find.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now it's all coming around again.
[SPEAKER_02]: And watch when Wii Sports 2 comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go again.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just going to be a constant cycle and they're going to slowly roll out stuff that they should have rolled out at launch throughout the lifetime of this console.
[SPEAKER_15]: Somebody needs to tell Nintendo I made you and I can break you just as easily.
[SPEAKER_02]: So much to tell Nintendo that people are going to stop waiting for stuff to happen and they're going to move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they may buy your console, but they're not going to buy any of your games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or buy your virtual console stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, sure, they've made a little bit of money off of people from buying the console.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't imagine that they're making a ton of money on each console sales, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: If people are just staying there and playing Wii Sports and then say, forget it, this online stuff, it's not happening and I can't find space to save my games and stuff and have to re-download them later, people are just going to get confused and get overwhelmed by it and they're just going to say, forget it, I'm not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it sucks because the people that are actually supporting them and utilizing this stuff, they're just saying, you're not important.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah, yeah, don't get me wrong, you know, at least way back in the day, I used to be a really big Nintendo fanboy and whatnot, but now once I started realizing that, you know, starting with N64, you know, relatively few games were coming out that I was particularly interested in, I kind of started, you know, slowly but surely moving over to the Sony camp, and I've been with Sony now for, you know, ever since, like, roughly when Final Fantasy VII came out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here's the thing, and in reference to what I said and stuff, is that I'm a Nintendo fanboy too, and this is what stinks about the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've been so supportive of the Nintendo Wii, and I've spent a lot of money on those virtual console downloads to have this happen.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: I kind of felt the same way going years back.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that's because they...
[SPEAKER_05]: make comments, you know, because they weren't really keeping up with the times and they weren't, you know, their gains weren't really going up with the people that have been supporting them since way back when, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, you know, the people that grew up with the original NES or SNES, eventually their tastes and gains were going to change and
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, hey, hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Ranma, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, a lot of things.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_15]: First thing I'm going to ask.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're coming out here in like two weeks, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you said something about you're going to fix our Justin TV cam when you're here?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to do my best.
[SPEAKER_14]: I am very technically inclined.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki thinks he can do it too.
[SPEAKER_15]: So between the two of you all, I think we're going to have a high-tech studio by the time the 4th of July rolls around.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, believe you me.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can talk about whatever you want to now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: Cool, cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: A couple of things.
[SPEAKER_14]: As for the guy from Nintendo of Europe by this comment, am I the only one that doesn't give two shits about what the hell he said?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_15]: Look, I get called a geek.
[SPEAKER_15]: I say thanks.
[SPEAKER_15]: Being a geek is not a bad thing, but it's the fact that he was  and I think Jamie kind of referenced this.
[SPEAKER_15]: He was using these things as a derogatory thing, so he's basically saying
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, we're not going to put something out because we don't really care about the people who want this.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it's kind of like, well, F you because if I've spent $100 on all these different virtual console games I filled up and I was planning on spending even more, then if I'm just poo-poo to you, then forget it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not going to spend any more money.
[SPEAKER_02]: He does a valid point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the proper thing to say would have been Nintendo understands that this is
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely a problem, and we are addressing it, and we are working towards fixing said problem.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or just say, he could have just said, unfortunately, at this time, Nintendo has no fix for this.
[SPEAKER_15]: He could have given the same BS, you know, the same line we've heard from Nintendo time and time again.
[SPEAKER_15]: Unfortunately, at this time, folks will have to delete the game, and they can always re-download it for free.
[SPEAKER_15]: He could have given that same line, and I wouldn't have cared.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would have still thought, Nintendo probably needs to address their storage issue at some point, but I wouldn't have cared.
[SPEAKER_15]: But the fact that he...
[SPEAKER_15]: That's what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_15]: Right, and GameGuru says, and Iwata actually did say that, Rob, and I have nothing but nice things to say about Iwata.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have nothing but, I am a Nintendo fanboy.
[SPEAKER_15]: The man's done a lot.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I'm fine with that line, because I understand they're dancing around the fact that their system has limitations, and that's the PC thing to say.
[SPEAKER_15]: But for this guy to come out with guns a-blazin' is like, whoa, whoa, whoa, buddy.
[SPEAKER_15]: You wanna pick a fight?
[SPEAKER_14]: Sounds like the guy was PMSing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: No more Nintendo Talk.
[SPEAKER_15]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm done with it.
[SPEAKER_15]: So what else is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_14]: I remember growing up that arcades were the shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: I remember growing up, my aunt would take me to this place called Nathan's.
[SPEAKER_14]: You go inside.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was like heaven.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was like 50, 60 different kinds of arcades you could play.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's why I first got my hands on Final Fight and fell in love with Capcom right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_14]: and nowadays it's like you go into like a little rinky-dink sports center where they have hockey, ice skating.
[SPEAKER_14]: You go upstairs, there's a concession stand.
[SPEAKER_14]: You go around the corner, there's three arcade machines and a bootleg Cusar.
[SPEAKER_15]: The place I remember was a little place called Nickel Mania where you would pay $2.50 to get in and then all the games ran on nickels.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's like the first place I ever played Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sadly, it's no more.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: When you make your visit out here, we're going to have to take you to Roseville Golf Land because that's really one of the last actual arcades.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm glad you didn't throw in good in there.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's what we got.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think that's a good way to phrase it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dan went to Scandia and he said that it's just completely meh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Scandia is just confused on what it's trying to be anyways.
[SPEAKER_09]: We might have to take a trip to Milpitas Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because that one's still fairly decent.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, Milpitas and Sunnyvale are still okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sunnyvale also has the test machines though.
[SPEAKER_15]: But slowly that stuff's been going out and Flamin' Fingers has been coming in.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not that Flamin' Fingers is a bad thing, but too much of it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: What about the jump rope game?
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to have to also go to John's Incredibly Mediocre Pizza.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, we do need to go to John's Incredibly Shitty Pizza.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you still haven't sent me a certain email, sir.
[SPEAKER_15]: No problem, I'll resend it out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, Ranma, quickly, anything else before we end the show?
[SPEAKER_14]: Uh, no, that's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_14]: You too.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rob D says, too much of the flaming finger is a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let me clarify my statement.
[SPEAKER_08]: Too much of the flaming finger requires soothing action.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's nothing wrong with a little flaming finger here and there.
[SPEAKER_15]: You don't want to OD on flaming finger.
[SPEAKER_15]: You need to mix it up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, forget it.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's going to do it for phone calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you guys for calling in.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you didn't get through, so sorry, but send us an email or try again next week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or you can always leave a voicemail.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've got voicemails we've got to play.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll try to catch up on those in a future week.
[SPEAKER_15]: For now, we've got to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: where it pays off to select different characters depending on the enemies you face or unique game environments you are in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Earn upgrades for each character you use.
[SPEAKER_02]: Experience unique combos specific to two... Are they just reusing the Marvel Ultimate Alliance engine like over and over and over again?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or I should say X-Men Legends engine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see what else here.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got...
[SPEAKER_02]: Some more stuff coming from this big leak list here, including... Oh, we already talked about all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have the Mensa workout.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess this is going to be another brain training game for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know how extreme Makeover Home Edition is going to be any fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, there was a game I had on the Commodore 64 called like Dream House or something like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: And pretty much all you did is you went through the house and you could paint all the, like you could paint the ceiling and the walls a different color, one of 16 colors.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cause you know, Commodore 64 was cutting edge and then you could put furniture in the house too.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, but you were only limited to like eight pieces of furniture in a room.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cause you know, there's all those limitations on the 64.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope to God that half these games are fake.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or not really fake, but just concepts that are never going to come to pass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if that's the case, there's going to be like 20 Spider-Man games coming out between now and probably a couple years from now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Including Spider-Man Agile Warrior, where it lets players control Spider-Man with the Wii balance board.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's Spider-Man Hero Evolved for the Xbox 360, PS3, and Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Replay as the son of Spider-Man in 2064 using spider powers and future tech to battle villains.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's Spider-Man New Heights for the 360 PS3 and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Upgrades Spidey's abilities as he moves from battling low-level gangs to famous foes in the New York skyline.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spider-Man Gangs of New York.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gangs take over the whole city and Spider-Man must pit them against each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spider-Man Adaption Spidey travels all over the globe from Tokyo to Paris to Moscow to take out foes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Marvel Team-Up Spider-Man meets X-Men.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that was the one I was talking about earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spider-Man Contest of Champions 360, PS3, and Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Destructible Fighter for 2-4 players with Spider-Man, Venom, Wolverine, Electro...
[SPEAKER_02]: Electro, Doc Ock, Carnage, and the Green Goblin.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spider-Man Mass Evolution for all three systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spidey skills from strength to speed to spidey sense are upgradable as you play.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spider-Man Chaos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spidey has 8 hours of frenetic action to save from certain doom Spider-Man Tactics, a stealthy and strategic Spidey game Spider-Man Vision, first and third person gameplay Spidey style Spider-Man vs. Marvel Zombies Spider-Man Webmaster
[SPEAKER_02]: for the Wii, a web shooting game for a third person action, Spider-Man Web Slinger, use precision web aiming to target enemies building or build web slingshots and snipe enemies.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think some of those are all ideas, but aren't going to come out, because that would be way too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: The avatars, one of the things that people noticed, there were some licensed things with them as well, so maybe some licensed clothing and stuff, you'll be able to get it, because they had one of them with an Incredibles t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Ultimate Band.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to be doing an Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 version, apparently, of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it will be, to I'm sure Rob's enjoyment, compatible with Rock Band instruments.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the Wii U version, of course, does not have instruments at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's actually got a video out there for it, too, on how you play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then there was also one of the things was the SBGs, which is server-based gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently it's going to be like a social networking blade or something like that that allow you to play games from game shows like Jeopardy, Who Wants to Be a Millionaire, and other things like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And finally, Powers and Titans, which is a multiplayer superhero game that's apparently going to be something that Joss Whedon is going to be a part of.
Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I don't know what exactly that is, but probably some sort of superhero game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I'm mad at him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_10]: For the end of Astonishing X-Men.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'll get over it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh no, you don't, that, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: And finally, in unrelated news, you may remember the Wii Fit girl who's been kind of floating around.
[SPEAKER_02]: She had the YouTube video where she shook her ass while playing Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Playboy's Joe Garcia has put out her own videos that are a little bit more seductive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also her playing Wii Fit as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trying to cash in on that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_15]: Boy, you know we've moved into a new generation where people are trying to cash in on other people's YouTube videos.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Absolutely amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so... Alright, awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki will review those videos next week on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if there's... Well, it didn't look that interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It didn't look that interesting?
[SPEAKER_02]: She doesn't get naked, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, this is a Playboy little pictorial thing that she does not get naked.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do not approve of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do approve of people taking it to the next step.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: To which I say, Wii Fit Girl, your rebuttal?
[SPEAKER_15]: If that's going to do it for our last minute stories tonight, I guess we're going to go ahead and wrap up the show and bring another week of Orange Lounge Radio to a close.
[SPEAKER_15]: Next week on Orange Lounge Radio, our sixth anniversary show, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But nothing too special going on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Same old shit we always do.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hopefully some guests.
[SPEAKER_11]: No one's made any suggestions.
[SPEAKER_15]: Miglitov will be here next week.
[SPEAKER_11]: I should get my husband here.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we'll at least have him.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was trying, by the way, I was trying to get one story we didn't get to tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know if you read this.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you read on the gaming blogs this week about that lady who's running for state senate in Connecticut?
[SPEAKER_15]: And how it's like this big deal like, oh, politicians are getting into games because she has a level 70 in World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you see that story?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know if you thought of this, but the minute I read that, I'm like, what's the big freaking deal?
[SPEAKER_15]: My boyfriend ran for state senate in 2006, and he has two level 70s in Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was actually trying to get him to come to the show tonight, but he didn't want to.
[SPEAKER_15]: He didn't know what he'd say.
[SPEAKER_15]: He was like, what would I talk about if I went on your show?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm like, you play more World of Warcraft than I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd fit in fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whenever you see a story like that, you just have to think of Austin Powers and Dr. Evil.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm hip.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I'm just saying, you know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Politicians come in all different flavors, just like regular people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why does it matter what your job is and what you like to do in your spare time?
[SPEAKER_15]: For real.
[SPEAKER_09]: For real.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who the hell cares?
[SPEAKER_09]: And what relevance does your gaming life have on your political views?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, hold on.
[SPEAKER_15]: To be fair.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: But I just don't see what, you know, what you like to do as a hobby.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unless, you know, you like to, you know, skin kittens in your backyard or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: As a hobby.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, but you play video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's the problem?
[SPEAKER_09]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, it's like, you know, I don't care what people's bedroom habits are.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't care what their gaming habits are.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, as long as they're not hurting anybody, what does it matter, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: and people piss me off.
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, speaking of not caring about what goes on behind closed doors, I do want to say, though, a very happy day tomorrow, Monday, June 15th and going on into June 16th to all the new couples who will be getting married in California who finally, finally have equality.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's so amazing.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm so happy to live in a state where that's going to be happening.
[SPEAKER_15]: Until they overrule it again.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Not if I have anything to say about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, did you hear from Amanda about... Um, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a chapel open up now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did that actually happen?
[SPEAKER_09]: I saw the website.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know the friend was talking about opening one in the Castro.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did that actually happen?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll have to get a link from her.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow, that's great if that actually happened, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I honestly think that, you know, eventually, and I think that more and more people are realizing this, that what does it matter?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, and personally, and I've had this discussion with other people before, I actually think that marriage should not be a government thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Institution, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, thankfully, and boy, we got off the topic of video games.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a topic that's important to me, so you know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Deal.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thankfully, the youth of America does not have their head up their ass in this regard.
[SPEAKER_11]: For the majority?
[SPEAKER_15]: In this regard, yeah, the majority.
[SPEAKER_15]: I still know people who have their head up their ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, there's always going to be somebody with their head up their ass, but it makes me very hopeful for the future.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Very hopeful for the future.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, I was going to say one thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, I missed one last thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is actually coming from our friends over at Bawani Style.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently there was an MTV pack or an advertisement for Rock Band that they were showing a bunch of songs kind of scrolling through the song list and lo and behold, there's a bunch of songs that haven't come out yet in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, four songs that they spotted on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Aesthetics of Hate by Machine Head.
[SPEAKER_02]: uh afterlife by avenge sevenfold which i believe is coming out this next week um breed by nirvana and burn by nine inch nails sweet sounds like fun and i i was gonna say uh i think there's a couple other stories that they had too there was something about like uh new ddr or something like that um also some um
[SPEAKER_02]: Beatin' Groovy
[SPEAKER_02]: is what it's called.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an E-rated Konami-published title.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says, from the sound of it, it sounds like Konami's rhythm game, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was found on Australia's ratings board webpage.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is also another Xbox 360 title, Domino Master, which is supposed to be coming to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wonder if that's Mr. Domino, because that'd be funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, now that we've had the last, last, last minute stories, let's go ahead and wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: We got all the final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_15]: We got the last, last minute story.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you know, Ultimate Band has Miley Cyrus in it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because it's a Disney title.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god, so I was right.
[SPEAKER_15]: It has Hannah Montana in it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have ESPN.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't Dolly Parton her godmother?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like Dolly Parton.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't like Hannah Montana, but I like Dolly Parton.
[SPEAKER_15]: Before we get out of here tonight, we have one more thing we wanted to play for you guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: It came up in the email earlier.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was what Katamaris Forever emailed us, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: And sent us the parody of Still Alive, but it's featuring the OLR-themed lyrics.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we're actually going to play that for the listeners before we sign off tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: So here it is, and then we're going to be out of here.
[SPEAKER_15]: So a big thanks to Katamaris Forever and all the fans who got together to make the lyrics.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't wait to hear this.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: This was a triumph I'm making a flood here, brah brah brah It's hard to overstate my satisfaction
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Launch Radio We podcast the news because we can For the laws in all of us Except the ones who are banned But there's no sense crying over every darn show You just keep on talking till you're out of FU The podcast that's done and she makes a bad pun For the people who are still tuned in
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm being so sincere right now Even though some stupid kid shot someone And tore him to pieces And dug every piece into the ground
[SPEAKER_06]: They decayed and Rob gave him a big fat stupid award Now the spears of earth make a beautiful shine The whole thing isn't in the podcast on time But I'm five miles by six, so the podcast's here quick For the people who watch
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay, Nomar Live, 365 The sound on here is great and we just know it But is it a stereo?
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a joke, haha, mono Jamie's eating puss grumpy, but then again it's not me Look at us still singing when there's news to read
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm doing podcasts with the 365 We're here on all games, not 365 And while you're dying, you'll know 365
[SPEAKER_06]: Podcast of the year, we are gonna strive, gonna strive, gonna strive
[SPEAKER_15]: Yay, nice job.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was very cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was a little hard to hear the voice, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think on headphones it'll come out a lot better.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think it'll be easier to hear on headphones.
[SPEAKER_15]: But nice job and very, very flattering nevertheless.
[SPEAKER_15]: So thank you very much for that, and thank you to everybody who was involved with that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, now I think we can end the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: So thank you very much for supporting independent podcasting as you always do.
[SPEAKER_15]: Remember, if you like what you hear, please tell two friends about the program and help spread the word because we don't have any big magazine or website backing us, so we rely on word of mouth to get the word out.
[SPEAKER_15]: We do this for free because we heart you.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we'll see you next week for our sixth anniversary show.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's going to do it for another OLR.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_13]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!