Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts? DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
This week, Square Enix announced one old and one new Kingdom Hearts game
A former would-be dancing game slips down and seeks a modern revival
And the creators of Missing Riven announce their latest adventure game
Everything old is new again on tonight's episode which begins right now
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show
Where every gamer has a voice, it is Orange Lounge Radio
For this, episode number 524, October the 20th of 2013
My name is Rob Roberts, here to talk with you about the latest and greatest in the video gaming world
With my co-hosts, first off, say hello to DarkSakura, or Jamie Summers
I have the coffee jitters
A coffee jitter? What is the coffee jitters?
I had, granted it was decaf, but I still had a venti americano before I came over
And then I had coffee just now, and I've had lamb
Now you want another?
No, I'm good
You don't want any more coffee?
I thought that's how you fix the coffee jitters, more coffee?
No, I'm actually quite good
Alright, are you sure you're not going to be driving home?
And then, Dan, coffee!
I've got coffee at home if it comes to that
An old OLR in-joke for those that don't know
Rob!
We have a few of those here, we have been doing this show for quite a long time
Our longest running inside joke, say hello everybody to tech master Loki
Hi
How you doing, Loki?
I'm doing fine
I'm just kidding, I just didn't have any other good transition
How have you been?
Um, okay
Yeah? Anything new and exciting going on?
What's your latest project you've been working on?
You are, after all, the man of many projects
Um, well, let's see
I'm still trying to work on finishing up
Actually, that's what I'm doing right now
I'm looking for a 12 volt battery
Um, just that separate screen thing
The, uh, wireless second screen for, like, the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360
Oh, right, you talked about that a couple weeks back
How's that going?
Oh, it's going alright
I've just been running a little low on money
So I've been kind of holding off
Just because, um, also I'm trying to find the right battery for it
Because I want to find something that's not too expensive
And I don't really want to ship anything from China
Because it's going to take a long time to get here
So I'm just trying to find something that's got somewhat decent battery life
And, I don't know
I took apart my wireless HDMI receiver the other day
And thankfully, it's actually, the board inside it's a lot smaller than I thought it would be
And they have, like, a daughter board on there as well
So it's going to be easy to take apart
And then, uh, I don't know
Once you get this second screen project of yours finished
What's the first thing you're going to do with it?
Like, what's the first game you're going to play with it?
Grand Theft Auto 5, of course
Because, you know, that tells me what's the whole point of this project
Grand Theft Auto 5
But here's the thing, though, is I don't really need it anymore
Because I have a setup in my living room where I have my office chair there
And my computer monitor, since I don't really have a computer on
So I actually play Grand Theft Auto on that
Um, so, technically I don't really need it anymore
Because I still have a screen to play it on
While my wife watches TV
But I'm still going to build it
That's fair, because it's a thing
It's become a thing
And now you have to see it through to completion
I had to prototype something this week
Uh, that it's some thing that they're planning on trying to sell or something
It's like, uh, some little figure with, like, a USB, like, Wi-Fi and Bluetooth adapters built into it
And a thumb drive or something
So I got to play with that this week
But, yeah, I do want to make this the thing
Um, I got to do
After I figure, well, after I get all the parts
So really only parts I have left are the battery
And probably a 12 volt step down to 5 volt
Um, and then some miscellaneous ports and wires
And then once that's all done
And I figure out how I want to, uh, be laid out
I have to get the wood to build a mold
Or, yeah, sort of, I guess, a mold for, um, vacuum for me
And then I have to build the vacuum for me rig
Which, that's easy, because that's just a box, so
Oh my gosh, alright
Uh, let's go to our chat room
We do tape live every Sunday night
At 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
At the Voice of Geeks Network, vognetwork.com
And if you are listening live on this Sunday
You can join us in our live chat room
Live.vognetwork.com
And, uh, Ragenator
Wanting to know in chat
What baconified food product
Did Loki bring to the OLR studio tonight
If it's your first time ever listening to OLR
Uh, hi and welcome
And thanks for checking us out, first off
Second off, Loki's pretty notorious
For bringing a variety of different
Fast food, slow food, whatever food
I mean, Dark Soccer
Pretty reliably brings a salad
But Loki can bring a lot of different things
I don't bring a salad reliably
I used to when
I bring a lot more meat these days
Alright, meat salad
I didn't bring anything with bacon on it
Just because I wasn't that hungry
And so I just kinda got
It's a two cheeseburger meal from McDonald's
Cause it's cheap, I didn't really need to eat anything
But I know, cause last time
I skipped dinner, I was just like
Oh, I'm not hungry, I'm gonna skip dinner
And then like when I got home at like 10 o'clock I was hungry
So I just, I got something
Something kinda small
Cause I don't really like going to McDonald's
In the evening cause their fries are stale
And yeah, their fries were stale again
I ate them anyways, but they were stale
And I'm not, not enjoying that
And their burgers weren't even that good either
So it was just kinda eating just to be full
That's pretty much it
I'd love to see you bring some In-N-Out
But, I, okay, I would
But to reliably get here on time with
In-N-Out, it's just a crap shoot cause I can't tell
How busy they're gonna be and
Sometimes it's like 30 minutes to get out of there
So, um
Yeah, I just didn't do that
Although I did eat just bacon the other day
For lunch, that's all I had was bacon
So, I guess that counts
And so I ran out of bacon
Cause we had to eat the whole package before it was gone
My wife says, well you ate all the bacon
I'm like, dude, I only had like three pieces
So, you ate all the bacon
That's right
Um, you know, your weakness
For bacon is like my weakness for pumpkin
And this is the time of year, let me tell you
Uh, oh, you're shaking your head
That's right, you don't like the pumpkin stuff, huh?
Went to Trader Joe's the other day, Alan and I loaded up
On all this pumpkin stuff, like pumpkin butter
Pumpkin bread mix, pumpkin
And, um, pumpkin macaroons
I saw those in the, it's
What? Yeah, oh yeah, you wanna try one?
I need to read the label
Oh wait, yeah, you're on a diet, nevermind
I should be encouraging
Let me read the label to see if it's good
Okay, go check the freezer
Burger King is better than McDonald's
Yes, I 100% agree
Unfortunately there is like four McDonald's on the way here
And one Burger King
And I just don't feel like stopping off the freeway
To stop at the Burger King
If the McDonald's by me was a Burger King
I'd be stopping at Burger King
Because I like Burger King way better than McDonald's
Just FYI, I'd be able to have one
If I wasn't so close already to my limit, so
Aw, next week
If they're not gone
Alright, you can do it
Alright, uh, let's see
I had a kickoff topic for tonight
I don't know how successful this will be
But I was thinking, you know, we're getting into the Halloween
Season like full swing now
And, uh, I don't know about you guys
I'm not seeing as many like
Costume stores this year
Last year seemed like there was one on every corner
This year I'm not seeing as many
No, I'm not seeing as many
Maybe it's just the normal locations I see them at
I've seen quite a few
Well, I thought I would ask
What good video game costumes
You might be seeing out there
Are you seeing anything gaming inspired
And what types of great
Gaming costumes have you seen in the past
But this is a tricky subject
Because my mind always goes to these great
Gaming cosplays I've seen before
Which technically is a little different than Halloween
Yeah, it's just Halloween is the day that cosplay is
Cosplay is Halloween for grown ups every day
Or every other weekend, really
See, the difference between cosplay
And Halloween is
Halloween you get candy
Cosplay you get sexually assaulted
I shouldn't laugh at that
But sadly it's true
Alright, um
So what kind of like good costumes
Have you guys been seeing
I find it interesting how Mario and Luigi
Have really kind of, you know
Gone into the mainstream
Well, I mean it really shouldn't be a surprise
Those games are obviously like landmark games
Like common that costume is now these days
When I remember growing up
Like if you were to dress up like Mario
Like nobody knew who you were
But it's kind of interesting that like now it's like so commonplace
A lot of like people dress their kids up as that
Um, act deaf in our chatroom
At live.vognetwork.com
Remembering Loki's Sackboy costume
I still have the head, I don't know where the bottom is
Though, but I still have the head
Yeah, you wore that to one of the anniversary shows
Or something right, that was good times
Was it 300 or 400, one of them
Good times
You know what I realized I still have
My organization 13 coat
So, I don't know
It was me and
Kristen and Megzi
We all went as our OC's
Our organization 13 OC's
Which was pretty fun
I do remember at Disneyland seeing a child
Dressed up as Sora and I was like
You have the coolest parents ever because
Like you don't see any Kingdom Hearts related stuff
At Disneyland anymore, which is really sad
Except for the pins
I guess now, I think there's one or two now
But yeah, probably just because
You're starting to see more and more Kingdom Hearts
With the game, you know, really releases
And leading up to three and so forth
I know that there's the
Organization 13 Mickey
And then there's one other that I haven't been able to find
Yeah, I've seen the Organization 13 Mickey
But, be interesting
It's never gonna happen, Regent Air
What's Regent Air saying? Loki's Tingle costume?
No, I think that's a lost cause
We gave up on that
Now don't get me wrong, I have the build for that
But it's just not gonna happen
I just don't want to buy that much spandex
What's your kid going as this year?
Are you doing anything gaming?
He's a firework
Oh wait, that's right, you mentioned that on a previous episode
Yeah, my sister is building the costume for that
Although, I'm wondering though
If they're not gonna know what he is
Because the
Costume kind of looks like a black t-shirt
With garland wrapped around it
And then he's gonna have a hat with
Kind of
I don't know what you'd call it
Not garland
But kind of the stars and stuff
Popping off of it
Not really streamers, but they have the stiff
Wire
Not really garland, but decoration stuff
Where the stars and things
Like those things you get at the dollar store
Yeah, I've seen wrapped in gifts and stuff
Yeah, stuff you would kind of picture
4th of July
He's gonna have that
You should have stars and stripes
Forever playing wherever he walks
That's what he's gonna do
I'm not doing a costume this year
Just because
I'm just not feeling it
I don't have anyone to dress up with
It's because they had to go and lay off all my friends
That's my boss
Cool, I get to hang out with my boss
No, I'm just not gonna do anything
I just don't care
This Halloween, it's weird
It's the first Halloween I've had in a while
Where I don't have something with Rocky or a picture show going on
Because that all finished up weeks early this year
So I don't really have anything this year
I did get invited to a party
That's right after Halloween
That's still a dress up party
Something that Captain Spike
Is doing
The theme is around internet memes
That sounds awesome
I know what I'm doing
But I'm not gonna say because I know Captain Spike
Does this occasionally so I don't wanna spoil it
Because it's gotta be a surprise
I'll take you guys off air because I think you guys
Get a kick out of it
Let's see, go into our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com
BobbyBlackWolf says
A vog starter
Buy the spandex for Loki
I'm not
You're gonna need a lot of money
No, don't buy spandex
For Loki
No offense
I think the world would be a better place
But then we can get the glamour shots
Come on
Let's see, codeband
In our chatroom says
Trying to convince my wife to let me dress our daughter up
As a white mage
Oh I saw the pictures of the concept stuff
That would be pretty awesome
That's adorable
A little baby white mage
Well not baby but toddler white mage
It's pretty cute
I'm sure this is something that they have
A white mage hoodie
You have a white
Plain hoodie thing and then you put the
Fringe on it
I don't know how
Convincing it would look but something like that
Alright
It really
Actually wouldn't be that hard because
To do one of the concepts of a white mage
Your basic robe would be
A pretty big circle skirt
With sleeves sewn on
And then just a hoodie top
It really would be that easy
I didn't have a pattern for one that I was going to do
As a cosplay eventually
But never did
It doesn't seem like it depends what kind of white mage
You're going for
It wouldn't be too difficult
If you're trying to go as Yuna that might be a little trickier
Because you have to get the right colors and all that
And you also have to be
Anorexic
She's also not a white mage
She's a summoner
She's summoner slash white mage
If you were going to be a white mage then you would have to be
Oh yeah yeah
Alright
Or that bitch face Aerith
Let's get into
How was your gaming week and the types of video games
That you've been playing this week
Dark Sakura what have you been up to?
I played more fractal
It's just my chill out kind of game
So I love it
I'm playing more Bejeweled
I actually broke a million points twice
On one of the modes
Which is actually kind of difficult
I played Final Fantasy 14
Which I am at
The Bukake Manor
Or was it Hauke
Hauke Manor yeah
And so I need help
Doing that one eventually
And what else did I play
I actually played
Mass Effect 2
Because Becky
Has this thing for me using the high res mod
Well not really doing the high res mod
But I do the high res mod anyway
To take screen caps for her
Of her shepherd
So that she can have pretty pictures
So that's what I did
And then I'm actually playing through
I'm trying to finish my game on three
Just because I'm like I should finish it
But that and I need more screen cap fodder
Because I'm really
Really really really running out of ideas
For my stupid caption
Bullshit
And yes
Bitch face Aerith
That was from our chat room
And I do not name Aerith bitch face
I name her Aerith with a T H
But she's still bitch face in my esteem
I played something
Animal Crossing
And I feel bad because I was going to open my village tonight
And I left it at home
So sorry
I have three characters in my village now
I have Sakura, I have Tsubasa
Who I made just for the sole purpose of redecoration
And making Ed move
Because Ed's fucking creepy
Did it work?
No, he's still fucking there, the shit
And I made a character for Julian
For Becky's son
Oh nice
I may have mentioned this before
He sits with me when I play the game over there
And he practices his reading
With Animal Crossing
So I have to, you know, skip past kitty fuck
And, you know, poot
Well, poot's okay
But I have to skip past the one that says pussy
The naughty language
Fuck and all that
So, um
He used to laugh his head off at
Pork Sword and he had no idea
Oh wow
And I can't
Take credit for that one, that actually came from
One of Queen Semiya's characters that moved into my village
That was hilarious
So yeah, lots of Animal Crossing
And, um
Dan
Busted out the Ness
And played Kickle Cubicle
Kickle Cubicle
It's just the way you say kickle that makes it
Sort of come out the other way
I remember that game
So now that we have the Ness hooked up
I'm actually gonna be playing
I'm thinking about trying to rebuild my skills in Guardian Legend
Nothing wrong with that
I am going to be in tears for the next month
Until I remember how to play that damn game
Because that game's fucking hard
It is hard, but it's such a good reward
I've beaten that game so many times when I was like
There you go
Alright, Loki, how was your gaming week?
I just played Grand Theft Auto 5
Of course, that's all I played
But we had our fog game nights
Yeah, I was hearing some good stuff about that on Twitter, how'd that go?
Well, the first night
When I was doing PS3
I was trying to do video capture
And I have the Elgato capture thing
But for some damn reason it would not
Pick up the Playstation 3
Even through the component cables
Which is weird though, because I thought I had another set of component cables
Maybe I'm just doing it wrong or something
I thought I had one that was
The Playstation, actually
The multi-AV input
It was just that to
The Elgato
I can't find that, so I used
The component thing
That did not work out at all
It just could not detect it for some reason
But it was being finicky
Even with my Xbox 360 is doing the same
Kind of bullshit
Kind of skipped capturing that stuff
It's okay though, because we only had about
Two people I think the first night
Then on
Friday we did the second
Game night, which was on the
Xbox 360 version of Grand Theft Auto Online
That was a great turn out, we had about four or five people
Including Bobby
And we basically
Bobby didn't want to do any death matches
So we just did races
And parachute drops
And then
The one I think I had the most fun with
Was Top Fun
And Top Fun is basically
It's a team game
One team is in jets
And the other team is in cars
Cars are motorcycles usually
And they have to get from one point
To another point on the map
Without getting killed by the people in the jets
And it was a pretty
Intense gameplay
There was one where we had some other people join in with us
And we had all died
And then we were just watching this guy
Just haul ass through
The entire
Los Santos area
And there was this one where he hit a jump
Somehow and dodged two missiles
And thankfully I had the foresight
To capture everything
So I have that all recorded and I'll be cutting
A highlight reel
The only thing that kind of sucks is I didn't manage to record
My voice when I'm talking over voice chat
So you hear a lot of one sided conversations
But
Next time we'll be prepared for that
4 hours of stuff I have to cut through
So are you going to do it again next week?
Or is this a one to one thing or what?
It may not be next week but maybe in a couple weeks
We'll do it again
I don't know
I had a lot of fun
I think we leveled up about 5 levels
Just playing that
It was great
It's hard though because I know
People on the east coast and stuff
It's really late and Bobby goes up to 3 in the morning
Because we played until almost midnight
He's always up that late though
He runs on west coast time
Even though he's over there in Atlanta
So I'm going to try to do it again
Because I'm really limited in my window
Of time
To actually play
Because I have to wait for my son to go to sleep
But yeah I'll definitely do it again
But yeah it was a lot of fun
Aside from playing Grand Theft Auto online
Those couple times
I also did play some of the single player
Almost 86% done
With my 100%
Storyline stuff
I did the rest of the missions I had left
And I did all of the
Well some more of the
What was it?
Off road races
And assassination missions
And then some of the
Tonya
Towing missions
But the last one she has isn't triggered yet
That's the only thing I'm waiting on
To get all my strangers and freaks stuff done
But yeah it's been a lot of fun
And I'm trying to get the 100%
So I can start doing that chili ad mystery stuff
And
I'll definitely be playing more online
Especially more on 360
Because my co-workers flaked on me
I had one of my co-workers up here
On the Thursday night game
So we played but
I was the only one that had a headset that day
So that was kind of difficult to get people together
And he didn't really know how to join games
So it was kind of
Unorganized
But maybe the next time it'll be a little bit better
When we have more people playing
But yeah the one
Major gripe I have with
Grand Theft Auto online is just that
You know if you're getting dumped
Back into the main world again
Unless you're doing what we did throughout most of it
Where we just went from job to job to job to job
You get all
Split up
You get to constantly re-invite people back into your game
Just to keep everyone in the same world
But we had a lot of fun
So definitely looking forward to doing that again soon
Alright
Well be sure to let us all know when the next
Game night is for Grand Theft Auto
And in the meantime you can join the VOG
Crew right? Yeah we've got like
46 people in there last I checked
Nice, very cool
My gaming week
Didn't play as much video games as I would have liked to
This week but I did play a little bit
Playing some Final Fantasy 14
My White Mage is
An end game I don't know how many of you are playing
Final Fantasy 14 out there are an end game
But if you are an end game then you'll understand when I say
I got my Ifrit weapon
From the Primal Fight and then
Two days later got my Garuda one after
So many tries on the Ifrit one
Like two days later I get the better one from Garuda but whatever
And I finally got enough
Tombstones to get my Dark Light gear
So again if you don't play Final Fantasy 14
That probably means nothing to you
But that's what I've been kind of clunking away at there
Is grinding away the end game there
As far as other games I've played
Was playing some more Audiosurf 2
They've been adding little bits and pieces to that every day
Since it is one of those Steam Early Access games
So that's pretty cool I want to do some live streaming
Of that pretty soon because I really
Really like what they're doing with that so
I want to kind of play that for you guys
And let's see what else did I play this week
I went back
And visited Pac-Man Championship Edition
Because I don't know if you guys know
But they just came out with the Pac-Man Championship Edition Plus
Like the Plus add-on
Which is pretty much just a free patch
For Pac-Man Championship Edition
But now they have a little bit of a
Store kind of built in there so you can buy some additional skins
You can buy a couple additional
Mazes and a couple additional songs
Not a lot of stuff
But you know it's fun to go back
And kind of have a reason to play that again
And I like what they did with the Dig Dug skin
And the Rally X skin
It doesn't change the game
It just makes it look like you're playing Rally X
But it's like Pac-Man style so
I don't know I kind of like that that was something a little different there
And some of the new songs are cool too
They also have the original Championship Edition 1
Song in there so it's kind of
Neat that you can go back and play that if you want
The other new game that I've been playing
This week
Oh thank you Act F to correct me in our chatroom
Live.vognetwork.com
It's DX Plus not Championship Edition
Championship Edition was the first
DX Plus
Excuse me if I'm getting confused with all these
freaking Pac-Man games
Then we had Pac-Man and Ms. Pac-Man
And Junior Pac-Man and Baby Pac-Man
Yeah Pac-Mania anyway
Okay so
New game I played this week
Last week I told the hilarious
Story about how I loaned my 3DS
Out to Princess Irene who then
Went to Japan which came back from Japan
So today I was finally able to play
Pokemon Y
I will play a lot of it but I will say
It is
It's about time we finally get a next gen
Pokemon game because
This is the first time I've played a Pokemon game
In a while where I'm like
Oh wow this looks really good
This looks like it's running on the
Current hardware because let's face it
Black 2 and White 2 and Black and White
Were not up to par
With where the DS was at at that point
And that's probably part of the
Or probably the decision to
Make those games DS and not
3DS probably plays into that
A little bit but since X and Y
Are 3DS games you finally get a little
More kind of power in those games
And it's about time like
Kind of playing the game really made me
Realize like just how kind of
Behind the times
The other last
Couple series were
So yeah and I'm
I'm loving that
Within just a few minutes
Of being in the game and kind of getting
Going and going into the first area
There's already a diverse
Amount of Pokemon in the very first area
Like you're not just gonna get
A bunch of Bidoofs and Pidgeys
In the first area there's actually like
7 different Pokemon like enough where
You're already sending Pokemon to the box
Within the first little zone
Is the box like putting them to sleep?
No it's putting them in the computer is
What it is and there's a
Pikachu in the very first zone
And you know that's the type of
Pokemon that people really want
People don't go into a Pokemon game going
I really want a Pidgey
Or I really want a ZigZagZoon or I don't know
Maybe you do but most people don't
Most people want Pikachu
They want the cute stuff
Oh hell no I want that dark dog
Looking one I think it's awesome
So
Anyhow I like that there was already
That diversity and so forth
And again the combat looks great
The only downer is if you're playing
Combat in 3D mode
Very noticeable dip in quality
And I'm sure you've heard this a lot of places
But I'm telling you too
Very noticeable dip in quality
It's almost as if this game was made for the 2DS
Honestly
And I kind of think it was in some regards
And I think most people will be playing it with the 3D off
Because like when you're walking around the map
And everything it doesn't even really
Doesn't really use the 3D
It only uses the 3D in the battles and maybe
Like in the opening and things like that
That's really it but I mean that doesn't really affect the game
At the end of the day but it is a very
Interesting sign for
Maybe this 3DS
Or 3D thing is
Gonna be gone a little sooner than we think
They tricked you into buying another Gameboy didn't they
No I did not buy
I waited for Irene to bring my other 3DS back
No I'm just saying that
You know the whole thing remember
The thing that Nintendo is really good about is getting
People to buy the Gameboy over and over and over again
They'll have the Gameboy, the Gameboy Color, the Gameboy Pocket
You know the Gameboy Advance
SP and so on and so forth
Different colors
The DS, the DSi, the DSi XL
The 3DS which is
Basically a DS anyways
And now they're like oh hey
We don't really need the 3D anymore
So it's basically a fancy DS
They got you to buy another DS which in turn
Is basically a Gameboy Advance which is
A Gameboy
I will say this it's not coming up in tonight's news
Other stuff to talk about but
There is that 3DS XL with the
Legend of Zelda the two Triforces
In the top and bottom that 3DS XL
Is coming out
It was in the leaked GameStop Black Friday
Ad I'm really hoping
It is not a GameStop exclusive
I don't know at this point
Please don't please don't be
An exclusive because I really want one
But I won't buy it if it's a GameStop
Exclusive I won't buy it
But I probably will buy that
Because I'm a consumer whore
Or more like
I haven't been this excited for a Zelda game
In a very long time like the fact that they're making
A sequel to Link to the Past I'm like yes please
Admit one please
So I'm definitely looking forward to that
However this whole fact that
Some of the games are really just saying
Ah fuck 3D that are coming from Nintendo
Well I guess technically Pokemon
Is not a first party Nintendo game but it's like a second
Party it's like
It's first party they own the company that makes it
But Pokemon Company is in a really weird place
Because don't forget Pokemon Company makes iPhone
Apps too which is something Nintendo refuses to do
Oh no I guess they're going to make Miiverse though
I guess maybe that is changing
It's first party
Well whatever it is
It's still you know
It's still interesting
Anyway I'm very
Curious to see what's going to happen next
With the DS and I'm kind of wondering if we're
Going to see a new DS like I don't know if we
Would see like a new full DS next
Next year but I kind of I just feel like
It wouldn't be Nintendo if we didn't get some
Sort of handheld next year you know what I mean
We got the 2DS this year which you know whatever
I'm really curious what happens next year
Is it going to be the 2DS and the clam shell that
Everybody wants or is it going to be like
3DS XL Uber
Or something you know I'm so curious
Tablet
It's already one screen you just take the little
Middle the middle thing out of the
Out of the way and then there you go
You have one giant screen that you
Can play 2DS games on or
3DS games whatever you want to call them
So a Nintendo iPad
And then basically the whole thing is a touch screen
So you can run these you know games that are that big
Or I don't know they'll allow
You to run 3DS games on your
Wii U
Because that's going to happen
Eventually I will say it
Again and again it's going to happen
Maybe every single week but eventually it'll happen
I'll be like see I told you so
Or it won't ever happen
And you'll just forget you ever said anything
So alright so yeah Pokemon Y
I'm enjoying it I'm going to play a little more
Way more into it than I was
Black or Black 2 or any of the
Previous Pokemon games that I have been playing
So I'll let you know how that goes
I'll let you know if I actually am able to stick with it
To beat a few gym leaders
Or if I end up giving it up and going back to MMOs full time
We'll see
Alright over at live.vognetwork.com
Techness in our chatroom says
I remember playing yellow
It was pretty much yay I finally have a Pikachu
Then it became crap he's useless
When you hit the first gym and end up wasting time
Leveling up some mediocre grass type
Yeah kind of
Is the one bummer about Pokemon games sometimes
Is that you don't necessarily get to really
Play with that starter if
You know the gym you want to fight is
Strong to that type but there's
Such a diversity you usually find something else
You like like I think it's I started with
Fennekin obviously but then when I got that
Pikachu in the first zone I was like hell yeah
So now I have a Pikachu
And then I like to have a Pidgey too
Because they have the air attack and all that
Although he'll probably get replaced later
But for now you know so
Anyway
Let's see going to the chatroom
At live.vognetwork.com
Codeman suggests the Nintendo 4DS
You move with the game
Now if you were going to go fourth dimension
It'd have to be time travel
Which is already available in Animal Crossing
And technically the
3DS has a gyroscope in it so
It kind of does detect motion it counts your steps
Right remember that
Alright so there you go
Alright before we get into
Some housekeeping and our
Gaming news I'll take another question
Here from Jimbo in our chatroom
At live.vognetwork.com says
Are Sky, Loki, and Dark Sakura all getting
The new systems?
Good question are we getting the new
Systems? We're likely
Getting a PS4
But I need a job
I still have a
PlayStation 4 on pre-order
Although we're going to get into some news here
Very shortly that kind of makes me
Make a sad face when it comes to that
I mean I'll still get it but yeah
Loki? Not at launch
Not at launch? I'm not getting it
Launch accounts on my pre-order sorry
Or pre-order because I didn't pre-order
The Xbox one please
Alright
Going to our housekeeping
Just want to tease that we
Have our Facebook
And our Twitter
So please be our friend
On those sites
Also just letting you know and this may be news
To my co-host too sorry about it
But there may not be a show November
10th it's looking like I'm going to be out
Of town thanks to Blizzcon
Even though I'm not going
I'm not going to Blizzcon
I'm going to Blizzcon and I'm going to the Blizzcon
Parties
So may not be a show
November 10th unless I'm able to rush home and be
Here in time we'll see
Just letting you know in advance but we still
Have a couple weeks of show before we get there
Alright let's get into gaming news
And Loki some of the sad
News for Playstation 4
Awaitors this week right?
It was bound to happen but games
Are being delayed I'm not too
Surprised by this Watchdogs has been
Delayed to Spring 2014
And the reason why I'm not surprised by this is
Because Ubisoft has a ton of fucking titles coming
Out in the fourth quarter including
Assassin's Creed 4 and South Park
Among them
So to have Watchdogs
Coming out at the same time I mean Watchdogs
Is almost kind of competing with Assassin's Creed
So why would they want to compete with themselves?
Might as well just put out your game
In a slower period of the year
And polish it up
Even more even though it does kind of suck
For people that were hoping to
Buy that as a next gen game
When I was actually thinking about getting a Playstation 4
That would have been one of the titles I would have probably picked up
For it but
Yeah I guess we just got the
Wait right now it's expected to be
Hitting in the next financial year
Which I believe they're estimating that
To be second quarter
Of 2014
Also to go along with
That the crew has been delayed
To mid 2014
And you know
Around the I guess
Summer period so that
Runs July 2014 to
September 2014
And
I'm not surprised I mean I don't even think they really had
A date for that other than I think it was supposed to be
Early 2014 so
Whatever one is kind of disappointing
Though Sony one of their
First party
Launch titles has been delayed Drive Club
Which was supposed to be one of those
Games they actually got at least a
Somewhat complete
Version of for
Playstation Plus now you're just gonna have to wait
To play it early 2014 for that
That one stings a little bit
That was the one I think a lot of people
Were looking forward to you know driving games
Are usually a great way to show off
The graphical oomph of a new system
So that one hurts a little bit
I mean I guess there's still Need for Speed
But
Yeah but this is more of I think it's more of
Simulation racing so
Need for Speed is definitely arcade
It's not necessarily like
4 is a 5 or something
Maybe Gran Turismo 6 but that's
Playstation 3
I think with all this stuff kind of
Being delayed once again it makes it also
A hard sell for a next gen system because
A lot of these games that are coming out
There's not a whole ton of exclusives
For these next gen systems at
Launch and there's still
Really good games coming out on current gen
I mean right now
Gran Turismo 5 is not on
Next gen, Gran Turismo 6 is not
On next gen
You know there's
Plenty of games out there that
They don't have next gen versions for and
Call of Duty let's be honest it's probably not going to be
That much better on Playstation 4
Or Xbox One aside from
Graphics it'll probably look nicer
You know it's also interesting that
Big controversy
A couple weeks ago when Sony delayed
The Playstation 4 in Japan
To next year because they said
You know what we're really not going to have games out
Available for it this holiday
And now it's kind of looking like
Yeah maybe that is
The case you know
I was curious what games
Are going to be out at launch
What is going to be out on the Playstation 4
I have a partial list here on wiki
This is wikipedia
I have mine full list up in my head
Okay so as far as
I can only really speak to North America because I have no idea
No that's fine that's what I want to know
So first party titles
Are going to be coming out you have of course Killzone
Shadow Fall
You have Knack
And that's
Pretty much it actually
That is it since Drive Club
Fell off that's it
Third party you've got Call of Duty
Assassin's Creed 4, Battlefield 4
Need for Speed
NBA Live
NBA 2K14
There's also
What was the other ones here
There was
Something no one's going to really pick up
Skylanders, Swap Force
Lego Marvel Super Heroes
Angry Birds Star Wars
The only ones
I'm not hearing is
Need for Speed Rivals
Did you Just Dance 2014
Yeah Just Dance 2014 is coming out
You said one of the NBA games
But there's two on the list
NBA Live which is next to
exclusive and NBA 2K14
Now there are some
Network games too
Which I know you wouldn't be as up on
But there's things like Contrast
Divekick
Minecraft and Pinball Arcade
Resogun is another one
Those are all things that are set to be
Available on Playstation Network
Injustice also
Injustice Ultimate Edition
That's right
And Injustice
Injustice, at least the next gen version
Is exclusive to the Playstation 4
So they do have that I guess
I was going to say also
Xbox One
They still have a decent lineup
They've got all three of their games
I was just going to say, Xbox One
As much as they've been getting the short end of the stick
With their popularity on the internet
Some things they do have
That they're going to have on the 22nd
They will have Crimson Dragon
Dead Rising 3
Forza Motorsport 5
Killer Instinct, although I kind of
I've got to be honest, I don't care about Killer Instinct anymore
Rise
And let's see, Power Star Golf
It says it's exclusive
The Xbox Fitness game as well
There's also the Zumba Fitness game
And yeah
And then a lot of those same third party games
We've already mentioned before
I mean, Xbox, it's funny
It really does have more exclusives
That comes out, but it's going to be interesting to see
Are people going to pay the other $100
To get in on that
And really
Are the exclusives good enough
I'm going to be honest, when I look at this list
I go, Rise
Eh, Killer Instinct
Maybe, but I don't like what I'm hearing about it
Crimson Dragon, okay yeah
I'd like to check that one out
But would that sell you a system? Probably not
I don't think so, no
Like, had it been a new Halo game
That might have tipped the scales
Had it been that Quantum Break, that definitely would have tipped the scales
So
You know
Honestly, it comes down to the third party games
For me, I think I would like to play Need for Speed
For sure
I'd like to check out the Lego game
Because usually those are pretty good
But the Lego game to me
If you really want to, it's coming out on the Wii U
About a month before it comes out on the other system
So it's not really a game that needs the next gen
Version of
Skylanders, please
That's not a game that needs the next gen version
I mean, seriously, that's going to be important
Angry Birds Star Wars
Really?
No one cared, no one cared
So
Yeah, that's kind of where it was
Even when they had their full lineups
Well, there's not really a lot that's selling me
On these next gen systems
The only first party game that looked really good
To me for Playstation 4 was Infamous
Second Son
Kind of cool
Killzone, I'm just not a fan of Killzone
If it was a new Resistance game that looked that nice
Okay, then
I would probably pick that up
I have to be honest
I almost feel like in a way I kind of have to get on board
With the next generation
Just because I have this show
And I want to be able to talk about games on the show
See, I felt that way before
The last generation
I bought all three systems
And that was a mistake because I just don't play all three systems
I don't play the Wii
And the Playstation 3 has just gotten a little bit more activity
Now that I'm playing Grand Theft Auto on both systems
But
It was pretty much collecting dust
And the Xbox 360 was the only thing I was playing on
And a lot of people now are upgrading to the Xbox One
Because they figure
Well, I've invested all this time in the Xbox 360
I might as well go along with that
To carry over my gamer score
Which really doesn't mean anything, folks
Just saying
Wouldn't your trophy information on Playstation carry over too?
Yeah, that's going to carry over too
I'm talking about the 360
So, I mean, that doesn't really count for anything
You know
I just, I can't do that anymore
And even when I do go to buy a system
I'm not going to buy
All of the different systems out there
Just because I don't have time to play all of them
And honestly, I don't want to waste money
On more than one system
So
I'll just wait and see
I'm sure the price drops will happen
Or at least there'll be more games out there
So might as well wait
For something that I really want to play
Like a next-gen version of Grand Theft Auto 5
Alright, we'll see
Anyhow
Yeah, I'm curious to see
How that all pans out this holiday season
Like what games end up being the big seller
This holiday
Because I gotta say
It's really funny, the games
I'm looking forward to the most
Are on Wii U
I would say the game I'm looking forward to
The most this holiday is
Mario 3D World 2
Or whatever they're calling it on Wii U
God, I can't even tell these games apart anymore
All I know is it's a new Mario game on Wii U
And I want
And that would be the game I'm probably looking forward to the most
So
Anyway
Speaking of Xbox One
Xbox One, not going to be doing any type of
Real name integration at launch
You're still going to be using your gamer tags
At launch, now don't
Miss-hear me here, I'm not saying that Xbox was going to
Plan to switch everybody to their real names
Although that would be hilarious for the trolls
But you know I'm not here for that either
I threw a fit
When Blizzard threatened to do it with real ID
And I threw a fit here too
Well, remember, Sony's planning on doing that
They are, but Sony's planning on doing it through your Facebook
And you can use a fake name on Facebook
You're not supposed to, but you can
They didn't steal it from your credit card
Which still rubs me the wrong way to this day
Anyway
The game tags
Are all you're going to have on Xbox One
They did say
Our teams are working hard to deliver a quality experience
For Xbox One, this means
Prioritizing some features and sometimes
Postponing others for a later
Update
Honestly, I don't miss the fact that they're not
Going to use my real name
Who cares? Not something I really want them to use
Did Xbox say it's coming off of
Facebook? Because if they get that from my credit card
I will not be happy
I would imagine it would have to come from Facebook
Because not everyone's
Going to be, they have alternate payment
Forms now, it's not all just through a credit card
I guess that's true
But just so you know, the real names are how
People are supposed to be able to search for you
Like if they want to be able to find you
Or whatever, but then I would think like, well what kind of privacy
Restrictions are they going to put in place? I kind of don't
Want people to search for my name and find me
Sorry, if I want you to find me
I'll give you my gamertag
Any listener of this show that's ever asked for it
Honestly, there's a lot of people that share my name
The upside of having real names
However, is that it removes that aspect
Of anonymity for trolls
But I don't think they're going to
See, that's where your mind goes
But I don't think they're going to show that
That would be a huge privacy thing
Or it's even worse and they are now
Able to track you down based on your real
Name and then they control you beyond
Xbox on
Facebook or
Having the
Maybe keeping the name secret
But having it for issues of just searching
If you know who you're looking for
That might be something different
However, I don't know
But yeah, I got to be honest
If I want you to find me, I'll give you my gamertag
Exactly, I don't need you to be able to
Just search for my name
Or whatever, I think what they're trying to do is
They're trying to integrate it with Facebook even tighter
So that way, you know, once you
Once it gets you to connect it one time
It's going to be like, look at all these people
You don't have on your Xbox friends list yet
But you're friends with them on Facebook
Add, add, add, add, don't you want to add them now
So you can send them cookies and
Fight with them on
Killer Instinct
And all this stuff
So
Going to our chatroom at
Live.vognetwork.com
Ragenator says, Sky, why associate
A credit card number with a system
Where there's those PSN, Wii, Xbox Live
Funds, cards that are everywhere
Cause it's an extra step
No, that's a good point
And I try not to give them that information anymore
But I think they have it on file cause my
Xbox Gold still comes from that
And historically, they would have had
That information anyway
So, there you go
S2100matt in chat says
I don't really want people to know my real name here
Sure, I want to play with people
But I don't really want people to know my real name
Yeah, I'm kind of with you and if these systems
Are going to review, either one of them
If it's unveiled that they're
Going to show the real names or whatever
I'm out, I'm not buying the system
If that crap is in there
Yes, I do want anonymity
But it's not to troll people, it's because
I play video games to escape the real world
Sometimes
So, just saying
Besides, we all know that the Xbox One is going to take
A picture of your junk and assign it to your real
And then it will have your real name on it
Just saying
Maybe Xbox should think about
Just not implementing that feature
Like, is it really that big a deal?
And even though I do have the PlayStation 4 on pre-order
I'm going to be very curious to see what happens
With those early units and what might come out about that
Anyhow
Wine, whine, complain, complain
DarkSakura
Well, for something that is not
Complain worthy, something that's actually good
Is that Squeenix said
That Kingdom Hearts 2.5 Remix
Is a compilation
HD compilation that has
The Kingdom Hearts 2 final mix, Birth by Sleep
Final mix
And the remastered cinematics from
Re-coded
And it's going to be on
PS3 and is
Going to be out in 2014
But no mention of PS4
So this will be
Coming after the 1.5 remix
So yay
More HD
More Kingdom Hearts
I
Saw that new trailer though
For Kingdom Hearts 3
Sexy
What did I say on my friend's Facebook? I think I said
This is serving up some Big Thunder Mountain Electric Parade
Realness
Now I did watch it and I was just like
This looks like more Kingdom Hearts
I think it wasn't really Big Thunder Mountain at all
I think that train was part of the Electric Parade
Yeah, and it didn't
His name was in the corner and it didn't say Big Thunder Mountain
Granted they might call it something
Different in Japan, I don't know
But it was interesting that
Anything they did show did not incorporate
Any other Disney properties
Besides the Goofy and Donald
Sidekicks that you expect to see
Because you saw Traverse Town
And then you saw a big pirate ship
That was like flipping around in circles
And then you didn't really
Like you didn't see
Mulan World
You didn't see Tron
You didn't see 100 Acre Wood
You didn't see any of that stuff
So we still don't know exactly what's going to be represented in the game
But I figure they want to keep most of that a secret for a good long while
Well and also if I'm right
At the two Disney parks in Japan
I think that there's not a Big Thunder
I think that they've
Combined that concept with the Indiana Jones
Ride to have an outdoor roller coaster
That sometimes runs backwards
And wouldn't that be fascinating
If they had an Indiana Jones level
Something that incorporates the Lucas Arts
They technically can
They can but
Marvel? I wonder if they will
I mean that's a little bit more separate but Marvel
I think they're going to keep it Disney
To Squeenix and leave it there
I think they will too
But I could see like a very subtle
Like here comes Indiana Jones
Like I could see that like being a thing
Just like a little bit of a
Wink and a nod to some of their recent acquisitions
I think putting Marvel in there
Would be too much
That's like a completely different universe
What about Pixar stuff?
I really hope they do
I think some of the Pixar games would make for great levels
Especially with how they've been pushing
The Cars franchise
Cars Land and all that
Has been huge
For a very short ride
Oh my god
I would love to do something in the WALL-E universe
WALL-E is kind of set on Earth
So I don't know exactly what they would do with that
But we'll see
Incredibles?
I'd be cool
But yeah a lot of the Pixar stories are sort of like
They're not really about their worlds
So much as they are the characters I think
Star Wars would be cool though
Star Wars would be very cool
Dark Soccer did you see the other news about Kingdom Hearts 3?
Um
Let me uh
No
Because my iPad's being a shit again
Hold on
I believe there is a little bit more news
And of course it is something that we're pretty
Aware
Was going to happen regardless
Is that Utada Hikaru is
Well may return
For Kingdom Hearts 3
Which I think is probably going to happen
She really should I mean
But she's been on a musical hiatus or something right?
Didn't she take a break or something?
She did
But there was actually a post
That came from
Utada Teruzane
Who is his
Her dad
Who said that the two of them were
Undecided when it came to Kingdom Hearts 3
So she's
Not contributing a new theme song
But there's a chance she might help
I sure hope she does
Do something with it that would be great
Because the songs especially Simple and Clean
Was so important to Kingdom Hearts you know
Yeah
Codeman in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com
Says Wreck It Ralph World
That would be too meta
Although Sugar Rush would be pretty great
I could still see them doing that
Like a Sugar Rush level would be kind of
Like just even like instead of the gummy ship
Tangled
I could see Tangled
Oh I could totally see Tangled
I kind of hope they do that
That would be great
Have they done this yet because I liked it
I thought it was a good movie
Emperor's New Groove
I don't think they did
Let's see
SSG100Matt says
Indiana Jones in Kingdom Hearts would be better than the Crystal Skull
Well ain't that the truth
As long as
I have bars low
Shia LaBeouf is not allowed to be in Kingdom Hearts
Do not let that kid anywhere near
Kingdom Hearts
You keep Shia LaBeouf away
From Kingdom Hearts
Not gonna happen
Ooh Act Deaf is suggesting Brave
Great Pixar movie
I could totally see that as well
That would be great
We could fan wank Kingdom Hearts
Worlds all day long but the reality is
We are just not gonna know until they make
Some formal announcements so we'll see what happens
Loki
Alright so some other good news for the Xbox One
Platform
They are making available to all the developers
The Xbox Live Compute
I don't know if you would call it
I guess
SDK which is basically
The ability to use the cloud servers
For off platform
Computations
Including physics and
More importantly dedicated
Servers and so because
Of that dedicated servers
For all multiplayer games
Is possible
But it has to be enabled by
The developers
Because they can also choose to
Have control over that
Versus using the Xbox Live Compute
Stuff and
I guess they are saying that they have
Over 300,000
Virtual servers
Powered by cloud technology
So it sounds like
That they could get some
I mean that's definitely a plus for a lot of people
That play multiplayer especially like Call of Duty
And stuff that year and a half
Dedicated servers and also kind of
Curbs cheating a bit because there's
People that hack the platforms and stuff
And having a dedicated
Server would kind of eliminate that
Sounds ambitious
And entirely
A good idea
I'm just curious to see
Because they keep talking about these Azure cloud
Servers and stuff and
I'm just curious to see how
Stable that all is
Because every
Every company comes out and says
Hey yeah we've seen these
Problems with connectivity
And stuff like that
It's not going to happen to us
We're prepared this time
And every time it's fucked up
So you know I'm kind of
Curious to see how all these servers
Are going to play into that
Or if it's just going to be a big fucking mess
Because I wouldn't be surprised
If it was a big fucking mess
Just because all the other
Online games and stuff have just been
Messy
What will be the first Xbox game to get that
37 equivalent or the
SimCity connection error and all these
Hilarities in the past
The one that I could see would be the biggest
Pain in the ass would maybe be fours of
Five because remember you have to download
Part of the game
Or most of the game
Because it's not done yet on the disk
I can see that being a problem
If you can't connect to their cloud servers
Also the other thing
Remember just like
Rockstar just had the problem where it wasn't
Necessarily all of the cloud servers
But mainly the matchmaking stuff
Was down and so even if you have
A part of your
Service down that it could still affect
Everything so
I don't know
It'd be interesting to see
My thought is okay
If it's so easy for you
To do this as a company
Microsoft then why isn't anybody
Else doing it that way
If this is so easy
If it's such the right way to go
Then why don't we have
Rockstar hosting their stuff
And azure servers and all that stuff
It makes me think that there's a little bit
More hype to it than
It's actually gonna
Be reality so
I guess we'll have to see when it launches
I'm sure we'll be talking about stories
Of connectivity and
I'm not saying it's probably limited to
Microsoft at all
If the PlayStation 4 relies heavily on
Yeah it's probably gonna be everybody
Alright
Shifting gears here a little bit
If you are a PC gamer
By any means or even if you've just lightly played
PC games in the past I'm sure you're
Familiar with the game Myst
This is one of the top selling PC games
They ever made it's an adventure game
And they've remade this game a ton of times
There were a lot of games in the series
Riven was another big game
These were both games by Cyan
Inc. was the name of the studio that made these games
Well they have announced that they are
Making a new game it's called
Abduction not Abduction
It's O-B-D-U-C-T-I-O-N
Abduction is the new game
But here's the interesting thing
It is a Kickstarter game this is where they're
Taking their case to Kickstarter and they're trying to get
1.1 million dollars
To make this game work
They're talking about very similar
Exploration driven gameplay that help make
Myst a reality
They're gonna do Unreal Engine 4
Is what they want to be able to license
To make this game work
And they're targeting mid to late 2015
So they're giving themselves
Plenty of time to make Abduction
Happen
So if you want to check that out you can go to their Kickstarter
Now the thing that really got me about this
Though is I'm like dude this is the studio
That made Myst and Riven
Like why do they have to
Turn to Kickstarter? Like surely there's
A publisher or somebody out there that's willing
To back them a little bit
And I'm like well what the hell else have they done
Outside of Riven and Myst
Anybody know without cheating
What some of the other games Cyan Inc. did
In the down time
Cause once I went to go look at the list I was like
Oh yeah there was that game that really
Didn't do well
It was the one that was that Myst
Not Myst Online or whatever the hell they ended up calling it
That was part of, was it GameTap actually?
It was Myst Online Uru Live
And it didn't, you're right
That's it, it went over to GameTap
In the Uru games actually
Uru I think was the third Myst
And then they did all these different Uru games
That Ubisoft was doing for a while
Including Myst 5
Went all the way there and then Myst Online
Yeah I remember that game kind of flopped
And GameTap picked it up and ran it for a little while
I actually played Myst Online
The funny thing is back in 2007
This show was around and I think there's some
Old episodes where I was talking about my experiences
In Myst Online
It was just such an odd game
It was just like, it was so like
Just kind of creepy
Odd, like the ambience in that game
Was really, like
Chills, but I mean I enjoyed what I did
Play of it even though it wasn't
As obvious of a game
As World of Warcraft or even EverQuest
Where it's like, experience leads to
Levels, leads to abilities, leads to gold
Gold, gold, you know Uru Online
Was a very different type of game
Other than that, that was 2007
And since then it's been a lot of
iPhone, iPod, iPad
Type of stuff
They adapted Myst, they adapted Riven
They did some games called Bugchucker
And Stoneship
Abduction is a very
Kind of anxious
Return to form, shall we say
For this company
Best of luck to them, they just might do it
They got a 1.1 million dollar goal
They have raised just shy of
Half a million, they're at $460,000
With 26 days to go
So they've already made
Between a third and a half of the money
With only 4 days down
So that's pretty cool
$25 or more will get you the game
Via Kickstarter, by the way
$45 is a digital collection
Let's see some of the crazy
Rewards they're giving, let's see
$10,000 or more will give you
An experience design at
Cyan, you can actually go
To an early abduction design meeting
You can either go there
Or join via Skype
And I guess you get to have your say in the game
Kind of neat
So there you go
And they're already looking at stretch goals too
But they won't say what they are until they reach the base funding
Which I imagine would just be more
Expansions of the game and so on and so on
So
Going to our chat room at live.vognetwork.com
SSJ100Matt says, Myst was odd
I should go back to it
I still have the original CD-ROM copy laying around
Reginator says
Riven original soundtrack is great to play
If you're having trouble sleeping
DungeonBuster says, Cyan went the way
That a lot of adventure games did in the 90s
Which is probably why they're kickstarting
This project
Tim Schafer had to kickstart his own adventure game
Just to get it going
Well it's so interesting because a lot of these projects
End up being very successful
So it's surprising to me
And especially with how well The Walking Dead did
Last year and was so well received
And everything, I'm like, I'm really surprised
That the mainstream is not getting
Like, dude, people never
Really got over the 90s adventure game
Thing, there's still very much an audience
For that, you know
Anyhow
Reginator says
SSJ100Matt is that even playable
On modern PC's
Well they had it in GameTap
Even though GameTap is a few years old at this point
You definitely could play all those games
I'm sure
It's gotta be on good old games, right?
It has to be there
Alright, there you go
Good luck to the studio getting that going
It'll be exciting if they get it done
I hope it's as creepy as other games
Dark Soccer
Well, Rob, this actually may affect you
May or may not affect you
And 50,000 other people that I know
Fucking play this game
Do I have to go get a shot?
No, no, no, but there is a bug
However, it's not a sickness bug
It's a sickness within Pokemon X and Y
So the entire game
Yeah, the whole game, no
Basically, if you save your game in Lumiose City
There is a problem where if you save in and around the streets
Outside the city
The game will lock up and make you have to reset your game
And when you reboot
The game will load the save and freeze again
Basically it loops and loops and loops
Now, Nintendo is aware of this
And they're working on making a patch for it
That will be downloaded
When they have it done
So at least they know about it
At least something is going to happen
It just hasn't happened quite yet
And they're saying
They've put out a map
It's only a Japanese one
Which I will go ahead and also
Link to the chat room assuming it loads
But for those of you who are affected by this
Sorry, start over and don't save in the town
To register participation for this week's episode
Of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com
Use the passphrase, rainbow
Yeah, I'm going to make a note of that
So I don't do that, but I do like how in the new
Pokemon games you can practically save anywhere
So that's pretty cool
Useful
Much useful, but it's better than trying to find a save point
And do it that way, that's for sure
Alright, let's travel around the world
And check out some release dates of some games coming out soon
That hopefully aren't broken
That have hopefully been quality tested
Which is, by the way, not to get all tangent-y
Or whatever, but that's the good thing
About those other games you were talking about earlier
Getting delayed, like things like
Drive Club and Watch Dogs
And everything is that, you know what
If they have to do that to QA the games
And make sure that they're going to be right
Then fine, delay them
We'll never remember that they were delayed
Wasn't Grand Theft Auto 5 delayed a bunch?
We all forgave them, we forgive them, right?
And it was worth it
That's right, it was worth it
So, you know what, I would rather the games get delayed
To test the QA
Now in this Pokemon, I don't know
Because you can save anywhere
I don't know if they would have found that
During QA testing or whatever
That would be a very tricky thing to find
It would be
I forgive them, but Nintendo's
Got to be able to patch these things faster
And more efficiently too, I think in some ways
You know what I mean?
Like you kind of expect on Xbox and Playstation
It's always going to patch right away if they have them
Nintendo can kind of be a pain in the butt
They haven't quite figured out this whole internet thing yet
Yeah, that's
And I think that's part of what's their worst nightmare
Right now with Wii U
I'm still convinced that plays into it
I mean, my friends have made good arguments
About to the contrary and about how
You know, there is DLC for like a
Now, they just started that a year ago
See, there's something about
All of that
And the fact that nothing ever showed up for Mass Effect 3
Nothing showed up for Injustice
And all that just kind of
Nothing showing up for Assassin's Creed 4
There's something really weird about that
I mean, granted Nintendo's doing it themselves now with Super Luigi
And all this other stuff, but
Are they doing it differently than it was done on 360?
I don't know, so
You know
I won't know, actually I don't think that has anything
I thought it might have been Uplay
Or something like that
They didn't support those extra
You know, services and stuff
That maybe that was the problem or something
Actually, that could be
Now that I think of it
If Uplay isn't supported
Then that's why Assassin's Creed didn't get the DLC
And EA
Uplay has a channel on Wii U though
Then I don't know
Maybe they changed something
I don't know, or maybe it's just
Nintendo or something, I don't know
Tangentrain, ChuChu, let's go to release dates
So this week we actually have quite a few things
Coming out, starting off with Naruto
Ship It In, Ultimate Ninja Storm 3
Full Burst, which is just a re-release of the game
With DLC, PS3, and 360
For that, Deus Ex Human Revolution
The Director's Cut
Coming out on PlayStation 3
Xbox 360, and debuting on
The Wii U
And of course those are re-released for
The other two platforms
Plankton's Robotic Revenge
PlayStation 3, Xbox 360
Wii, Wii U, 3DS
And DS
Hometown Story
If you're a fan of the Harvest Moon games
Sort of a spin-off of that
That's on 3DS this week
Lego Marvel Super Heroes
PlayStation 3, Xbox 360
Wii U
3DS
Vita and PC
The Sims 3
Into the Future
Getting, that's a new expansion
That's on PC of course
Um
Let's see
Also
Disney Infinity, some more of the
Packs are coming out, Toy Story
As well as the
Woody figure, and I believe next
Not next week, but the week after next
Is Jack Skellington
Where the hell is Nightmare Before Christmas? It's that time of year
Well, it's been a GameStop exclusive
For right now
It's exclusive on the figurine, and Woody I think
Is exclusive to Walmart or Target or Toys R Us
One of those
I got an exclusive finger for GameStop right here
Sorry to the employees
My anger is not with you
The front-end associates
If you want to get some
2K games that have been
Out before, there's some collections
Coming out, including the 2K Essentials collection
Which is, I believe
Bioshock
Borderlands
And I want to say
Oh, what the hell is the last game there?
XCOM
The first XCOM game
That was on 360, Enemy
Not really the first XCOM game
On 360
No, I said the first XCOM game on 360
Okay, okay
That's on PlayStation 3 and
Xbox 360
They also have another collection
The strategy
Collection, which is Civ 5
And XCOM, that's on PC
And then there's
Another one with
I don't remember, I'll get to that in just a second
Let's see, Rocksmith 2014 edition
Coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox
360 and PC
Of course, they also have a version without the
Little adapter in case you bought
The game before
And a version with a guitar
You need a guitar for that game
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
3DS Wii and Xbox 360
And that's based on the new
Cartoon series on Nickelodeon
Just Dance Kids 2014
On Wii and Wii U
And Xbox 360
Oh God, there's a kids game this year too?
There's been a kids game for the last few years
I knew there was the one, I didn't know
There was four kids games last year
God, does it have that horrible
God, that joke
What does the fox say?
I don't know
That would be pretty funny
Oh my God, that song gets on my nerves so bad
I've finally, by the way, seen that
And I was sorry I saw that
They play it on the radio now and I'm like, okay
That was funny for a day, stop
I'm so glad I don't listen to the radio
It made me laugh the first time
And after that I was like, yay
My wife has told me, and I also saw this
But I actually haven't listened to this song yet
Well apparently it's a huge kids song
It's a kids thing, but what does the fox say?
I thought it was a stoner song
What does the bong say?
What about
What about that Chinese food song
Now that, I'm here for that
That song
Cracked my ass up, and the video
Is fantastic
I hated myself for finding it funny
I have not seen that song yet
The Chinese food, that's great
Just seeing that guy take the panda thing off
I'm like, is that dude
It's the little things too, the little
subtly, horribly racist things
In the video, like when they're talking
They're playing Monopoly, like he rhymes
Some freaking Chinese who have Monopoly
And then he moves the piece to Oriental Avenue
In the video
It's like they're going for every
It's like they're going for every fucking
Stereotype in the universe
I love its badness
But then again, Showgirls is my favorite movie
It's sort of like, I don't know if it's trying to be
Lisa Lampanelli style funny
You know, offensive on purpose
To make you think about it, or if
It's just really being stupid
Other things coming out this week
A little game called Batman Arkham Origins
That's coming out on Friday
That's this week? Yes, on Friday
For some reason
That's on Playstation 3, Xbox 360
Wii U, and PC
And of course they have the Blackgate version
Which is not quite Arkham Origins
But it's a little different
That's on 3DS and Vita
And then Wii Party U
For the Wii U
And, you know, this game was so
Great looking
That they also have to throw a remote in there
In a horizontal stand for your
What games are in Wii Party U? I know nothing about this game
It's crap
Okay, Wii Party was terrible, it's gonna be crap
In Soviet Russia, Wii Party U
Just what the name makes me think of
Some other random games coming out
Cradle of Egypt 2
Which is a puzzle game
And Girls Fashion Shoot
Which is a fashion simulator game
That's it
That would be everything
Although, I do have to say this week though
I believe it's also the DLC
For Saints Row 4
So there's some DLC coming out
For that, the Enter the Dominatrix
Stuff
Alright, now's the part of the show where you get to
Hear me horribly butcher Japanese
Release dates, yay
On the Playstation 3 in Japan on October 24th
BlazBlue, Chrono Fantasma
Comes out, as well as
GQ Powerful Pro
Yaku 2013
Which is that soccer? It's baseball
Baseball
I knew it was a sport of some sort
Also on the 24th on the Playstation 3
Sengoku Musou 2
With Moshuden and Empire's HD version
Tears to Tiara 2
Hau no Matsue
What is Tears to Tiara?
That sounds like somebody who cries a lot
And becomes queen
I don't know, but it looks like some type of
Roleplaying-esque game
I don't know what this is
This is like half the other things
I see come out
Let's see what else, there's Root Double Before Crime
After Days Extend Edition
Kazuko Kiyakutomugu Ito
In regular and limited edition
From Cyberfront this week
Which looks like
I'm looking at a screenshot from this game
And I'm sorry
But those breasts are too much
For that face
For that cute little chibi face
She's got these breasts
She would be tipping forward
However
I can say
I was quite young
And quite stacked
So it is possible
That's a bit much
I'm gonna put it this way
I've been a D since I was 13
You're blessed
Nothing wrong with that
Some girls too
So if they don't show the boy's face
Then it's a date rape game
I don't know about this
This is a little bit of an awkward picture
That's a
Fucking game
So the quotes South Park
Nice
Not okay
It's essentially a moe game
Which Alan just said in the chat
Yep
Going to the Xbox 360
This week in Japan
Zero, zilch
On the PlayStation 3 though
That same baseball game
GQO Powerful Pro Yakyuu 2013
That's a Konami one
An ongoing series too
On the Wii U this week in Japan
Sonic Lost World
Which I think came out here this week
Sonic Lost Meh
On the Nintendo 3DS
A bunch of Sonic stuff
Including the Sonic Lost World port over there
But also some little
Headphones and cute little stickers
And all that shit on the 3DS
And lastly the
PSP still getting a lot of stuff
Right now including that same
Baseball game from Konami
Diablok Lovers More
Blood
Yes that is the name of the game
Diablok Lovers More
Blood
And it does kind of look like
Oh god it looks like Twilight
As an anime video game
A ton of visual novel games
Nope
Nope to that one
Nope N-O-P-E
Alright Dar Sakura how about the UK
There's a few things
On the 21st which is already
The 21st there as of right now
Eldritch on PC
And Warfare on PC
On the 23rd Alien Rage for PS3
The 24th Dream Chamber
Just Dance Kids 2014
And Ace Attorney 5
For the 3DS
On the 25th
God tons of stuff
Batman Arkham Origins
There's even an iOS and Android
Version
There's Batman Arkham Origins
Blackgate on the handhelds
Naruto Shippuden
Ultimate Ninja Storm 3 Full Burst
Rise of Venice
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
And We Party You
Alright
Dirty We Party You
Or maybe
It's a question We Party You
How about this
Nintendo maybe you put out
A game on your new platform
It doesn't have the fucking name of the system on it
Oh ok
I would be with you there but remember
Wii Sports biggest game ever
Ever
No no no I have no problem with Wii Sports
That's fine
I'm talking about
I mean the U at the end
Like do we really need new Super Mario Brothers U
Or you know
Anything
Kind of just what they do though
The only system that didn't really do that was the GameCube
I mean even with the Super Nintendo
It was super everything
Super Adventure Island and Super Star Wars
And Super you know
But they were so much better than their previous versions
I mean come on
There wasn't really anything that was super that wasn't awesome
That was a pretty super system
The 8 bit the 16 bit everything looked pretty super
Thank you actdeft in the chat room says
Blank 64 everything was blank 64
On the N64
Superman 64 Mario Kart 64
Mario 64
This is just what Nintendo does
They beat that name into you
Or remember when they used to do it subtly
And this is more third parties but
They would use it subtly on the DS
Where it would be like you know
Something dual souls or something
Dragon Spirit or
Even the third parties got into it like there was that Castlevania game
Right there was DS
That game made me cry
Cry because you didn't like it or?
It was just not good
Alright
Let's get to a couple more news stories
For you guys and then the classic game of the week
Heck yeah
And also I'm looking at our chat room
Live.vognetwork.com if you want to join us in our chat room
And lots of talk
actdeft says super all the things
It's like it's pumpkin
Or something right now
So there you go
Live.vognetwork.com
Let's get into some stories
Alright so let's talk a little bit about
Games with Gold
And this was something that I was
Kind of meh I mean it's only two games a month
And stuff and I know a lot of direct comparisons with
PlayStation Plus
Which by the way folks
If you haven't jumped on this yet
Shadow of the Colossus is available on PlayStation Plus
I need to jump on that
This is Ico
Yes Ico was last month
I think it's still available
They cycle them through every now and then
But Shadow of the Colossus is on there now
And also
The what was it
The poker game from Valve is on there now
Or no not Valve
Telltale Games
The poker at the inventory 2
The second one was
Oh yeah I played that this week too for a little bit
I suck at poker that's what I learned
Yeah so those are available
Anyways this month
Of course there was Halo 3
And then I forgot the other game
That was coming out but they say
Though they are going to continue on with the
Program originally it was only supposed to go
Through the launch of the Xbox One
But they figured out that hey
You know what people like values so
They are going to keep on doing two games a month
So far
A lot of the games I already had but
You know okay
Yeah I mean it's cool that they are giving these away
It's hard to complain about free stuff
I'm going to
It is a little hilarious that they are giving away Halo 3
For free I don't expect them to give away Halo 4
But I mean come on meet me halfway here
Like maybe ODST
Or yeah I mean
Halo Reach
Yeah or Anniversary Edition
Because you know the games that are coming out
Like the Shadow of the Colossus
I think that was about a year
Or two old
And I mean Saints Row the Third
About two years old and it was already on
On there or hell Hitman Absolution
To be fair that is a little bit fuzzy
Math for Shadow of the Colossus because it is a remake
Of a much older game
I understand but the release of the HD version was
I'm with you I'm with you fair enough
I would be I would love to see
Like some Playstation 1 games on there
Or you know like Final Fantasy
Yeah they kind of stopped doing the PS1 games didn't they
You know like Final Fantasy or something
They gave away Tactics at one point I think that was on PSP
Yeah I think they might have given away one of the older Final Fantasy games too
Or they all went on sale or something
So I don't know
Alright let's see Nvidia
Doing an update to what's called the Geforce
Experience this is that gameplay
Optimization software and I've never used
This because I have the AMD
Or some ATI
Yeah I got a pop up this morning saying that I needed
To update that and I'm like shit I didn't even
Know I had it so okay
But I bring this up because one of the things
They're going to be adding to this is that they're going to be able
You're going to be able to capture gameplay
If you have a 600 or a 700 series card
So you can edit and you can upload
And of course even more people now
Streaming their games on Twitch I mean this is becoming
A real huge thing which is
You know as somebody who really loves independent broadcasting
I mean I do kind of love it but at the same time
I'm like wow
It's going to be even more like competition
For watching
Like if everybody's streaming who's watching
So it's going to be very interesting but I do love that it makes it
Very easy at least
And let's see there's also what they call shadow mode
Which will follow your gameplay and it will
Save the last 10 to 20 minutes of action
In a temporary buffer on your hard drive
And if you hit a hotkey you can save
The buffered footage and that way
Your stuff doesn't pile up on the hard drive
There you go that's basically what we have on the next gen
Yeah what the next gen consoles are doing they're starting to catch
This up a little bit
But it's 10 to 20 minutes and not you know
I would imagine it's whatever you have available
On your drive too
So
Most likely
So there it is
Some folks are going to be checking that out
I'm pretty sure ATI is only a matter of time before they have a response
To this and their own thing
If they don't already
Exactly
I can't watch your channel because I'm streaming on my channel
Yeah
It's going to be that
Eventually there's not going to be anyone to view these channels
Because everyone's going to be streaming their games
And clogging the internet
And it's all one site too
Which is fascinating to me
I mean I know there's like Ustream and a couple others
But it's really fascinating to me that like one company
Has such a huge share of this
Clearly they must be using those
Microsoft cloud azure servers
Or something
Alright let's travel to a time
When gaming was a little more simple
If you wanted to see a hot new video game
You had to go over to your rich friend's house and watch
That's what you had to do
You had to sit on the couch and watch them play
Or if you wanted to see streaming
You had to do it through a VHS tape
If you wanted to see streaming you went to the lake
Alright
It is the classic game of the week
Every week Dark Sakura steps into the gaming vault
And finds a game that she thinks
Hey brat
Get off my lawn and play this game
Get off my lawn, get off twitch
Sit down, blow on this cartridge
And check this game out
Dark Sakura what is the classic game of the week
The classic game of the week is Adventures of Lolo
Which I think Dan suggested as a joke
But it actually was kind of fun
This game was great
It had good music
Why would you suggest it as a joke
I was just like pick something Dan
He's like I don't know Adventure Lolo
I'm like okay sure
Here's the music
Even Loki's head bobbing a little bit
I play this game
I know I used to love this game
It is a great game
Anyway in the Adventures of Lolo
Basically his sweetie Lala
Is captured by the villain
King Egger
So Lolo's like bitch you give me back my woman
And he watches right up to the castle
And kicks the door down
And says I'm not taking your shit
You know I don't seem to remember it going that way
That's my version so much
The Dark Sakura version
And then he sets the castle on fire
Yeah
And then he and Lolo
Make little round babies
Lala
Somehow Lolo became
Gay in your version
Would that be
Auto-gay
And that's how
Kirby was made
God
We're going to break
I'm done
So yeah you basically go through the stages
You get harder and harder
Every four rooms you get to go upwards
Closer to his victory
His sweet sweet victory
And if you get stuck on a stage
You have the option of dying
Which was great
God dammit death
So you commit suicide when you're done with life
SSG100Matt in our chatroom at live.vognitework.com
Says Lolo the game with its own suicide button
Exactly
So you can destroy the enemies
And shoot at them and you turn them into movable eggs
And when you shoot the egg
It disappears
Now the game was produced
I'm sorry developed by HAL Laboratory
And published by HAL America
For the NES
And it came out on April 20th
The day after my birthday
Remember it everybody and get me stuff
420 it's not hard to remember
In 1989
And it came out in Europe in February 1991
So they had to wait two whole years for Lolo
It is now out
On Wii's Virtual Console
As of June 8th, 2007
And August 6th, 2007 in the PAL regions
It is the only game
In the series not to have come out in Japan
However Lolo 2 and Lolo 3 did
It's just a fun little adventure game
It's cute
It gets kind of frustrating
Later on
But it's a fun game
And it's one that's pretty much held up
I played probably more of Lolo 2
Than the first one
Or the third one
Because by the third one it came out I was like I don't care
But I always had fun with it
I've always loved little
Spatial puzzle games like that
You know the little enemies running around
Well like your gaming week you've been playing Bejeweled and
Fractal it's a bunch of the same type of
Puzzle games
I fucking love Fractal
I wish it was 10 years later
So I could do Fractal
As my classic game
It's like instant fucking classic you have no idea
Going back to Lolo and Lala
It's a fun game
I mean basically
Like I said Lolo 2 and Lolo 3
Came out in 90 and 91 respectively
There's a Game Boy version that came out in 1994
That came out
With the same name Adventures of Lolo
In Japan it came out as Lolo no
No
Lolo no Daibouken
Lolo and Lala did appear
In Kirby's Dreamland Rob
And in Kirby Superstar
As Lolo and Lala
And in Kirby's Avalanche
As Lolo and Lala where they are antagonists
I thought it was funny
That you were making the Kirby joke earlier
But act deaf yeah I was bringing up that same thing in our chat room
And it was making me think as well
I was like well yeah both these games were made
Both Kirby and Lolo were HAL laboratories
And if you think about it too
I always thought that the little
Blue critter in
Guardian Legend was Lolo
Yes but it's
It's not
It's from that shooter game
Not Xanax
I keep thinking like Xanax
Is it Xanax?
Yeah I think it's Xanax
The little lunar lander
Yeah that's what I thought
But before I was familiar with Xanax
I often thought that it was
Lolo
I mean I guess having a blue puff ball
With legs you know
You can't get too uh
Too far away from that so
So anyway that's uh
According to act deaf they also appeared in the Kirby anime
So yay
So are you
Oh you're looking it up?
Well I'm trying to remember what that little thing was called
And somebody in the chat room
What is the name of the little blue fucker?
I don't know how to spell Xanax that's why
It's Z-A-M-A-C
That was the game
What was that little fucker called?
Yeah his name was little fucker
It was, that's Lolo and Lala's
True uh, that's Lolo's love child
They're twins I swear to god
But they're from different companies cause Xanax was an
FCI game
Or compile, it was compile
But FCI published it
Wasn't FCI like the publisher?
Or was compile, compile was the developer
Compile developed, FCI published
In North America
In Japan Xanax was published by
Pony Canyon, but you know what the segment is about
That's what Pony Canyon has done
PORN
At least they're not pink pineapple
You know
You were talking about the classic game of the week
Adventures of Lolo and now we're talking about
PORN
Only here at Orange Lones area
Well I'm sure somewhere there's a Lolo shaped vibrator or something
I don't know
This is after you made Lolo gay and set the castle on fire
No! Auto gay
Alright whatever
He is only, he's uh
Self sexual
Or would it be auto sexual?
Are you done?
I'm trying to think of what the politically correct term would be now
I think it's auto sexual
I'm gonna be thinking about this all during the break
I just love that it's to this music
PORN
Hey this is a wonderful clip for the highlight show
I love you guys okay?
Alright
Cause I wouldn't have thought up all this fucked up shit if not for you
I love you too are you fucking done?
I'm fucking done god damn it
The classic game of the week
I think it was Adventures of Lolo
But it might have been Xanac
So
It's always the guardian legend every episode
Alright that's it
We're gonna take a break
Yes I agree with Queen Simia
Just narcissistic
Stay classy part A
Live.vognetwork.com
Alright and what's this?
Dark Tetsuya says wow it took an hour and a half
To get to the porn talk. Sit down be quiet
Alright we're gonna take a quick break
Guys when we come back we have plenty more of
Orange Lounge Radio up next
Rapid Fire News the Fugal Question of the Week
Emails and your phone calls
1-877-GAME-OLR
When we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio
Right after this
Music
Welcome back everybody to Orange
Lounge Radio we are
live on this Sunday night October
the 20th of 2013 with the
524th episode
of our show you know next week
that means it's episode 525
which might mean something
but cause it's a multiple of 25
and it's a palindrome
but I guess we don't really do anything to celebrate
I don't know what else to do
it would be the Halloween show
I would say we could do like a specially themed Halloween show
but we never have so why start now
I don't know
what would we do
sit here and play Silent Hill during the show
I don't know if that would be as effective
alright go to our channel
live.vognetwork.com some people
guessing the songs we were playing during the break
now for you folks listening on the podcast
obviously you can't hear the copyrighted songs
we played during break but tonight for the
live participants I promised some obscure
stuff cause I didn't want to just play like
Mega Man and Zelda and all the stuff
you guys know but I did some
slightly obscure stuff tonight and for
those playing at home like if you're not in chat
but you are listening live you had Terranigma
started that off the middle
song nobody got that's because it was from
Cold Sept which was the
that was that card battle game meets Monopoly
I should have noticed that because you know I remember
you playing that game yeah I'm like the one guy
that liked that game and then the
third song that we played tonight was from
Intelligent Cube or IQ
remember that on the Playstation 1
there you go those are the songs we had there
and I was looking at the chatroom
props to Orange Wright I'll say your name on
air because you got he's the only one that
knew 2 of the 3 which is a pretty good score
I didn't see anybody else really shout things out there
let's see
also in the chatroom at live.vognetwork.com
before we get back into the news here
Akuma JP says I have a request
for Sky please do the
Cookie Monster voice and I'm like
I don't do a when did I do a Cookie
Monster voice I've done the Grover
I've done Grover I've done near
far
near like that whole thing I've done the
Grover voice but then I'm like what do I
say as Cookie Monster and Akuma JP says
I don't know porn porn porn
and I'm thinking is he thinking of that
song the internet is for
porn like is he thinking of that one that's
not really Cookie Monster that's that's
the rip off Avenue Q style
thing I don't know I'm still mad I missed
that when it was in town I know you know
it'll come back you know what they have at our local
theater down in Folsom right now
they have
the stage production of
Evil Dead the Musical oh nice
with the splash zone with all the blood
I'm like dude that's awesome
yeah I've seen the shadow cast
troop here does that for Repo the genetic opera
with the movie that's pretty awesome
and then I was looking actually another
big stage show this time of year the Rocky Horror
show and that was also brought
up during the break is that Rageinator said
he found this game that has my
name written all over it it's the actual
Rocky Horror video game that they
made there was actually two I don't know if you guys know this
there were two Rocky Horror show games
neither were the picture show
I think they're both based on the play the first
one was like on the Commodore 64
and Apple 2e it was kind of like an adventure
game where you walk around and you're trying to find like the
transducer or something you can play as Brad or Janet
it's not good it's really not good
like there's a reason why most people
telltale games should do an adventure
game based on it wouldn't that be something
well in the 90s the late 90s
there was a revival of Rocky
Horror show
in London yes and they did
a CD-ROM game
inspired by the 80s classic
that went with that and it also
wasn't very good because it was inspired
by the 80s classic which in turn
that was not good the one with the blonde Frank
yes yeah yeah because
not everybody wants to look like Tim Curry necessarily
for the record before I
forget coming up in a couple of
weeks at my college
there's going to be another production of the Rocky Horror show
oh really it's a touring production
I'll get the info for you I sent you the hairspray
one this is the time if you're going to
time warp now's the time to do it I did also send you one
for hairspray I do remember seeing that
that's right I know how you love
John Waters things alright I do love John Waters
things but like let's be real they're never
going to do Pink Flamingos live unless it involves
unless it involves drag queens
which then anything goes
right maybe we can write to
Peaches Christ alright maybe
I'm sure I'm sure
she's done some John Waters movie
but anyway this is not a show
about John Waters films as badly
as I wish it was sometimes this
is a show about video games and we have some
rapid fire news to get to
sadly no John Waters movies being made into
video games but I think there's some other stuff
um so yeah there's
been some news regarding the Oculus
Rift um the consumer version
of the Oculus Rift
still no firm date on that
yet but it's supposed to be out sometime
next year um
one of the other things they're looking at is maybe in the future
also switching those displays
that are inside of it to 4K displays
so that would probably look pretty realistic
especially for some PC games
um so that's pretty exciting
um
anyways
there's a brand new game from one of the
um designers that used to
work at Harmonix and it's
kind of silly it's actually uh this
indie studio called No Goblin
and they have a game called
Roundabout and Roundabout's basically
this limo driving game where
you're a chauffeur of a limo and you have to get through
busy streets but the limo is always
spinning and so you have to
dodge traffic you do
run over a lot of people to like do different
things like you know deliver kittens
to orphans or you know
uh run over the orphans on the way
why does that why am I
reminded of that the kittens are safe
why am I reminded of that no breaks
valet game it's sort of the only
thing to play on the Ouya it's sort of like an evolution
yeah of that
or revolution if you will
uh it looks
it looks silly and um
I don't know I think that
yeah it's it's due out next
year um although they're taking
pre-orders for it right now at ten dollars
normally it's gonna be fifteen and that includes a digital
art book and soundtrack and
I guess it's like seventies themed as well it's set in
um it looks funny
so yeah definitely check that
video if you haven't seen it yet and
uh last but not least there's a brand
new Minecraft mod and
it's involved or involving
quantum physics it's uh
called Qcraft
and allows I guess
players to do different things including like um
they have different blocks with quantum
entanglements um
I guess they're saying that uh
observer dependency characteristics
see this is all stuff that's
over my head um
cool
I don't really know what exactly that means since
I'm not really into quantum physics but uh
I like Minecraft
mods so let's let's dabble
with that
alright why not
Minecraft will be one of the
launch games on Playstation 4 right?
yeah that is kind of neat
so quantum physics in uh
Playstation 4 maybe?
alright let's go on to some other news stories
uh Pokmon X and Y I talked about earlier
in the show my first uh couple
couple hours in that world well some people
some people already beat the game
Shane if you're out there listening
and others I think ActDeft was saying he was on the
final four well there was a lot of
people there was a lot of people playing X and Y
over four million copies in
two days moved of Pokmon X and Y
Nintendo's going
bankrupt you guys the Wii U's gonna
bankrupt Nintendo everybody
they're gonna be making games
for the Playstation 99 cent iPhone
games y'all
yeah four million copies
of Pokmon X and Y it's just these
games print money there they go
and uh yeah uh they say
by the way that Pokmon X and Y tracking
ahead of Pokmon White 2
and Black 2 by more than 70%
well that's because White 2
and Black 2 were obvious cash-ins this
at least is a little more you know effort of a
cash-in let's be real alright
uh other stuff I love that
they are still making DLC
for LittleBigPlanet and LittleBigPlanet
is getting DLC in the form of
Nightmare Before Christmas
because it is that time of year and
lots of people love this game and it's adorable
the little sack boy in the uh Jack
Skellington in the Sally outfit like I
single-handedly want to go back and play this game
for this Rob you don't even have to play LittleBigPlanet
you can play LittleBigPlanet Karting and still have
that stuff in there too nice you did
see what Victoria happened to mention
yes it's the 20th anniversary
I know you know how I want to
celebrate this I want to bust out my
laserdisc player and watch
my laserdisc version I want to go over there
and smack her for reminding me of that fact
you know what you know what you know what
that means that we were out when all the cool shit came out
that's true that's true well I just
want to say though that according to the LittleBigPlanet
website the character is actually
named you ready for it?
Sack Skellington
shit alright uh
one more so what is Sally called
Saki I close the
tab because I stopped caring I'm gonna buy
I'm gonna buy it anyway
okay calm down
calm your tits calm
them alright soccer
is freaking out because we have
another story this is two weeks in a row now we're
talking about ColecoVision
because last week we
talked about that whole Kickstarter thing
and I kind of said my
honest piece that I don't think they're gonna make their funding
but you know I hope prove me
wrong please do I would not be sad
however we have something else this is different
this is a different retro device
that's gonna bring back the ColecoVision
it's a retro hardware company
called AtGames and they're
gonna be launching these devices that are based on the
ColecoVision they already make Atari
and Sega Genesis based handhelds so
I'm assuming these are those shitty
little plug and play things you
see just littering one of the aisles
at Target right so soon you're gonna have a
shitty little ColecoVision thing too
but you know it won't be shitty because it's ColecoVision
I love my ColecoVision Rob
uh so there's that
so that is coming I guess soon all we know
they've acquired the rights
that they've got the deal we just don't know
when we don't know how but you can
assume soon I
would think they're trying to get this on the shelves before the holiday
because you've got you know people in
their mid 30s like Darsakra and me
who remember this shit from when
we were kids and it would be a great
thing to find you know under
the Christmas tree or menorah or whatever
under the menorah yeah there's a
menorah on top of a ColecoVision isn't that where
you put the gifts
that's how it works right where else are
they supposed to go no no
you have the Hanukkah bush
the gelt goes in my belly
you know what though
it is kind of funny that Hanukkah
is the same week that Thanksgiving is
so I'm gonna make sweet potato pumpkin
latkes oh my god Hanukkah is that early this year
I know it's because
see they don't believe in solar calendars and
Judaism back in ancient
Israel we had the moon
stop complicating everything
you know what I didn't invent
I didn't invent the lunar calendar
these guys are just high maintenance that's what it really is
high maintenance
and I say that with love put the
angry emails down I tease because I love
I tell you what was absolutely hilarious was
when Christmas and Hanukkah were the same week
it was a nightmare in my house
because we were also moving
we had
blue stars and Christmas
presents everywhere so once in a while there's video game
talk on this show
Darsakra
oh yeah I got stories
well how about
a petition that is out
for the Grand Theft Auto 5 PC
version and it's at
change.org so you know it's an annoying piece of shit
however
you know what my problem with
change.org is all the damn emails
so anyway
they are over
600,000 supporters
to have a PC version released
and they have generated
as far as
the sales of the game goes
over a billion what was it in three days
so yeah it's made quite a bit of money
so there are also
sources in the industry saying that there should be a PC
version out early 2014
I was going to say
they're already making a PC version
they just haven't announced it yet because why would they cannibalize
the sales of the current versions
because people like to jump on bandwagon
especially if they know it's
going to happen
who doesn't like to come back and say
I was right
I totally called that
you guys I totally called that
how about all of us who said we totally called it without
signing a fucking petition
they're going to make Grand Theft Auto 6 you guys
I fucking called it here on OLR
also if you happen
to pre-order
Zelda A Link Between Worlds
you get a musical chest
it comes in a nice big box
now granted
this is
just for the US
this is buying the bundle version
the 3DS XL that comes with the game
it has
a golden Triforce cover
and A Link Between Worlds loaded on the console
and this was
already linked
from a
Gamestop Black Friday ad
so as far as
any type of European release
Game actually did confirm
that they're getting the
musical treasure chest as a pre-order bonus
so all of our friends
in the UK you're not screwed
this time
and
well
I don't know if I'm happy or sad Rob
because
well you're always happy to be in my presence
I know that
you know what
we have a little bit more news about the Mass Effect franchise
that will have a brand new story
completely unrelated to
The Shepherd or The Crew
or
any of them
so basically Bioware wants to take it in a new
direction
and they have said again
doesn't necessarily relate to The Shepherd
events whatsoever
but it has to be
Mass Effect Universe it's not just a spin-off
it has to be a part of the series
so
but they said something similar
6 months ago and we all
accept it then right?
yeah
I don't know how I feel because
you know I used to back in the day I used to want
a Mass Effect MMO I thought it would be
fantastic to play in that universe
to go around and hang out on the
different worlds and do stuff and maybe if it was something
kinda
kinda more like that
where it wasn't just all the human centric
bullshit that was you know Mass Effect 3
then I would be completely
okay with that but at this point
I don't necessarily trust what Bioware
is going to do so I'm probably
still gonna buy it because I'm a whore
sigh
I don't know
alright
I'm still looking forward to it
because you know it's Mass Effect and
it'll be great you know what I want
Turians the game
Queen Simeon is in our chatroom
at live.vognetwork.com and says still needs
Turians and Krogan
Alan Alchemy says it can't
be a sequel that takes place in the
same universe unless it's literally thousands
of years later because otherwise they'll have to
pick a canon ending between the red blue
green horse shit and that would be bad
well they did pick a canon ending
for part 2 didn't they
you wouldn't have had a 3 if they went with a bad ending
and 2 everyone dies
oh my god have you watched that
oh yeah it's great it's hilarious I mean it's sad
but it's hilarious the YouTube of the
Mass Effect 2 bad ending or whatever which is
the everybody dies ending OMG spoilers
for a 4 year old game
they have the shepherd the thing that makes
that video funny is they have like the ugliest shepherd
possible at least the one I saw
have you seen the the ones that
that have hacked it to give shepherd
garris a skeleton
yes that was creepy
there's another one that did that to give Jacob
garris a skeleton and they just got this huge mouth
it's so fucking weird
um and
yeah raginator asks so no
more garris they
won't garris all the things I won't garris
all the things does this make dark sakura
a sad panda dark sakura is kind of getting
over some of her attachment in the
fandom so and also speaking
of herself in the third person
so at this point I would actually
like a new series that has
characters that I'm attached to but not like
singularly attached to I would like
to be able to explore more options
instead of having just the one freaking awesome option
so
alright I'm sorry I wasn't into
lizard man alright are we ready
to get to the foogle question of the week I
sure hope so because it's about that time
it's very
cool
haha
you take
facebook you take google plus you slam
those words together you get foogle it's the
foogle question of the week where we ask a question of our
facebook and google plus communities
and uh starting on facebook
tonight with some of these answers to this question
two words
cookie clicker
have you heard of it do you know the cookie
clicker dark sakura no
you click and it gives you cookies
I want cookies for real you hire
grandma to make cookies for you
no and then like you get like cookie
cloners la la la la I don't wanna
alright well anyhow cookie
clicker is a free to play web game that has been found
to be pretty addicting for some and it's
inspired parodies like I don't know if you saw but
there's a clicking bad
which is it replaces cookie clickers with
bad references so you're cooking meth
and you get like rvs
and abandoned trailers and all this
and bathtubs so anyway
uh so there's all
these parodies of cookie clicker
so what we wanna and if you've been listening to horde house
at all we've talked extensively
about cookie clicker and I'll just leave it at that
um anyhow
uh do you have a
free to play web game that
maybe you're embarrassed or proud to
admit you've spent way too much time
what is the game and share the link
with the rest of our listeners if you want links to these games
check out our facebook and our google
plus page so here we go
unfolded raptor says I've never been able to
get into facebook games but I spent many hours
on super mario brothers crossover and
happy wheels there used to be this really
fun flash game on disney.com based on
their version of tarzan many years ago
it was really fluid and fun to play I was a kid
but I'd still go back and play it now
uh our good buddy from koopa
club renee says there
are a few free to play games I've enjoyed over the years
but the best one being the kingdom
of loathing simple interface
much like clicking bad but totally
aloof and light hearted fantasy story
especially when you can be a
pasta mancer or a saucer roar
and it's been running for 10 years even I've
played the kingdom of loathing for a hot minute like I
think a lot of people check this game out and it's a
fun one I haven't oh you should check it out
I think you'd have fun maybe alright
degenerate johnny says I'm actually proud to say
that I play my vegas slots on
facebook it's a game in which you play
slot games and table games in order to earn
points that can be spent on real
vegas rewards like a drink at the
mirage or complimentary rooms at the
mgm grand ps I'm at
10 million cookies on the cookie clicker
mobile app you're welcome rob
I got to 15 million suck
it uh code man
says well it's a web based
and mobile game robot unicorn
attack oh god
love it love it this
game is beyond addicting and after robot
unicorn attack 2 was released they added
a feature where you gain levels unlock new
abilities and you can customize your unicorn
plus online pvp matches
I didn't know they put pvp
in the game oh my god that's awesome
and now that song is stuck in my head
freaking erasure always
I wanna be well in robot unicorn
attack 2 you can play the never ending story
they have like dlc and you can do the never ending
story you know what as awesome as that sounds it
has to always be erasure every time
it does it really does
have you
played robot unicorn attack
what
of course I have oh ok
how good are you at it
pretty good ok I need to read the rest
of the fugal answers here to
this song here ok
I actually super love this video too
I just wanna say this is gonna be so
hipster of me but I don't give a fuck
I liked this song before it was in
that game well yeah but you
like erasure for the record
I love erasure myself I've always loved erasure
you know I think they're doing a new
album they just had one out
did it just come out I wonder if they're doing a new tour
that's what I wanted to see I'm pissed
off cause I had to say no to a pet shop boys concert
for free cause I had
fucking homework to do
worst day ever it was in
oakland and everything alright
critical myth says at one point
there was a sardicus clicky game on
facebook I was fairly addicted to
and I was playing a game called equilibrium
on my vita for weeks earlier
this year
raginator says to be honest I never
got into the free to play web game scene
wah wah
now I know
it's not exactly the same thing and this answer really
doesn't fit the question but the closest thing that sorts
of fits is pc gaming in general be it
on steam game for windows live or whatever
and the vod community already well knows
I've traditionally been a console gamer and a console
gaming fanboy since 1981
and for the longest time would have scoffed
the idea of pc gaming it wasn't
until the theft last year on my original laptop
my ps3 and tv that I
got into pc gaming albeit
begrudgingly if only because I couldn't afford to replace
my tv and ps3 now
I thoroughly enjoy pc gaming
well raginator go check out some of these links people
are leaving and you can fill up your pc with
crap
uh austin s says
oh and I'm sure we've all played this one being music game
fans we are ffr
flash flash revolution it was a web
based step mania game I used
to play it a lot back in the day but it's dated now
fair enough
alright let's go on to google plus
we have a couple answers there
actdeft says mostly facebook
games I used to play them a lot but I
eventually got tired of them like song pop or even
you don't know jack I do play the occasional
bejeweled bullets and tenders friends
and lastly
rettertainment says yes the sims on facebook
I never spent a cent on it and got
really far in it until I got a girlfriend
and started having sex in the game
then I got oddly disinterested
weird I also started playing
the sims freeplay on my ipad until I found
that I couldn't play it at work because I wasn't connected to the internet
that's stupid the game
is downloaded on my ipad and the file size is
mighty large why can't my save be
on the ipad as well
I guess because it's harder to take your money
if you're not connected to the internet
alright bye erasure
I'll miss you
you totally should use this every time
for the segment now I kind of want to
alright there it is our frugal
question of the week I'll quickly
ask are there any free to play games
maybe that weren't brought up that you've been getting into
lately or even in the past
cookie clicker is definitely mine they have
an iphone it's not official though
it's a follow up to horde house
the iphone one is cookie
clickers and it's a
knock off game it's still pretty good
but it's not official there is an official one
in the making just to say
I can't remember really
the last free one that I did
because remember
when I got my ikade
I kind of went on a purchasing spree
which I probably shouldn't have done
oops
yeah all the ones
that I actually still have on my phone
are
ones I paid for
I mean I'm actually looking at
my folder now
I have a robot
unicorn and I played for that
droplets I paid for that
yeah everything
on here I paid for
so no nothing free
Loki what about you
I don't think there's really been anything that I've played
for free aside from that time
when I was doing the whole ready
player one thing where I had to play that really shitty
garage sale
game on Facebook
oh god but I didn't necessarily
want to play that it was
did that guy really win that DeLorean or whatever
yeah he did there was a guy that won the DeLorean
because he got
the world record in Joust
I think of the 2600 wow
alright grats to him I guess
alright more
stories coming your way up now Loki
yeah no
no DeLorean for me that's right
it probably would have been more
you wouldn't have wanted to
pay the taxes on it
well the taxes and then on top of that
servicing the thing the only service center that
does DeLoreans
at least around here is in LA
so that wouldn't be very convenient
um okay
so let's talk a little bit about the PlayStation 4
hey you want to check out a PlayStation
4 well there's going to be some demo kiosks
coming soon to
Sony stores, GameStop, Target
Walmart and Best Buy
and uh
they have a website that you can actually go to
to see where they are at if
you go to it's the experience
playstation.com and
you put in your zip code and they'll show
you a map with all the different
stores that are
you know supplying it
and um
we have none there is absolutely
none in our area so I noticed
Best Buy is making a lot of room for both the
PlayStation 4 and the Xbox although on the whole
on the whole it seems like Best Buy
has really scaled back their gaming sections
I guess in
favor of other stuff and some of the things
we've been hearing about the company you know on
CNN or other new sites where the margins
are bigger cause gaming isn't it
that's for sure I guess so
so yeah and then
it's a little
I don't understand this
to be honest and this is basically
you can pre-order
digital downloads of
PlayStation 4 launch titles
look if you're willing to give them your
credit card they'll take it on the
PlayStation 3 and
guess what you get for doing that
no discount
so why the
fuck would you do that because you want
to be able to play that shit day one
even though if you're gonna have to
go and download it anyways so
go and pick up your PlayStation 4 somewhere unless
Amazon's bringing it to you let's put it this way
ok yeah I know that you can partially download
the game and then you can start playing it
once you've downloaded the game but
the thing is these
downloads are fucking huge remember we
mentioned on a couple shows back they had
this NBA Ultimate
Fan Pack or Super Fan Pack
or something like that it's basically digital versions of the
current gen and next gen versions of the game
the next gen versions of the game
were like 60 gigabytes to download
and I'm
sorry but there's
you want to do that just go to retail
and buy the game yeah you may have to pay taxes
on it but just go
buy it or hey here's a wonderful
idea maybe wait until Black Friday and see if they
discount that shit
might be something you know
I don't know there's just no reason
I can see the pre-order
a game unless you get something
I mean cause so far they haven't really said
anything it says I guess the only
game that you can pre-order that seems like you get
something for is
Warframe which is free
so I don't understand that at all
but it's free and I guess you get some
in-game money and exclusive weapon skin
so sure why not go pre-order that if you're
going to give it to PlayStation 4
in case you want to play it cause it's free so
but as far as
Nack you know
Killzone or something like that
unless there's charge I mean like
you know $53.99 or
some sort of discount there I just don't see
a reason to pre-order
anything for a
digital download I mean
fuck if you want to do a digital download
and you decide that you want to do that
do it at launch day make that decision on launch day
not necessarily
Well it just goes back to that old thing we were talking about
way back when the Xbox One was rumored to have
all these restrictions it's like what's the benefit
of going digital? It's not like they're not going to have
a digital copy for you it's not like
they're going to sell out a digital copy
of a game I mean
it just doesn't make any sense
Alright they just want
a really easy way for you to hit the button
and they can charge the card and give you
make another sale really easy
that's what this is all about nothing more
I think you're thinking too much about it
Logie
Alright well this game fell off
our radar years ago and
the last time we were talking about this video game
I think we were exclusively a show about
music based video games
this game was being developed for an arcade
release in 2005
I don't know if you guys remember when we were talking about
a game called Neon FM
remember this? Because it had
like freeze pop and it had some really other
like kind of questionably
good songs in it well it's been a
long time obviously and this game has kind of
reinvented itself a little bit because
Unit E is the
group now that's putting this arcade cabinet out
I think I heard a rumor once that at one point
Betson who ended up doing the DDR
cabinets years later was going to do this
game and they didn't so now Unit E
is doing this and it's no longer
a dance game that's the other big change
it is now a I guess
to me it would strike me more as like pop
music because it's got the big
circular pads that you hit
it was originally supposed to be played
the same way except the dance pad would look like
what that pad looks like right there
it was like 3 on the bottom 2 on the top it wasn't
like your typical DDR dance pad
it was like Beatmania with your feet
right
so yeah so Neon FM
is apparently now like a thing
there's a video out there you can
see it on YouTube and so forth
but is girls
butts in it and it is because I can see
that in the screenshot apparently it is
the song is so
awful that song is horrible
but I think by now it probably gets the joke
vote right no
it's still awful so apparently
it is still on target for release this
year to show up in arcades
that is if you still have an arcade near
you that contains games that don't shoot
out tickets I will say the cabinet
does look nice I hope this does show up in an arcade
you know what the best ticket game ever is
Giant Tetris
I would say either Spider Stomp or
Giant Tetris no the one where
you have those little like the balls that
you see in the McDonald's ball pit or whatever and you
throw them at the screen and break things on the monitor
ok that is pretty cool that one is a lot of fun too
because it involves breaking shit but I still love
Giant Tetris Giant Tetris is like a close
second yeah
but Neon FM no
word if Neon FM will shoot out tickets I don't
believe it does but that's all
they had to do if they wanted to make this game super popular
just put a little ticket dispenser in it
and the better you do on a song the more tickets you get
yeah well being that
based off step mania they could probably
do that or if you play that horrible girls butt
songs it will actually take your tickets
as like a penalty
no if you play the girls
butts then you get like
kicked in the crotch I would laugh
I would really laugh if they had
like a game like that where the
tickets would go in and out depending on how
well you did I guess it would get all
fucked up though because you know if
you tore it off
then it goes back in well they should be in like a
glass case that you can't get into
until the very end or it cuts it
or something like it should be like
look I'm going to give you all these no I'm not
I'm going to give you all these no I'm not have you ever
worked at an arcade of course
not I did
why would I subject myself to that bullshit
one of my two of my first jobs involved
arcade games and I know for a damn fact
someone would figure out how to get in there
my minimum wage job I already told you my minimum wage
job was I worked at a video store and we rented
porn and that was awesome
anyhow
alright
whatever dark sorrow
what do you have for us for the news I have some shit
no um
blizzard has once again
changed the name of
what was blizzard all stars
and is now heroes
of the storm
I don't know why the fuck they're calling it that
but yeah they even are quoted saying yep we
changed it again so
um basically
they've also said set aside whatever you
think you knew about blizzard all stars
and it's supposed to be um
more about it will be revealed at
Blizzcon November 8th and
9th and uh
there apparently is a trailer
online so look for it
I kind of
am like whatever although I have to
say that the picture on here of the
um whoever the
uh orc is
what am I saying orc uh
whatever the fuck they're called
god I played World of Warcraft for how long
that looks like an orc yeah
orc I'm just thinking ogre for some reason
oh no it's an orc no the orc just
looks absolutely hilarious so
it's got a little cartoony vibe to it I will say
though I actually think the new name is much better
Blizzard all stars is a little dinky dinky
yeah I mean I wonder if it's going to be
cutesy like that though it opens it up to a
bigger audience too because they're going to have to compete against
all these other mobas that are already out there but
you know I think um
it's going to be interesting because I think
uh the heroes of the storm
or whatever has the potential to draw
in a whole new audience to this
you know with their built in warcraft audience
and the people that are running the hearthstone and all this
I think it's going to be very interesting to see how
that plays out I might check it out I've just been
a little bit burned on all things
blizzard I finally uninstalled curse
did you? I did
reminds me of playstation all stars
well yeah but it's not going to play anything like that
it's going to be more like maybe that's why they changed the name
because it's going to be it's basically
league of legends which is ironic because
I would argue that it's not
final fantasy 14 or any of those games
that wow has lost its players
to it's to league of legends
I think wow's probably lost more players to league of legends
than anything else so
and sucking
it's interesting that they're going to
kind of have their own answer to league
of legends now so we'll see how it works
by the way can I ask you about something not to go on a horde house tangent
but I'd love to know what you think
what did you think about the uh
siege of orgrimmar ending
I like that it was different
if you were alliance or horde
but here's the thing
I hate to keep comparing it
but I can't help myself like times
have changed right like it's cool that you
get a two and a half minute cinematic or whatever
when you beat the game but over in final fantasy
14 like that ending was seriously like
15 minutes long and it was very satisfying
and it was just
I don't know like it kind of just made the warcraft
endings look a little bit like
oh that's all you get for
putting up with all the abuse you take in LFR
but as far as like you know
what went down story wise
I don't know it's kind of obvious
well I mean we knew he was going down but I was actually
a little bit surprised at who took over
I wasn't at all
but I was actually
a little bit more surprised with
Douchebag with Varian
so that was a little bit more what surprised me
well I was also a little bit surprised that Jaina was so bloodthirsty
in the ending too cause she's
they're really trying to make her the alliance
answer to Sylvanas
they were really trying to do that
it just doesn't suit the character I mean it didn't surprise me
given you know having your whole town blown up
but at the same time
it just seemed out of character for her
anyway too much wow
no no no I wanted to ask because
that's fair it's a video game
it is a video game we can talk about it
you don't like it email us
mailbag at orangesontrader.com stop talking about that stupid game
alright Loki
so Ubisoft
has adjusted
their financials and basically
have deemed Splinter Cell
Blacklist and Rayman Legends
under performers
and they said you know we've had games that were released
for which we anticipate
today lower sales than
we anticipated when we first gave our targets
and already released games
of course such as Splinter Cell
and Rayman and others
you know also
probably doesn't help too as we mentioned earlier
they delayed Watch Dogs and the crew
so
I don't know what could they have done
better
I just don't think there was a lot of interest
in Splinter Cell Blacklist like they thought
like everyone was kind of hyped up about it
I think at E3 and it was just kind of
eh you know
maybe because that's when the Grand Theft Auto
train started or Saints Row 4
coming out around the same time and stuff
I don't know
maybe it's just I know the reviews
weren't that fantastic for Blacklist
Rayman Legends looked good
but I guess a lot of people
you know it would have been a better February
title I think I think people saw right through
what they did with Rayman Legends I think
it's not that like pissing off the Nintendo
fanboys had that big an impact but I think
a lot of people saw right the people that would
tend to buy games on day one see
right through the fact that it was a Wii U
game that was backed into the parking
spot of a 360 place I understand that
but what about the difference in
you know had they released it just on Wii U
what their potential sales are
and even now like with the Wii U
coming out you know version coming out in September
versus February that's still a lot
more you know months in between there
and systems being sold that there's
potential buyers I mean they kind
of had to do that it was the logical way
to do it they should have released the Wii U game
the way they'd always planned and then they should have
released the Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3
version later and called it
a gold edition or an enhanced
make it feel like an enhanced version
not a scaled back version
maybe or maybe just Nintendo
wasn't giving them any money to make it exclusive
and so you know there was no incentive
to do that maybe if they threw a little bit of
money their way then they could have had another
good exclusive title I don't think these games
are necessarily damned though because you know
it's gonna have staying power throughout the holidays
I think again I said the people who will
buy it on day one may be able to
see right through it but you're still gonna have it's a very
family accessible family friendly title
you know I think Rayman does very well
you know there's parents aren't
afraid to buy that for their younger kids so I
think that title can still tend to do well
throughout the holidays I don't know I gotta be honest
when I hear a story like this I think about
just a few months ago we heard that
Square Enix story about the guy getting up there
saying Tomb Raider underperformed
and we were all sitting here going are you high
Tomb Raider was like the best
that they've done in that series it's a very
long time it's a little different you know because with
like Splinter Cell that was the number four game
of the month in uh you know
August they're Madden Saints World 4
and Disney Infinity beating it out
um I mean
there's not a whole lot of other games
besides those
you know in the month
uh versus Tomb Raider which is like
one of the top selling games of the month
I think it was like one or two
you know cause Bioshock Infinite came out
that same month so
it's hard to tell I don't think
it outsold Bioshock Infinite but it was
definitely popular
um so I could
see the demand there for you know Tomb Raider
and stuff but I'm not seeing a lot of like people
saying oh I need copies of Splinter Cell because
it sold out you know it's just Tomb Raider
was like oh I need more Tomb Raider but
I don't
know we'll see maybe
they still have Rainbow Six
Patriots supposed to be coming
out at some point you know and um
I'm sure they'll
do well in the fourth quarter Satsuns Creed
is going to be a strong title for them and South Park
looks awesome so
they're not going to hurt too much oh
and Just Dance I mean that's definitely going to help
so they've got a pretty solid fourth
quarter
alright um moving on to
a story about a game
that is disappearing not because it underperformed
but because of license issues
Yoshi's Cookie I don't know if you
guys remember this game it was a game that was on the NES
it was actually what they don't
say in a lot of these articles about this story is that it
was also on the Super Nintendo because it's where I remember
playing it was it was on the Super Nintendo
but they released the Nintendo version of it
for the Virtual Console some
time ago Yoshi's Cookie
it got delisted this week it's
removed you will no longer be able to access it
on the Virtual Console it was pulled on
October 18th which bummer I
should have got it but the Super Nintendo version was better anyway
um
here's the thing about the game Yoshi's Cookie wasn't developed
by Nintendo it was developed by Bulletproof
Software Bulletproof made the
Tetris port for the Game Boy in 1989
which was you know huge
so that's why Nintendo you know trusted
them with the Yoshi stuff but
expired licenses being as
they are the game is no longer available
for sale
this is not the first game to be delisted
for similar reasons Konami's
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles no longer available
Irem did a version of R-Type that was on
the Virtual Console no longer there the Donkey Kong
Country trilogy also no
longer there so
if you didn't get this game I
guess you'll have to go steal it from a ROM
or go find it at
Garage Sale good luck to you
I guess I could lend it to somebody
do you have the Super Nintendo version because I like the
Super Nintendo version I don't believe I do actually
I might have to check I mean at this
point I don't know what I have
after playing the Super Nintendo version the NES version
felt kind of gimped you know
as sometimes happens there were a few titles like
that that were on both platforms
but anyway
it's not like it was that good of a puzzler
it was just kind of fun it had a
good versus mode in it
alright it is that time of the week
where we go to the mailbag where you guys
email us because every week you do
email us mailbag
at Orangelaunchradio.com
again our email is mailbag at
Orangelaunchradio.com DarkSakura is going to dive into
the email bag head first and pull out
oh an email or two or seven
that she feels like reading tonight
DarkSakura mail
well thanks
Flaco Jones sent us an email
that has a YouTube link in it
oh that means I've
got to pull up the mailbag too
I'll just leave it to everybody to listen to
um hey OLR since Mark Hamill has
retired from doing the Joker voice I wanted to
know what you thought of Troy Baker talking
I'm sorry taking over the role for the new Batman
Arkham game I had my doubts until
I heard a sample reading from
the killing joke that he gave
during the Arkham Origins panel
at New York Comic Con this guy is
super talented for sure I linked the
YouTube video if you have time to play it it's just
over a minute long and starts 2
minutes and 11 seconds in if
the link doesn't jump there right away what
do you all think? I've heard it's awesome
uh actually I remember
hearing about this but I didn't
hear the actual voice so
courtesy of Flaco Jones
memories
can be vile
perfect
repulsive little
brutes like children
I suppose
but
can we live without them
memories are what our reason
is based upon
if we can't face them we
deny reason itself
okay he gets a pass
that's good I like that
I've heard him do something else
and I'm trying to remember where I've heard that voice before
4 for you Troy Baker you go Troy Baker oh god he's a
hugely popular voice no I know but I'm trying
to remember um what
specifically I have recently
um well he was in Bioshock Infinite
which I haven't played
either
what would you have played that he
was in I'm trying to think
because he's done a ton of anime
hold on which I don't
really watch Fubbed Anime
Snow he was Snow in 13
Kid Icarus Uprising
you mentioned you played uh he's in that
um
Metal Gear Solid he's
Ocelot in 5
okay so he was Hawkeye
which I
have watched because of Jennifer
Hale oh and uh he's
James in Silent Hill 2 oh but only in the HD
version I think
oh then yeah which I didn't play
either oh well anyhow
moving on yeah well
oh no he was Robin
in Arkham City and Two-Face
so I knew he had been in another of
the games before Game Guru
in chat says wait that wasn't Mark Hamill
nope nope that was that was Troy Baker
good job yeah well I mean
I'd have to say that's pretty good if you know you can actually
get him confused with Mark Hamill
so um anyway
moving on um this
comes from um
Brian
and I did see Shane
say that he's sung with Akira Yamamoto's band
um okay
hi OLR I'm disappointed
with current gen Star Trek games
Star Trek Legacy was released on
360 N06 it took the franchise
seven more years to release a Star Trek game
overall the franchise has released
low quality games for current gen consoles
do you see a future for Star Trek games in the
next gen consoles thanks
um well Brian I don't think so
I mean
if they do anything it's gonna definitely be like
um a movie tie in I think
well the last movie tie in was pretty
terrible too that's the problem there's nothing
to make the games really
on right now unless
you know they go back and
do a new next generation game which would be
awesome uh they do
have the Star Trek next generation pinball table
in pinball arcade just random tangent
cause when I saw that I got giddy
um I will say this though so one thing
that email left out and I don't know if that's just because
this person is very console focused but
you neglected Star Trek online
which I don't think I mean it's free to play
it's worth a look I don't think it's bad
especially if you're a Star Trek fan I think it's worth checking out
and I have to say that they did actually retool
um that the skill system
that I kind of got pissed off when they changed it
the first time it's a lot more
manageable now um space battles
are still kind of you know you have to
ease into it from beginning to
admiral for you to finally get and they
got rid of rear admiral as a rank I'm just saying
but um
it was it was
Star Trek online was really good
I liked it I mean really all I did was ever
play it hang out at deep space night and play
Dabo Dabo with
Lina so
so there's that
I mean but unfortunately the reality is
without that stuff to tie into
and the fact that the video games unfortunately
have been tanking like it doesn't look
good which pains me because
I love me some Trek and I would love
to see like a really good video game
happen and it's kind of irritating that
that last one was such a stinker
actually going back to Star Trek online
I do suggest if this person has not played
it to do so because no matter which
era of Star Trek you liked
and yeah I really did not like Enterprise
but there are enough nods to the
even TOS characters show
up like you actually do a time
travel one and meet you know McCoy
and actually the model looks pretty
pretty much like he did
so I mean it's really really
fun I think
if you like Star Trek it's got enough nods that I think
it would keep you interested
nice
so um
back to the email
we have a kind of long one
but not terribly long so I'll read it
hello there OLR
hi
I always feel the need to say hi back I'm friendly
yeah you're friendly you're so
friendly um well last week
I had a very very unfortunate thing happen
to me when looking for alternative digital
distribution network now you
guys know I'm not big on DRM so I was really
happy that gamersgate.com
had a selection of DRM free titles
I bought a couple only to find out that the games
weren't all they seemed wait who is this
because they say we have to make some assumptions
about them in advance
ah I see okay
okay
um instead of giving
me a full installer I got very small files
that pull temporary files from the internet for installation
as I would find out after
perusing the site you're not able to get full
proper installers even if you keep the
temp files you can't install your game
without an internet connection needless to say
I was angry I shot off an email
to gamersgate asking for
remedy for this issue only be told point
blank there only called
them DRM free because there were no serial
numbers the person
who emailed me back even had the gall to say
that Steam and Origin weren't DRM
and that theirs was an industry standard
despite my never having seen something like
this before for the record the Steam versions
you do get the full games downloaded
so that is a point um
I demanded my money back but they
refused to budge so now I'm left sending you
an email and hoping to steer anyone else away
from there you know you do have the better business bureau
you can file an official complaint
especially if you feel like what you got wasn't
what was advertised I think you know you do
have a legit basis for complaint there
exactly especially since you
messaged them first to remedy
it cause you have to have taken that step
and I'm gonna be real this
is Orange Lounge Radio not
you know a TV network or something I mean
we're a small group
here we love our audience we love the
small following that we have but
this wouldn't really make waves
the way that I think you
you really want this company to
own up to what they're selling
well just but I appreciate
the heads up nonetheless seriously
I don't care what your attitude is towards DRM
it's unacceptable for a company to say that
something is DRM free when it really isn't
it's the most
disgusting dishonest thing I have ever experienced
and I wholeheartedly recommend people stay the hell away
from gamersgate.com after all
if they're lying about this what else are they lying about
however this is not a tale
of total loss I emailed Robert Boyd
of Zeboid Games and told him what happened
he immediately sent me
a desperate copy of the game that I had
bought and they were actually DRM free
moral of the story avoid gamersgate
and thumbs up to Zeboid
still waiting on response from Valusoft though
well that's my story hope I've steered a few people away from
gamersgate if I've helped someone the money I lost
was worth it sincerely we're all still UT
kinda interesting way he went about
the second half of that email where he says
I emailed the people that made the game
and said did you know this
but what's interesting to me is that he kind of breezed
by the fact that he got the Desura code
so why not is Desura
now your option of choice because
I know a lot of people are using Desura as a Steam alternative
and even I've used it because
one of our listeners was kind enough to give me a game
but it was on Desura so I've used it and it's fine
so is that
is Desura like your happy
alternative now that you've found
I don't know if I really heard that part of it
but I will say this in the email
in our chat room live.vognetware.com
actdef says
gamersgate is a mess of a site
I try not to buy from them
I've never heard of this site I have no opinion
I can only go off what the listeners say
and Rama says to file a
chargeback on your credit card
usually you want to do that as a last
resort because that can come back to bite you
I would say better business bureau first
and I do believe if I've
heard right if you've done a chargeback
then the company themselves may actually file
with a collection
which shows up on your credit report
you've got to be careful with that stuff
but no I'd say
you don't want to burn your chargebacks because obviously the bank
is going to take issue if you keep doing it
I wouldn't want to burn it on something like this
like use a chargeback when you really want to
fuck somebody over
my suggestion is
have copies of all of the emails you've sent
plus the responses dated
make sure they're date stamped
and use those with your filing
to the better business bureau you know I got a free hamburger doing that
once
I got a free meal
from this place and they didn't give you fries the
cheap bastards no no no I got a sweet potato
fries I got a whole meal nice and
they actually we actually
got to see them make the meal
a free voucher for a meal for two
because I complained about
the strata place that's on
Watt Avenue I used to work
next door to them so oh I don't even know
it's attached to like a Days Inn or something
but oh but it's a nice
restaurant attached to a crappy hotel
but anyway yeah I
can say for a fact that I've actually gotten something
out of filing better business bureau complaints so
and it was a pretty damn good hamburger too
that
is a tasty burger maybe
Gamers Gate will send you a hamburger
well we'll
cross our fingers and our toes
and then share with us okay
last email
okay hi OLR it's
Reginator again
I just had a question about computer
OS's currently I'm on my laptop
I have no currently on my laptop
I have Windows 7 home premium installed
which overall I'm happy with now the
trouble is I am a supporter of Zune
Xbox video in order for me to continue
buying content for it either I
have to replace my 360 that I sold
off two years ago or upgrade to
Windows 8 now the question is
is it possible to finagle things so I can keep
Windows 7 and use Windows 8
I don't know like put Windows 8 on a USB
drive or something how would I do
that I never once did anything on a
computer regarding an OS and I hate to either
brick my PC lose Windows 7 etc.
thanks in advance
I will tell you this that Windows OS
in both cases are very
well
extraneous with the other stuff that they
install with it so you'd probably
depending on how big your hard drive is you could
probably partition
yeah that's probably going to have to be the way you do it
because you can dual boot your system
but I don't know why you'd really
want to do that if you want to go to Windows 8 then just go
to Windows 8 you know if you need to see
the new movies which I think is kind of a dick move
on Microsoft's part I don't want to go to Windows
8 but I know that when I rebuild my computer
I'm basically going to put Windows 7 on it no matter
what it comes with
well don't forget 8.1 is out now
I haven't used that myself
there's stuff that make it like a lot more usable
like you know so it's more like 7
and Windows 8 overall is
more stable than Windows 7
it's just all the crap that they throw in the
front there that you have to dig through
and stuff's kind of moved around
see at this point I'm ready just to go back to
Linux Mint and Runwine for
my other programs
I mean they've now got most
of the game drivers and everything
compatible with Linux
comments from our chat room at live.vognetware.com
Rama says you don't need to upgrade to 8
SG100Matt says dual boot if you want
but there's no need for 8
Brad from Pod Culture says just go to 8
it runs everything from 7 just fine
and then Bobby Blackwolf says this is a
tech support question not a podcast email
question well I'm wondering because
he said the USB boot thing I'm wondering if he didn't
think of that because we were talking about it with
Linux a couple weeks ago
I don't know though that Windows 8 will
live boot you can't do a Windows boot like that
I'm pretty sure yeah
although I have done a
USB installer for
Windows for
fuck what that was
a netbook
I have made an installer
so I don't know
is that it for emails? yeah that's it
alright give Dark Soccer more work next week
mailbag at orangelaungeradio.com
send me a recola we need like essays
nooo
rawstealUT I want five emails
kidding I'm kidding
alright no I want one
let's get to the FUs short one
let's get to the FUs of the week
FU to emails
no
here's the part of the show where we get angsty why?
because we can't
um FU to all the people who are
driving 10 miles under the speed limit and I mean
it was like five fucking people driving 30
in a 40 and I was like
really people don't you know what a speed
limit is and how to you know use it
flow of traffic hello
and the um
wasp sting that I got
that still hasn't healed look at this
it's still there
and also not having a job
if somebody is listening to the show and you love
the sound of my voice just keep in mind that I can
also transfer the
sexyness to web design
and print design and fantastic customer service
and amazing customer service I love
talking to pissed off people
it's what you know how do you de-escalate a customer
de-escalate a customer well if they're yelling
and cursing at me I give them a time out
it works seriously we weren't allowed to
hang up on people right so
if it was all I want my pay off
I'd be like
now I'm sorry we need to have this
conversation like civil adults so
I'm going to put you on hold for two minutes
let you calm down a little bit
so we can come back and discuss this like adults
bing!
you know what they'd either hang up on me or they would come back and be nice
that'll get you a job alright
you know what it works
and they can't and the thing is they can't
complain about it because I did nothing
uncivil
she's got great attendance she's shown up to
most of these shows
unless I was like dead sick
I even came here sick a few times
alright Loki
F you to Wingstop because
why does it take 30 minutes for you to
make wings for us
I mean 30 minutes
seriously you fry the wings
you dip them in sauce
done! Wingstop is fucking good though
they're not that great that's not an endorsement
if I want to eat like if I want food
that will make me fat that's what I want
because if I can go to KFC and get the wings
dipped in sauce
within the time that I order
in the drive through and pull up to the window
it should not take 30 fucking minutes
to cook wings
I'm sorry I mean it's like
you don't fry wings for 30 minutes
oh
and their fries fucking suck they're
soggy stale
unsalted it was just like some
of a crap potato into
a little
cardboard tray and try to pass it off
as french fries it was just not
good
here we go the food show again
orange lounge foodie
Nelly wanted to try Wingstop even though
I've been there and said listen it sucks
you know we shouldn't go back
take her to Hooters next time although I did get to try
for the first time actually going inside and doing one of those
coke freestyle machines and that was pretty
those are pretty awesome
she says we should go in these for our home I'm like
yes we should
that's a project you should work on building your own
oh yeah that'd be expensive
you could dispense the taurani syrup
think about it
I'm gonna give an FU to iMessage
because we all know
they're already having some type of bug
and I've been trying to text message during the show
and I think iMessage just stopped working
and I don't know what the hell is going on
but then one of my other friends sent me a text and I got it fine
so I'm afraid I can't let you
iMessage is my FU of the week
and yes I'm an
apple sheep and I have an iPhone
I just want to text message people okay
you can't text message breakup
during the show? what?
did you just
quote a Kelly song over there? I did
alright
just a couple more stories and then Twitter topics
and the Skype line at 1877
game OLR
first Loki
alright so there's a new
Kickstarter for a new
augmented reality glass
thing it's done by some
ex-Valve employees
I guess they've reached
their goal already but they're doing their stretch goals
what's kind of unique about it is
it's these shutter glasses
and they actually have projectors
so it projects 3D
images onto
the environment
the other thing though that seemed kind of weird though
is like
in the video and stuff
it just didn't seem like
I mean if you're moving your head and stuff
the projection kind of change where it's at
unless it's updating really fast
I don't know
I don't know, interesting, don't know what the price point though
of it is
certainly I'm not going to back it because
I don't need to spend money on this kind of crap
but you kind of want to
no because it's not expected
to come out for like a year
you know a starter package is
$189
and you get a cast AR
oh that's the weird thing about it is you have to have this like
actually cast onto it's like a
looks like a fabric
thing almost like a green screen but it's
grey so
it seems like a lot of
hassle but hey
maybe if it's cheaper then
I don't know
the Oculus Rift it might be
I think the Rift sounds more interesting because
it's VR whereas this is augmented reality
stuff and just I don't really
care about AR stuff I remember
trying to pull that shit off with the Vita and
it sucked remember the Vita what they
are you know stuff it's like oh
let me try this soccer game
wow that's that's shit okay cool
alright
one more story for you guys I swear it's like
it's like Blast from OLR's past
tonight and I guess Jason kind of referenced that
in the intro tonight it's kind of true
because we have one more story here tonight and it's about
one of our favorite
DDR knockoffs they ever had
it was a game called Dance Dance
Immolation and if you didn't know about
this game this was the DDR
game where if you made a misstep it would
literally set you on fire
and you're probably wondering how in the hell is this legal
well A you had
to wear this hugely flame
retardant suit and all this stuff to even
play the game and I'm sure you had to sign waiver after
waiver and B it was
the kind of thing that they would just take to Burning Man
and like that type of like artsy
stuff that's what you expect to see at Burning Man like that weird
stuff also
there were some other festivals Dance Dance Immolation went
to including the fine arts festival
a Denmark
thing called Smuck Fest
DDR for hipsters
but anyway
the game was officially retired
at Burning Man 2013
and then the display was
ripped apart and then in
true Burning Man what the fuck are they even doing
anymore fashion and look I have friends that
go to Burning Man and love it and swear by it and
I'm not knocking it but I'm just saying
the randomness
of some of this shit doesn't help the
theories that everybody's on drugs there
I'm just saying
I'm just saying but anyhow
the way they destroyed it
what I meant to say is that
they dropped a piano on it
actually they dropped
a piano on what was left and since I know
Dark Soccer is dying to see
here it is
they dropped
an old
powder blue upright
and then
all the people I need to go to
Burning Man Rob it's just so fucking hard
no no
but
I love you
if you want to take drugs and run naked through the desert
I guess you can do that I love you
but sometimes
little things make you pretty
irritable and going to
the desert
for seven days
I'd probably want to murder everybody
I don't know where these people
poop
they have an RV
I guess it's RVs or whatever
there's no such thing as money
it's a barter system
Dark Soccer
I don't think you'd enjoy it
I think you'd complain a little bit
I probably wouldn't
every so often I want to go see
some of this stuff in person
and then you just reminded me
no air conditioning
fuck that shit I can't stand hot
and I live in Sacramento
what am I thinking
well you're on drugs
I'm on the drugs that keep me from murdering people
I just want to make it clear
I'm just teasing
I don't want to offend the people because I have friends that go to this
and they have a great time and they always tell me I should go
but I'm like my
red headed ass cannot
handle seven days
in the desert
it's not going to happen
I will watch the YouTubes
what if you went through the desert on a horse with no name
I don't even want to do this show anymore
alright
I'm just kidding
I do want to talk to you on Skype
maybe you'll have a better topic to talk about
1-877-GAME-OLR
talk about Rob's red headed ass
stop being weird
our username on Skype
Orange Lounge Radio
all one word if you want to give us a call
Bobby Black Wolf is in our chat room
saying I go to Dragon Con
instead of Burning Man
they're at the same time
and you know what
that's my new drug of choice too
I did really love Dragon Con this year
I can't wait to go back
I can poke fun at myself too
because I said everyone's on drugs at Burning Man
well at Dragon Con everybody's drunk
and I say that as a proud Dragon Con attendee
responsibly
we're responsibly drunk
but I'm just saying
Rob, next year, Fauna Mae
I really do want to go back to Fauna Mae
you should cosplay Black Mage
and I should cosplay White Mage
which kind of Black Mage
Classic Black Mage or Final Fantasy XIV
maybe XIV
Gamer X2
Dark Sakura, I've got to take you to Gamer X2
because I know
that all my gay gaming
podcast guys
want to meet you
they listen to this show
they love you
they like Loki too
you are the one that tried to make Lolo gay
let's be real
look, I can't help it if Lala
is really a cross dresser
no I'm kidding
I don't know if you are listening to these shows
I don't shout them out enough here on the program
unfortunately we don't really have a shout out segment
but I do want to give a shout out to folks
like Game Buoy, you know them
very well, right?
Koopa Club, I don't know if you're listening to them
but they're a lot of fun, they're out of Chicago
you would love them
Video Game Realness, Canadian, hilarious
they kind of do what we do here
where they're all at one table in one room
and they should send us some poutine
he was bitching about soggy fries
from Wingstop earlier
I do not want FedExed poutine
there's actually a place in town you can get poutine
alright, Game Bar
is another one
no, it's an actual restaurant
not a strip club
no, Poon-teen
I'm sorry
you're thinking of Poon-teen
shut up
we did already have Kirby
birth 1877
Game O.L.R. or a username on Skype
Orange Lounge Radio, you need to call us
or it's going to be the Poutine Hour
and Loki may not
give you what you think that is
with the Poutine Hour
or we could go to Last Minute Stories
while we wait for some calls
sure, why not
let's talk about Grand Theft Auto 5
it's number 2 in Japan
after debuting
what was number 1 though, I'm kind of curious
oh, Pokemon
anyway, number 2 is not bad
they're corrupt, y'all
they are, they're going to have to do something about it
yeah, that's it
that's all I got
there were some stories on
the Xbox One also is not going to support
third party headsets at launch
not until 2014
there were some
stories on Zelda this week
that we didn't get to, and I don't remember what they were
does it involve Poutine?
yes
yes, because Poutine is
the national food of Hyrule
if you do the dungeons in a certain order
you can actually collect the gravy and the
cheese curd power up
and go to town
we have pianos
dropping on DDR machines that set people on fire
what
what, I just haven't done that in a while
I thought you were cutting sugar out
of your diet, yet you sound like
like a four year old that
just ate a Snickers bar
because I now have quite stable blood sugar and I'm hyper all the time
alright, fair enough
alright, yes, thank you actdeft, I'm going to Twitter topics
I'm trying, I'm doing Twitter topics
I want someone to call us
who hasn't called before
because I'm running out of things to say Poutine
about
that is actually
true, ssh100map
you misspelled
p-o-u-t-i-n-e, Poutine
and dongles
those are like two, you know another word that makes me
giggle like that, balls
I'm turning dark side with my stuff
oh thank god, we're getting a call
thank the lord
somebody's going to help us talk about something
maybe Canadian, maybe not, I don't know
hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio, who's this?
hey, this is Zappi, and I officially endorse Poutine
what's that?
I officially endorse Poutine
are you Canadian?
I'm from French Canada, so it's really
I love Poutine so much
god dammit
and I haven't had it since Louisiana
alright Zappi, have a great night
no, I'm just kidding
what did you call in to talk to us about tonight, Zappi?
well, besides Poutine, I was
going to talk about me playing the Xbox One
this week
why, how'd that happen?
well, I just went to my local Best Buy
and lo and behold, they just had an Xbox One demo out
I went into my local
Best Buy, and like, I had to ask
to get a copy of Pokemon, why
like, may I buy a copy of Pokemon
because I don't see it on the shelf
I didn't see no Xbox Ones or PlayStations
apparently they got their shit together in Canada
you know why? Everyone's happy
because they're eating french fries smothered in gravy
and, cheese curds
alright, well I hate to break it to you, but they had no Pokemon
oh
dicks, I'm just kidding, alright
is that why you went there?
we're moving to Canada tomorrow, by the way
so you went there, Zappi, to get Pokemon
and you ended up with Xbox One?
well, I was going to get the Pokemon from my boyfriend
and, no
oh, ok, alright
well, how was the Xbox One?
what'd you play?
they had fours of five
oh, ok, cool
I'll say this, it's very pretty
but there's one thing that really has me concerned
they had this demo unit
that looked like a complete factory finished Xbox
and the game was stuttering
like no tomorrow
really?
it's because it's not actually, it's just
the PC and the
units, I don't think it's actually the
well, actually it's the test units, I think
they had like a clear
container for it, it looked like
a finished Xbox One
but it's probably not a finished version of the game, remember
fours of five isn't done yet, they need to
patch in the rest of the game when it comes out
we're only a month out, too, I mean
I would think that the real deal is starting to show up
but this is the copy
that they were confident enough to bring to a retail
store and have people try out
and you know, and funny
enough, I was teasing Bobby Blackwolf
because he has the show before us here at VOG Network
and I was teasing him earlier because he was talking
about demos, and I said, well you know, Bobby
he will make his
impression off a video game based off the demo
and that's that, because I think back to Nino Cooney
and how he refuses to play that full game
because the demo was so awful, which it was
but the game's really good
I bring that up because, you know, if you're gonna
make your impressions off this in-store
demo unit, then yeah, it should run
a little better than being stuttery all over
the place
besides that, it was very pretty
the controller is really awesome, I want one of those
and it plays like
Forza
but more like the old Forzas
and not like Forza Horizon Arcady, right?
no, no, it's like the numbered
Forza games
fair enough, were they
showing anything else, like Killer Instinct or any of that
or just Forza?
nope, it was the Forza show
they had two reps they probably trained over the
weekend showing it off
fair enough
I was gonna say though
since we were talking about Pokemon a minute ago
have you tried playing the Pokemon in 3D?
it kind of stutters too
yeah, that was a little bit disappointing
as soon as you turn off the 3D, it's perfectly fine
but
I guess that's why the whole game
isn't in 3D to begin with
they want you to not notice
I guess so
it's kind of interesting
at the end of the day though
maybe we are hitting that point
because it's no big deal
I don't feel short handed
or like I'm losing something by not having the 3D
you know what I mean?
Dark Sakura, what the hell are you doing in chat?
I don't know, I tried to put like one stupid little link
and the whole thing copied
and Dark Sakura got kicked for flooding the chat
you know what?
she was speaking in tongues
that was actually a complete and total accident
whoops, alright
good job Dark Sakura
sorry Zappi
well the thing is, sure, 3D isn't that useful
but this is what they sold the system on
you have 3D games
and it looks like they're moving away from the thing
they were selling their own system on
well, what's the verdict for you?
are you on board with next gen gaming?
are you gonna get an Xbox One
or a Playstation 4?
well I'm considering it just because
I was able to pre-order an Xbox One
for $100 off
because I just used the staples to
stack a whole bunch of coupons
so you're gonna go
Xbox One with that money off then?
I'm thinking about it, because $400
it puts it at the same price as a PS4
that's true, if you can lessen the price
Xbox One does have
some exclusives that are
worth looking at
yeah, but on the other hand
the launch line up just isn't there
yeah, I hear ya
he's waiting six months, so there's nothing wrong with that
alright, well Zappi, I'm gonna let you go
to see if anybody else calls, but thanks for calling
I don't think we've heard from you in forever
and it's good to hear the impressions of the Xbox One
alright, cool, later
next time, Pre-Poutine
alright, sounds good, bye
bye
1877 Game OLR, our username on Skype
Orange Lounge Radio
I figured out what it did
it actually copied the image data and not the URL
I have no idea how that happened
because I highlighted the URL to copy it
so
my iPad is currently the devil
1877 Game OLR
our username on Skype
Orange Lounge Radio
we need more poutine
I'm trying to go to tweets and see what else has been tweeted at us tonight
someone new should call us, I want new
I mean, I love all of you people
seriously, and I love talking with you, but we need someone new calling
new voices, new blood
we must sacrifice you to my iPad
so that
it doesn't spout
devil noise at us, again
actdef sent us a tweet, but it's a tweet from Eurogamer
about the extension of the games for gold
on 360, which I think we had talked about earlier
I was trying to see if there was more games
announced on it, but I don't think so
I didn't realize they got the exact same games in Europe
but I guess that makes sense, that they do
um, Sturlock
tweeted us saying, what was the music from tonight
very awesome, well clearly
you're talking about the song Always by
Erasure, it's what we play during the FUGL
we need more Erasure on the show
we do, I can make that happen
don't, uh, don't think I won't
I think that's it for Twitter topics, I didn't get a whole lot tonight
so, twitter.com slash OLR
we need a new ending song
and it should be all through the years
alright, I'm gonna put out one more
call for phone calls, and then we're gonna
wrap it up, no, you should call tonight
Seattle, do it now
1877 game OLR
or username on skype
orange lounge radio
and we're out of last minute stories, right
yeah, is there any more
food stories somebody wants to tell
poutine
I think they have that actually over at sprouts
they, or even like uh, Whole Foods
or something like that, they have like their weird food over there
I could just make it at home
yeah, it's not that difficult
let's just sacrifice your face first
alright, degenerate Johnny
alright, well I guess nobody wants to call
that makes me sad, so I'm gonna close up the skype line
and I will encourage you guys to email us in a future week
mailbag at orange lounge radio dot com
or you can also send us a tweet
twitter dot com slash OLR
and uh, those are all the ways you can interact with us as well
uh, otherwise
that does it for another week of orange lounge radio
I just wanna say thank you guys
very much for listening to the show
um, the nominating stuff is over
for the podcast awards, but I do wanna give a quick
thank you, if you did take the time out of your day to nominate us
or at least nominate another deserving
independent podcast, even if it wasn't
us, I wanna say thank you
and uh, we'll know the results of that, I think
I think it's the same time as the show next week
so that could be interesting
so we can have our disappointment
drinks when we don't get nominated
we'll have a pile of poutine that we'll drown our sorrows in
yes, fist bump
poutine
do you want some poutine, Loki?
is that part of your diet?
budget for it
I don't think there's a ketogenic version of poutine
just budget for it, that's all you have to do
alright, um, thank you very much
for listening to our show
if you like what you heard here at orange lounge radio
we don't ask for your money, all we do
just tell a friend or 5 or 25
about the program, help us spread the word
about OLR and grow our family
cause you know what, we've got some pretty cool people
that listen to this show, both live
and in the podcast forum, thank you very much
for participating and being a part of it
thank you very much
you could also leave us a nice review on itunes
stitcher, thumbs up, you know, all the places where you found this podcast
other people will find podcasts too
um, it's time to go around and get everybody's final thought
Loki, starting us off tonight, your final thought
uh, well
we'll be playing more grant the thought of this week
and hopefully you should see an announcement
about the next game night
we'll maybe do another game night
or maybe we'll do like one week
cause friday seems to be a lot better
for people, cause it's hard to
play, so maybe
maybe we'll do another game night friday
and then we'll switch it up to the next platform
the next friday or something like that
switch off until
you know, some other games come out
um, my final thought tonight is
um, I don't know
uh, I
uh, I need to get working on my halloween costume
cause I haven't started yet and I really need to do that
and I need to not slack off
and also I need to do more live game streaming
cause I've been slacking off on that too, so
uh, even though I was joking earlier about
how everybody's live streaming, oh well
I'm gonna do it too, cause there's some other
games out there I'm playing that I wanna show you guys
that aren't just Final Fantasy XIV, believe it or not
and last but not least, Dark Soccer, your final thought tonight
the closest thing I have to cheese
courage is cottage cheese
that sucks
could you put cottage cheese on french fries?
I can't eat french fries
oh, alright
you know what?
I feel healthier
I feel healthier than I have in the last three weeks
and I wanna start
playing DDR again, that's my final thought
alright, good luck
I wanna make it a thing
alright, well
that's the end of this thing for tonight
we'll be back next Sunday, seven days
to do it all over again, yet another thing
just in time for halloween with episode
multiple of 25 palindrome episode
so we'll see you next time
here on Orange Launch Radio, good night
Orange Launch Radio
Orange Launch Radio is a production
of OLR Studios
to join us for a live show
tune in to vognetwork.com
Sunday nights at 6 pm Pacific
9 pm Eastern
the views and opinions
expressed in this program do not
necessarily reflect those of the staff
of Orange Launch Radio or
VOG Network, but you know
they were all still true
see you next week
thanks for watching