Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts? DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
Tonight GTA Online opens for gamers to experience the latest load screen simulator
The Neo Geo X is ordered to be pulled from shells
Nintendo announces another hit game delay
And could SimCity finally become playable offline?
All this and more begins right now
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet
And welcome back to another week of the show
Where every gamer has a voice
It is Orange Lounge Radio
Live with episode number 522
For this October the 6th of 2013
It is officially October
Only how many more days to Halloween? 25
If I did my math right
And she'll keep me in check for sure
Here she is everybody
DarkSakura or Jamie Summers?
Meh
No it's not on, now it's on meh
Did I do my math right?
I don't care
Math sucks
Why are you meh? Sunday is fun day
Because I'm waiting for Halloween to be over
So I can buy Purim costumes
Fair enough
And then get all the candy on sale
And then make like candy corn muffins or something
Actually I am planning
Even though I'm not doing sugar very much
I'm planning on making candy corn vodka
Hooray
Vodka doesn't count
If you're gonna drink something
Vodka is the best for you anyway
Well it liquefies the candy corn
So it's like candy corn syrup mixed in vodka
Oh my gosh
I bet some people would find that absolutely disgusting though
It's amazeballs
I have to ask you though, what do you think about
Because we do talk about video games
The gaming culture, the gamer lifestyle, it is a video game show
But let's be real, it's also a foodie show
Because we always talk about food on this show
So I have to ask you DarkSaga
What do you think about this time of year
Where it's pumpkin all the things
And then candy corn
And it's like candy corn oreos
This is the time of year
That I actually make my
I kind of call it gourd soup
But I make
Butternut squash pumpkin and sweet potato soup
Yummy
And it's really creamy
But now the way that I make these is I make them all savory
So I put like garlic and rosemary
And all kinds of savory herbs in it
So that it's sweet and savory at the same time
And you guys, she's gonna bring some to the next show
Yay! Maybe I will
I've actually got the stuff to make my soup
And this time I have
Purple mountain yams
To add in it this time
This sounds delicious, I can't wait
All the listeners are hungry now
But everybody should be jealous of my amazing dinner
Because I had rabbit and beef liver
For dinner
You know what, Bugs was delicious
If my sister could hear you
She would hate you, she's a bunny enthusiast
And she loves bunnies
I love bunnies too, they're fun and I'm allergic to them
But they're soft and fun to pet and delicious
Alright look
Going to our chat room at live.vognetwork.com
We'll start off tonight with
Rama who says, too much fucking pumpkin
Yo
Well, even our chatters have wrong opinions sometimes
Here at Orange Lounge Radio
But after all it is the show where every gamer has a voice
I don't like pumpkin
And there he is, Techmaster Loki, what's wrong with you?
You don't like pumpkin? No
Well some people think I'm weird
Because I don't like mayonnaise
I don't think I introduced myself, I'm Rob Roberts by the way
If you don't know me, I'm Rob Roberts and I hate mayonnaise
I can understand eating straight up mayonnaise
But honest sandwich is fine
Or chicken salad
Or everything with mayonnaise
Okay, Alan and I went and got sushi
And we got this one roll and I was kind of like
Think that's a mayo based sauce
And I'm going to have to kind of like eat the edges
You know what, I got sushi the other day
And I had an allergic reaction to it
Because you know what was mixed in with the crab?
What? Sriracha
Oh no, sriracha crab?
That's weird It was how they made their spicy crab
They mixed sriracha in with the crab
And normally I'm fine with spicy crab
Because it's just like maybe a little
Something else hot, but they mixed sriracha in it
Which I'm like stupidly allergic to
So I actually still have a hive
And it hurts
Let's see, going to Raginator in our chat room
Says pumpkin flavored mayonnaise
I'm sorry, that won't work for me
Just like it probably won't work for Loki
That's not okay
Well here's the thing, I don't understand
Like putting mayonnaise on like
Hot things
You know like with a sandwich it's okay
But like people put it on burgers
Or they'll like get a sandwich at like a sandwich place
Yeah I like that toasted
It's like okay cool, now it's like this nasty
Hot mayonnaise
I am literally gagging right now
And I don't mean like fashion runway
I'm gagging at that, I mean like I am actually about to barf
When you're talking about that
I won't tell you about what my mom used to eat as a snack
No, ugh
Canned pears with mayonnaise and cheese
This is horrible I actually grew up on that
It's pretty good Alright look, we need to talk about video games
What about like a mayonnaise flavored
Flurry or something like that
What's wrong with you people? I like homemade mayonnaise
As a garnish on dishes
Look, be nice everybody and respectful
Cause we got a guest here in studio tonight
I bet she likes mayonnaise
She might, we're gonna say hello to our guest here
It's actually her second time on the show
But you know welcome back
As the case may be to Chell is here tonight
Well thank you very much for having me
Chell, I think you can like
Chow? Chell
Chell, it's Chell, I keep thinking Chell
You're a hero and a half Chell
Sorry Chell
You know the computer name
from Portal I can't even think about
pronouncing in real life so you're in good company
Alright fair enough
So you were on the show before
and you talked about what kinds of things
We did talk about your love of Portal on the last show
Oh yes and my deep deep love affair
with Earthbound slash Mother
Have you seen, I think this happened after
you were on the show, have you seen it's on Wii U virtual console now?
No I did not
I could get that puppy over here right
now for you to check out, it's awesome
That would be awesome
I need to play more of it to be honest
Have you checked out anything lately?
I know we're going to get into gaming weeks a little later
but what kind of stuff have you been into in general
as of late?
Since I've been busy, I've been getting my nostalgia on
with old Lucas Arts stuff and
a lot of free RPG stuff
You people light up my life
with your independent
RPGs that are fan made stuff
but at the same time guys
sometimes you need to work on your programming
because you know
I want to meet you half way but
when I no clip into a shelf
yeah
There's such good stuff out there though
There are a lot of great indie RPGs
and the great thing about RPGs is that
they take forever to beat usually
so they're a great time sink and I'm thinking of things like
Cthulhu Saves the World
Have you played any of that stuff?
Adorbs
Are you a Steam user?
My computer is broke as hell
It's also 4 years old
It's doing some interesting breakage right now in fact
Well if you're able to
put some band aids on it
check out Steam and some of these indie
RPGs are like $1.50
Nice
They'll be a winner sale as there always is
going into New Years and such this year
It'll be like
hand us a couple quarters and here's like 50 games
Sales all the things
Exactly
That's something we're bringing up in part B for people
who are not on Steam
Absolutely a little teaser
So Chell will have to pay attention
in part B there will be a quiz tonight
I don't know if they told you there will be a quiz
What other stuff do you do for fun Chell?
I haven't been doing much fun lately
I've mostly been working on just
getting stuff for my degree together
I'm working on a lot of
learning 3D stuff because one day I hope to
join the unwashed masses
and start churning out games like I want to play
Awesome
Have you thought about what would be your dream
company to work for?
Well Valve obviously
The minute the words left my mouth
that was the stupid
Rob doesn't usually ask stupid questions
haha at least I had to tell myself
but that one was pretty dumb
It's not just that
they make games that I want to play
it's that they seem like a really
chill workforce
Have you seen that leaked handbook
that's online that's like the Valve company
handbook like what the employees
get you know their corporate
culture is so interesting
Valve like I really
it's just so neat and like I kind of
think about like gosh if they try to do something
like that at my day job I just I don't know
something like that would fly like some industries
need structure but it's so interesting as
Valve has really pulled off this
everybody's equal we don't have
titles your desk is on
wheels and you roll it where you need to go
and we don't tell you what to do
you find projects
like you guys have to Google
this if you've never seen this before the Valve handbook
and technically I don't know if it's legit
or not but it seems like it
would be I have no reason to doubt it
Sounds pretty close yeah
and it's just like so interesting
that you know
a person might
start work at this company and they don't have any
assignments so they just have to go like find
something to do but that's the type
of people they're looking for
yeah work raising
alright well unfortunately as we're broadcasting
live here we're having a little bit of stream troubles
I'm going to keep going for the sake of the
podcast but for some reason
we're not actually able to reconnect
and what's going on
is actually on server room's
side because
we are not able to reconnect at all
so I'm going to try to
keep this show going while doing tech
at the same time
alright
I
well you know what we could go
and bring up our
next topic we could
or I have another idea too is that
since this is for the sake of the podcast
why don't we do a quick musical interlude
while we try to fix things
and then we'll be right back I could sing
alright you want to sing us out
fly me to the moon
no
To register participation for this week's episode
of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com
use the pass phrase dash
alright we're back that wasn't awkward
or anything but the joys
of doing live radio is
that sometimes the feed just
the internets go down there's a
server reboot or something happens
and the tubes get
untied or I don't know what happens
just being a butthole or a cat
just pulled out the plug let's be real
that's probably what happened but for
once that wasn't our fault at least I can say
so alright
where were we when we left off
I was talking to the lovely Chell
over there about the dream company
she wanted to work for we were talking about Valve
and just kind of
what a different type of company
Valve is so let me ask you this
knowing that the employees at Valve can work on
whatever project they want
if you were to get hired by Valve
hypothetically what would be your dream
project?
Barring Half Life Part 3
which may or may not be a thing
make sure that mics on by the way
siblings, siblings
so Barring Half Life Part 3
oh
that is a tough one
I really always wanted to
see a Portal sequel but I just wanted to
work on something new and fresh
coming down the pipe
they kind of hit me where I live
story wise everything
they put out is just
right along the lines of what I try to bring into my fiction
just you know the continuing themes
of kind of being alone
in a strange place and having to kind of survive
through strange circumstances
you are a little quiet by the way
just make sure you talk right in that mic
so
you would hope to work on Half Life 3
or something kind of new
because I'm a little fancy
speaking of new and fancy, Valve did make a bunch of announcements
last week about this Steam Box
have you been following this news at all?
I'm completely out of the loop
that's why we're here
to help you stay current
the Steam Box they announced is
it's going to have its own operating system
SteamOS which you can put on any computer
it's basically a version of Linux
and then they're going to be selling these computers
that are basically
it's kind of to rival consoles a little bit
to bring PC gaming closer to living room
but they'll be all these different types
there's no way they're going to be console prices
Loki's shaking us out over there, no way huh?
well did you see what the test specs are?
the test specs are going to have Titans in them
oh wow
like the super super super high end
Nvidia cards
I hope I'm one of the lucky 300 people that gets one of those
exactly, I'm like dude I
I could totally use a new PC and that would be awesome
just to get like
something like that
even the low end was like a
I think like a 680
that's still way better than I've got now
nice
and WhattupG says how about that new controller for the Steam Box
yes don't forget there is that little controller too
with the fancy little
it's really kind of weird, it's got like thumb sticks
but they're like touch pads
it's interesting, it's different
you know it's not the same old same old
anything with like a million joysticks
makes me want to hiss and run into a corner
I mean that's one of my main issues with
one of my continuing issues with Xbox
remember when Nintendo announced the Wii
and they came out with that Wiimote
and a lot of people were like it's really like simple
and Nintendo was like that's the point
so many people are intimidated
by all the buttons like on an Xbox
or a Playstation controller
the nice thing about the Wii controller is that
you know yes there's some smaller buttons
but for a lot of people there's just one big giant button
that says A and then the little trigger thing
and that's why so many senior citizens do the bowling
and all that you know
you think they learned from the clusterfuck that was the N64 controller
which was a good controller
but still
exactly
it gives me horrible horrible flashbacks to
Rebel Alliance N64
my brother having me help
hold down all the buttons so he can just
oh god
alright well Chell will be talking to you
about the news and such throughout the show
please feel free to chime in as you like
to have your say on whatever's going on
and those of you in chat rooms
same thing for you guys live.vognetwork.com
and Act F says
Loki that's only for the prototypes
Act F says the retail version
of the Steam Machine will probably offer
lower specs
for the prototypes it has the really kickass cards
of course you do
Daddy I want the golden
Steam Box Daddy
I want it
what do you mean I can't have it
I want the whole world
alright
I wanted to do a quick kick off topic here
and we are running a little behind because of the live stuff
so I'll just quickly talk about tonight
I know right
we're only ever here for like 4 hours
this is going to be a big week in gaming
I don't know if you want us to admit it or not
because Saturday October 12th
sees the release of
Pokemon X and Y
you're not a Pokemon fan
no
why not
because I have other things to like
like free time
I see
so you value your time
so much that you don't want to get sucked into Pokemon
because you see how Pokemon ruins lives
yeah thanks Shane
no no
the last one I played was Pearl
and I only ever played it at the gym
which was ironic because I was going to gyms
at the gym
ha ha ha
and I just
I don't know why that's so funny
but I'm laughing
so here's a Pokemon gym
so you can go to the gym at your gym
be funny
because if I were a dude
I could be gym
ha ha
oh my god stop
so
Rob's red
this is like one of those nights
where anything's funny
because there's probably people out there listening
going Rob it wasn't that funny
it's not that funny
alright hater
why are you hating
on the Pokemon
it's not serious I'm into
and don't get me wrong I understand that there are fans of it
I was just thinking
that's probably why they have Shane working at a certain company
because he is the crack dealer
for getting people into any game
and they have him behind
Pokemon
I've said this on Horde House
that Shane was born to do sales
that's where his ultimate calling
is going to end up being someday
stop making this the Shane show
I'm sure he's listening very happy
that we're talking Pokemon
I don't understand it
the way I look at a Madden release
it's like oh cool
instead of colors this time it's X and Y
cool
and that means nothing to me
other than I assume that there's just going to be a few more
Pokemon
and you have to collect those
to add to your ever large collection
of Pokemon that you battle each other
for whatever reason
I don't understand
if you are moving in that direction
I'm kind of disappointed that there is an opportunity
for a chromosome so you get Pokemon with some
autosomal disorders
you've got the down syndrome Pokemon
that you have to help a little out
but he's punched for it
yeah he's pulling for you
that would have taken gaming into a whole new area
what about aspie Pokemon
where they take everything really literal
and then
yeah
and I'm allowed to say that
so I'm looking at our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com
and actdeft says
Jim at the gym
Jimception
alright
need to go down another level
let's see
blackwolf says Loki's not into Pokemon because
it's not Grand Theft Auto
well to be fair we had a
discussion last week where Jamie's like I'm not that
into Grand Theft Auto and now this week
I'm not that into Pokemon
and to be fair if they had some sort of mini game in Grand Theft Auto
where you had to raise dogs and fight them or something
like Michael Vick of Pokemon
I still probably wouldn't play that
because that sounds stupid
I don't know
I'm not into that type of game
especially if it has to do with
raising stuff
I blame the 10 dogs for that
because that made any sort of raising
of anything extremely boring
hey cute puppies what's wrong with that
oh everything because have you raised a dog before
it's not all
petting and playing
frisbee and stuff you have to fucking feed
that shit, wash it
you're going to be cleaning poop all day
they just want attention all goddamn hours of the day
come to think of it
right after I quit wow was after the whole
Pokemon mode came out
so maybe that has something to do with it too
to Loki's thing
they put Pokemon in wow
and I quit
huh
I thought we all quit because of LFR
that was the real reason anyway
I liked LFR to be honest
just because
I could just pew pew stuff
and as long as I didn't fuck up
which I never fucked up
I'd get pissed off at other people fucking up
but then it gave me an excuse to be mad at somebody else
my one issue with Pokemon
I like Pokemon as a franchise
I respect the games
I understand why people love them
and I really did love the old anime
judge me all you want but it was great
my one thing with Pokemon
that really got to me was that
it's kind of a grind fest
that you have to like and only the ones
you send into the fight actually get
XP and it's like oh my gosh
I gotta grind this and grind this
and it's like the OCD gamer in me and like
Shane has tried to tell me this like why are you
leveling up all your Pokemon you only need like
three of them to be really good to go somewhere
and I'm like you don't understand how I play
RPGs
yeah I totally get that it sets off my OCD
like woah it's like 100% completion
and it's in the lyrics
I want to be the very best
first sentence
yeah that re-release of the first
three games when you've got all the new
areas and you've got the three new islands
I thought it was never gonna crawl out of my room
I was gonna crawl out of it to die basically
and not for water or food or anything
so here's why I'm really excited
about X and Y is that apparently they're gonna
have this experience sharing so that now
you can actually level everything
that's in your party at once
new based Pokemon
I am so excited
so we'll see
no putting Magikarp into battle first
and hoping like hell
but you gotta admit
once you got Gyarados
everyone was fucked
it was worth it
so worth it
and I have to say that
Pokemon has offered me comfort over the years
my Charmander pillow
was my AX pillow
and my Togepi was my present
after I got held up at gunpoint
oh my gosh
you know that happened
I found $10 in the parking lot
and Dan gave me another $10
and I bought a Togepi
and I still have my Togepi
I love Togepi so cute
alright so
it sounds to me like there's
half gonna get it and half not gonna
get Pokemon
so we'll see
Pokemon is like STDs
you don't gotta catch them all
stop
alright and of course
there's the mandatory
actdeft in chat says how about them
mudkips? shut up
alright Matt Cube says
it is popular because it is a simple RPG
well you know I don't wanna spoil the
frugal question of the week cause we're gonna get into it
a little later but I just will say in general
I'm hearing a lot of people that are
really attached to Pokemon
and the reason behind it a lot of times
is that we're from that certain generation
where like we were like
13, 15 when these games
first came out
and so we've really kinda stuck to it the whole time
so for many people yeah it kinda was
the first RPG
they should totally go the route where
your Pokemon catch diseases
where you have to put them down with a shotgun
they do catch diseases
Pikachu has rabies
you have to decapitate them to figure it out
they get like burn and paralyzed
and all that
is it a sick burn?
right. Pikachu you're lame
burn oh no
it was very effective
little mini game where they have burn
outside of battle and you gotta
swath them in gauze and take them to the hospital
and they've got like 5 weeks of recovery
and then nurse joy won't let you
have them because you have to be evaluated
for being a Pokemon crudely
nurse joy is my favorite
she's my absolute
favorite character next to jigglypuff
and the whole thing is nurse joy
you know they had like
I think a new mini series of Pokemon that they're
putting out yeah they are somebody was just asking me
in chat about it too oh my god oh my god oh my god
ok I have to talk about this did you see that gif
that's going around on tumblr
of like a Squirtle beating the shit out of a
Charmander and Red's like there with his mouth
I'll be like holy shit
I mean beating the shit out
of him and he's like no come back
literally forcing his fist
into his ass and shit is popping out
god why are you being nasty
it's a gif I'll have to find it on tumblr
but it's like seriously just like
going full on ballistic
it's hilarious finding a gif on tumblr
man that is like a needle in a haystack right there
it's a particular one shut up
alpha kenanagram says are you gonna watch
pokemon origins I want to it's
supposedly really short yeah that gif is from
pokemon origins so alright
ok we gotta move on with the show
we gotta get into gaming week still
we'll talk more pokemons later
but I
think I made my decision I will
say as far as pokemon goes I'm going to get
hold on shut
up I'm gonna get pokemon
why I've decided I'm gonna get pokemon
why and
I'll tell you my starter
pokemon
a little later in the show alright
let's talk about our gaming weeks
and the types of games that we have been playing
this week ladies first
dark sakura what have you been up to this week
I've been playing some stuff I actually did get on
final fantasy 14 but I was
kind of drunk at the time and
getting really motion sick so I stopped
and I finally
beat level 19 on fractal
I am so freaking happy because
it was pissing me off so now I'm on like
23 fractal is
pretty much video gaming crack
and thank you rob
for gifting
bejeweled 2 to me
because I
played the crap load of that but it's still more
fun on my phone that actually was
left over from some giveaways we did a long
time ago we just never
I mean it's bejeweled 2 it was a long time
ago so actually popcap gave that to you by
proxy but I like the the puzzle
mode in the computer version
it's actually pretty fun but for the most part
and act deft I cannot
look at videos on my ipad while
I'm doing the show sorry
he linked the video
the actual video oh well the smackdown
luckily I can bring up videos
so I'm hoping if I get
rick rolled so help me god I'm gonna get the
ban hammer and you're gonna die
blame act deft that's it
that's it okay this is only 18 seconds
and I'm sorry that this is radio
and we're about to watch a video but
enjoy this audio presentation
oh my heavens
that is the most gruesome
thing I've ever seen
those are that was
squirtle taking cream was
not okay
a bite out of charmander's neck
no the audio had to be
even worse because
that sounded like
I don't know that was that was not
okay that high pitched screaming
that was that was a little too
that was a little too visually vague for me
yeah act
deft I want you to apologize to the listeners
right now poor charmander
at live that is a rabid
squirtle that squirtle needs
to be put down oh my god that sound
was horrible although
it has settled the age old debate of
reptiles versus amphibians
because you know
turtles and salamanders natural enemies
so I played other games
that did involve squirtles biting
the crap out of charmander's
and the ahhhh
ahhhh
act deft says
sorry I'm so sorry
good good mean
it
next time loki goes on to one of his
rants I'm just going to have that queued up
oh I did buy something on sale
on steam oh what
I bought bioshock infinite last night
oh yeah they've been having six bucks
uber sales 13 is 13
and also half life 2
is like
3 dollars so I picked that up for
pc so that
you know I don't have to hurt my
hand playing it on xbox
so yeah I've
I just pretty much oh yeah and of course
my crack my animal crack
animal crossing animal cracking
which just
to say I'm actually considering busting out
the gamecube again and
playing my double
2 no mori why not because you can
unlock the nes cartridges
well yeah well the one that I have
there were two versions that came out on
gamecube there was
double 2 no mori plus which is the one
I have which was what
then we got a better one in america after
that and so that one was re-released in japan
as e plus well wasn't the original
original n64
I was n64 and we never got that
no however the
the whole reason I bought the import version
was to help me practice learning
reading japanese
because my
reading comprehension is not all that
great I read very
slowly so it was to help me
learn to
read better and so I'm gonna
be starting with that and I'm also trying to find
kids books to help me practice reading
so yeah
I've been I'm probably gonna be sort of
doubling up on my animal crossing
in the next few weeks
um and
then um dan is
all like starting to
get on fire emblem but then he's
back on gta 5 so
I'm like are you gonna be done
he's like well wait until blah blah
comes out and you're never gonna see the ds
again I'm like you watch and you're
not touching the game because I'm playing animal crossing
and I
am still trying to get the
stupid kitchen island but none of the
islands ever have it so fuck the
fucking fuckers but I have a tan now
so you have to go to the island
to get your island
to get a tan yeah to get
my island oh so
there's too much this and a that
I'll suction
but for anyone who wants to know
how to keep your tan in the winter
months go visit the island in the morning
and don't wear
a hat
some of the hats actually block you from getting tanned
is it real life is it animal crossing
I don't know anymore people
I don't know anymore hey my character is cute
alright act up
do you need to give me that
you can get another one now just give it to me
act up has a
kitchen island that needs to give it to me can't you like
visit his town and order it I'm
plugging in right now
nice
she took
my ds charger off my
ds charger off the table
and going I'm taking this
this is mine now because there's an island
for me to go steal from somebody else
she's stealing from two people
nine tenths of the law
don't encourage her alright
Chell while you're still on my good
side how was your gaming week
oh you know pretty chill you know
when I get a free minute
usually during school months
I'm kind of a casual gamer
mostly been getting my pc game on
can I plug something on there
so there's
this one indie game coming out
I've only played the demo so far
but oh man you know it's
I think it's made
an RPG maker something very similar
it's called Undertale
and the lead creator is Toby Fox
man you know give money
to this developer any way
you can if he's walking by throw money at his head
because this was like just the demo
just blew me away it has all the emotional
punches of earthbound which I'm pretty partial
too what'd you say this guy's name was
Toby Fox oh that poor guy
you know has got to be getting asked what does the
fox say she is encouraging bags of pennies
to be flung at his head
he will thank you through the tears
cause you know
he had a kickstarter and you know that
closed but you know this comes out
buy it you will thank yourself after you
stop crying which maybe never
wait so is like crying laughter
or crying like this game is really sad
or crying like they punch you in the emotions
and not even necessarily sad but it's
a really beautiful unique game experience
the whole thing is you're this kid
lost in this kind of underground place so
you know earthbound kind of
so the combat
is kind of unique the combat system is
you can choose to spare a monster
or fight them
and the whole you know this has been kind of
done before but it affects how
people interact with you and
yeah no it's saying
what I love about it will
spoil it that's how much you need to go
out and like play the demo and yeah
throw money at him hopefully paper
that's fair because there's
like in the beginning
when I first played Journey and since the game
has been out for like over a year now I think
it's fair for me to spoil it especially
cause I think everybody knows this twist
I said it was best to go on a journey to not
know that it's secretly a multiplayer game
because that so
enriches the experience cause the twist in Journey is that
you're not alone on the journey
and you can't communicate with the other person
though except through little hums
and like I can't even
explain like it's really just something you have to
experience like the bond you
start to feel with this little
thing that
you know is a real person
but is it like it's so hard
to explain I'm like but it was one of those things
because I didn't know when I played it for the first
time that that was like the twist in the game
I was like I want everybody to play Journey
like that where they find out that twist
on their own and I think that kind of keeps it
like all the more shocking
I'm sorry you just
the chat room made me think of another game
I'm playing Mass Effect 3 again
of course of course you know emotional manipulation
I'm all for that
I've also you know I really
need to pick up the first Darkness but I've also been playing
Darkness 2 cause I'm
so topical and you know I really
I'm enjoying the gameplay
but mostly I'm playing it for Mike Patton's juicy
juicy voice
fair enough
yeah you know I know it's been set up and down
but no post production the man
is demonically good
awesome
alright well I'm sure
the indie scene supports
or loves the fact that you're plugging that
stuff so yeah by all means
is there a website that you know off the top of your head?
well they've got a Tumblr and
it's just search Undertale
they should pop up I think they've got an official site
but so far it's just got the demo
on it the Tumblr is mostly posting
fan art right now and updates which are kinda
sparse and you know
I'm doing this completely unprompted
which you know I might appreciate
a game kicked my way someday
fair enough
not naming any names Toby Fox
alright
alright well let's move on then
if that's everything Chell has for now
over to Loki, Loki how was your gaming week?
I just played Grand Theft Auto
oh Mass Effect
there's a shock
to be fair I see Tim Tripp
in the chat room says oh man I missed
the Mass Effect tiers that's kinda what prompted
Jamie to go down that path she was
she was provoked by chat
but yeah Grand Theft Auto Online
and how's that going? well I heard
it had kind of a rough start
well yeah like any MMO this
they pretty much ironed it out after about three days
so it's working
so just quickly like I'm sure a lot
of people have experienced first hand and done it but
what do you do in Grand Theft Auto Online
what's the game? well there's an actual
storyline that goes along with it so basically
your character comes a little Santos after
Lamar which is Franklin's
friend in the single player game
he like follows you on Life Invader
which is their version of Facebook and
so he comes and you come into town and you're
doing jobs for different people they have
a guy Simeon that you're doing
repos for there's
some other guys that you're
doing like drug stuff for
getting you know stealing
meth from people and
that's just like the missions and then
on top of all that you can do the free
roaming stuff or you can rob liquor stores
you can steal cars
you can just
shoot people you know one on one do that stuff
or there's races, death
matches
you can do skydiving
stuff a whole bunch of
different activities in the game
and it's up to 16 players
and you get randomly thrown in
with some people usually
and then on top of that you can do these death
matches and stuff with other people so
a lot of times what I've found is I'm
getting dumped in a game I'll go do a mission or something
I'll come back and it's not the same people in the same
you know world anymore it's like
a whole different set of people
did you have something to add to that Chell?
I was just gonna say
kids don't take drugs
buy your own
don't
say that
but I've been enjoying it so far and you get to
create how your character looks based off of
like your ancestry and stuff
they have different people
that you pick as your grandparents
and your parents and then
or you pick the grandparents and that alters
what the parents look like and then
that alters what you look like
and I heard and I was reading an email
a little bit ahead of the game so I apologize
to the emailer I'm gonna spoil a little bit of their email
but I heard you can be a woman
in Grand Theft Auto Online
so that kind of helps the whole like you can never
be one but you can in Grand Theft Auto Online
yeah well you could
in 4 as well you could play a female
character in 4 for the online stuff
and of course your character is silent
so you know it's
whatever but yeah it's been a lot of fun
I've been enjoying it there's been a few people
that I've played with and stuff on there
but you know there's the
occasional kids
that are on there and stuff like I've had
a few people try to come kill me and it's great
cause you know that they're trying to kill you cause you see
them like I'm going to the store to go buy some
guns or something like that and I see this
guy just like posting up outside
and trying to hide and stuff and
it's funny cause they try to come in and shoot
me but you can't shoot in the store cause
when you walk in the store your gun disappears
so they have to wait outside the store
and so I know they're doing that so
immediately when I go out there I switch my gun and
I shoot them cause I'm like
so you shoot kids is what you're saying here on the show
I'm shooting kids playing the game
Loki is the
Loki is the enforcement to keep kids out of
Grand Theft Auto if he sees a child
playing Grand Theft Auto he will shoot them
but you can you can
you can do all sorts of things you can buy property
in the game and garages and
you can customize your cars and the way you look
and it just it's
kind of fun it's just this whole leveling up
system and stuff and you level up your stats
based on what you're doing in the game
so
I don't know I'm enjoying it I've been playing both on
PS3 and 360
the PS3 I'm on level 12 cause
I've been playing that mostly because my co-workers
say oh yeah I get the PS3 version we're gonna
be totally on there playing PS3 yeah
not a single one of them on PS3
so I may go back to 360 again
and level up my character there but
you know we have the
crew it's open we've got our
fun little logo there and stuff so
Rockstar Social Club look for crews look for
VoG Network and you can sign up
and come play with us I
guess there you go all right
well moving on to my gaming week I'll
go last and honestly there wasn't a lot to
it I have really just been playing Final Fantasy
14 this entire week just like
Logan's been playing Grand Theft Auto Online I've
pretty much only been playing Final Fantasy 14
I'm in the end game now I'm a level 50 white
mage and I'm kind of doing the stuff that you do at
end game which is running
you know CM and AK
and Praetorium and all that
to get my seal or my
I keep saying seals but they're tomes
actually and that's really mostly what I've
been doing I gotta say though I was really impressed
with the ending I'm using my
quotey fingers because you know it's an MMO it doesn't really
end but Final Fantasy 14 has
a pretty definitive
story from start to finish and when
you finish the actual story you get like
this 25 minute ending and I gotta
say I was happy with
it and it's simple
but it's effective like for somebody
that's really invested a lot of time in the game
I was like I really get the sense
that I accomplished something
and now I see what's next for my character
and that's such a great feeling playing an MMO
which usually doesn't
ever end
so yeah that's really all I can say
I can't really talk about a lot of other games I will
say I did pick
up a new toy the other day I did
pick up a new HD
game capture card or I should
say more like a box it's more a box it's like
a USB connected thing and I am really
excited because I purposely wanted to get
something that would do the new consoles through HDMI
and this does the old
consoles because the
component doubles as a composite
plugin so I am really excited
to stream a variety
of stuff as soon as I can get it working with my
laptop and all that so
that's something in the future
in the coming weeks so I
will be able to diversify things
a little more than just playing the same MMO all week
long I'm going to force myself to do that
I've been very busy with personal life
stuff Rocky Horror which I'm
directing is this coming
Saturday so as you can imagine I'm
super busy with that I wouldn't know anything about playing
all games to the exception
of all else
and how many hours have you spent on Mass Effect?
shut up 3 digits or 4 now
alright
alrighty that's enough
for our gaming weeks quickly some
housekeeping actually
I actually have things for housekeeping tonight
I want to plug another podcast I was on today
and thank them for having me check out
the Let's Wow podcast
that is World of Warcraft
so yes I still dabble in World of Warcraft even though
I've talked about a lot of Final Fantasy 14
lately but I did guest on their show tonight
that's episode number 31
and you can check that out that will be in their archive soon
available on iTunes and Stitcher
and all that again that's the Let's Wow podcast
thank you kids for having me on and we talked about
World of Warcraft and other MMOs
and I razzed my good buddy
Gemet for a good 500
minutes
let's see other things I want to plug
it is that time of year again
where a lot of podcasts
are going to be asking you to vote for them
in the podcast awards
which is right now kind of what we have
in the little podcast industry to recognize
the podcast media
sometimes
I'm a little iffy on how I feel
with it all being kind of a popularity
contest at the end of the day but
I will say being able to
be nominated for it and
collect the votes and stuff is
really good promotion for us
and it's always really
nice to be able to
kind of share in that with other
gaming podcasts that really
work hard for what they do so I hope we
will get that honor again this year
to be in the podcast awards but if we
aren't we're still going to do what we do
here every Sunday night regardless but I
would encourage you podcastawards.com
if you like what you hear here at
Orange Lounge Radio please consider
nominating us for best gaming podcast
and because you can actually do
you can do the
one of the top two categories and
a subcategory, gaming is a subcategory
we're also going to urge you to vote for People's Choice
for Orange Lounge Radio which kind of
makes sense because we're a
show about people and community and you guys
all having a voice so People's Choice
and gaming and we're choice
so there you go
check that out podcastawards.com
we really appreciate your consideration
and consider supporting other independent
podcasts that you listen to throughout
other categories as well and
if you feel that some other podcast is
more deserving of a nomination than us then that's cool
we're good just
you know support your favorite show
no matter who it may be
alright I
think that's it for housekeeping Twitter
twitter.com slash olr and Facebook
facebook.com slash orange lounge radio
alright now we can have
ourselves some gaming news
so Loki let's get on to
some gaming news
alright so let's talk a little bit about
the Xbox One
it was
I guess put out there this
last week that it's going to take
about 15 to 20 minutes to download
the Xbox One day one patch
so expect a short delay before
you get into your gaming
which if I remember
quickly I believe that is a lot
less of a wait than
you had to for the Wii U
wasn't that Wii U
day one patch like
an hour or something? well that's because
Nintendo's download servers are slow
as hell like I don't know
well I think they've gotten a lot better
but remember all the crazy Nintendo
fanboys were all hammering that thing at the same time
I mean not that it excuses it but
it's the reason why it was downloading slow
alright
and then I was going to talk real quick
because I actually had noticed this and I posted
it on Twitter earlier this week
about the
next gen digital file
sizes holy shit
so there's
some new SKUs that are coming out for a bunch of
different things and I don't know why
I guess they're just trying to get people to
buy in on this stuff but like NBA2K
14 they have a super
fan pack and also for
Call of Duty Ghost they have
an Xbox edition
and what these two
things are is they're digital
they're retail items that are digital
that you go to the store and buy
this packaging and it comes with codes for both the
Xbox 360 version and the
Xbox One version or in the case
of NBA2K the Xbox
360, Xbox One version or
PlayStation 3 and PlayStation 4 version
the fine print though tells you how big
those files are like how
much hard drive space you need so
it's not a big surprise that the current gen stuff
is anywhere from 8 to 10 gigs
the next gen stuff and this is
kind of like you know imagine if they
went that way where they were trying to really push digital
60 gigabytes
that's a long fucking time
to download that I mean that is a good
like even on my good internet connection
about 15 hours
that's a lot of HD stuff
and I mean
isn't it still out there these caps
on bandwidth that people get in a month
I think there might be some I think Comcast
suspended theirs for a little while and they were going to
up it to 300 gigs but still
imagine Comcast up their thing to 300 gigs
that's like six games in a month
which I guess that is a lot but
I mean and then nothing else on your internet
so let's be real it's still
I mean that's a long time to wait for something
digitally and yeah I understand that they do
have the technology where that they can start
streaming the game after a certain
amount of it's downloaded but shit
even if it's half of it that's still eight hours
that you have to wait before you can start playing
that game and
if that's something that you're planning on buying
at launch you know you
might as well just buy
the disc I mean cause really the
cost savings of it isn't very
significant cause basically this
pack is like 100 bucks if you get the two
games so you're really only saving like
20 bucks maybe you know
the fact that you're basically pre-ordering
this you know quite in advance and you have
to buy digital copies for both so you can't actually
trade them in whereas some of these places
I'm sure will allow you to trade in like say your
NBA 2K copy on
360 get you know maybe 40
bucks back or something like that you know
it's not that far out and
you know buy the next gen version for
20 bucks or something I still
think it'd be cheaper than having
the download all that shit I mean that's just
that's ridiculous and especially
since they're trying to push that it
one of the reasons
why the you know their big
ideas of making this all digital world is just
not feasible right now with
our internet infrastructure
it's just not gonna work
so that's it
well what do you think though if the console life cycle
is like 10 years or whatever do you
think that maybe in that amount of time
we will be at that point?
Possibly I mean it's gonna take some sort of
I think government funding
to kind of
put you know
I guess get these companies
to want to improve their infrastructure
cause right now a lot of these companies have
monopolies in the different areas and so
there's really no
no need for them to try to get their
internet speeds faster just like you know with
Comcast I was trying to get this one plan
that they had that was 70 bucks
cause I pay about 60, 70 dollars
right now for just internet it's in a
different area where it's double the internet speed that
I have now plus cable
for the same price and
of course
oh I'm sorry that plan's not in our area
it's just that's the problem
there's monopolies everywhere so you're not gonna
they're not gonna be in a big hurry to
offer faster internet
without some sort of government funding because
why bother spending the money
to upgrade our service when we can just charge more
and you know keep the same level
of service or decline it
alright well one thing people
were using their bandwidth for this week was
to watch the latest Nintendo Direct
you know Nintendo likes to do these where
they just take the news they take their case straight to
their hardcore fan base and
it's been working for better or worse for them
they unveiled the latest
Nintendo Direct on October 1st which kind
of ran down here's where Nintendo's at for the
end of the year one big
shocker maybe not I don't know
depending on what you think of these things there was
a delay Donkey Kong Country Tropical
Freeze moving to
2014 it will not make the holiday
season this was one of their big holiday
things they were hyping but unfortunately
Donkey Kong Country did move
to February 2014 is
when this game is coming out
I'm gonna go out on a limb
and say that this is strategy
that I don't know if this was necessarily
because the game's not done
but this was maybe to buff up
next or this coming winter
where things didn't work out
so well in 2013 I think you're right
because they had too much stuff coming out and
there's the fourth quarter there's too much stuff coming out
Nintendo themselves they have We Fit
You in the beginning of November
and then they have Super Mario 3D
World coming out at the end of November
and this was originally gonna be like
a couple weeks later in the early part
of December right and I think
this could also mean and I'm definitely
tinfoil hatting here a bit so don't you know
take what I say with a grain of salt here but
this could mean that Mario Kart 8 is
bumped back a little bit because what Mario Kart 8
they had said March before right?
I'm thinking
I'm thinking more like April at this
point and maybe there's something happening there
where they want to strategically spread
out the first party releases plus
I don't think there are a lot of releases
on the Wii U right now we're running
in the same situation we did last year
where there was nothing coming out for a few months
and I think that's what we're gonna see now
I definitely know there's nothing
coming out in December and there's nothing
coming out right now in
January. Well how does Xbox One and PlayStation
4 look for next year in the winter?
I mean aren't they gonna be the ones that are kinda
hurting for games in the winter? I think that
they're gonna run I think everyone's gonna run in the same
situation but right now we don't have a firm
lineup for what we have for you know
the first quarter of the year
so it's still
they haven't really announced that stuff you know probably
later on into
the fourth quarter we'll know that because
you know right now their focus is on the
fourth quarter so I don't think anything's gonna
get delayed to the you know
beginning part of the year but they still haven't made their announcements
of what titles they have coming like you know
EA hasn't announced what they really have coming aside
from you know
was it
yeah but EA's not a factor on Wii U either
true yeah very true
unfortunately
I know but even like other companies like there's
just no big titles have been announced
yeah at least not a lot of titles for
February well what up G says Titanfall
is next spring right I guess that's a big one
I think that's more summer I don't think that's
coming out in spring at all you think Destiny's gonna be that
same time frame too I know that's a big one I think Destiny's yeah
maybe fourth quarter that it's
second half of the or at least second quarter I think
fair enough going to our chat room at
live.vognetwork.com
SHJ100Matt says further proves that their whole
E3 conference video just showed
2014 games
CaptainSpike says absolutely gutted
about Donkey Kong one of my most anticipated
games of 2013
well at least you're
still getting a solid platformer in the form
of Super Mario 3D World which
some of the early previews are coming back very
positive which is no surprise at all
I mean you know a lot of the Mario
games are very strong performers I can't
think I what was the last one that people
didn't like Sunshine
that was a while ago Hotel Mario
what's that Hotel Mario
Hotel that's a long time ago hey Sunshine was fun
yeah Sunshine still has its
defenders I like Sunshine actually
myself so
I mean most Mario platformers aren't bad
they just aren't I mean there's been some
that are like that's okay but
some most of them are very very good
so
that's at least you got a solid
platformer in that to look forward to
in November now in Japan and Europe
Sonic will be
coming to Super Smash Brothers
whatever they call it which well
I was I see you rolling your eyes over there Loki
I was actually a little surprised because of the fact
it's a third party character I didn't think they'd
recycle those but I guess
cause Nintendo's not publishing
Mario and Sonic at the Olympics
I guess
this is not surprising at all
that's about surprising oh hey Luigi's in this
game oh alright
fair enough more surprising they said he wasn't in the game
next up character
Scarlet Witch
let's hope
let's see and
Pikmin 3 is getting DLC
Nintendo's kind of further going down
the DLC spiral with
Pikmin 3 DLC but a lot of people looking
forward to it and you know I gotta say the Super
Luigi U was
pretty good so I mean if Nintendo
can keep making robust DLC packages
like that this isn't a bad thing at all
also some folks very excited
I'm sure Act Deft was screaming
shaking crying and convulsing
over the fact that there is a new Kirby
game on its way to the 3DS
as if the 3DS
needed more powerhouse games but here's
another one Kirby's on its way
and Loki's going yup yup that's what I was
saying like you know all these announcements like wow
more great titles for the 3DS and then like
but when people are like Nintendo's
dying Nintendo's gonna go under
it's like the 3DS
is like
da bomb right now like you can't
I mean yes the 3DS in the
beginning little shaky but now
you've got it like if you play
handheld games at all the 3DS
we've already established on the 3DS
for 3D anymore and now we have two
screens one that's HD one that's a touch
screen just fucking put it on the Wii U
already god dammit it's gonna happen
eventually it's just
make that announcement and then done then you don't have to worry
about content because you have a ton of fucking
games already on the 3DS
that could be on the Wii U
alright I don't understand it a game I am
very excited about also on the 3DS
speaking of powerhouse games I can't think of
anything for me more a powerhouse than
Zelda A Link Between Worlds
which is coming out November 22nd
this is the spiritual successor of
sorts to Link to the Past from Super
Nintendo which holds a place near and dear
in my heart and I'm sure many of you out there
one thing they announced about the game that's
very interesting the dungeons can be played
in any order
which is not common
for the Zelda games usually without
certain items you can't get to places but like
in the early like the first Zelda
game you could run into level
you know some of the later levels
if you had a bomb you could probably go all the way
to level 9 right at the beginning right
you might need a ladder some of us have made the mistake
of doing that the first time we found it by accident
and went what the hell dead
so I would imagine there's
still gonna be an optimal order just like
in any Mega Man game or something but
the cool thing is it'll kinda open it up
for the speed runners and people
that like to bend the rules a little bit to
try different patterns so that'll be pretty cool
yeah I'm just looking forward to it
you know being just a smash hit and
quieting the people who will not
shut up about Ocarina
of Time slash Majora's Mask
look guys we all love those games
they're not the only Zelda games come on
thank you will you give me a
fist bump for that statement thank you very much
thank you like I you know
I understand those games Ocarina
and they have their place but
for me Link to the Past oh my gosh
I give a clump just thinking about how great that
game is I've got a gold cart
Ocarina of Time I agree with you
fair enough
alright I knew I liked having you on the show
alright so that is out of course
November 22nd and lastly I'll mention this
the 3DS StreetPass system
the relay points
that they instituted recently like at Starbucks
where you can actually street pass people
at Starbucks because what happens is that
when you go there
whoever was last there their data is
on the little machine waiting for you
to get it on your 3DS well they're gonna
upgrade these relay points six
people now will be on these
things so if you go to Starbucks you can get up to six
people on these things that's even better
because I mean I actually do go to the
like there's this one that Becky and I
go to like at least twice a week
yeah I know that's great that's awesome news
and some content distribution
events are planned for use
over the relay so
interesting
very cool stuff I guess it'll push demos
through to your 3DS if you opt in for it
so that'll be really cool
Dark Soccer I think you have more Nintendo
stuff for us right? But I'm putting my
island up yes I do have other news
thank you ActDeft because I've
really been wanting an island for a while
well how about
the new Wii U
firmware is also going to have a bunch
of other features now it's gonna be
700 megabytes so
it's gonna take a while to download
but it has internet browser
updates it has
more demos and trial
software USB keyboard support
Dolby Pro Logic 2
smartphones will be able
to connect to the
Nintendo network ID
you can view a friends list from the Wii U menu
you have your headset
that can hook to the gamepad and be used
for chat and you can read
PDF files on the Wii U
and you can also save your passwords
for websites so
lots of stuff
you also have to accept a new license agreement
I'm telling you this because I just updated
my Wii U not that long ago
I also want to put this PSA out there
those Wii U updates can take a little while
especially because it was what like 700 megabytes
that's what I was saying
so put on a movie
call your mom
my point is don't wait until
the day Mario 3D
comes out to do this
like if you're listening to my voice
and you haven't done this yet you probably just want to go turn
that guy on right now and just let the update be over
and done with and then be ready for
Zelda Wind Waker HD or whatever the next game
is you're going to get
or get up in the morning have an update and call your mom
or whichever relative
you have living right now
fair enough, fair enough
talk to them
and go outside and get some fresh air
get a job, wait I need to get a job
alright Loki
alright
so let's see here let's talk a little bit about
PlayStation 3 getting its own
firmware update as well
4.5 finally came out
and what it does is adds the
auto downloads
to people that are not in
PlayStation Plus so you'll be able to
also transfer data between your
PlayStation 3 and Vita versus
via Wi-Fi
and ethernet connections I guess
originally you could only do it through the transfer cable that they had
and
also lets you
set up I guess groups
of players that can
see your trophies so you can
either have that open to everybody I don't know why you wouldn't
why you would hide your trophies from
people unless there was like a trophy
for going to the strip club a lot of times
and Grand Theft Auto 5 or something you know I don't
know well
remember when I was getting
all those achievements in Dance Dance Revolution
Universe because I had it like the day it came out
and I started playing it right away and I got a
message from what was his name
that guy who had all the achievements
he ended up getting banned from Xbox
because it turns out they were a strip club DJ
that was his name he sent me a message like
how are getting the achievements in that game
what's the difficulty like
like I don't even know how he found me I think he used one of
those like websites that shows you like
who's doing well in achievements and I think
at that moment in time I had more
achievement points in that game than anyone else
I mean like on release day so
maybe if I'm in that situation
and again I want to hide trophies
oh it just occurred to me
if I'm reviewing games
people might ask me to turn that feature on
to not spoil because a lot of the trophy lists
leak from review copies
so maybe that's to encourage
critics and so forth to not leak it
I bet that would be one
anyways they have it
so
cool but yeah so basically
so the auto download is kind of cool
about time everybody gets that
here's the thing okay and this isn't really a playstation
but like you know speaking of
system updates and stuff fucking 360
man every time I log in live
now I'm still getting that fucking prompt
to add a second like
a second method to confirm my passwords
or stuff if I need to
you know like a second way they can contact
me basically and I've filled it out
a bunch of times
and I've even filled it out either via
you know texting via email
and it still fucking says oh
sorry you only have one form to
contact you are you okay with this
I'm like yes I'm okay with this nope sorry
you need to please add another
way to contact us that's weird and I even did it through
the website they have a special website you go
to to confirm that because obviously it says
oh yeah you can go ahead and
add it through this oh I'm sorry actually no you can't
add it through this you have to go onto this
website to do it and I did that and
it confirmed it and it still
fucking doesn't work and I get prompted every
fucking time I log in you need to call Microsoft or something
it's not like something's wrong fucking flip
them off is what I need to do aren't
you kind of doing that right now
because Microsoft executives
right now and their tech supporter
listening to the show and going oh
no one customer is having a problem
well I'm a
customer that has a podcast
fear me he's a loud
ass customer let's be real dark
sakura so are you
everyone has a voice that's right
and we use our voice to say fuck you
alright
speaking of like consoles
and things one console will be going
away rest in peace
bye it's
Nintendo's Wii believe it or not Nintendo's
Wii will be ending production
soon in Japan
so we don't have any
worry about you know the US or other
territories Canada Europe we don't know but
in Japan let's be
real the Wii isn't selling so hot anymore
Wii units were sold in a week which
really isn't a lot so the Wii is going
to be fading to black and
it kind of makes sense for Nintendo like
you know push the Wii U make people buy
that to play the games make
sense for them so yep they'll be
sunsetting the Wii and I
I wouldn't I would bet that maybe
trying to push the Wii U a little harder
especially in a year where
in Japan there's no competition
isn't exactly a bad
move so
nice knowing you Wii
good not to have yourself as competition
right because well in a way
that's what Nintendo would have right now in Japan
if you think about it in terms of production
cost making a machine that no one's buying
then yeah
there's no need to keep putting the production
money into it when you could be
using it for Wii U I mean what is going to be
on the shelves in Japan there's Wii U
now there's not a Wii there's 360
but in Japan that's not
a factor sorry and the PlayStation 3
you know so it's literally gonna be
do you want the new system or the old system
that's the way it is in Japan right now
it'll be interesting
so of course handhelds
it's a whole nother Oprah because they
are making a push with the Vita in Japan
big time we talked about that already last week
alright one more story and then we'll travel
around the world and check out release dates Stark Sakura
I was giving you back your
power supply rod thank you for bringing back what you
borrow yes because I'm always
good that way well here is
something that how long have you had some of my
games
what you mean
that I've actually played
I'm just gonna be
playing games okay
so well this should interest
you you like SimCity
don't you I like the old SimCity
I like the first SimCity game
I like SimCity action news on the
CD-ROM remember that do I have
to go get those YouTubes because I will
ah there's a big mine
no
they should make me a voice actor
well Maxis is
considering an offline mode for SimCity
the note
was put on the state of SimCity
blog where the Emeryville
manager Patrick Beutcher
I guess is saying
that they are considering
an offline mode apparently since a lot
of people yes
Alan I will check out your Saturn
um since
a lot of people have been complaining
that it is specifically on
the quote says right now we
have a team specifically focused on
exploring the possibility of an offline mode
I can't make any promises on when we
will have more information but we know this is
something that many of our players have been asking for
so
who knows maybe it'll be sooner rather than
later I'm interested
I don't have the game
yet but I'm interested in offline mode
here's my concern because
SimCity is starting to come down in price a little bit
I have a feeling that
they'll do it as part of an expansion
or something to get you to spend the full 60
bucks which
I mean whatever I would consider
still spending it on an offline SimCity
that doesn't require Origin
but we'll see
yeah
well I honestly
and just on the same note
I wish that there would be
updates across the board for all of them so you don't
have to use Origin but that's me
and everybody else that plays
Mass Effect 3
alright traveling around the world
and checking out some release dates things that
will be coming a little sooner than
SimCity offline mode Loki
this week on Playstation 3 we have
Beyond 2 Souls coming out
also Borderlands
2 game of the year edition making its way
out on Playstation 3, Xbox 360
and PC
Disgaea D2 A Brighter Darkness
on Playstation 3, the Capcom
Essentials Collection on
Xbox 360 and
PS3 and
that's a bunch of old games by the way
Just Dance 2014
on Playstation 3, Xbox 360
Wii and Wii U
Dishonored game of the year edition
on Playstation 3, Xbox 360
and PC
and then
let's see here
also
on Saturday
just a small
portable game called Pokemon
X and Y those will be coming out in 3DS
might sell a couple copies
yeah maybe a couple
and then on
Sunday
they have Skylanders Swap Force
it's new because
you can take the top part of the character
and put it on the bottom part of another character
woooo
innovation
and jumping you can jump now
woooo
sell me a thousand copies already
it will sell
much more than a thousand copies
uh yes so
hey you know my 5 year old nephew is nuts
about that game so
5 year old nephew checked out Disney Infinity
as well? I have permanently
disbarred him from anything Disney related online
so no
wow this sounds like a story
I also want to mention
that also on Saturday
they coincide with the Pokemon
X and Y on the 3DS
you can buy a 2DS
one less
DS in there
if 3D is too much for you
if the 3D will blow your mind
the 2D will just kind of simmer your mind
I am hearing, take it with a grain of salt
but I am hearing that the 2DS
a lot of people kind of like the way it feels
when they play it for what it's worth
I mean despite the fact that
a lot of people have been very critical about the design
how it doesn't fold the same way and so forth
hearing a lot of positive feedback about
how it feels when it's in your hands
I'd like to mention though
even though I do happen to peruse
the Evil G website for some release dates
sometimes I am kind of
confused at why they're selling
GoPro accessories for
Gamestop
I don't know
Moving on to Japan and checking out
the releases over there on the Playstation 3
on October 10th
the Batman Arkham Twin Pack which came out here
just last week I think
comes out in Japan
it's called the best series
also coming out in Japan on the 10th
F1 2013
Grand Theft Auto 5's Japanese release
Mina no Golf 6
gets a best release
a price reduction
Sakatsuku Pro Soccer Club
comes out from Sega
and Tales of Symphonia
the Unisonant pack comes out
there's like a regular
there's a Famitsu Deluxe pack
and there's a Lalabit Market
limited edition pack
so there's all that if you're Tales of Symphonia
looking forward to that
also worth mentioning a game called Fairy Fencer F
comes out from Compile
in a regular and limited edition
Fairy Fencer
is that like fencing?
you put them on a spike
and then you fence
each other with dead fairies
that would be awesome
they're not Navi fairies
they're like
they're like carrying
pole arms
she's fighting a grizzly bear
and yes of course she's wearing a short skirt
and you can pretty much
see her hoo-ha hanging out
by fairies do you mean Vocaloids?
because that's what they look more like
I think it might be I'm not sure
but Fairy Fencing
they're fencing your face off
basically if you're that grizzly bear
I'm a fenced
alright
let's see what's coming out on other systems in Japan
this week
moving on over to the Xbox 360
ha ha I know but there are still things
coming out including Grand Theft Auto 5
F1 2013
the Batman Arkham pack
and there's an Xbox Live 12 month
2 gold membership card that comes with
Grand Theft Auto 5
I don't really know what that means but that is something that is happening in Japan
they probably had something similar here
I just missed it
on the Playstation Vita this week Dream Club Zero Portable
gets a price reduction
a new game called Getsuigakuen
cool comes out this week
wait wait what?
Getsuigakuen Co
comes out this week
can I see what that looks like?
you sure can
this is the one screenshot I have
unless this other
let me check out this other page
might have more
fantastic radio here we have
that just shows what it comes with
I want to see what the limited edition comes with
I thought I've heard of it before
but I don't remember off hand
aha it looks like they get the game
a book, maybe a school book
a music CD
and trading cards?
that's a drama CD
no
the CD is
basically like a play
like radio drama
so maybe this is based off some type of
drama series
alright also on the Playstation Vita
Metal Gear Solid HD edition
getting a price reduction
and I think some new Vita
equipment comes out this week
is this the week of the Vita Slim model?
it is, so this is the week where
your black, khaki black, light blue white
lime green white, pink black
white and black slim models
all come out, so no wonder
there's so much on the Vita this week
oh my gosh there's Slaughter Mania 5
like slaughter, like slot machines
not like I'm gonna go kill a bunch of zombies
Slaughter Mania
Uncharted Golden Abyss gets a re-release
in the best hits
Soul Sacrifice gets a re-release
and then Sakatsuku Pro Soccer Club
Osukuru
comes out this week also
so lots of stuff going on on the Vita this week
now that makes sense
now that I see that the
Vita Slim is out this week
so I'm sure there will be some people here for that
on the Wii U, sadly nothing to report this week
but Rayman Legends coming up next week
you got a little time
and on the Nintendo 3DS this week
Pokemon X and Y is also
on Japan, it's like a worldwide release
also a big release for them
on the 12th and
there's all sorts of accessories
you can get
Froki pens
Chesapeake pouches
and
Lord knows what else, there you go
all that coming out in Japan
this week on the 3DS
Dark Sakura?
Well we have a pretty
slender selection for the UK
on the 9th there's Montague's Mount
for PC
and
on the 11th we have
Beyond 2 Souls for PS3
that's about it
alright just a couple more news stories for you guys
and then the classic game of the week
and it will surprise no one
Loki?
alright
so let's see here
SNK
they are getting rid of
the Neo Geo X, you may remember
the Neo Geo X is kind of that
rebuild I guess of the
classic Neo Geo
they also had this
portable system that was
plugged into this dock
it was kind of emulating everything
but
now they have cease and desist
against the website that sells the Neo Geo X
I guess they were saying
that the notice which
appeared on October 2nd
demands an immediate cease and desist
of manufacturing, distribution, promotion
and selling of the Neo Geo X
gold limited edition mega pack
volume 1 and classic volumes 1 through 5
as well as the Neo Geo X
arcade stick in order to
protect our intellectual property rights
such as Neo Geo and SNK
see here I thought
me being naive I guess that
they had the go ahead to go ahead and make that stuff
since they had SNK on it
and it was a fucking Neo Geo
I mean at least it looked like one
come to find out they didn't
they just kind of put it out there anyways
wow, it's been out for a while too
I was going to say I forgot the thing even came out
how horrible is that
but I mean they've recycled those Neo Geo games
like a ton of them are available on
Virtual Console and Playstation 3
download I mean
if you want something a little more authentic
I guess you could get this but
keep in mind those licensed ones
SNK gets money for
true, they would get no money
if they didn't
provide their license
ok, here's what it is, I get it now
I guess it was licensed
because Tomo was the one that was putting it out
they do a lot of license, weird shit
but now they're ending
their license agreement so
it's no longer going to be sold after the 2nd
wow, the 2nd of October?
well then it's done
it's done, yes, so
kind of makes me wonder
it sounds very like
not like we've decided
to, you know, end our
licensing agreement with Tomo, we're just not going to
produce anymore, it's like please be informed that
our company is
or the licensing agreement is
terminated as of October 2nd
so what happens to all these unsold consoles
they go in a landfill in New Mexico?
no, they still get sold, they just can't produce anymore
oh, well that's good
go get them now
if they're sitting on some then yeah
I don't think they can sell them
they don't have an agreement to do so anymore
if there's some out there in a while
there's something they can do about that
this will be a collector's item very soon
no company for ET down there
I'll still
stick with my Neo Geo
you got the real thing though, why even bother
with this stuff if you have the real thing
because it has the games loaded on the system
you know how much I paid for the last cartridge
I bought?
we paid $300 for
what was the last one we got?
King of Fighters 2000
when I had money
blows me away how much those cartridges cost
the 48 in 1's
there's a ton of them on one cartridge
Bobby knows
alright
one more story about Terraria
which is a hardcore fan
I saw Terraria on
Playstation 3 this weekend
I was at Fry's randomly when I got the
capture box
and I didn't realize because it comes with
all that extra stuff, it has a neat little box
that it comes in with the drive and everything
so I was kind of looking at that going
oh neat
I personally way preferred Minecraft
to Terraria but I know Terraria
definitely has its fans, people love the
retroness and the 2D that Terraria has
and so the good news is Terraria 2
it's a thing that's happening
Andrew Spinks the creator of Terraria
talked about Terraria 2
saying it is definitely something
that will be happening but contrary
to several of the articles that went live today
I have not started development
I have a list of features and mechanics
I want the game to have but that is the
extent of the development at this point
so in other words, he's going to do it
it's announced in that regard
but that's it, we don't have anything else
so don't plan on this happening anytime
soon
let's see, also in the interview
mentioned that version 1.2
will be the last
7 month update for the original game
but that he will change the end game
up for the update within the next month
or two because there was no final
boss and there may be some other
smaller updates a few more months down the line
he might hire a team to
do some updates but he'll be
focusing on Terraria 2 soon
so there you go
Darkstalker, you played a little bit of Terraria right?
Yeah, you gave me a copy
Yeah, I remember that, I bought like a 4 pack
It was interesting
I don't think I could quite get into it very well
but it was interesting, it amused
It amused me for an hour
Thank you for amusing me for an hour, Rob
You're welcome
Alright, well let's talk about a game that has amused Darkstalker
for a hell of a lot longer than an hour
and it amused her earlier today
when she picked it
as the classic game of the week
because every week Darkstalker dives into the gaming vault
and pulls out a game 10 years or older
and says
Hey!
Respect this game and play it now
Dust it off
Darkstalker, you better play bitch
You better play
Darkstalker
What is the classic game of the week?
The game is
Animal Crossing
AKA Dobutsu no Mori
Animal Forest
It is a life sim game
and I miss this music, Rob
The old school music
Wasn't it good?
It was good
I was actually running around the house
making up lyrics to this to Midna
because she was looking at me like I was insane
She probably does that a lot, I bet
Shut up
So anyway
and of course the one that I linked on here
is actually the Nintendo 64 one
which was the very first Dobutsu no Mori
It came out in Japan on April 14, 2001
and came out on the GameCube as
Animal Forest Plus
in
the next December
so that was in 2002
and then came out in other countries
as Animal Crossing
and like I had mentioned earlier
in the show, because we got
so much more stuff over here
they released a new version that was called
Animal Forest E Plus
which actually has characters in that one
that are in no other versions
of the game
If you want to read more about them, look on the wiki
There's a really, really good
Animal Crossing wiki
So the game itself
is
No, Bobby, I'm not doing Halo
So the game itself
has evolved over time
but I'm going to focus on the
GameCube one since that is
probably the one
the majority of us have started with
So with the very first
game, and it was
like this on the Nintendo 64 as well
you would
arrive in town
homeless
penniless and get forced into
indentured servitude by the
evil Tom Nook
who is the mobster
boss of your town
it's in all
reality, you know, it's a very
open-ended game, it keeps going, you have
different holidays in town
you have to, you know, earn money
and pay off your mortgage
and you can expand your house
people were there
to collect NES games
that's what they were there for
sorry, I can't contain myself
so anyway
you have to
you know
you earn Bells, which is the in-game currency
you pay off your loan
and in the
and you hit villagers with bug nets
you know, I keep hitting that fucker Ed
with a bug net and he won't move
I'm not the only one having to
deal with Ed by the way
so, he's a dumb horse
so anyway, you also could
collect Nintendo
Entertainment games
and as far as I'm aware
I think this just popped up
in
I want to say just in the
GameCube ones
you basically
you could get, you know, Ice Climber
and Mario Brothers
those were available via
eReader
there were all kinds of
they also said that The Legend of Zelda
was in the game, but they had no means
of obtaining it
I think it was supposed to be like a prize or something
so yeah
there were different multiplayer modes as well
where you could
have up to four people living
in the village
you couldn't play at the
same time as anybody else, but you could take turns
like, Dan and I would see
who could pay off our mortgage faster
and who got the gold statue and who got the silver statue
and finally I'm like, bitch make your own town
so he has Danville
that was his town
you also
can
ship items from one to another
via codes
and you can say, hey
milk you asshole, send this to Rob
and Fetch, which is your town now
isn't it? What was your old town?
Rob is...
sorry I was eating
my old town was
I think it was like Robville or something silly
yeah, well Dan had Danville because Danville
exists
you could also leave messages to each other
on the big board
that's in the center of town
and I still do that when I visit people's
towns as I'll say, hey Jamie was here
so and so sucks
steal Ed from me, still trying to steal Kabuki from you
now this I wanted to play a little bit
do you hear how the voice sounds?
now
in the Japanese version
basically they are
they say every syllable
every kana
so you can actually, I mean it's really
sped up and fast, but you can actually kind of
pick out what they're saying
for the American, for the English versions
basically they say each letter
so it really does sound like a bunch of gibberish
and the voices of course
went a little bit differently because they had to
redo them to say each of the letters
you had another thing
that was only in the earlier ones
and that was
Mr. Resetti or as he was
called in Japan, I think he was Resetsan
so
if you turned off your game without saving
the next time you turned it on, he'd pop out of the ground
and berate you for like an hour
so basically he annoyed you into not doing it again
you um
now the part that's showing on the video right now
if you can kind of hear some of it
is where you talk to Rover
who basically he asks you questions
and depending on how you answer it determines what your looks are
so
I always cheat and use an FAQ
so that my character will look how I want her to look
um
now with the GameCube one you could also use
the Game Boy Advance to do stuff on the island
you were able to
um
uh
basically get fruits from villagers
you get bells, you would be able to
use the islanders tools
and bury things
and pick them up later
you also were able to um
use uh
the pattern design tool for the Able Sisters
on your Game Boy Advance
so you were able to use that to create
different things
another thing that you know
is still one of my favorite parts of the game
um is that uh
you had a character who
in the Japanese version his name was Toda Keke
who if I remember right
he was named after
a music composer
um over here he's Keke Spider
and he would
he would sing different uh
songs in the old ones he would
sing in I believe it was the town square
um in later versions
he would also sing at the Roost Cafe
now he actually has Club Lowell
where he sings on Saturday nights
and you listen to the song and you can
get a demo version and now the stores
actually sell his music
you can also use um the music
as the album art
on your wall as a poster
but going back to the um
okay here it is it was actually um
Totaka Kazumi
um so that's where Toda Keke's name came from
so uh
at any rate the game had
absolutely
adorable music just really neat songs
you had all kinds of genre
represented in Toda Keke's music
um
and then um just the background music
was really iconic I mean
to this day I still like I was
saying I've gone around singing the stupid
theme song to my cat
you know I'd like to play
the game at certain times of the day because
certain music will play I really
love the midnight music I love to play
at midnight just because of the music
now the other thing that you had going on in this game was
your collection
you could collect um
uh well I'm not gonna
say these are officially a collectible item
but you get the um haniwa
which uh we got as gyroids
which after it rained you could dig them up
in the ground because back in the old school
days haniwa were buried with the dead
so that's why you dig them
up out of the ground
um and
Alpha Kinanagram also wants to point out that
Totaka has um
his uh song which actually
is in the game
as Keke's song
the little hidden thing that was also in Mario
Paint and all the different
you know things that he ever did sound designed
for so
um
at any rate um you could
collect fish and there are certain fish
that show up at different times of the year you have different
bugs that show up at a different time of the year
you also could collect um works of art
different paintings and like
and you also had different special
characters that would pop up I already mentioned
Mr. Resetti you had the able sisters
who made the clothes you had
Tom Nook who was the
evil mafia boss of the town
um also there uh
he was the one percent of
my village you had
uh
the police dogs copper
and what was the other one's name
I can't remember the other one's name
um there were
uh
now we have Isabelle and Digby
in the newer ones uh
Isabelle is your uh apparently she never
sleeps cause she is at the stupid
uh town hall all
the damn time you could change
your town theme you could change catch
phrases like we used to make people say some
really dirty ass things and Nintendo finally got
smart and yeah
might have been an offender with that
well I've got um
Rowan going around wearing the Link
outfit saying kitty fuck
hahaha
um you know
we used to have Dina remember Dina
and she apparently
um is no longer
a gym teacher but a music
teacher she's a folk singer
Rob staying with her ways
nice um
but you know all of your different villagers you've got
different um types of personalities
they actually brought back the
uh sort of big sister personality
the perky and the
uh sort of friendly older brother personality
that were in earlier games
um and different characters that go back and forth
now the other thing with this is it is
and I've mentioned this before
Bobby, Bobby said he made
all this town people say just ignore him
Halo classic game of the year it's not gonna happen
he's trolling you and it's working I know but I'm just
laughing at him because he's still trying
and it's just not funny
um
I've made
Ed say I totally suck is his
greeting and then his catch phrase is
I really suck
I fucking hate Ed
um now in the newer ones you've got
like you can have a campsite where people can
visit and they'll play stupid games and
steal your money fuckers
I mean just all kinds of stuff to do
and there's the island you know I mentioned the island
and
I can't help it I had
I've had so much fun with
the first game now to bring up
um what I was talking about about
the dialogue about it you know since
Japanese is basically a syllabic
uh alphabet
I picked up the GameCube
one in Japanese to practice my reading
and lo and behold my
reading actually improved I mean I'm way
out of practice now but it was a
very very good educational tool so
I'm actually offering this out here
to anyone who happens to be
a beginner learner who's
wanting to practice your reading to
understand grammar and syntax
basically get Animal Crossing on GameCube
I mean use it to import
other copies it will really
really really help your reading comprehension
in Japanese and it's not kanji
heavy so
you don't have to really worry about it
um so anyway
there's so much to do
the original was fun
the newer ones are fun I mean they kind of got
stale with City Folk
and Wild World but I think
that um the last one
that um New Leaf
really has brought back a lot
of the fun that was in the game I mean of course you
don't have the uh NES games heading around
but it's still super fun I mean
I think
anybody can appreciate it I still say though and I said this on
a previous show but I wish they'd just develop a
handful not a lot but a handful of very
simple like flash style games
that you could unlock that would be a lot of fun
or maybe old Game & Watch
oh yeah that would be cool
things that they don't sell at all in Virtual Console
until then I will have to make myself
happy by being very very
this is the other thing I was going to mention
is that there was a full length movie
um based off it and it actually had
as your animal characters it had
they were all characters in the game
and one of them lives in my village now
in the US she's Margie
in uh in Japan she's Sally
the elephant who's like one of the main main characters
lives in my village and I found out
that Act Duff has a bouquet
or Rosie in the US one
so I was sort of like oh that's
cool sort of like a way to be
involved so anyway
um Animal Crossing
lots of fun alright there it is
your classic game of the week
Animal Forest
or Animal Crossing is the case
maybe uh very awesome
game I do love that game
uh yep and I love the 3DS one too
so um even though I do miss the NES
games but uh a good pick
another great pick while we're going down
these games that are 10 plus years
old yet I remember them like they were
yesterday anyway
you know if Bobby keeps trolling me about Halo it's never
happening oh threatening
now alright not threatening that's a promise
alright
uh we're going to take a quick break guys
when we come back there is plenty more orange
songs ready to come including the Fugu question of the week
some more updates on Wii U and
Jamie I know is going to be excited
about this release for Steam she will
probably buy this yet again on Steam
it's got to be that good we'll talk
more about it when we come back with more of
Orange Lounge Radio right after this
welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge
Radio live on this
Sunday evening October
the what day is it today October
something October the 6th
how about of 2013
where our 522nd
episode is in progress
and uh looking at our
chat room we were playing a kind of a variety
of music during the break there some
uh mostly like Super Nintendo classics
in there uh although we did have Animal
Crossing music starting it off we did have uh
I played something from Chrono Trigger
but then I played a Super Metroid song right after it
to try and troll Bobby back a little bit for you
Dark Sakura but then I followed it with a game
we can all agree is amazing A Link to the Past
so just a variety of music and uh
I like how our chatters who are
with us live on Saturday night will try to shout
out like what song is that or try to guess the music
while we're playing it so uh always a fun
time here live but we try to make it fun for the podcast
listeners too I was happy you played Animal
Crossing for me well you're welcome
cause it makes me happy I miss the first
game song sooo
much
I have a really good story about Animal Crossing
and that would be the way like I actually got
Animal Crossing um actually
Loki actually bought Animal Crossing for
me um years ago we used to
all put well you know we were all playing DDR we all
used to post on these local forums for
uh Sacramento DDR players and
I remember we were all pretty close I mean there was only about
like maybe 20 of us that actually ever posted on these boards
regularly but we were all a pretty close group
you know this was before Facebook and any of
that shit maybe about the time Live Journal was starting
to boom and uh Loki was
like you know um
what would you do if you just got a big bonus at work
what would you spend the money on I said I'd get a
GameCube and Animal Crossing and I come home from work
and what did Loki do he bought me a GameCube and Animal
Crossing it was one of the nicest things
it was one of the nicest things anyone's ever done for me so
now we're all poor as much of an asshole
as you are on this show sometimes Loki
deep down in he's a really nice guy so
there you go I told a nice story
about Loki on this show but no I
really appreciated that to this day that was like one of
a really awesome thing so
uh so hearing the music I
came home and that was on loop because I guess they
left it powered on I don't even know how you got into the house
you must have contacted my roommate at the time or something
yeah and uh set that all
up so that when I got home from work it was already on the
TV it was really cool so
alright well let's get back into some
rapid fire wait I gotta ask before
we get into rapid fire news Chell
you're quite the artist over there I see you uh
I see you what is that crocheting over there
what are you doing I am macromang a
frickin' belt nice I'm
working my way up to creepy owl
I have got I've got I got an entire
box of you know old hemp and jute
from um this customer of my
mom she's got a yarn shop but um
yeah she uh people tend to
just drop off fibers with her so I'm like
score nice
so you're actually making like you make like do you
do you do like etsy or any of the online sales
stuff for crafts you do no you know
usually um since my mom's got
a shop front I just you know
put stuff out there oh right I work
in ceramics too so I try to kind of add on
to what she has I make uh yarn bowls
and people always ask do you have an etsy
I'm like you're standing literally two feet
do you wanna what do you wanna do
very
excuse me I'm choking on a sunflower seed very nice
well good luck with uh all of those
projects and I like the belt you got going on
so far it looks very intricate with the way you kind of have to
tie that together so yeah it's it's my third
so I've I've kind of it's been a steep learning
curve trust me well yeah
I can't even do this I can't even sew
hey I hear the 70s are making a comeback
it actually is looking really good
I like it it's cool all right you should post
a picture on the tumbler or something one of those places
all right uh let's
get to some rapid fire news and
uh quickly running down a few
of the fast game stories this week
Loki all right so the mighty number
nine kickstarter finally finished
and they ended up with four million
dollars and
uh will be coming out on a lot of different platforms
like spring 2015
let's say
maybe summer of 2015
because we all know how these kickstarters are
uh Xbox 360, Xbox one
PlayStation 3, PlayStation 4, Vita, 3DS
pretty much every platform everything everything
got funded for everything I forgot to kickstart it
oh well that's fine did I
not say it
would get funded for everything I know you
did I predicted I just
I forgot they had the PayPal
and that the $150,000 in the
PayPal was going into the funds too
I forgot about that they still made
like other kickstarters they still may take money
via PayPal after
you know everything's said and done
it's fine I'll just wait
and buy it yeah it's spring 2015
fuck why am I buying stuff that comes out in 2015
exactly I need the money
now yeah I'm not buying stuff that comes out in
2014 yet let alone but thanks
to everybody who funded it for me so I can buy it
later
all right and uh
I know this game was crack for us
a little bit ago
seems like a little bit ago probably a couple years ago
tiny tower
is back and now tiny tower
has a new licensed product
Star Wars tiny
death star
coming to a mobile platform near you
that sounds kind of awesome I've got to say
are you going to build a tiny death star dark
sakura maybe
she's already building one in her house no
because I have
I have a
I have a village to run I'm the mayor
I'm empress sakura of normandy and I don't have time
for a death star
this makes me think of when they did that whole like
what's that website where you can do the white house
petitions or whatever and somebody
actually asks whitehouse.org
maybe or .gov
I thought they had like a spinoff site or something where you can do the
petitions specifically
oh I thought it was like a separate website
I don't know if I'm looking forward to
the inevitable
version you know kill ball heights
you know where they
have where you know
design your own
yeah
and then finally
you know because there's a lot of movie
or games
based on movies coming out but we have another
date for one warcraft
the movie coming to theaters
December 18th 2015
and
yeah
hell I know need for speeds coming
out next spring
I kind of want to see it just because it looks like
a generic racing action movie
we still don't know who's
in the cast for the warcraft movie though just a date
and I'm thinking like
ok that's a placeholder date that's one of those
hollywood games of chess
where they start to block out what movies
are coming out when and get away from my movie
and all that and you know
so don't hold fast that this
will actually go through
because it might get delayed to 2016
it might come out earlier sometimes movies come out
earlier although I doubt that because I haven't even started filming
yet so
yeah I mean I don't know
I guess it starts filming next year
in January but
I'm not really excited
for it because I don't know any of the
lore so it's just like hey
Lord of the Rings again or something
if the movie is going to be successful it's got to be accessible
to non warcraft players
it has to be all about thrall
I don't care I want thrall the movie
I think they're taking it way back well it was supposed to be alliance centered
but that was an early rumor
but Varian's a dick and no one cares
I think it's going back I don't think the game
is going to be based off of World of Warcraft
or the movie is going to be based off of
World of Warcraft I think the movie is going to be based off of
Warcraft or like Warcraft 3
maybe well that's cool
because then you get
a what's your face who I think is awesome
Sylvanas that'd be cool
now Tigerclaw
points out that the Warcraft movie is going to
December 2015 because 2015 is
overcrowded with some huge blockbuster
movies during the summer already
yeah isn't that when the
Age of Ultros comes out is 2015
as well right Avengers 2
and then what else is in the summer
2015 is that when Independence Day 2 is
finally happening oh my god I'm so
excited I only care about
it see like it starts you know
just like you know last Independence Day I saw it
was a third fourth and fifth I
kind of want to do that again I hope it's terrible
I hope it's absolutely I hope it is absolutely
god awful and I will be there every day I hope
Elizabeth Berkley is on the cast because that would be
awesome but it still has to have Jeff
Goldblum it is supposedly having
Jeff Goldblum the only one that's not coming back is Will Smith
but it'll be like Will Smith's kid
because he's like I'm a real actor now bye
Will Smith's kid well it's not even Will Smith's kid
it's just going to be some other like
other dude that's going to be like some
some other black pilot you know that's
going to be in the role who cares
you know what it doesn't matter it's not all about
Will Smith you know what they need uh
Randy Quaid ghost only way
they can make this movie Randy Quaid ghost
slash zombie the chat room
is making fun of me because apparently I had
a Freudian slip and I said age of
Ultros instead of Ultron
you know you've been playing too much
Final Fantasy when dot dot
dot wow
it would make for a more interesting movie
to be honest yeah it's true
honestly let's be real it would be a better
movie okay I'm I'm
I'm pissed because no actually
in the Marvel comics right now they're
they're pushing an age of Ultron right now
and I think that's the only reason why the next
movie is going to be Ultron
because it was fully set up for
Thanos hello yeah I know right
they just want to make you wait till three
I just I just thought of a tagline since
we're bringing Elizabeth Berkeley
into the cast as she should be uh
independence Independence Day
everybody got independence and shit
that
that is so obscure
there's like maybe five percent of the
audience if that is going to get that reference
but I love you just a little bit
more for making it Rob what
darling you are independent
I don't know what you're doing
in that jet but it sure as hell
ain't fighting any
no
one understands no
one I think the people who do understand
will make up for the ones that don't other movies
coming out in 2015 star wars
uh star wars episode seven
star star what
yeah
some flop movie in space
no I'm kidding actually if the rumors are true that Daniel
Day-Lewis is going to be in it
like that guy can like he could
act the phone book and it would be amazing
did you see the mock-up poster that some
I think it was like a photoshopping job but it was
sure it was really cool yeah that
had like the original actors and everything
you know looking their age and all that
as the characters would have been later on
that's pretty cool oh I do want drunk
Carrie Fisher in the movie so that would be
awesome
uh yeah oh man
alright and also in 2015 sorry I know this is
rapid fire news I'm using my quoting fingers
also in 2015 let's not forget
Batfleck is in 2015
and
you know what here's the thing though
here's the thing I
love Batman
stuff and
my favorite Batman honestly
is the Adam West era Batman
um
can it really get any cheesier than that
I don't know yeah but did you see
Daredevil well that was bad
can it really be worse than Batman and Robin
can it really get any worse
that's a good good question cause
that movie was bad you know the only reason
I saw it was because someone else paid for
it and drugged me along to see it
must be nice cause I wasn't gonna
spend any money on that and that's still two hours of my life
I can't get back I wanted to see it because
there is no such way there is no
way that Arnold
Schwarzenegger as Mr. Freeze is not gonna be
entertaining there is like no
way everybody chews
there is no way that's not gonna be entertaining
oh god as a lifelong Batman
fan I'm kinda resigned to the fact that he kinda
goes in cycles you got the goofy Adam
Westing kinda thing then you got the ultra
super serious reboot and then you
got you know it bleeds into the Adam Westing again
eh you know come back around
I'll give it a chance because everybody
hated the idea of Michael Keaton as well
and he turned out to be awesome but here's the
thing the original Batman was also
a Tim Burton movie and then
you know who was the guy that did the next trilogy
why am I his name is slipping my mind right now
no not Schumacher fuck him the next guy
those movies were terrible the guy who just did
these recent three where did he get the goddamn name
oh my god
bad fan
well I'll put it
he proved himself and when he cast Heath Ledger
I know a lot of people were skeptical but I was like
no Batman Begins was the shit
Christopher Nolan thank you Christopher Nolan
Batman Begins was the shit
this guy knows what he's doing I will trust
his judgement but here's the thing Zach
Snyder I don't
know about you sir
for the record by the way I am not
going to see it because I am currently
on a DC boycott
no I'm serious
because of how they're
treating their writers for their portrayal
of women in their comics and
for the whole marriage bullshit
just so that they don't have to let Batwoman
get married yeah that was a little weird
also their audition for a new
artist here draw Harley Quinn trying to
kill herself in three panels sexy
underwear sexy yeah that was a little weird
DC needs
to be a publicist they've seriously
fallen off the taste truck
off of the progressive taste truck
because DC used to be pretty progressive
with their characters and hit every branch
on the idiot tree and they've fallen
into the stinky
republican onion truck alright
look moving on
to something happy much more
happier and gay and I mean it
I like gay gamerX
is returning to San Francisco
gamerX2 electric
boogaloo no that's just what I think it should be
called but it's gamerX2 it
is going to be happening July 11th through
the 13th of 2014
they have moved to a venue that is
three times as large thank god
it's the Intercontinental Hotel
in San Francisco which is right next to Moscone
Center if I'm not mistaking and they've
already announced some of the guests for it
and also Cards Against Humanity already
signed up as a sponsor of the event
which cross your fingers
your toes hold your breath
this means an exclusive gamerX
set of cards because that would be
amazing
there's also some guests they've announced
I know that Ella McClain is coming
back and what's
sniper's name John
Maury is that his name sorry
he'll be back this year
they're coming back and apparently
the couple that got engaged
at gamerX1 and the video
is huge viral all over the internet
they're going to get married at gamerX2
and they're actually sent like everybody
is getting like little wedding invitations
I want to go and throw flowers
right who doesn't so this is going to be
fun and all I have to say and I'm going to
give a shout out right now to my
folks in the gay podcasting
circle we got game
bar we got game
buoy.org we got
Koopa Club we got
video game realness
and so much more out there
I know there's plans to do something
podcast cross zone 2 but like
bigger better
and it's going to have to be
with all these extra people that now want to be a part
of it which is a great thing
what a horrible situation to be in
it's too popular of an event
I want to go
you can get your tickets now
but if you can't get them right now because of financial whatever
they'll be on sale until they're not
we need to do a panel
it'll be fun I think we should
let's do a panel
alright we'll talk we'll get to talking
anyhow gamerX.com if you want more information
on that information on Rocksmith
2014 edition
adding some more songs to kind of round
out their song list
Rocksmith 2014 edition will include
Def Leppard's Pour Some Sugar On Me
Queen's
We Are The Champions
and Mary Jane's Last Dance from Tom Petty
and the Heartbreakers
and a song for Bobby Rush is going to be in the game
with the Spirit of Radio
I love Rush. Rush is Canada's best
export
I still love Alanis Morissette that's the 90's kid in me
but anyway some disagree with me
but deal with it
there's lots of great songs in the game I'm not going to read the entire song list
but remember that Rocksmith is like
the no really stop hitting plastic
buttons and learn how to play an actual
guitar so you know
if you want to go to guitar school Rocksmith 2014
is the way to do it. Also there's
what's called color blind mode which I think is
pretty cool
one of the producers is actually color blind
and you can actually adjust the hues
and the color saturation levels throughout
the entire game to be a little
better for the color blind because I guess
the first game got a little flack for
it so they are going to make it a little better
this time around so kudos for accessibility
and lastly
coming to an arcade
near you
yes an arcade near you
Plants vs. Zombies
The Last Stand
I'm assuming they turn Plants vs. Zombies
into a ticket spitter because that's
all arcade games are anymore
yeah it is a
video redemption product yes yes of course
there's already a
bejeweled one that surprised me I've never seen one
of those but I guess that is out there but yes
look for more information on Plants vs. Zombies coming
to an arcade near you soon
Dark Sakura
we're actually having a small discussion
in chat by the way
there needs to be the Jessica Jones
TV show I'm going to cry
have you been watching Shield at all?
no and I need to
but
Jessica Jones is my favorite Marvel character
ever and if none of you have read
Alias which had nothing to do with the TV show
read it well if Shield goes anything
like another ABC show Once Upon a
Time they will roll out
those characters just to like
make you watch now they have their
spin-off yeah they have the spin-off they just released
a picture of Jafar apparently for some reason
is in Wonderland I'm not even going to try and figure that one
out but it's just like you know
who can we roll out next?
yeah Chell what'd you want to say
yeah the character thing
I was you know
I started watching
Once Upon a Time as kind of my trashy show
and then I got emotionally involved
and then it jumped the shark like
whoa and I'm just
I'm basically watching it out of train wreck syndrome
so yeah I hadn't heard about Jafar
but now I need to check out the freaking
Alice in Wonderland well here's the thing
even I'm not really watching
Once Upon a Time but it is like next on my
list once I finish off Scandal
which is far more important but
even I've seen
the pictures of Captain Hook
and that is uh oh yeah
you know I said
you know not even Robert Carlyle can get me
back for the third series they got me back
for my
rapid fire news there's
I am getting so sick of these
websites that are not iPad
compatible uh oh
fuck them um this actually
is uh called the not on
Steam still which I'm trying to give you guys
some advertising but your site's
not working on my iPad so why should
I um basically it's about
66 games that are not
on Steam they're all by indie developers
that are for sale at
notonsteam.com
Super Markdown there's some really cool
stuff like um girls like robots
Photonica uh Uzi
Earth Adventure One Finger Death Punch
which actually I think is now on
Steam. What's Pushcat?
That one I haven't checked out
there's one called Rose in Time
there's uh scanning a truck driving simulator
Six Sided Sanctuary
looked like a fun one I almost bought that one
The Sea Will Claim Everything
Tiny Barbarian DX
lots of really neat games on there and there's also
Alphas there's another game on here by the way
that's called We'll Fight for Food
Nice. Oh this one
called Spud's Quest looks cute
yeah there's just a lot of neat looking games on there
Nice. And in a not
so indie game um
we all like Borderlands don't we?
Well
2k and Gearbox
have a $100,000
worth of prizes for an
in-game loot hunt for Borderlands
2 so basically on
October 11th at 10
Eastern Time
the game will be altered so
that these weird guns are gonna start
dropping in odd places
so like
the knuckle dragger will drop on
Gwen's head
no sorry the knuckle dragger will drop Gwen's head
my apologies
so basically you fulfill
their little requirements and
you could win a prize. I will not tell you
anymore about it cause you need to go check it out yourself
and then
last but not least there is a new Sonic
game in development for
Xbox One and PS4 and Wii U
and
I believe it's just a working
title Sonic Thunderstorm or Sonic
Blue Thunder
there is
a
looks like there's going to be
a new character named static
the hedgehog and
a teenage clone of Sonic Knuckles
Rogue Eggman will also have teenage clones
and
Knuckles clone will be called
Slash the Echidna. Hurray more shitty
friends static the hedgehog
he doesn't move very much
he's very placement
he's a pretty clingy friend
you can also play as Tails, Amy, Debra
all these other characters
and you also have team Chaotix
which is all that I care about
29 levels, different objects, return of old animals
and chaos drives and
the Chao Garden
game play will
change characters like in Sonic Heroes
there's just a bunch of stuff I don't know if it's gonna be any good
but there is the return of the chaos emeralds
yes but what mode
allows me to make them act out
my fan fictions
none, sit down
they're also saying that
wi-fi will transfer Chao data
and you have a Chao Garden
it will be
DLC and available in PS Vita and 3DS
so
yay
it better not suck
let's hope this is a good Sonic game
don't they kind of alternate back and forth
like Star Trek movies
except that
doesn't apply to the
Star Trek re-releases
the revamps
because both of them have been good
I think the first one was way better than the second one
but that's just me
womp womp
let's get to
the FUGL question
of the week
every week we ask our listeners
a question on Facebook
and Google Plus
you put that together and you get FUGL
the FUGL question of the week and this week
as I promised it's gonna be all about Pokemon
so we asked our listeners
the most important question possibly
of the millennium
are you team Fennekin
Chespin or Froakie
and for those that don't know
those are the starter Pokemon
in the new X and Y
they're like Bulbasaur
what about option 14 don't give a fuck
well actually I did ask
as part of the question
Pokemon mania looks to be starting all over again
in just a week what do you think of Pokemon
are you picking up X and Y
or are you shocked at the number of grown adults
who obsess over Pokemon
so let's go to Google Plus first
where actdef says team Fennekin
and then he gives us a link to a
community on livejournal
called Pokemon collectors
talking about
his second question and I see that
there's two 3DS's
stuffed animals
yeah actdef might have a problem
but that's okay we still like you
he says seriously though
I've been a Pokemon fan since the red
blue yellow days and I don't see
leaving the Pokemon games and
fandom in his time soon I'm so hyped for X and Y
Jim or excuse me
Flaco Jones says
despite my love of RPGs I never
got into Pokemon in the first place
now when they come out with a game it seems like
they just expand on old stuff to make the fans
happy a new Pokemon release has never
said to me hey you've never played this
before but this version will really pull
you into the series to be fair
I think they're trying to do that with X and Y a little bit
one thing I noticed about the 3 starter
Pokemon is that their final forms
kind of fall into the fighter
mage thief
kind of generalisms
you expect in RPGs I found that interesting
Evel
which
might be pronounced that way or E3VL
I'm not sure but Evel responds and says
I'm only purchasing one version of the game
this time around why
seeing the diverse age groups who enjoy the franchise
I hope the creators make the plot more complex
or adult oriented so that varying age
demographics may have a more meaningful
discussion while playing the game together
well yeah but it's Pokemon I mean how
deep is it gonna get
just saying just saying my personal opinion
alright going over to Facebook for some answers
Seattle says
I'm looking to
Team Froakie closely
followed by Team Fennekin and I'm picking up
Y as soon as I can get into the Evel G
to get it as for what I think of the Pokemon
series Yellow was the first game that I
actually owned so they hold a place in
my heart in gaming library which reminds me
I need to make an attempt at figuring out what is wrong with my
copy of Yellow
Shane replied and Shane is Team Chesspin
and I have been counting down the days since
January which is when they announced the games
but had no release dates
this is the most important release this year
it is already my game of 2013
you sound like Loki talking about a different
game just a few weeks ago
JVMON replies
and says Team Froakie I've never
chosen a non water starter
ever since I chose Squirtle and Pokemon Blue
now my only decision is between
X and Y lucky I have both reserved
so I can decide on release day
Pokemon will always be a go to game for me
sure the structure is predictable but that's part of the charm
For the Fallen Dreams says
Team Fennekin motherfuckers
I'm 22 and
Pokemon will never get old to me
it's hands down the best handheld RPG in my
opinion it's the sole reason I'm getting a 3DS
minus a few other titles it's a breath
of fresh air from the constant gore
and violence from more adult oriented video games
Clover N says
my wife and I have pre-ordered an X and
a Y I always choose water type
and my wife always chooses grass type
and let's see
going to the next answer
Burr says Fennekin all the way
I'll see if I can pick it up I haven't actually finished
a Pokemon game yet though I got the
furthest in blue when I first
flirted with it during my freshman year of college
TimTrip
replied and said gonna have to go with Chespin
I don't obsess over Pokemon
but there is a lot about it that is surprisingly
compelling I don't play every generation
because the changes have always been a bit too
incremental from the looks of it
XY has made some significant forward steps
without changing the core of what makes Pokemon
fun so I'll be picking up a copy
Matt J says I've yet to decide
on my starter so can't commit to a team
yet I'm not surprised at all that so
many adults are into Pokemon I'm nearly 29
and still love it however you think
folks around my age were kids when the first
Pokemon games came out I was only 13
when Red and Blue came out here many
of us adults grew up on the series it made
a mark on us a mark that sticks with us to this
day GeoVidea says I
don't even have a 3DS yet hoping for
it as a holiday gift hint hint
and I always pick
fire types it's all about the burn
Andy R says
I got pretty bored with the last few games I didn't even
finish white I'm still considering
buying X or Y but it will probably depend more on
how many of my friends pick it up am I shocked
at grown adults obsessing over Pokemon
no nostalgia is a powerful force
Fifth Dream says Froakie
all the way I always pick water type
starters unless I'm playing a second game
in a generation then I pick a grass
I even bought a Team Froakie
t-shirt to wear when I go pick up my
copy of Pokemon X I'm 39
years old so I am one of those
grown adults who love Pokemon I've
played it since Blue came out and have played
every single generation some twice
and the spinoffs so yeah Pokemon's great
Raginator says I'm on
team who gives a fuck finally
well I mean we haven't
we haven't had anyone yet say
I don't care but here's Raginator to
break that trend saying I'm not getting
Pokemon X and Y I've yet to buy any
Pokemon game I'm not going to start now
Pokemon is about as interesting as being
repeatedly anal probed by aliens
non-stop for six months followed by swimming
in raw sewage you're nasty
you nasty you know what but it's
it's hard I don't think one can make
a judgement until they've played one yeah what's the
why there though I'm not hearing the
why do you feel so strongly
against Pokemon I'm not hearing that some people
just want to be ornery
yeah I don't know did you just post that
for shock value sir
alright degenerate Johnny says I'm with team
frokey because it rhymes with Loki
alright
anyway I'm not at all surprised that so many
adults play these games because
they want to rub it in the faces of six year olds
I mean to dominate six year I mean
I really mean never mind I give it up
our pal wicked from the
nerdgasm network says I've been out of the Pokemon
fold since emerald and given how
X Y looks like a pseudo reboot
it looks like it's time to get back in I'm glad
that we're finally getting a game that looks like the
anime and while the Pokemon count is
count is utterly nutterly butterly
I still think there's a lot
to be had in collecting them all to collect
them all I'm going for frokey
because Greninja looks
sick as hell plus I'll have a fire
starter from the Torchic special
event and I can never say no to having a Bulbasaur
a well rounded team ahoy
uh Hitstun says at the moment I think
I'm getting Pokemon X and starting with Chespin
once the game's been out for a week and we
know more about the popular Pokemon and how to
counter pick them I'll be ready to delete
my save, start again, and
work towards my ideal team from the beginning
I already preordered Pokemon
Blue fifteen years ago but I skipped
generations three and five completely
building a good competitive team is a lot
of work but it's worth it when the game is new
and my friends are playing it too
SSG100Matt says Pokemon came out in 1998
and I've been playing it since then I'm
almost thirty which means I have played
Pokemon for half my life
I will get Pokemon Y when I finish
Black 2 sigh
and lastly Codeman I'm
not sure about Pokemon I love
the blue and red but I just can't add to
it the huge amount of games I will have on the
table already I will be picking up
a 2DS so maybe then I'll try it
for now probably not
but I was a huge fan of the Pokemon anime
it was fantastic so
overwhelming Pokemon
fans versus non
Pokemon fans
there
and kind of even it sounded pretty even
on who's picking up what starter so
I will say this that for all the past
ones that I have played I've
always started with a fire type
that's just been me Fennekin's super cute
that's what team oh and
to answer the question earlier in the show I am team
Fennekin absolutely
I have no idea what that is
he's a little Firefox not to be confused
with a popular web browser ok well if he's
a fox and on fire maybe I have to get the game
let me show you
does it like fire
oh my god that's fucking cute
right
that's Fennekin let me show you the others just to compare
that's Fennekin do you remember when we went to that E3
and I came back with all those damn Pokemon plushies
like the plus and minus
that's Chespin
the grass type oh he looks angry
in that particular picture he does here's a
happy Chespin just to be fair
there you go and uh
here is
fro-key
looking that up right now ew no one gives a shit
ok so we know it looks like an old
like a frog with a beard on his back
ok so Jamie is definitely
not team fro-key
Fennekin's cute I go with Fennekin
even if I'm not getting the game I vote for
Fennekin thank you
thank you Dark Sakura who has a
partially correct opinion
hey
yeah Act Deaf I had Plessy
and Minun whoever
but I gave them to my friend
Julie because I don't care
I was in a good mood this week so I read
every single answer I may have
cut some of them a little short but check out
the full responses at facebook.com
slash Orange Lounge Radio and our Google Plus
community just search for Orange Lounge Radio
on Google and you'll find it and thank
you guys for your answers and don't forget
those of you out there listening don't forget to follow us
on those communities
alright more long form news Loki
starting us off
alright so
layoffs
god you don't like them
but it happens so there's a
couple companies laying off people first off
Sega of America is confirming
an unspecific number of layoffs I'm assuming
this is tying in with the fact
that you know they are taking on Atlas
and perhaps there's just
you know
some of those jobs kind of overlapping
each other
so basically
as the gaming industry continues to
evolve companies must adapt
and adjust in order to compete and succeed
in an ever changing environment as the
result Sega of America has recently undergone
a restructure that will enable the
company to focus efficiently on developing
new and existing content across
digital platforms as well as continuing to focus
on key brands for packaged goods
alright
so yeah
and then
Capcom well that sucks what else can you
say I mean I know layoffs are kind of
inevitable in this industry but it
always makes you sad especially when it's like big companies
like Sega you know yeah also
Capcom Europe apparently is going
to be laying off more than half of its staff
and this
is coming from I guess MCV
who understands more than
they're saying more than half of the
firm faces redundancy with
the number of jobs set to merge
so
that kind of sucks
and I guess following a
restructure in the US operation Capcom
Europe organization is currently evaluating
its structure to ensure it's
in the best position to take advantage of the
changing market condition the industry is facing
in other words they're doing more digital stuff
I believe because I think
a lot of their
you know a lot of franchises I mean they have franchises
but there's not a ton of different franchises that they're
kind of continually putting out games for
well
and just to say I want to address something too I see
around the internet for those that are saying like
you know good or that'll
teach Capcom or you know
Capcom deserved it or whatever
like okay stop stop
stop because the people being
affected by these layoffs probably
have nothing to do with the decisions that you don't like
you know that's the way
these things go unfortunately is that the people that are
actually getting laid off are probably pretty hard working
people that are just trying to make a good game
and usually these types of decisions
come from high up
then you can start
saying that you know well maybe it's
for the best or whatever so
yeah I just kind of want to get that out there
like don't be all like well should've
made the new Mega Man game because
that's
I mean while that may be true
that's like laughing at somebody's
face when they're going through tragedy you know
did you see what the new Mega Man game was going to look like
remember the leaked footage that
came out of the cancelled Mega Man game
yeah well the 3DS
one didn't look bad at all
too bad not enough people
downloaded the demo or wait they didn't
release that no they didn't
so yeah but not enough people
downloaded the demo because they never released it
so yeah but
are these layoff news about the people
that made that decision probably not
it's kind of the equivalent of not tipping
your waitress because the food was shitty or
you just didn't like it it's you know
they're really they're just usually conveying
it to you they have no say in it at all
unless they spit in it oh yeah
that would be yeah
alright fair enough alright
I have a story that's
hopefully a little bit happier news this
is something that you know
ever since we saw Sony do this with
the Playstation 3 and the Playstation Vita
we've wondered if Nintendo
might do something similar and that is cross by
play which on Playstation 3
is awesome because who doesn't like more
games for more systems for free
games like sound shapes and
Zen Pinball 2 they have the
cross play available or if you buy it on
the Playstation 3 you get a copy for the Vita as well
well it was questioned
of Dan Adelman who is a manager of business
development at Nintendo
will there be something about cross
buy and quote we don't
have anything new to announce on that but
I believe that the idea has been talked about
so if it's something we're definitely up to
considering so it's something we're
definitely up to considering
that's not a non-committal answer I don't know what it is
if there's enough demand from developers
but nothing to announce for right now
so that's interesting this will work
in nicely when we announce our
you know the brand new technology
that we're putting in place to play 3DS
games on the Wii U because then you'll
buy your 3DS game and play it on
your Wii U or on your 3DS
because that's totally gonna fucking
happen someday it might
it's not a might it's an inevitably
it's just gonna happen
and then cross buy all the things
but I can see where they might make that decision
leave it up to developers though
a developer has a right
to double dip if they want even if it
you know we don't like it and don't want to
support it well a lot of time also
with like the 3DS and the
Wii U version it's gonna be two
different developers on it because you have
you know developers that'll do the handheld ports
of games and then you'll have the console
developers doing that sometimes it's the same team
but a lot of times it can be two separate teams
so you know it's
why would you want to give
something away for free considering that they're probably
selling plenty of 3DS
games and they need to sell more Wii U games
so I don't know
uh tiger claw on chat
says what if they take cross buy a step further
speaking on the Sony side now
buy the Playstation 4 version and you get
not only the Vita version but the PS3
version too well we
don't know enough about the Gaikai thing it doesn't
sound like it's gonna be there at launch and if it will
do the Playstation 3 games
so I don't think we can assume that yet but
um I
I don't know like why would you go
back and play the Playstation 3 version if you have a
Playstation 4 version maybe I'm missing something
but I would think the newer one would be
a better experience but I mean I don't
know I guess I could be wrong there are people that like
retro but I'm like if it's the exact same game
I don't know oh well
anyhow
uh let's move on
more gaming news Dark Sakura
we do have some other gaming news
we have
a game that
I'm not any good at
my husband's pretty good at it
a lot of people are bitching about this
too and I'll tell you why in a second
but uh Ikaruga
has hit the green light so Treasure's
uh wonderful
shooter game is going to be
out for Steam
and apparently though
um while it's based
off the Xbox 360
version it is
um
going to have I think some different patterns
from what I understand so basically
people who had the old patterns memorized will have
to learn new patterns all over again
um so
there's also a
statement that came from Treasure on Twitter
this is new challenge we are trying to distribute
Treasure games on Steam
so maybe we'll get Radiant Silver Gun next
who knows
it seems weird they have to go through
Steam green light I mean it's Treasure
why can't they just put the game on Steam
why did they have to go through the green light process
let's I mean
maybe I'm not being fair here or whatever
but it just seems like you know Treasure would be
a big enough name that they kind of get to
cut ahead for a game like Ikaruga
and maybe they're also thinking
we might maybe get something like Silhouette
Mirage or Troublemakers or
maybe they want to see what kind of support they're getting too
I think green light actually is a really
good way to gauge support because you have that whole
voting system so true
maybe they don't want to put the effort if
there's not going to be enough people clamoring
for it but Ikaruga has been
popular enough I would love to have
an accessible home version
of Radiant Silver Gun that would be
amazing
alright let's move on
so Microsoft is promising hey you know
we got that brand new Kinect that's going to be
coming out with the Xbox One and
hey you know that they have that
feature now that I guess it
allows well the only thing
this is really new because I think they have this for the
Xbox 360 as well but it
can be used in advertising
like for example they're saying that
Kinect actually recognizes
expressions and engagement
or can recognize people's faces
that
you know they could tell you know
who's actually watching the ad or start
you know targeting ads towards people and stuff
and say hey listen you know
just because it could be
you know using that you know some of the new
Xbox One Kinect fixtures
could be used in advertising
since we see expressions engagement
etcetera and how that
might be used to target advertising
this is the point
that seems to draw some controversy first
nobody is working on that
I'm not aware of any activity
or any active work
in this space second if something
like that ever happened you can
be sure that it wouldn't happen without
the user having control over it period
as they
emphasize
yeah but at the same time you know
there's also all this controversy
going on with the NSA and you know
they're talking about people
being spied on and
Microsoft is the first to jump on board with
supporting that kind of stuff
when we first talked about the mandatory
Kinect thing when all that E3
shit blew up I said what a
horrible time I think we all said
what a horrible time for this to be happening with all the
NSA stuff that's coming to light right now because that
all also happened over the summer and it's like
this is not going to help Microsoft's case
to make the Kinect mandatory
so I mean that thing needs
to work and haven't they come out since
it's been said it'll be fine if you unplug your Kinect
they won 80 on that point didn't they
yeah they did and honestly I don't see
this as big a huge problem
I mean because I mean I'm assuming
I haven't really gotten a good peak
at the interface and stuff but I'm assuming it's very
similar like how the 360 is where
you have those tiny little okay well there's
let's be honest there's a lot of fucking ads
on the 360 dashboard
that really probably don't need to be there
I mean come on Microsoft's been
collecting money for these internet
services and stuff and don't give me
that oh sorry we need
this extra ad revenue to you know
cloud things or something I don't know
whatever um
but I just don't see the point that we need to
have even ad people make
like these interactive Kinect
ads or something because who the fuck
is really going to play that or actually
you know half the people don't watch those ads
anyways and who's going to really want
to see an ad where like oh hey
throw the mountain do it you know
Jeff Gershman or whatever it is
so I
just
Jason in chat says
God get over the fucking NSA
which you know
despite all that political hub
baloo it's not that
honestly it's not really that that concerns me about the mandatory
Kinect which is like you know the Kinect has the voice
commands and everything right I just
whether legit or
not I am paranoid that that thing
would capture a really
unflattering picture in an inopportune
or something or you know
those things are going to be able to broadcast online and call
people with voice commands and stuff so it's like
hey I recognize Rob has the mountain do in front
of him I'm going to take a picture look he's doing the do
with underwear on
the listeners thank you for that
visual Loki but
no for like for real like you know
I'm I would my plan all along
was just to turn the
Kinect to face the wall when I'm not
playing probably
that's what I do with my current Kinect
is just turn and face the TV or you know
turn around the other way when I'm not playing and it's none
the wiser throw a shirt on it like poltergeist
right yes that's a great
answer too and then the Kinect's like
hello are you still there
there you
are
advertisements
you know what I think
would be fun is like make one
of those little room boxes out
of a shoebox you know a little stick figure people
and then put it in front of the box
just so that that's all it sees
is the stick figure
room box these people are really
skinny and made of popsicle
sticks like put like um
like Halloween full
people sitting on my couch
so the Kinect thinks somebody's sitting on my
couch 24 hours a day 7 days a week
that somebody literally died on my couch
you know what you get
put a blow up doll on your couch
and then that's all it sees
wow
a hardcore pornography
alright
we should just put a continuous loop
video of Elizabeth Berkley
doing the pool scene
you don't know shit
of course why are there so many
showgirls references tonight
not that I'm complaining alright
well I think a lot of people are complaining about this
Half Life 3
was trademarked in Europe this week
that's right
the office for harmonization in the internal
market or whatever that is
in the European Union forgive my
ignorance that's just an overseas
agency
trademarked Half Life 3 this week being owned
by Valve Corporation
the trademark covers computer game software
it was filed on September 29th blah
blah blah blah but
it was fake y'all
as sometimes happens with
the trademarks this
was a fake it was therefore
removed from the trademark
it was actually a part of the actual website
or whatever the
entrant disappeared completely
and yeah it's
it's not there anymore
is this what we've come down to?
trolling with fake trademarks
same thing happened in World of Warcraft
same thing happens over there
whatever
you know what when Valve's ready
they'll fucking say something
to them
it's happening soon
so then you have a 1 in 300
you have a
300 opportunities to get a really nice PC
in your house
that's right that's the way I'm looking at it
alright we'll see
who plays Half Life 3 hey I guess that's a bonus
hey Rob
it's a fake
yes it is
alright let's get to the mailbag
every week you kids email us
and DarkSakura dives in the email
bag head first and picks out a few of her
favorite emails to read for you
why do you have to tell everyone to send all those
emails I know we got a lot this week
thank you listeners
I'm gonna be hilarious if Gabe Newell is just sitting over there
he's like ah I'm gonna totally register that
yep yep I just did it
no I didn't hah
I totally fooled all those guys
it's hilarious
luckily Gabe Newell is not a troll like you
you don't know that
so I am super excited about Beyond Two Souls
I loved Heavy Rain despite its flaws
and from what I've played in the demo so far
this game seems to have corrected a lot of the issues
people complained about in that first game
I wanted to talk about playing
excuse me
I want to talk about playing the game via this app called Beyond Touch
sounds kinky
they designed the game to be fully playable
without a controller at all
but with an app you can download for iOS and Android
if you'd like to
it sounds like it's an easier way to play
is it more accessible for people who aren't traditional gamers
this along with marketing the game
like a movie and even premiering footage
of the Tribeca Film Festival
make me feel like they're really trying to
make the game appeal to a wider audience
do you think this could backfire?
I guess it depends on which experience
is the better one
because I can see gamers getting upset
but don't they always?
if the traditional controller play is inferior to the app play
or is this just good business sense
and would you like to see more games do this?
I think it's a good idea
I think gamers are going to be pissed off anyway
so it doesn't matter
I think the point is
the bottom line, making the money
making the money means selling the game
selling the games makes it accessible to more people
so there you go
that's my thought
and also making these sort of apps
that work with games
are basically just a way to get people
to talk about said game
as we just did
there's a lot of MMOs too
like having the Warcraft app
is a great example
you can actually chat to your guild mates
from the Warcraft app on the phone
you can actually still be in the game
while you're not playing the game
there's been calls to make that enrichment even stronger
but even non-MMO games had it
Mass Effect had that little companion app
that meant you didn't have to do multiplayer
which I still sometimes use
it's off the store by the way
it's officially gone
that reminds me since
Microsoft came out with this wonderful app
called Smart Glass last year
as part of the Xbox 360 thing
it's something that's going to be included in the Xbox One
have they even shown anything that
uses that yet?
have they shown anything that's going to
I think they were talking about enhancements
for Xbox One
but as far as the 360 is concerned
I think it's a lost cause
I understand that, but I'm talking about the Xbox One
have they even shown anything Smart Glass does?
other than mention it, like, hey
these games are going to use Smart Glass
because I know we've seen stuff with Watch Dogs
and stuff like that, but they have their own dedicated apps
for that thing, it's not really Smart Glass
it's kind of this other thing
so
yeah, I thought the Halo 4 Smart Glass thing
was great until I was like, oh, it's just another app
in the store, alright, whatever
so they just kind of
I think it's meant more
for movies
like being a second screen experience
for movies and TV, but
we'll see, I will admit
TV on the Wii U
is kind of neat, and it's a bummer
more people don't use it, it's kind of a neat
little second screen experience where you can kind of chat with people
as big shows are happening and stuff, but
it would be neat if there was something like that
on Xbox, but I don't know, we'll see
alright, next email
yes
Hey, OLR, it's your friendly neighborhood turtle
I wanted to share a quick, funny story
my wife was downstairs last night cooking dinner
when she heard me let out a shriek
as if my soul was being ripped out
she ran upstairs, concerned that I had hurt myself
and found me laughing at myself playing
Alan Wake. I was pretty embarrassed
she had a good chuckle at that
sorry, I'm laughing because I'm like
what does one's soul being ripped out
sound like? But then I thought
back earlier in the show to that Pokemon
fighting video somebody linked us to
and I'm like, oh, it probably sounded like that
Loki, can't wait for GTA 5
to come out on PC, I refused to buy it twice
and then this one's to me
I hope that this week you aren't sick
you know what?
I'm not sick all the time
how are you feeling right now, you good?
allergies
having allergies is not the same as being sick
and granted
I also got stung by an asshole
wasp
which I'm sure Rachel will attest to
I get pretty sick from
waspies
it was at her house
keep on being fabulous
will do
I look forward to downloading the podcast
every Monday morning so I can listen to it while working
keep up the good times, your loyal turtle
in Philadelphia, serious turtle
next email
it's nice to know I'm not the only one that screams
like crazy playing scary video games
but nobody's as bad as Gamet
y'all, I don't know if he's still listening, I just had to
rez him you know what?
if a game scares me, I actually
you've seen me on scary
rides, I don't make a noise
if I am truly freaked out
or scared
I freeze up, get the big eyes
and I am completely unable
to speak
the only time I rode tower of terror
I was literally mute
for the next 30 minutes
I could not speak
note to self, get Jamie to ride
tower of terror before OLR
not even funny Rob
oh come on, it's just a joke
yeah but it's a real thing and it's horrible
so I will sit through
a scary movie and just like
eyes wide open and won't say anything
you know I'm scared if I haven't said shit
next email
hello OLR, although PS4 certainly has
a very positive vibe about it, I was very
compelled to buy a Playstation console for the first time
I decided to get an Xbox One
anyway, the reason might sound strange
but it's Kinect that convinced me, I like
the first Kinect a lot
for several reasons
for the first time I could play video games with everyone
around me, my girlfriend likes it and she's very good at it
kicking my virtual ass all the time
even my dad and mom play from time to time
and they never played video games before
everyone likes it because it's so simple to use
even more simple than
Wii
or PS
there must be a typo, or PS Move
since no buttons are used at all
also Kinect is a fresh wind and gaming that is needed
it's something completely different
than just another
standard first person shooter
that's why I don't get why Kinect gets all the hate
because it sucks
mostly from so called hardcore gamers
sure it's not perfect at all
and it has to prove itself a lot more
that's why Kinect 2 needs to get it right this time
but I think that it's an important step forward
in the general development of gaming
a step of which we don't understand
its importance yet
a step as important as the joystick
or am I giving it too much credit?
yes
what if Kinect becomes well used and mainstream?
god I hope not
what would be the next step in gaming beyond that?
as always I'm very thankful for you guys making a podcast every week
Fabrice from Belgium
and I am super opinionated about it
I don't like the Kinect
I don't have fun with the Kinect
I've never had fun with the Kinect
if I want to play something that's going to involve
me using motion
I want a peripheral
I want my dance pads for DDR
or my maracas for samba
I want something that's going to be
specifically related to the game
that I'm playing
I hated
I don't like watching myself
maybe it's just a me thing
but even though I had a lot of fun
with Dance Masters
to do Para Para
I could not watch the screen
if that made sense
I did all the stupid Para Para dances with my eyes closed
well you can also turn off your silhouettes in that game
if you really want to
well here's the thing about Kinect
yeah I might razz on Kinect a little bit
but I get that it's
super accessible
and that people who don't even play a lot of games
will be like oh what's that dance game
oh that looks kind of neat I can do that
I can just move and play the game
I get where it's highly accessible
but for me the thing that really bothers me about Kinect
is it's like the same three punchlines over and over
it's dance and fitness
it's
or I should say it's dance games
it's fitness games
and once in a while other weird
voice integrations and things
I haven't really seen a lot of Kinect games that made me go
wow this is the future of gaming
a system is only as good as the games that are on it
right?
and I thought maybe like Child of Eden
that was kind of neat but that was like one game
there hasn't been a lot that I feel
has really pushed gaming forward
which is why it really surprised me when they said
Xbox One is going to require it
and I'm like oh my god
but this joke is dying fast
if they're going to use the Kinect
they need to do Kinect plus Oculus Rift or something
and maybe that would be real immersive
that might be a little scary
that would be lawn mower man
but still
I personally have very little interest in it
I usually play a game
because it's my relaxing thing to do
I would rather go to the gym
if I was going to exercise
which I do anyway
so what's the point?
I saw a thing with the Kinect and the Oculus Rift
and a stationary bike
for the paperboy thing
yeah I was going to say
I'm pretty sure those mods are out there
because if you think about it
Oculus Rift, PC, Kinect
they have PC devices and things
or drivers and things for that too
so it's out there
I'm sure it's probably a pain in the butt to develop for
Kinect always reminds me of
it's in the book of Hitchhiker's Guide
because you can't really translate this into a movie
but it talks about how their society
goes from push button to touch screen
to Kinect like thing
and it finally ends up where Zefod Beelbrox
is sitting on the bridge of Heart of Gold
trying to listen to music
and you have to operate these systems
you have to sit absolutely still
because any motion towards the console
whatsoever is going to trigger
that to me seems like
that's where we're going with this
yeah I hear ya
I hear ya
alright so next email
god we still have four emails
oh my god really?
Kiflom O.L.R. it's degenerate Johnny
it's a GTA 5 reference ask Loki what that means
okay
is it wet now?
Kiflom
oh yeah it's the
made up uh
Scientology um
it's what they say to each other
I couldn't help but notice the argument
that wasn't really an argument
that Jamie Loki had last week over their taste
in video games I'm often entertained
by your arguments but they sometimes
have a tense feel about them just an observation
the beauty of interactive entertainment
is that there's a variety of good games that will
appeal to many but not to everyone
it's for this reason why
Alan doesn't play Dead Space
why Bobby doesn't play shooters
why Rob doesn't play Cookie Clicker
that's not true
personally I don't
very much care for the Elder Scrolls series
melee combat and the first person perspective
doesn't work well for me
as an individual who appreciates both game series
I can see why one of the main problems between
Mass Effect and GTA
involves a relationship between stories and gameplay
I may be generalizing here but
Mass Effect's heavily involved story and dialogue
often gets in the way of the stellar gameplay
I know
the dialogue can be skipped but
some people just want to play the game
the opposite can be said about GTA 5
the variety of side missions and extra
activities in the game
can often
derail a game's superbly written stories
and that's what we call ooh a piece of candy
factor in the end it's different
strokes for different folks
I didn't think it was an argument was it?
there was definitely
a heated discussion
on last week's show but I don't
think that was arguing so much as it was
passionate viewpoints and
don't mistake the two because
hello we've been doing this show
11 and a half years do you think
yes we're going to get a little heated
when we disagree on topics sometimes
Rob I disagree with you all the time
fuck off I'm just kidding
you know I love you
and we've been doing this a very long time
so of course there's going to be opinions
there's a little bit of stubbornness that comes
with that passion but I think everybody here on the show
is stubborn to a point
yes we're very set in our ways
but when there's a good
viewpoint expressed
I don't think any of us are beyond saying
I disagree with you
but I hear what you're saying
yeah I got a little heated last week
but there's definitely
some deep rooted issues
that Grand Theft Auto 5 makes us face
that people are passionate about
for a very good reason
the next part of the email
I also want to address the misconception of the
GTA series having a misogynistic
atmosphere even though GTA
has often been littered with prostitutes and
strippers the game series has had
a variety of strong female characters
dating back to GTA 3
I'm going to go ahead and say this having a few
strong female characters does not make up
for misogyny just saying
the one thing about the GTA
series is that it plays the role
of social commentator in the world we live
in today i.e. life provider
equals Facebook medical cocaine
equals marijuana
GTA 5 is no exception to this because it often
has commented against our patriarchal
society throughout the game
even though there is yet to be
a lead female character in the GTA
series GTA 5 has strong female characters
throughout the story one such example
is
I'm trying to get to this is female crew
members that you can select for heists
many of the
most skilled crew recruits are women and they
know it which is why they get a higher take from
jobs than the male crew recruits
not to mention GTA
Online offers the option for you to be a
woman with that being said maybe sometime
in the future we could expect Jamie to join the
VoG crew to take down the patriarchal douche bags
and infest the online community I'm actually
already working on something for that but more later
anyways
as an individual who has a significant appreciation
for strong women in video games
the KOTOR series Final Fantasy 12
Mirrors Edge I just wanted to add in my
two cents sincerely degenerate Johnny
I think what my problem
is more with the
misogynistic presentation
in the game is the fact that it
is coming from
real life
that it's an aspect of
real life that seems to be
almost
an ingrained part of culture
that shouldn't be
that we should strive to be better than
I have to make a tough
counterpoint though or at least I see it as one though
that isn't the point of Grand Theft Auto
and I kind of see it in this email too
isn't the point of Grand Theft Auto to be
over the top and silly
and ridiculous so yes
there's misogyny but it is presented
very tongue in cheek that maybe
people and I'm gonna
use something you've said on the show before
maybe people are looking to be offended
is it possible?
I
I think
it's not necessarily just a matter of looking
to be offended people are going to
be offended as a reaction
and as I've often
said not necessarily on the show
but in real life
you can't necessarily help
a reaction you can help
by acting instead of acting
on your reaction so
I think that the problem being
is that illustrating that
yeah this is a part of society
the fact
that it has to be something that's brought
up in a game to be a realistic
parody means that something that needs
more attention to be combated if that
makes sense. Yeah
it's something to think about
and I mean and you know
honestly it was a big turn off for me
in trying to play the game
I've sat and watched a bunch
of the missions in the game while Dan played because
I could not touch
the PS3 any time
Dan was home because he was always
playing that game and I watched
a lot of it but after a while there's just like
so much you can
take before you're like
wow I've hit my saturation point I
feel really
down
you know
it's a really
hard thing to put a finger on because
I think I'm hearing that maybe the problem
is that like okay yeah the joke
is funny the first 500 times
yeah but there's only so much
you want to hear
derogatory terms being used toward women
even if it's done in a parody
since after a while it really does
stop being funny. Chell wants to chime
in here. I think this is
you know if we are going along the lines of GTA
as a big over the top parody is
it sounds like it's kind of falling prey to
Dave Chappelle syndrome where
after a certain point he stopped doing the show
because he realized the wrong people
were laughing at his jokes because
there's only so far you can go with ironic racism
before it just loops around and becomes
good old fashioned racism
and that seems like what's
happening a bit here you know the parody is getting
too close to the truth and
it's you know it stops
being funny for some people like
it's my two cents
I actually fully agree with that
that is
on the money.
Alright well in the interest of time I'm going to ask Jamie to go to the next
email but keep those emails coming on
this topic or tweets
mailbag at orangelandradio.com or twitter.com
slash o-l-r
Well since Ragenator just told me to skip
his email I'm skipping it
sorry
I don't know I might go back to it. Roll it over next week
I guess. God this one's
long too.
No I mean it's fucking really fucking
long. It's from Ralston UT
oh
no it's
really okay I'm gonna
go for it.
Can we try to get a TLDR
version of it?
Just for time's sake. I'm gonna just read the first
paragraph because it has to do with what we just
talked about. Here's my suggestion you go to the next email
I'll read I'll skim this email
and try to pick out the key points.
Hey o-l-r gang as I typically
save this show for my commute 2 plus hours
a day I don't have much opportunity to call
into the show. I noticed that the mailbag
has been fairly empty lately so
I had a suggestion why not address comments
from the podcast entries on the vog network page
as well. By the way
I'm well into my first playthrough of Mass Effect
2 just in case there wasn't a requisite mention
of Mass Effect elsewhere in the show.
I've also been playing Dragon
Fantasy Book 1 on my PS Vita which
is hilariously old school 8 bit RPG
in tradition of the early Dragon
Quest games. Until next time
John K. Critical Myth
Great question from Critical Myth
we do try to incorporate the
vog network comics
comments especially on a slower
news week but we haven't done them
in a while to be fair and I might actually
be confusing with Horde House because I know we do
vog comments more often over there but
certainly I mean the thing
about the vog comments I tend to
just respond to them on the spot
like when I see those comments I can't
wait for Sunday I just have to respond
on the spot so if you want to get something
right away the vog comments are the
place to go but if there's like a really good
point or counterpoint or something
brought up it's gonna come to the show
one way or another. I'm gonna inevitably
say yeah somebody was posting about this on vog
you know. Well while you're back
to scanning that one I'll read
Raginator's
email. Okay you got it. Since it's short
Hi all this is everyone's favorite email
or hero to many and a total amazing all
around guy Raginator.
Hey it was on the email
so I said it. I just thought
I'd pose a little food for thought this week
it's fairly common knowledge that I've
traditionally been a console gamer since 1981
and it wasn't until after
last year's break in my moving and the replacement
of my computer where I actually started playing PC
games albeit reluctantly at first
as late as
August 2012 I would have scoffed at the notion
of PC gaming having been a console fan
boy for the better part of my life.
Now that I've been on Steam for a while now
plus having played Diablo 2 as well
I'm quite thoroughly enjoying PC gaming.
I also as of late
been questioning whether or not I
really need to replace my PS3.
That being said I'd like to pose
this question. Have any of you been in a
situation where you enjoyed X so much
do you question whether or not to replace Y?
This email has been brought to you by
the clearly superior Japanese soundtrack
Japanese version of the Sonic CD soundtrack
the US version is just lame y'all better recognize
for the record I don't think it's
lame I just think the Japanese music
is better. Thank you
that's the same thing I say about Chrono Trigger and Super Metroid
I'm like I'm not saying Chrono Trigger is bad
I'm not.
In fact it's better than good
but it's just
Super Metroid is like top tier. It's better than bad
it's good? Sure.
And I'm gonna say this I've never
been in that situation because I
mean shit I probably have
just about every video game system
that's worth owning.
I've never been in that situation
that I you know
now I've had games that
like for example Dragon Ball
GT Final Battle when I owned that game
it was worth a lot of money. I traded it for Blue Stinger
I've never regretted it. Even though
I can get that game any number of ways
now I don't
care. It's not that
great of a game and I'm totally not into
Dragon Ball that much anymore
unless I'm like watching the old school stuff.
Alright
I am gonna try to tackle this email from
RossDielUT and I'm gonna shorten it
so I apologize to RossDielUT in that
regard but it is a very long letter
and we're already at 9 o'clock and we gotta wrap up
we still have to get calls and wrap the show so
Do you think it'd be possible we can allow it to be reposted on the forums?
No I would want his permission for that so
Why doesn't we ask him to post it on the forum?
Yeah so but let me get
some of the stuff because first it starts off with
a couple paragraphs about the whole Grand Theft Auto 5
thing so he says
I thought it explained to Loki why the casual
sexism, racism, and homo-transphobia in Grand Theft
Auto 5 is offensive to people.
I firmly agree that not every game needs a female
lead. There's plenty of room
in the space between lead character and joke
character. When a group that you're in is
exclusively depicted in an offensive manner
that's not going to be fun. Vice City
put that into focus for me as a Cuban American
who went to school with more than a few Haitian
American in his day. The gangs were simply identified
by race and all the characters were racist
cardboard cutouts. Compare that to games
based around the Clancyverse. The main protagonist
tends to be a white dude but women and other
races are treated with respect and are never
relegated to the sidelines.
Both GTA and the
Clancy games are plainly aimed at
the male demographic but the latter does so
in a manner that respects minorities and women
while the former makes jokes out of them.
This isn't to say Rockstar should be forbidden
to do what they do. I'm a big proponent of
free speech. However that free speech
goes both ways and if Rockstar
wants to continue to take the cardboard cutout approach
to their characters and rely exclusively on
negative stereotypes they should be ready to be
called out on it. In fact I don't think Rockstar
cares as they've been relying on cheap
headline-grabbing garbage to sell Grand Theft Auto
for years now. Solving the problem
might lead to less sales so why stop
degrading women and minorities?
I think
I'm a little
bit with you Ross Deal UT until like your last
two sentences and the reason for
that is that I think you're also kind of dismissing
why that quite
possibly there are people that are drawn to Grand Theft Auto
because it's a good game
outside the story. Like I kind of think
for Loki, I don't mean to put
words in your mouth but I always got the sense
you're an open world explorer do your
own thing kind of guy. That's what you
like out of Grand Theft Auto way more than
the story. I would say that there's a lot more
depth that's been put in place
aside from Vice City
what came out in 2002
I mean that's
you can't judge
a game now like Grand Theft Auto
5 based on Grand Theft Auto
1 or even like
some of the games that were in the early
3D series
3 through Vice City
and that kind of stuff. It's just it's so
different now that they have a lot more
writing involved in the
characters. It's not just hey
it's this Haitian
guy. He's a gang member
now and stuff. There's a lot more
to it unfortunately
so I'm not
really going to go with it. Granted
some of the earlier games are probably more like that
where it's like hey we've got the triads
and they're going to act Chinese and oh hey we've got
this gang and
this nationality because
they were limited in what they could do as far as
looks and stuff. They couldn't
get that many characters that look
different. Memory. Also if I
may say something he made a point
though that is something that I have very
recently said to my mother
freedom of speech does not mean freedom from consequence
and so
I'm sure they had
to have anticipated some fallout from it.
Alrighty.
Now the big bulk of the email talks
about Steam Machines and
kind of a bit of counter points to
Steam Machines and he basically says
congratulations on being one of the
few podcasts that didn't declare the Steam
Machine the greatest thing ever and
I often find that Steam and Blizzard
and Nintendo have a tendency to get away with things
that other game companies would be eviscerated for
and there's a double
standard in gaming media and it sickens
me says the email.
And then he goes on a great deal to talk about Steam
Machine and I'm going to apologize because this is the part I've
really got to trim down for time.
But basically he says
A. People who don't already
have PCs are not going to buy a thousand
dollar hardware and two hundred dollar yearly upgrades
for the privilege of being locked to a single vendor
and losing all the portability and
control they enjoy on consoles. I think there's
a little bit of worry that
the Steam Machine is not going to give you the plug and play
that PCs essentially give you in the build
drone PC world. You don't have that
same freedom and I get that.
And he kind of draws comparisons
to 3DO with that as well.
And then he talks
about
how many games
sorry
I'm trying to paraphrase
this here. It's basically
if you're
invested in Steam you likely know how to
get your PC working on the television
which also has the bonus of allowing
you to play games from anywhere not just
Steam. How many games particularly
games that wouldn't be god awful on any
kind of controller don't come to consoles
anymore. To hear PC gamers
tell it much of what comes out on PC nowadays
is console ports outside of a few
indie outliers in Valve so
that's not going to be enough to push people who aren't already
in the PC space. Then he goes on
to talk about the controller and
you know is it really going to have
everybody on board to support it
and so on.
Ownership of the software is another huge
point. PC gamers
he says have
gone to Valve in force but
the mainstream market isn't going to spend
$60 on title they don't feel like
they own. Steam
has lots of sales to alleviate that but we're
never going to get the point where 99 cent or $5
or even $5 to $15 is the
norm for new released AAA
titles. Activision would laugh Valve
reps right out of the office in mere suggestion
of devaluing the massive call of duty money
machine to get that way. But Activision
I think Activision is kind of
in the minor well they're not in the minority
but they're them take
two and
EA the big three
guys you know they put out some massive
titles that are also on PC
yeah call of duty it's still
$60 on PC and
that didn't used to be the case it used to be
10 bucks cheaper but they for
our call of duty so we can get away with
that you know but that's
not true for everything like NBA 2K
14 is 30 bucks
on PC versus
60 on console and
so and I think
you know some of their bigger tiles yeah
the price point is the
same as console but
you know there's also modding support with
some of these games there's also
you know all the different features they can get on
you know PC and plus the
PC retail market there's not really a
big retail market anymore for PC good luck
finding you know
the one rack that they have a GameStop
or something that has your PC product that's the
biggest point I get from this
email that I really want to call out and this will be the
last thing I say about this email I want to read this one paragraph
all this of course ignores
the likely fact that these things will almost
certainly not be heavily promoted by
GameStop or Best Buy at least in
a manner other than trade in your steam machine here
both of who have very lucrative
pre-owned programs that won't that they won't
put in jeopardy good luck selling a box
with no mainstream appeal at Walmart
especially the most mostly disinterested
hardware partners who aren't going to make a massive
push without software compensation
I do get that point
and it is a good question to ask
who is this for?
I don't know that's the thing it's like I don't
understand because if they're trying to compete
like he does make a point sorry
he does make a point the hardcore
PC users already figured out how to
hook these things up to their TV the
casuals aren't going to buy something
like this when there's like the consoles
and other especially like at a Walmart
there's lots like cheaper stuff sitting on the shelves
who is this really for?
I don't know because you know
the thing is
if they're going to compete with consoles
if they compete with price I mean because this is
look at we give at least I
give shit to Xbox One for being $100
more than the Playstation 4 but
fuck a PC with a
Titan graphics card
it is not going to be anywhere near $500
that shit's going to be like $1500
alright so
to give a counterpoint to
Ross Deal's email let me go to our chat room at
live.vognetwork.com and I think this is a good way to
end it on Dungeon Buster says
who says that Valve might decide to
go the general retail route at all?
and I think that's a good point and
maybe something we need to consider that
maybe the media
gaming media or whatever you want to call it
maybe we're making a bigger deal out of this
than it really is
who knows?
alright let's move on
lots of email tonight
I fully look forward to the origins machine
no thanks
pass pass
alright let's get to the FUs of the week
where we get a little angsty on the show
because
um
my FU goes back to
the Wasp from last week
because the stinger finally came out
and my finger hurts a lot less now
thankfully
also FU to the blisters on the bottoms of my feet
that are right up at the top by the toes
because I was stupid
I take responsibility for this
I wore my Vibrams walking on concrete
and I hadn't worn them in a long time
so I rubbed my foot a little bit off
and then FU to
Wasabi the restaurant
their sushi is normally very very good
but they put sriracha damn near everything
like
thankfully it wasn't touching my food
except that I think that there was some in my food
I think there was some cross contamination
going on because I broke out in hives
and my throat swelled
and I had to take lots of Benadryl when I got home
so and for me
my food allergies yeah they're weird
but they're easily avoidable
so
fuck sriracha
uh
I guess you didn't buy into those sriracha
lace chips when they were out either
Dan told me that those just tasted like
hot ketchup
um FU to
my head hurting
cause I have a
I think allergies cause my eyes are burning too
I'll just
give a quick FU to the stress of putting on
a show and directing it
as much as I am very proud of the
people that are working very hard to do this show
and I know it's gonna be great
I want my free days back
less stress but
I've only got six more days to go it will be a kickass show
it really will alright um
last up Michelle
uh I'd like to give an FU to Gina Gershon
cause she don't know shit
but she does a great
Versace keep in mind
she is playing Versace in a Lifetime movie
just saying
alright
I can't believe you gave an FU to Gina Gershon
I love that woman alright
just a couple more stories and then we'll do some quick
calls we're running a little long tonight
the tech issues earlier put us back
so you're not gonna have a lot of
time to get through so I will
put the call out in just a couple minutes here for calls
but first Loki
so the OUYA
is coming out in European markets
is anyone excited
I know I'm excited
Europe's excited
are they who bought your OUYA
was it a listener or just some random
I think it's a random guy ok that's cool
I'm done with it so
wash my hands of that
so yeah it will be coming out
99 euro
Germany France Italy
Austria Switzerland
Spain
and it looks like Scandinavia
Norway Denmark and
oh I guess that's it
late October and the
distributors I guess Flashpoint and Digital Brothers
will be handling the distribution duties
in Western Europe while Action and PA
will
take Eastern Europe
so
hopefully
the people in Europe will be luckier
than the people in the US because
OUYA themselves can't handle distribution for shit
so handing
off to somebody else might be a little bit better
and I still wanna know and
I'm probably gonna check this right now
I wanna know if people still actually
haven't gotten their Kickstarter OUYA
because I think there were still some people
out there that did not have their
Kickstarter OUYA
that's sad and such
alright speaking of sad
this guy has
definitely left his mark on the video game universe
which is funny because he wasn't necessarily
a game designer but Tom
Clancy passed away this week
in Baltimore at age 66
and if you didn't know Tom Clancy wrote
books he didn't just have his name
in video games
he was a hell of a writer
like Ghost Recon and Splinter Cell and all that
but he actually wrote books and obviously
these military themed novels
went on to be adapted into video games
and these games do very well
Ghost Recon, Splinter Cell and so forth
he ended up co-founding Red Storm
Entertainment as a part of this and then
Ubisoft bought that in August 2000
and that's just been doing the games ever since
the latest game Tom Clancy
The Division coming out
late 2014
I imagine these games will still
carry his name for a long time to come
so rest in peace
Tom Clancy that is
you know that's too bad but
unfortunately
as time goes on
people that provide
our beloved entertainment pass away
so take a moment to
66 is pretty young
that does make it
all the more tragic
yeah those games are very popular
I'm going to be completely honest
I'm not going to fake it
I don't really play these games myself
but I listen to other podcasters that really do
enjoy these games and I get why people
are really into them
I think if you're into that military stuff
they are a heck of a lot of fun
or at least they sure sound fun
that's the thing and hey
actually we may be past the opportunity for that
never mind that was
last month I think Rainbow Six Vegas
I remember was part of the free games
with live so
yeah
Halo 3 now
because you know I didn't buy
that game at launch or anything
I know right
oh I want to say real quick
as I mentioned that I think
there might have been some people
from the kickstart that still haven't fucking gotten
their system yet and they
are not too pleased by that
gee I wonder why
using such colorful language
yeah
alright
we are going to go ahead and open up the skype line
1877 game OLR
or a username on skype orange lounge radio
again that's 1877 game OLR or
orange lounge radio
I will go to twitter as well but Loki
any last minute stories
um
grand theft auto
online or I should have said
grand theft auto is the most played online game right now
for you know the Xbox 360
cool
I can see that
um
that's it
alright let me oh nope the phone is lighting up
I will go to twitter in a minute first we will take a phone
call hi you are on orange lounge radio who is this
it's the only one with the fastest internet
in the chat room it's Rama
alright Rama what's on your mind tonight buddy
I had a lot of things I wanted to bring to the table
but since we are cut for time I have
one thing I do want to bring to the table
go for it
long story short
we are working together with other
anime gaming communities
to work together we are having a fundraiser
for a friend of the show
I don't know if you saw me screaming
this out on my facebook and my twitter
but we had a friend of the show
I did see this and my stupid ass
forgot to retweet it because I got it while I was working
but please I think this is great so please
by all means pimp away
alright we have an Indiegogo going called
Love for Venus a charity for Kathleen
long story short her and her mom
and her friend were driving to
AWA and there was a car
accident she made it through but
unfortunately her mother didn't survive
the car accident so we
opened up this Indiegogo fundraiser for her to help
cover for medical and
bereavement cause because
there's various issues
within the first day alone of the
soft goal we hit our
goal which was $500
we're still going strong
it's still going for the next 39
days and we've raised
$4850
oh that is so good that is great
because you know what funerals ain't free
y'all and that's
I mean I can't imagine what this
poor girl who
just lost her mother in a horrific
you know accident has to be
going through you know and to even
like you know she's trying to pull through this thing herself
it's like this is awful
so I'm really glad to see the communities there and
supporting and putting money where their mouth is
so to speak
definitely but one good thing
is she is home from the hospital and
we do have a Facebook page for her
facebook.com slash project
love Venus she we have a
video up of her thanking everybody
for what we've done and she's truly
appreciative for it
that's really great
yeah you said there was one other
involved in the accident her brother
another friend of hers we don't
know the status about her though
that we don't know oh gosh okay
yeah wow
it's just I'm just happy
that even though
it just happened within the cosplay community
we have people who are connected to
the cosplay community anime furry
gaming tabletop
just running it around
like a telephone just spreading the word
coming together
as one giant family
to help one of our own
and Atlanta is the place for that to happen
too I saw that at Dragon Con
with everybody coming together and so
I'm sure anime weekend Atlanta
is probably just the cool down convention
from Dragon Con in some way I shouldn't say
that that might be offensive to some but
I don't mean it to be whatsoever
because I think I had such a blast
at Dragon Con I'm sure
Atlanta puts on some great stuff
I'll give you a hint this is how you know
this is your cool down con if you're at
the convention you find yourself drinking
more than anything else
that's your cool down con
I like that
we did a lot of that at Fonomy though
yup
I remember trying to find the one vending
machine that actually had soda
that wasn't horribly expensive
and you were ready to attack you were
ready to jump over that counter at that
woman who couldn't serve us alcohol
because it was clothes or something like that
thank god for Pineapple Malibu
Rama
one more time what is the
link for the
Indiegogo you said
alright the short version is
igg.me
slash at slash
love for venus the main
facebook page is facebook.com
slash project
love venus and there is a little button
that takes you to this information
on our website at animejamsession.com
that sounds awesome
thanks for all you're doing
for that it's such gamer good news this
week between you know I talked about
the GEMET breast cancer stream earlier
and now you've got this going on and
I'm sure there's lots of other great charitable
events going on at the gaming community we're starting
to get into that season with the holiday season where there's
going to be a lot of child's play fundraiser
events so very excited to see that
so alright
well Rama I will let you go so we can get some more
calls but take care and everybody should
listen to Anime Jam Session Tuesdays
at 6.30 Pacific 9.30
Eastern Time that's right right after
Electric Sisterhood show enough
alright take care alright thank you bye
1877 Game O.L.R.
our username on skype is OrangeLoungeRadio
we'll try to squeeze in one more call I know
some folks have a bad time
it's probably already past it on the East Coast
so thank you to our live listeners who stay up late
with us unfortunately
we got a little bit of a late start tonight and then
it got bumped with the whole hiccup
we had during part A where
our radio provider just
took a crap
or something I don't know anyway
weirdness but we do have another call coming
in so let's go to it hello you're on OrangeLoungeRadio
who's this? Legend Zaku here
hey haven't heard from you in a while how you doing
Zaku? I'm doing fine
yeah I've been at my girl's place for
a few weekends now but
other than that it's yeah
I've been missing out on O.L.R. so I'm
playing catch up while she's in Europe for
a few weeks alright well I suppose
we can forgive
this one time but what's on your mind?
nothing much just
trying to order on GTA V
as much as I can
it's been pretty much the center piece of my
gaming life for
the past few weeks now
so what is it about this game that just makes you
so crazy about it?
Trevor I'm not going to spoil it
but just that character alone
I see Loki smiling
over there so you get it
mmhmm
and I probably haven't
even gotten through half the game
and already he's already
he's already proven to be the
you know the
batshit insane one
otherwise the others are just as
fucked up you know like Michael
and Franklin but yeah
that's what I've
been doing so far and
you know trying to get myself
in that steam machine beta
I think a lot of people are with you there
good luck though I hope
somebody in the O.L.R. gets one
and please give us the exclusive
hearts
yeah I know I mean it took a while
all I had to do was just like the last thing I had to do
was play something with the controller
which I was able to do
a few days ago but other than that
I'm already in
what was I going to say
what
about Grand Theft Auto 5 online
have you been dipping into that at all?
haven't done that yet
I guess I've made it a personal
mission of mine to just
wait it out as much as possible
instead of having to deal with the disappointment
of not getting in and speaking
of which have you guys
thought about creating a crew for
O.L.R. in the social club?
that's already happened
you might have missed Loki giving it a shout out in part A
but one more time Loki how can they find the
VoG community club?
if you go to
the rockstar social club
which I believe is socialclub.rockstar.com
and then you can
go to I think it's slash cruise
slash VoG network
would be how you would
get to it
socialclub.rockstargames.com
slash cruise slash VoG network
and the other option
would be to also go into our forums
and we have a link there too
I see
I guess I'll
end up trying that and hopefully
it won't be as
try to shoot Loki a bunch for me
since I don't know when I'll get in there
I mean
you gotta give rockstar credit
given the fact that they're doing their best to try to
you know, lurch this thing forward
as much as possible without any false starts
but then again it's like a bad
week to be an IT
grunt
if it's not Grand Theft Auto online
it's the health exchanges basically
not being up
so it's basically
all around, there's demand for just about
everything. The woes of being
popular on the internet. That is
true. Alright Zaku
I gotta let you go, we gotta go wrap up
but thank you so much for the call buddy
take care, have fun shooting
people in Grand Theft Auto
yeah, will do
stay good
sadly guys I am going to close up the skyline
I am so sorry, I know there were more trying to get through
but we are almost to
9.30 our time which for us is really late
I do want to just encourage you
if you do have something to say
Twitter is a great place to do that
twitter.com slash o-l-r or you can also email us
mailbag at orange lounge radio
dot com and Dark Zakra
loves to read your emails
speaking of
tweets, I wanted to read a couple just
real quick here, Tiger Claw
sent us a couple, we talked about the offline
SimCity one earlier so let me do this one
which is Activision Blizzard
turning the patent battle up
a notch, I didn't even know there was
a thing going on there with that
trying to bring it up here
let's see, this is when they got
sued over worlds inc on an online
game patent, Activision Blizzard is
suing back over different online
game patents
so essentially
what is the worlds game that was
worlds player software was
a toolkit for creating 3D
multiplayer online worlds
this goes all the way back to
2008 when worlds did a lawsuit
against NCSoft claiming
City of Heroes violated its
virtual space patent, it was
dismissed after the two companies settled
but it looks like Activision Blizzard
not going to settle anytime
soon and they are taking these patent guys
to court
I hope they can get that all sorted out
I think patent laws need to be re-examined
in this country myself because we hear a lot
about these patent messes all the time
but that's just me and that's probably
for another week, there's a lot of shit in this country
that needs to be fixed
but unfortunately we're out of time
Chell, I want to thank you so much for being here
tonight, thank you, I know you didn't get to
say a lot a lot outside but the
stuff you did say, I had to fist bump you several
times tonight so thank you for
your viewpoint tonight and
please come back again sometime soon
Thank you so much for having me and as soon as I can
Alright, anything you want to plug
even if that's your friend's game again or
what have you? I kind of want to plug
another game too, it's
also an indie game, forgot to plug it earlier
it doesn't have a demo out
yet but once it does I am downloading
that shit, it's called Coral Cove
completely traditional art
illustrated and animated
so cool
very nice, and Gabe
if you're out there listening
prime candidate right here in studio
hire this woman when she finishes
up all her schooling, I think she'll be great
alright, last
but not least, we go around and we get the final thoughts
I do want to say real quick though
before we get the final thoughts, thank you guys
so much for listening to our program
supporting the show, supporting independent
broadcasting, thank you for taking the time out of your
day to listen to us, if you're staying up late
listening to us live, thank you
your support means the world
all we ask if you do enjoy what you hear here at
Orange Launch Radio, tell a friend or two or five
about the show, and yeah
help spread the word about Orange Launch Radio
and we will grow our family even more
don't forget about the Podcast Awards
thing too, just again for your consideration
we would love it if you'd take the
15 seconds to go to PodcastAwards.com
and nominate us for People's Choice
and Best Gaming, but even if you
don't choose to nominate us
be sure to keep it independent
because the commercial guys
don't need the additional exposure
they already have plenty of money
let's go around and get everybody's
final thought, I guess I should start with our guest
Chell, do you have any final thoughts tonight?
It is weird
not having anybody come on me
I had
to do the last Showgirls reference
you know I had to
I like you a lot
even if that quote's gonna get you into trouble
Alright, Dark Sakura
I don't know how you're gonna follow that, but good luck
what's your final thought?
I'm very irritated that
Homestuck just updated and everybody
is on the page and now it's 503-ing
because I wanna know what the fuck
happens because it was like a
20 page update. God dammit
hussy. Alright
and my final thought is
Chell, maybe you could do my
nails sometime
then again I'm getting a little too old
for that hoary look
Loki
your final thought
I'm disappointed that I missed the leaked
Godzilla trailer. What?
They're making a new Godzilla?
Didn't you know? It's been all over Tumblr
It's like a Matthew Broderick one, I remember that
No, this one's the French President
Oh, really?
Interesting, alright, well, have to check that out
Who thinks Matthew Broderick?
He's Godzilla
What happened to my career?
Good things apparently
Oh, Matthew Broderick, yeah
Oh, yeah, no, the other guy did Breaking Bad
and all that, yeah, but
What happened to my career? I'm making tons of money
Matthew Broderick, well, I think he went to stage
I think he's done a lot with stage
Election was one of my favorite movies ever
That was like 13 years ago
The Producers
Yeah, that's true, that's why I think he's done more like stage type of stuff
Alright, there we go
There we go, that's it
Thank you again for tuning into the show
Have fun with your games, people
And we will see you next time
Next week we'll do it all over again
Here at Orange Lounge Radio
Good night
See you next week
Thanks for watching!