[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, January 18, 2009, could we see the DSi released in April for the US?
[SPEAKER_01]: Circuit City goes under, and are the .hack games set to make a comeback?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are that podcast on the internet dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are back after a little bit of a break.
[SPEAKER_07]: Took a little break last week because I was in Hawaii taking a little vacation, but I'm back now.
[SPEAKER_07]: and refreshed and feeling better.
[SPEAKER_07]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll be joining you for the next several hours.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not joining us tonight, sadly, the happiest bunny on the farm, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_07]: She has the night off.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's her last week before going back to school, so she's taking care of some things around the house.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we have somebody filling in tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: I called the other woman that I know, the other female gamer I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: So say hello to Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm your mistress.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: How you doing, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about yourself?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm doing great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's good to hear.
[SPEAKER_07]: I see you're wearing a Silent Hill t-shirt showing your love for Pyramid Head.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because I thought the camera was going to be working tonight and I did my hair and everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's the funny thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know you look very cute, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can take a picture and post it to the website or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: All in vain.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I get to see you and that's important.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because you're not gay at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to say you and Jamie both have Silent Hill shirts that you wear to the show, so we need to get you both here sometime and you can be twinsies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are they the same shirt?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think she has a slightly different one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mine's thermal, so it keeps me warm.
[SPEAKER_07]: I see.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's good because we have a cold garage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm going to survive tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm going to get the heater on in just a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: But thank you also for bringing Snickerdoodles to the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because you know bribing us with food always freaking rocks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Always.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Say hello as well to the one and only Techmaster Loki, who's joining us tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_07]: How you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Doing fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Great.
[SPEAKER_06]: How was your week off?
[SPEAKER_06]: What did you end up doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Trying to get Grand Theft Auto PC to work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's taken a turn for the worst.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was doing so well.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was working just fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: And all of a sudden, Rockstar's like, ah, fuck this shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're not going to work no matter what you do now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've reinstalled it like eight times now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I've uninstalled all the other things that remotely might be related to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it just does not want to work.
[SPEAKER_06]: And apparently I'm not alone.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I just don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I give up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually bought this game, and see, that teaches me for not pirating this shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: See what happens?
[SPEAKER_06]: If I buy it, it breaks, and it sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I had just downloaded it like I should have, wouldn't be having this problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well alright, well hey, you had tuned in, because also last week we missed, you know, our buddy Bobby, Bobby Blackwolf does a show before us here on All Games Radio, and he does the Bobby Blackwolf show on Sundays, but he just launched a new Friday night show, right, Friday Night Gaming, and you tried to play Grand Theft Auto with us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, that was even more fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, for some reason then Xbox Live said, no, you're never going to connect to this game ever if you even want to.
[SPEAKER_06]: I tried four different times.
[SPEAKER_06]: I even reset my system a few different times and it just said, no, I'm sorry, you just cannot connect to this game ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: So fuck Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_06]: That being said, still been playing lots of Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of Grand Theft Auto 4, I have to bring this up.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I gotta rub this in.
[SPEAKER_07]: While I was in Hawaii, I got Grand Theft Auto 4 for $30 on the Xbox 360, and I got Metal Gear Solid 4 for $20 for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Both new and wrapped.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like getting them for $5 in Hawaii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really cheap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Radio Shack, apparently.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had forgotten that they had gotten in the market of selling games, but then when I saw that they were clearing them out, because I guess I hadn't been performing very well, I suddenly remembered, oh yeah, I think we reported that on the show once, is that Radio Shack was selling games.
[SPEAKER_07]: And not anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, actually, I was going to say that...
[SPEAKER_06]: Best Buy was clearing out some games as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had Ninja Gaiden 2 for $10 for the 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't buy it because I don't have a 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should get one one of these days.
[SPEAKER_07]: You really should.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you still on your anti-Microsoft thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought you finally caved and you were going to get one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not anti-Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just anti-Xbox because it's a piece of crap system.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys missed it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bryce, Princess, and Loki were getting into it before the show about Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe we'll talk about it later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, well, why don't you just tell them what you said and I won't even need to do anything because, you know, it was so asinine that, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll get to it later.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got to introduce someone else because she's been sitting there very quiet and patiently, which is so unlike her.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that going to be your first words on the show?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, it is going to be my first words on the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: She has never been on the show before.
[SPEAKER_07]: Miss Victoria
[SPEAKER_07]: See now, I'm looking, the chat room is going crazy right now for two reasons.
[SPEAKER_07]: The earlier, and of course you can always join us in chat, chat.orangeloungeradio.com The chat's not working on the laptop, so we can't see it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll get it working somehow later on.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Loki and I can see it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're there.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're freaking out.
[SPEAKER_07]: They want pics of Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'll try to get something on the Twitter because, you know, OMG woman.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'll try to get Rice Princess and Victoria to pose and maybe I'll get them to make out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still have that one jello shot in the refrigerator from New Year's.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, they're freaking out because right now in chat, a brand new Orange Lounge Radio website is being previewed.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's been made by our buddy Deekman, and he's posted the preview link there in chat, and it's amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am so excited that finally our website that looks old is going to be going away and looking new.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am so freaking excited.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you know why that's why I love our listeners?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's like, which one is giving them the bigger boner?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like women on the show or the new website layout?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Back to Victoria.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's never been on the show before.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have to interview Victoria a little bit.
More about me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all about you, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Duh!
[SPEAKER_07]: So what kinds of video games do you like?
[SPEAKER_07]: What kinds of video games do you play?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you play a lot of games?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's okay if you don't.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_09]: I play Rock Band when I come over to your house.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the only video... Well, we have a PlayStation 2 at my house.
[SPEAKER_09]: My roommate plays Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the only thing I play is on my GameCube.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I play Mario Party 7 because that's the only game I have.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I stole it from my brother.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so she knows a little bit about her games.
[SPEAKER_07]: She knows what she's talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: So she's got some stuff that she plays.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: What is it that you write, bitch?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I'm a Harry Potter role player.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a big Harry Potter nerd.
[SPEAKER_09]: I admit it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm proud of it.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, you need to shut the fuck up because you used to be the vice president of the Star Trek Club.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like 15 years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: He has such a boner when the movie is going to come out.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's going to drag my ass to the midnight premiere.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can already tell you.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what exactly do you mean by... Or like...
[SPEAKER_09]: role-playing basically I take on one of the roles of one of the characters in Harry Potter and somebody else takes another role or make they make up their own and we just plot and we don't I'm not like no no no no no no no no no no no yeah basically that's that's that's it and we just plot and make our own little storyline it's glorified fan fiction basically
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, alright So you do other nerdy stuff too though, like I know you watch Lost religiously All the time, oh my god, Wednesday, I'm so excited!
[SPEAKER_07]: The thing I love about Victoria is she's so animated, this is great I gotta read some comments from chat about the whole roleplay thing Chat.orangelawnsradio.com, we have GS68 says she puts on a robe and wizard hat Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_09]: I do not.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's only for the premieres.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you going to dress up for the next premiere?
[SPEAKER_09]: I might.
[SPEAKER_09]: If it comes down to it, I'll just buy a t-shirt and wear my Harry Potter jacket.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's nothing wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: What else was I going to say about you being a nerd?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you went to Comic Con last year.
[SPEAKER_09]: I go to Comic Con every year.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm from San Diego.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I go to Comic Con every year.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be huge this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can already tell you it's the 40th anniversary.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't bought my tickets yet, but I should do that soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is it you like to see when you're at Comic-Con?
[SPEAKER_09]: I go for the movie premieres and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last year, I saw the panel for The Day the Earth Stood Still.
[SPEAKER_09]: I unfortunately went to the Twilight panel and wanted to kill myself because all the little screaming 12-year-olds were creaming their panties over Robert What's-His-Face.
[SPEAKER_09]: I go for the movie premieres.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've met so many celebrities because of Comic-Con and
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, met Matthew Fox, who I kind of creamed my panties over.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, all right then.
[SPEAKER_07]: Suddenly the chatters are lining up to roleplay Matthew Fox in your next Harry Potter thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, we've got to take this back to video games at some point.
[SPEAKER_07]: But my buddy Shane, an old friend of the show, Miklatov, is listening, and he's sending me private messages.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell Irene and Victoria hi, and they need to make out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell them now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, Shane!
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll have to get the liquor out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe that'll happen later.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, let's actually get back to some gaming here real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do want to ask you one other question, though, speaking of video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't take it back to gaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love World of Warcraft, as you know, and Rice Princess also dabbles in World of Warcraft once in a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really funny story.
[SPEAKER_07]: She played her boyfriend's account last night and out-DPSed another character because she didn't even know what she was doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyway, you are what we call a WoW Widow.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a little bit of a grudge against WoW.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: All day long.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would stop doing Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I have a friend in San Diego.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of my gays in San Diego plays WoW just so he can dress his characters up in pretty outfits.
[SPEAKER_09]: He told me this.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's like, it's a guild of nothing but women, and we dress our characters up in pretty outfits.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: There's so many great things to say, but first off, Victoria has her gaze.
[SPEAKER_07]: She has.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there really is just a guild of women that dress up.
[SPEAKER_09]: A guild of women and Patrick that just dress up and they run around and like, I don't know what he says, they run around and just, I don't know, do things.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you know what it was your ex-boyfriend was doing in WoW that took so long?
[SPEAKER_07]: Was he dressing up in princess outfits?
[SPEAKER_09]: Serving the castle.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is it you do when you play for four hours?
[SPEAKER_07]: Raiding.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so, yeah, that's what he would do.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so when...
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I broke up with him, to say the least.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you tell him that that was the reason you were breaking up with him?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it wasn't the main reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: He was a douche, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that had a pretty big influence on why I am no longer with this person.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I'm sure we'll get into it later if we're talking about Warcraft stories and you hear a big, Ah!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, hell no!
[SPEAKER_07]: From the corner.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stop talking about that shit!
[SPEAKER_07]: Grand Theft Auto 4
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: There's other sandbox games that have come out on the PC, like Saints Row 2 just came out, but that sucks on the PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Horrible port.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rockstar, unfortunately, is not doing anything to fix Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: To be honest, I've never seen a game where I can reinstall it and it still doesn't work correctly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Except for Crysis.
[SPEAKER_06]: Crysis also didn't work correctly when I reinstalled it, but that was a whole different way.
[SPEAKER_06]: I couldn't finish that game because, you know, I would get to the general or whatever and he'd be standing there like a mannequin and couldn't progress any further because the event didn't trigger.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that sucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Other than that... Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I watched Nellie play more Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I forgot I had that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys have Animal Crossing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: I ruined it for her, apparently, because I cheated.
[SPEAKER_02]: Were you time-traveling?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, we did that before.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, this is actually pure cheating now.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have devices that you can, you know, hack the memory and stuff and give yourself all this crazy shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Including download content.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's pay for unlock content.
Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the game's really boring because it's just Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they had some fun codes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had a code where you can go into the characters' houses and you can steal their furniture and move it around and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you can also do it to the stores, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can just go and pick up stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And see, that was funny because we had maxed out money and there were some characters that were pissing us off so we just trapped them in a corner and surrounded the furniture around them.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that was mildly satisfying for a second there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, really what I've been doing with my consoles lately is I've been streaming movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty much what I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually downloaded a bunch of the Rift Track shorts last night.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were watching some of those.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, the PS3 actually works really good.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: and it's really nice actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very, very nice looking.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes full screen video really easy.
[SPEAKER_06]: The layout of it's really big so that you can see it on your TV and it works great.
[SPEAKER_06]: So definitely something to check out especially if you're just browsing YouTube stuff or you want to show your friends something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just happened to show them the new shorts that they did for YouTube Live for Charlie the Unicorn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to actually show us everything and they're bringing me a turntable I get to keep.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the one that Newark's actually doing the turntable for.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the only thing I don't like about it though is it's all urban and hip hop music.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it makes sense in that game because there's not a lot of scratching in techno music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I was going to say that's kind of...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: The music that is produced by Turntables.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just wish there was some more house music.
[SPEAKER_06]: And maybe there is.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'll find out more this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I get to see it on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm pretty psyched about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So definitely tune back in next week for Loki's review.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rice Princess, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Victoria grabbed your boob.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just didn't want to acknowledge it on air.
[SPEAKER_07]: But thank you for doing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I totally downloaded Samurai Shodown 2 on Virtual Console and I was having good times with that because that was one of my original fighting games that I loved to play all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was playing that for a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's your character?
[SPEAKER_02]: Galford because he has a dog.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the only reason I ever played it because Galford was on there and he was hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else?
[SPEAKER_02]: PopCap games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I got Silent Hill Origins for Christmas kind of late because it came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, on the PlayStation 2?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, how is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not the best Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not bad, but it's different.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because it was made by some European team.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you ever play Silent Hill 5?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to, but no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Technically, it's Silent Hill Homecoming.
[SPEAKER_06]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Homecoming 5.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't it only on the... Silent Hill The Room, you know, that's 4, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't give a crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, isn't it on the Xbox?
[SPEAKER_02]: 360 and PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: PS3, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have any of those.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I keep forgetting.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're stubborn.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't get a 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you have friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you know me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do I have to come over here and play?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I am so fucking lazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to drive here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Silent Hill, but I also love not driving places.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of these days, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe I'll pull a Victoria and stay the weekend at your house.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can we tell that story real quick?
[SPEAKER_07]: Can we?
[SPEAKER_07]: The reason why Victoria is here on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Victoria, why don't you tell our listeners why you're here on the program tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I'm kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm opening a hotel right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a new hotel opening out in...
[SPEAKER_09]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and my roommate isn't home because she's in Sonoma seeing her boyfriend.
[SPEAKER_09]: So she's not going to be home until tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm basically stuck at Rob's house until tomorrow imposing on his good hospitality and all that nonsense.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm very grateful to him for letting me stay here.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: You better gush.
[SPEAKER_09]: If not, I'd be sleeping in my car.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell the listeners about how wonderful I am.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's so good to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I just thought that was my story.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, there was one game I did forget about that I actually played this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ninja Blade.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played the demo for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game looks kind of like a rip-off of Ninja Gaiden 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually more of a rip-off of Conan or God of War.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game plays very similar.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have three different weapons with varying speed and damage.
[SPEAKER_06]: and, um, you know, it's all ninja themed and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then, there's a lot of, like, quick time event, um, cutscenes that are in the game, which are pretty cool looking, just very cinematic and action packed.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's one scene where you're actually running down the side of a skyscraper, and, uh,
[SPEAKER_06]: Killing these dragon-looking monster things, which are pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's definitely worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's definitely not Vampire Reigns.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'll be a good one to check out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's coming out at the end of March now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's one of those secondary FromSoftware games that Microsoft's publishing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times, good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp So Victoria, you know how you can extend your stay here at Rob's?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do his laundry, do his dishes, clean his house The guy that I was seeing told me to cook for him, but you know, he's all diet-y and stuff
[SPEAKER_07]: I wanted to give Loki the presents I got him from Hawaii.
[SPEAKER_07]: What did you get me?
[SPEAKER_07]: So I got him an authentic dashboard hula girl doll because I thought he'd like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got Jamie one too.
[SPEAKER_07]: She'll find out about that next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I got some, since you like food, I got you some macadamia nut covered toffee which is really good.
[SPEAKER_07]: So eat it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll give this to Nellie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Eat it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nellie will like it too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just remembered that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you were done with your gaming week too then, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_07]: Victoria, I don't know if there's been anything you've been playing, but why don't you share?
[SPEAKER_09]: I played Rock Band with Rob yesterday.
[SPEAKER_09]: We made a band, The Shrieking Beavers.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I have a game on my phone that I've been playing, but that's as awesome as it gets.
[SPEAKER_07]: What game on your phone?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's called Pump Jack.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like a little, you're like a little... Sounds dirty.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it came with my sidekick.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, like, it's like your little wheel and you have to go collect all the gas cans and you have to avoid the little cactuses that can explode and kill you.
[SPEAKER_09]: The new Pump Jack!
[SPEAKER_09]: Pump Jack, yeah!
[SPEAKER_09]: No, and I've been playing it since I got my damn phone, which is almost a year, and I still haven't beaten it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm on the last level, and it's driving me crazy that I can't win.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which goes to show you why I don't play video games, because I get frustrated, and then I just don't want to play anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we have an interesting story later on that might appeal to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll talk about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: What they're doing for frustrated people like you.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: The old school one for PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was playing that like crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't really touched it since I got back from Hawaii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I got to a part of the game where it actually got hard again.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm getting to the Victoria level of frustration with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'll go back and try to beat it at some point.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then as far as new stuff I've been playing.
[SPEAKER_07]: The new stuff I've been playing is on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Konami put out some interesting games this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: They put out a demo for Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_07]: The new iPhone DDR game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is...
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Its biggest problem is it's choppy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, if you think the Xbox frame rate thing is an issue, try playing DDR on your iPhone.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty horrible.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's very pretty.
[SPEAKER_07]: For a cell phone game, it's actually very pretty looking, and the sound's very good, because obviously iPhones are iPods, so the music is obviously full quality, which is kind of nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: And basically what it is, a little dance pad shows up at the bottom of your screen, and you play with your fingers.
[SPEAKER_07]: You dance with your fingers to the music, which is cute, but I don't know how...
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, luckily it's free.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can't complain.
[SPEAKER_07]: Totally free.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's just the one song for free.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just one song?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's one song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's like a preview of what they're working on or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: The other game I got on the iPhone is Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_07]: They actually have on the iPhone now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a new version of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's called Silent Hill The Revenge.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember the name of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm actually looking it up on my phone right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's called...
[SPEAKER_07]: Silent Hill The Escape Silent Hill The Escape
[SPEAKER_07]: I have no idea if they can hear that over the air, but a little bit of what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, you actually... It uses the touchscreen.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a whole new interface that uses the touchscreen.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can slide back and forth to move through the maze, and you turn left and right, and then to fire your gun, you tap on the crosshair to fire the gun, and the crosshair is all tilt-sensitive.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you want to aim up and down, you tilt.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you will run across these nurses in the maze, and you can blow their brains out, basically.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not really a Silent Hill game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically a dungeon-crawling game that they've slapped Silent Hill graphics onto.
[SPEAKER_02]: Surely you just, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, Silent Hill is all about avoiding things.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't necessarily have to shoot everything in the face, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: But this game kind of encourages that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have never played Silent Hill, so I appreciate you explaining it to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm telling you, for the listeners, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what it's about.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've seen the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you didn't like the movie, did you?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was pissed at the end.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was like, what the fuck is this?
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's more one of those things that's much better if you've played the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I was told.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, Silent Hill on the iPhone is kind of eh.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's only $8.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can be honest.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually a really smooth running game.
[SPEAKER_07]: The controls are kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Compared to DDR, the frame rate is much better.
[SPEAKER_07]: It runs a lot smoothly.
[SPEAKER_07]: For a mobile phone game, the graphics are actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you play with headphones, the sound and stuff is actually kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's actually not a bad game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just kind of short and not really Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I mean, if you want to get kind of an interesting maze exploring game that you shoot things in, get this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or if you want like a, you know, just, it's a cute little time waster.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, there's only like six levels, so I don't know if it's necessarily worth $8.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think maybe $5 would have been a better price point for this, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: whatever, I guess yeah, when I think of Silent Hill I totally think of shooting my way out of a maze they had to come up with they have these little story elements that are in it too, although not much I haven't seen Pyramid Head yet, but I might not have just played far enough it's alright, you have to remember it's a mobile phone game, if your expectations are high, you're only setting yourself up for disappointment I know, why don't they just make it a generic game or something it's nothing like Silent Hill well it is
[SPEAKER_07]: We have a Victoria mic because we can't hear it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because then it wouldn't get sold if they didn't put Silent Hill on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty much it right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But what's interesting about this is that, hey, there's a Metal Gear game coming out and a lot of people are like, OMG, Metal Gear on the phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if it's anything like this, don't get your hopes up.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, it's worse than that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a real shooter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then it's not even going to be anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then a pad comes up and you just use your fingers to hit the buttons and it's only one song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so there it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was my quick review on the Silent Hill The Escape, the iPhone game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Otherwise, I don't think I've really been playing a lot of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, just playing the same old stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there's console games too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm the best warrior ever
[SPEAKER_07]: So we'll do that a little later on.
[SPEAKER_07]: And she'll be back next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And apparently also in housekeeping tonight, we have a brand new Orange Lounge Radio website coming soon, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because the beta looks great.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you're in chat right now, just ask Deakman.
[SPEAKER_07]: He did awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: He did.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't look like it was made in the early 2000s.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks very modern.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's still simple, though, is what I like about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's sophisticated.
[SPEAKER_07]: He didn't load it up with a bunch of crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: It still looks efficient, which would be cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm very excited.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's attractive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Big thank you to Deakman.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we'll find other ways to thank him later on when the site goes live.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe we'll send Victoria out there to babysit because he's married.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Victoria can go babysit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a 10-year-old brother and I want to kill him every time I see him.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't stand children.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm reporting you to the authorities.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I don't hurt him.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just kind of pull his hair a little bit and smack him in the head and tell him to quit looking like a little girl with his John Lennon hair.
[SPEAKER_07]: Doesn't your 10-year-old brother play Grand Theft Auto?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, he does.
[SPEAKER_09]: He called me on Christmas Day asking me to find him cheat codes for Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I said, God damn it, you have the fucking internet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look it up yourself.
[SPEAKER_06]: To your 10-year-old brother.
[SPEAKER_09]: To my 10-year-old brother.
[SPEAKER_09]: He knows I love him.
[SPEAKER_06]: He shouldn't be playing Grand Theft Auto 4 anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's been playing Grand Theft Auto since he was like 6.
[SPEAKER_09]: My dad thought it was appropriate to buy him GTA 3 when he was 6.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, fabulous parenting on my parents' part.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wonder how I turned out so normal-ish.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Cuckoo, Kudo, Kodo, Bunko, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so Kodu.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, it's basically a very simplified game-making program.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're comparing it to LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's anything like LittleBigPlanet at all, but it's kind of object-oriented programming stuff, and you can use the characters and stuff in there to basically create your own little games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're all kind of pixelated-looking because of the...
[SPEAKER_06]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: One of these days, I want to get Aaron back on the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm hoping he'll listen at one point.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's the guy who did Snake 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to talk to him now, like six weeks out after his game's been released and see how it's been going.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw him respond back to, there was an IGN review of his game or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: They were talking about the hot or not of community games, and his was actually in the not section.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the reasons that they gave are retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're all, oh, it's Snake game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it totally looked like the guy did not play the game at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it was retarded, but it was funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because he called him out on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's like, doesn't sound like you played this at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, there's a lot of features that you didn't mention.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's some other games that were just crap that they gave good reviews for.
[SPEAKER_06]: But remember, it's just one person's review.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just because they happen to be behind a website...
[SPEAKER_06]: UGO bought the 1UP Network
[SPEAKER_07]: This week, and basically, it caused, you know, long story short, it caused EGM to go under Electronic Gaming Monthly.
[SPEAKER_07]: The magazine is no more.
[SPEAKER_07]: And lots and lots of folks that were working at 1up.com, goodbye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Including the people that were doing the 1up show, and 1up was 1up Yours, was the video show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to be honest, guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's not a lot of extra news to talk about with us.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure you guys all read it in the week we were gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you all are probably pretty familiar with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: If not, go look on any blog that was running last week, and I'm sure you'll read about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very interesting, like, really how much love was out there for these shows and this site, which was interesting to me because, honestly, I've never...
[SPEAKER_07]: And no offense, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, and to be honest, I don't even know who Yu-Gi-Oh is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I've never heard of them as a website.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't they run a lot of other websites for entertainment, movies, things of that nature?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're trying to be like a one, not one, an IGN type of service, but I've never visited them ever, and you know, I don't know, I just have never heard of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's, you know, maybe that's my own ignorance, but I've never heard of them at all, and
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: How much these guys that were producing these shows and doing this stuff were really into video games and really into their craft because as many independent podcasts have shown for years and years and years, you don't have to get paid to do this stuff if you really, really enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So my kind of thing was I was going to say, well, guys, here you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's your chance to keep doing what you do just because this may not be the day job anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can still keep it going.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they have.
[SPEAKER_07]: So props to them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because now there is the whole Rebel FM, I think it's called.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think there's another one called Geekbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: So props to them for continuing to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm kind of curious to see how much this is going to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: And kind of where some of these guys end up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think... Well, this is the same thing that's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember, you know, that's how we got This Week in Tech.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you know... True.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fallout from Tech TV, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sure that they'll make it just as well and probably even better now that they're away from 1UP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why do you say that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just because.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at this week in tech.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they're doing very well and I think that if they were still part of G4, the whole tech TV thing, I think they wouldn't be doing as well as they are now independently.
[SPEAKER_06]: Less influence from other things that are more corporate oriented.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, good luck.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's never fun to talk about job layoffs, but good luck to those folks.
[SPEAKER_07]: And good luck to 1UP too, staying kind of on top of things now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, they've taken a lot of negative press over this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got to ask you, Rice Princess, because you were on 1UP for quite some time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Years ago when I was posting on there and participating on the site, you were kind of the one that got me into that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think you kind of hung out there for a little while after that.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you think about all this news about it closing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is 1UP a site you would still visit?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or are you like, eh, the people are gone?
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's interesting because, yeah, I actually did revisit my 1UP account a couple weeks ago, actually, before any of this ever happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I still have the same friends and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't really do anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, it's always sad when a community, a group of people, just can't meet at the same place anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like having your favorite local coffee shop or something close down.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like, oh, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: You just moved to a new coffee shop!
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, that's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: People can get each other's information, go to another place and do it, but you can go to another coffee shop, but it might not be as cool or as quirky or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, the thing is, in defense, I guess you would say to UGO, print
[SPEAKER_06]: Game Informer, something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Electronic Gaming Monthly News
[SPEAKER_07]: has been dead to me for 10 years.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember that magazine back in the day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my God, that issue where they actually had the Shang Long lie in it for the April Fool's.
[SPEAKER_07]: I freaking had that issue with the magazine.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember some of that stuff happening, but honestly, I stopped subscribing to that a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people did.
[SPEAKER_07]: So for me, it was more the news of, oh, well, you know, that's too bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's an icon of my youth that's going away.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, with the advent of, you know, internet news outlets and especially blogs, blogs are becoming more popular than, you know, normal media sites because people like to identify with other people who are on their level, who are normal, who can give, you know, a perspective, you know, that's not like corporate.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a big purpose for magazines now in this day and age is to read when you're on the toilet.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now that they have iPhones, you can look at blogs when you're on the toilet now.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I don't even need magazines anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can look at websites.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only, oh wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: What, Victoria, what?
[SPEAKER_09]: You a nasty hoe.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't want to know what you do when you're taking a dump.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, everybody poops.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haven't you ever read that book?
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody poops.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you wipe your butt and you get a little bit of poop on your finger and you put it on your thing, you can't throw it away like a magazine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm down with the old school magazines being in my bathroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You see all the Maxims lined up on my toilet.
[SPEAKER_02]: La la la la la.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can move away from that now.
[SPEAKER_07]: But what I'm talking about is that, you know, people used to have the magazines or the, what was it, the bathroom reader books or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now we can have the internet even when we're pooping.
[SPEAKER_02]: We could.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we can look at blogs and all that there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess you're right about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's gross, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So magazine, I'm just saying magazines are, you know, it's one last use.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you take your, oh, I'm holding your laptop right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've had this in the bathroom with you, haven't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's poop somewhere on here, isn't there?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, damn it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why are the keys so sticky, Rob?
[SPEAKER_07]: You're disgusting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody burn my hands off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there's a rumor coming from IGN.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have multiple sources close to Nintendo that have told the site that the DSi will be out in the US on April 4th at $179.
[SPEAKER_06]: I somehow don't believe this.
[SPEAKER_07]: And why is that that you don't believe this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there's just a few things that strike me as weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo, for some reason, likes releasing their stuff, especially hardware, on Sundays.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the 4th is actually a Saturday.
[SPEAKER_06]: For one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, that's my only thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a Saturday, not Sunday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Therefore, I am calling the whole thing bunk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't really matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think, if anything, they would want to hold off on...
[SPEAKER_06]: Selling the DSi because they've been selling tons of DSs already and you know I think if they bring the DSi out it's just going to cut into their DS sales and they're not really having trouble selling DS systems and I don't know there's not really any DSi software out even in Japan right now I mean other than the download stuff but
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, they could always just cut the price of the DS that's out there right now by like $20 and release the DSi.
[SPEAKER_06]: For $99.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, then people will start making love to DSs like crazy or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then they'll sell both because you'll have the more high-priced ones for folks that want the camera and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: They could do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, what Loki says about the date is especially interesting because Nintendo does usually do Sunday.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder if it doesn't mean maybe shipping on April 4th to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, it just doesn't really seem like there would be any reason to release this now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, there's just a few download games and that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just not really that worthwhile.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if the DS was kind of tanking a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really tanking, but like if sales are starting to drop off a little bit in Japan and maybe that's why they released the DSi, but I don't think they're dropping off at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: We're still selling tons of DS systems, not having a problem whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some comments from chatroom on this story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sai says, I think their strategy is that Nintendo fans will buy the 179 DSi and most people will buy the DS Lite at regular.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of similar to what I was saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, so the DSi is for hardcore gamers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, uh-huh, sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: or people who want the extra garbage that it's going to have.
[SPEAKER_07]: X-Link says, and you can take it to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can indeed play your DS in the bathroom, and I'm sure there's people that do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has a really crappy web browser.
[SPEAKER_02]: No pun intended.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has a horrible web browser built into it as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bobby says, Activision Blizzard doesn't want the DSi released because their best-selling DS game won't be compatible.
[SPEAKER_07]: Guitar Hero on tour.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Activision and Blizzard don't have a say in it, so poop on them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just... This show is really poop-filled.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll just come out with another peripheral to plug into the SD card slot and then they can make their crappy games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to have some stupid drum peripheral.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: All their DS guitar games suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to concur with you on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though I used to play DDR with the remote control when I couldn't afford to go to the arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's one of the biggest iPhone games right now, in fact so big that Apple actually displays it on a big banner inside their store?
[SPEAKER_02]: Silent Hill The Escape.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, not Silent Hill The Escape.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tap Tap Revenge.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tap Tap Revenge is like a somewhat DDR clone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hit the buttons.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's a clone of Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've played the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like Guitar Hero, if anything else.
[SPEAKER_07]: The notes scroll down and you tap.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what it's closest to, is Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: But still, though, you're not dancing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are tapping.
[SPEAKER_06]: If it's like a Beatmania game or something like that, then yeah, it's a little bit more acceptable, because...
[SPEAKER_06]: DDR on a DS DDR on a DS
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well, hey, speaking of some systems, there's still some love for the old systems too.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, systems so old that Victoria actually owns them because she can afford them.
[SPEAKER_07]: You are such a bitch!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_09]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_07]: I love you!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: PlayStation 2 reaches the 50 million sold mark in North America.
[SPEAKER_07]: PlayStation 2 has actually hit that mark, 50 million, and I believe that is more than any other system, if I'm not mistaken.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, that's a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they keep breaking, and you have to keep rebuying them.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, there is a note from John Kohler, the marketing head of Sony Computer Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't intend on discarding the system anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, they still sell like hundreds of thousands of units each month.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, because they can't play the games on my PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to release the PSI on April 4th for a price tag of $159.
[SPEAKER_02]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, people are saying the PS3 needs to come down in price and they might actually sell some more units.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be too late.
[SPEAKER_07]: Too little, too late.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just a little too late.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just, might as well give up this console generation, just, you know, work on the next one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, we talked a little bit before about the video download service that they have in Japan for the Wii, which is kind of
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very family friendly, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have cartoons and other Japanese programming stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, something similar may be coming to the US this year, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: And...
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, Fujisoft, the company behind it, was at CES and told GamerSight that they are planning on bringing the WiiWare video service to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: It says, we can't quite tell at the moment, but if the negotiations are a success, maybe within the year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is cool, but we still need some better storage on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or an SD memory card What's that, Victoria?
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't work the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm, like, retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've tried playing and it's just... You know what's funny is that the Wii is, like, made for, like, people to be able to understand very easily, but you can't figure it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I can, but I'm just not good at it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like having a little control in my hand.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I guess it's kind of good if you're one of those people who, like, you know, moves the controller to the left when you want your little person to go to the left.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, when you're playing Mario Brothers, old school.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, just jump right, right, right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, no, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but I fail epically at the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: What games do you enjoy on Wii?
[SPEAKER_09]: I like that Wario one where you have to go through the little movements.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what it's called.
[SPEAKER_07]: WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_09]: That one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that's like one of the only games I've ever played on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: Other than Guitar Hero because my cousins have it on.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you're a Wii-tard is what you're basically saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I'm a Wii-tard.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, hey, if you want to get a wee cheap, you might want to run over to Circuit City because Circuit City has gone under.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know, so many of these companies are going under recently.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I almost feel like we need a theme song on the show for when companies go under.
[SPEAKER_07]: So let me try reading the story to this music.
[SPEAKER_07]: Circuit City has announced that they are going to be filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, no, they filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy already and closed 155 stores.
[SPEAKER_07]: That wasn't enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now they are unable to find a buyer to keep themselves afloat.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are being liquidated.
[SPEAKER_07]: So basically, sadly, and I...
[SPEAKER_07]: I apologize to any listeners we have who work for Circuit City because this news has got to suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we really hope somebody else will come in and buy up some of these old stores.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they are going under.
[SPEAKER_07]: And from what I'm hearing from people who do work for them that I know on LiveJournal and stuff, apparently the company was horribly managed.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's finally come back to get them.
[SPEAKER_02]: They kind of had an old business model, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, like...
[SPEAKER_02]: with places like Fry's and Best Buy and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Circuit City was just kind of the little guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they just can't keep up.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they kept building them next to Best Buy's.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, or Best Buy's kept building them next to Circuit City's.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, like, you know, they kind of didn't have a chance.
[SPEAKER_07]: And here's the interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, the way liquidation sales usually work is that they will be... By the way, this doesn't affect Canada.
[SPEAKER_07]: Circuit City Canada is still going because it's not the U.S., so you don't have a U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: bankruptcy thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Circuit City Canada is still fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Circuit City U.S., they're going under.
[SPEAKER_07]: And when a store liquidates, usually they're going to have sales for the first week 10% off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then in the second week, 20% off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Third week, 30% off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's the thing is that people are already snatching up the TVs, the Xboxes, and all this stuff because they're like, OMG, 10% off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Church of City was marking half this shit up to begin with, which is probably part of the reason they're going under.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you're really sadly not going to say much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, they're doing some stuff 10, some stuff 20, and some stuff 30 all in the same week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't been to the one here yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you check it out already?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nathan went.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's where he was going to look for his RAM or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good luck with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: All the good stuff is going to be gone already.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure it went this weekend.
[SPEAKER_07]: All that's going to be left is DVD and CDs of bands you've never heard of.
[SPEAKER_06]: We went over to Circuit City the other day to look at their... This is before I got my new car stereo.
[SPEAKER_06]: They actually had less stereos than Walmart did.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, and Walmart has a pretty pathetic car stereo section.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I think Circuit City had like eight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know that Walmart had a car section or car stereo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they're very, they're, they suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I was like looking for a price for one of them and the woman's like, it'd be on that shelf over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just like, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, honestly, I hate to be rude, but it was actually kind of a selling point to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember that one time back when they were selling Wheeze and stuff and we drove by the Circuit City and there was like no one there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it was the night the Wheeze came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Best Buy had a line going around the block.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember we went out when the Wheeze came out?
[SPEAKER_07]: We were giving out, what was it, orange soda?
[SPEAKER_07]: We were trying to sell our show to locals.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so we did that, went to Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Circuit City had like five people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, that's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Poor guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: I feel bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know there's someone who listens to this show who works for Circuit City, who just left their job, who's a little pissed that we're riffing on him a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it does suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I have friends actually from school that worked at Circuit City, but they kind of knew it was coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they've been looking for a little while for another job.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, like they had something lined up.
[SPEAKER_02]: They knew this was going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I mean, it sucks, but they prepared.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they've known.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I hope that's the case.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good luck to all those that were impacted.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unless you were part of the reason Circuit City went under, like you're one of these upper managements that didn't know what you were doing, then, well, sucks, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, apparently there was a story about this dog that was as dead as Circuit City for at least a moment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently a woman in Michigan nearly killed her dog when she accidentally struck it on the temple with a Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, she was busy doing some Wii Sports bowling, didn't have the wrist strap on or something like that, and the Wii Remote went straight and hit the dog in the temple, killing him instantly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: But then, but luckily though, the dog, Ozzy, was not moving and stuff, so they called a neighbor who apparently had some veterinary training and she was able to revive the dog using mouth-to-mouth.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the dog had to be taken to the real vet where, you know, apparently had some severe brain swelling due to cardiac arrest.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the dog, you know, apparently is fine now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, she had to kiss the dog on the mouth?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not kiss.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's not mouth to mouth.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually nose.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to blow down the dog's nose.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love dogs, but not that much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, if my cat was dying, I'd do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck that, it's my cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's family.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care if there's boogers on its nose.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Irene's dying, but her breath kind of smells.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, I wouldn't blame you, Matt.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I'm just going to let her die, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, I'm never going to give you mouth to nose.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you're dear to me, but that's nasty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just let me die, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe your mouth, but your nose, hell no.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then when I wake up, I'd be like, ew, why are you trying to kiss me, pervert?
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I'd throw a Wii mode at your temple and hope you die.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: You shouldn't joke about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a cute puppy.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm sure pretty soon there will be video of these Wii accidents as if there aren't enough already of people destroying their TVs and stuff showing up on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the ironic thing now is it'll be much easier to watch someone break their Wii on a Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DogKillByWeRemote
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, but the dog actually lived.
[SPEAKER_06]: The dog lived.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was only dead for five minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which makes him a zombie!
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, he was dead for five minutes?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought you could start getting brain damage after three or four minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if it's a border collie, it's like a miniature collie I don't know, because border collies are a little bit bigger
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, there's some other interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: A little bit more positive, I guess, for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a new patent that shows Nintendo is possibly working on a motion-sensing DS card.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perhaps something that was similar to what they had for the Game Boy Advance, for different games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think one of the WarioWare games had it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's a DS direction-sensing card.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: No word on what it's going to be used for, but it's something that has built-in direction and motion tracking.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I can get my iPhone's games ported to my DS?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that's what I see happening when this comes out, is that now we'll just get ports of iPhone games on the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: With that whole little tilty thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can get Silent Hill The Escape on my DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wouldn't that be fabulous?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's exactly what you wanted.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't they do... No, they didn't do a Silent Hill game on the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did a Resident Evil game on the DS, and that was not very good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was there like a play novel or something that was on the... That's it, but a motion sensing card.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, those DS cards are not exactly that big, so that's pretty impressive.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would think that they would just do... Well, the actual chips that do the motion sensing are really super tiny, so it could be done.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just... I don't know, in...
[SPEAKER_06]: Really, I mean, you can have those things kind of hang out of the slot a little bit, you know, because remember with like the WarioWare one that they had, it was pretty big.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I guess technology was a little bit older then, but, you know, the card itself was huge compared to what normal Game Boy Advance, you know, cards look like.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like this comment in chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sai says this in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why not have that in the DSi?
[SPEAKER_07]: A new system is just out and already an add-on that should be built in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, exactly, just like the Wii Motion Plus Something that should have been done in the first place Because Nintendo really cares about its customer base Damn it, we're not getting into that argument
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, alright, I guess we'll see what comes of this or what possible game they could be making with this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to suck, whatever it is, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be like Wii Sports for the DS or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you imagine that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wii bowling, people throwing their DSes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh no, I broke my DS light.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guess I gotta go buy a new DSi.
[SPEAKER_06]: I see conspiracy here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy Legend 2 is being remade for the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, is that the Game Boy one?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, the one that's not really like Final Fantasy, the one that's more like part of the Saga series?
[SPEAKER_07]: You got it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was actually Saga 2, Hiho Densetsu, and that was Final Fantasy Legend here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love when you pronounce Japanese shut up but yeah it's getting the full 3D little views and things kind of like Final Fantasy 4 and the Dragon Quest games have had so that's being released here awesome I actually think I still have Final Fantasy Legend 2 or 3 on my old Game Boy cartridge yeah and in this Japanese magazine they are definitely selling it as Saga too so awesome I liked the Saga series I'm like the only person in the world maybe they'll call it Saga when it comes out over here instead of Final Fantasy
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe, because it would be very weird to have Final Fantasy Legend 2 come out over here, you know, and it would be kind of like, well, whatever happened to the first two?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because who remembers that far back of the Game Boy, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's just hope that they never do a Mystic Quest remake.
[SPEAKER_07]: I somehow don't see that happening.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mystic Quest wasn't terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it wasn't good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I'll just leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It wasn't terrible.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yes...
[SPEAKER_06]: It figures that the homebrew community of course is doing something that Nintendo isn't doing on their own.
[SPEAKER_06]: A new device has come out, Matrix Wii Z. It's being prototyped right now, but it basically is sort of a mod chip that plugs into your...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: and so I can put... So, well, they say that you can put ISOs on there and stuff like that and actually run pirated games from it, but you can... Oh, we wouldn't want to encourage people to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can also... The system itself will look at it like it's part of the actual storage on the device, so you can use it for storing games.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this, yeah, you can actually store ISOs and stuff, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob just tried to rape me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you were falling asleep, so I went over there to give you a lap dance.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I was getting a cookie.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm frightened.
[SPEAKER_07]: All I hear is blah, blah, blah, wee, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You shoved your dong in her face, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I not shoved my dong in her face.
[SPEAKER_02]: You were like, how many licks does it take?
[SPEAKER_02]: And you were like, waving your dong in her face.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I waved a snickerdoodle in her face.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's what they call it, your snickerdoodle.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's why you thrusted your nutsack in my face.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, oh my goodness.
[SPEAKER_06]: You make it sound like I'm not wearing pants or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, it's basically this device will allow super fast loading of ISOs in homebrew.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, I was just hearing blah, blah, blah, Wii, blah, blah, blah, system that doesn't have any games out on it I care about, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're doing, you know, the new play control.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, that's a title that they stuck with.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, for instead of play on the Wii, you know, new play control.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario, was it Mario Power Tennis and then new play control Pikmin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aren't you excited about those?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, those games are totally new and not ever been out on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, wait, no, they have.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Irene, care to comment?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything?
[SPEAKER_07]: What Wii games are you looking forward to, Irene?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm dying to know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, things and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's probably actually a Wii game that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Things and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Things and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: When it's a collection of mini games.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Things and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds like a dream game to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: You too?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that coming out on the Wii in April?
[SPEAKER_02]: On April 4th.
[SPEAKER_07]: 5 million consoles sold by Nintendo in December.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although that's a little bit, it's actually not Wii's alone.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was actually the DS sold 3 million and the Wii sold 2 million.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you put it together, they sold 5 million systems that Nintendo moved.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a lot of dead collies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Matt!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to wipe out the Kali species off this planet.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are terrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lassie will be just a memory.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, she is, but she's dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Timmy will be stuck in the well forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where's Jamie here to yell at you?
[SPEAKER_07]: But look, the reason why this is newsworthy is December.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, Christmas.
[SPEAKER_07]: So these are the numbers that were going into the Christmas and what ended up under people's trees.
[SPEAKER_07]: 3 million DS's 2 million Wii's 1.5 million Xbox 360's 1 million PSP's 3 quarters of a million PS3's big surprise and not even half a million PS2's but still going in there it's kind of an old system so that's actually pretty good DarkTetsuya says OLR is going to get an angry email from PETA I hope we do because Jamie would have to read it
[SPEAKER_07]: and Jamie is very opinionated when it comes to PETA.
[SPEAKER_07]: I welcome them to write the email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please, by all means.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, I totally encourage people going out and murdering animals with Wii remotes and controllers.
[SPEAKER_06]: And why stop at the Wii?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, hell, look at the original Xbox controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: That thing is like a blunt object of death.
[SPEAKER_02]: Try dropping an original Xbox on a dog.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, they'd never survive.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can take out like three dogs with that thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Am I really here right now?
[SPEAKER_07]: If we get sued, I don't want any part of this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm distancing myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you ever see that Mythbusters where they were...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I like to chop a frozen turkey on Miley Cyrus I don't know about anybody else out there
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, perfect.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, so this week we've got a few things coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's January.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty slow still.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's some good stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Star Ocean 2nd Evolution for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be a pretty good game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of these Square Enix PSP games are doing very well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jumble Madness for the DS Big Bang Mini for the DS
[SPEAKER_06]: Something that needs to die in a fire.
[SPEAKER_06]: Imagine Fashion Party.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, no thanks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: These are the games I'm going to get for Victoria because she'd love this type of game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Imagine Fashion Party.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, look.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: This bitch right here.
[SPEAKER_07]: We were walking through Walmart and we got to the section with the top model clothes and she was like, oh, top model.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got a top model tank top for Christmas, so bite me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you imagine the possibilities with that game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say also the Ultimate Shooting Collection on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's three Japanese arcade shooter games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to remember what was in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was Coriolis, Radio Allergy, and I don't remember the last one that was in there, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: Really, like, bullet hell shooter games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wonder World Amusement Park for the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: A bunch of mini-games on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: R-Tonalico 2, The Melody of Melifacisha, I guess?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Was that a Disney villain?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I totally butchered that.
[SPEAKER_06]: The melody of Metafalacia, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Falatio?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm totally good too, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: With some extra crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's on the PS2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: The subtitle to that, none of which I just said.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: Skate 2 is coming out on PS3 and 360 this week as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: and let's see here.
[SPEAKER_06]: To tie in perfectly what we were talking about just before I started talking about release dates, Sim Animals, another sim game where you get to control the wonders of nature.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, they actually have this hand, which is the pointer, and you can poke badgers and stuff and they will attack your hand.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Badger, badger, badger, badger, badger, badger, badger, badger, mushroom, mushroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it football or mushroom?
[SPEAKER_07]: Mushroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's Mushroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that'll be out on the Wii and the DS, so awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you simulate, you know, dropping stuff on your animals?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can throw animals.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw them shaking a squirrel violently, so I'm sure you can throw rocks at them.
[SPEAKER_06]: or maybe feed them to other things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you done with US release dates?
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to take the bear in that game and just feed it all sorts of animals and it'll become rabid and just eat things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very rare bear.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying my hardest, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: It just never works.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on to the UK and the release dates over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do it in a British accent, British accent.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you want me to do it in British accent?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do, yes, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I really annoy everybody overseas when I talk like this.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a really bad British accent, I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a really bad one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you want to read these in a British accent, Victoria?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I don't want to read them in British accent.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you should.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, do you want me to get you some tea and some crumpets to put you in the mood?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't like tea and crumpets.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, knock it off.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're going to talk in an accent, talk like you're from New York, alright?
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't be such a wanker.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're a wanker.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the 20th... I'm going to get so much hate mail this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the 23rd... British.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the 23rd... Football Manager Live is coming to the PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: and Neopets Puzzle Adventures coming out as well on the DS and the PSC and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know who's playing Neopets, but somebody is for sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Skate 2 comes out for the PlayStation 3 and the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not doing a Japanese accent for the Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Left 4 Dead comes out, the Japanese version, on January 22nd on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, that's very good.
[SPEAKER_07]: The PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, she can do that because she's actually Asian.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do it and I'm a racist.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you are.
[SPEAKER_07]: PlayStation 3, Prince of Persia, WWE SmackDown vs. Raw, and Juice 2 all getting releases in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_07]: And on the Nintendo Wii, Rayman, Raving Rabbids, TV Party, like anyone cares, Fragile, Sayonara, Tsuki no Haikyuu, Suzumiya, Harui no Gekidu comes out as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to read them?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: You think you can do better?
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think anybody could do better.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: PlayStation 2, some price reductions for Destroy All Humans and Juice 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the Nintendo DS, Monster Racer comes out as well as Rayman.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: When you said that, you said destroy all humans and Jews too, but I thought you said Jews too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sounded like destroy all humans and Jews too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, but they're humans too.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I don't even think that would be acceptable in Japan, let alone here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know they get away with some pretty crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's mine and Irene's fault It's awful
[SPEAKER_07]: On the Nintendo DS, Monster Racer, Rayman Raving Rabbids, TV Party, Teguato DS Series 1, Tetsudo Datafile.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, what the hell that is.
[SPEAKER_07]: But a game called Zubo is coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bet that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Zubo?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's a music game that's from EA.
[SPEAKER_06]: They look like crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: And on the Sony PSP, we have Patapon 2 comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least the Chinese version comes out in other Asian territories.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ratchet & Clank gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_07]: Looks like the only new game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hokuto no Ken Rao Gaiden Ten no Hawa comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what it's called.
[SPEAKER_02]: Totally.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a fighting game coming out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Guitar Hero World Tour Travis Barker Track Pack
[SPEAKER_06]: and featured in there will be What's My Age Again by Blink-182 Low, the Travis Barker remix by Flo Rida featuring T-Pain and it looks like Lycanthrope by Plus44 and that'll be available for 160 Microsoft points per track and
[SPEAKER_06]: or $440 for the entire bundle.
[SPEAKER_06]: And no word on what the real money is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think $160 is $2 per.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rock Band, Steve Miller, Space Cowboy, Take the Money and Run, and The Joker.
[SPEAKER_06]: All of those will be available for 160 Microsoft Points each or $2.
[SPEAKER_06]: The pack will run you 440 Microsoft Points or $5.49.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the individual songs, you'll be getting I Stand Alone by Godsmack, Feed the Tree by Belly, Wind Me Up by Ghost Hounds, Typical by Mute Math, and Warzone by Rob Zombie.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if I remember correctly, I think Warzone says new single.
[SPEAKER_06]: And all those will be available for... Where's Dragula?
[SPEAKER_07]: That song's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I want to play that on Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's back in the 90s, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up, I hate you.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's where it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Warzone wasn't that good from what I remember I actually bought that so it was okay not worth the single though it's a shame finally Lips the karaoke game has some stuff coming out for the rest of this month available actually came out earlier this week when I Grow Up by the Pussycat Dolls
[SPEAKER_06]: you've lost that love and feeling by the Righteous Brothers and Erased Rewind by the Carnigans those all came out on the 16th I love that song next week we've got let's see on the 23rd here Hate That I Love You by Rihanna featuring Neo and Thanks For The Memories by Fall Out Boy
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, they're so hip that they don't use vowels in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: We need to have Victoria just sing these songs as Loki reads them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm doing it anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then finally, Look What You've Done by Jet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look What You've Done.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I don't think that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, and then finally on January 30th, Sunday Morning by Maroon 5.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know that song.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take a Bow by Rihanna and Water Runs Dry by Boyz II Men.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, what is up with these random old songs like Belly Feed the Tree?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, oh man, I was so glad that made a comeback.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then like Boyz II Men, one of their songs that was not even all that popular.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some comments from chat I gotta read.
[SPEAKER_07]: Redertainment says, why pay for tracks from Lips when I can steal them from BitTorrent sites, plug in my iPod, and play them for free?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's not quite the same, and I think these actually come with the videos and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And...
[SPEAKER_07]: Leo Shen says, where the fuck is my Love Fool and my favorite game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Love Fool is in SingStar, for whatever it's worth, and it has the original video, not the one they did in the US.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like the old school one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like it, Race and Rewind.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a good song.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like my favorite game too, but I don't know what a good karaoke song that would be.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's more of a, that other series, the racing series had that in one of their ads.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gran Turismo?
[SPEAKER_02]: Gran Turismo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Two.
[SPEAKER_07]: My favorite game was like in the commercial.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it was a song in the game, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: My favorite game was also, I think, one of the Euro DDR games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, I could be completely wrong on that, but that's a guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of awesome music games, this news has me very, very happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Harmonix CEO, Alex Rigopoulos, was interviewed with Ars Technica recently, and he has basically professed his love for Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_07]: You might remember that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Harmonix, these are the games they did before Guitar Hero, Amplitude and Frequency.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, he was basically confirming that he does want to eventually revive the series.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_07]: Excited!
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except the only problem is, Sony actually owns that property.
[SPEAKER_07]: Harmonix developed it, I guess, for Sony.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you ain't gonna see this on Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would probably be like a PlayStation Network type game.
[SPEAKER_07]: But hell, I don't mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would love to see this game make a comeback because, you know, there's certain songs...
[SPEAKER_07]: That you can only get in these types of games.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're not going to get in a rock band type game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I am definitely for this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope they do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They really need to revive some of those older rhythm games from the 90s and early 2000s.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like Guitar Freaks, and then they'll make a game called Rock-O.
[SPEAKER_07]: GS68 says, didn't Harmonix also do Karaoke Revolution with Konami?
[SPEAKER_07]: They did.
[SPEAKER_07]: They developed the first couple versions.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then by the time I think they got to Karaoke Country, I think finally Harmonix split off and Konami did it themselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, we're not doing Country.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something like that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's exactly how it went down.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so we're going to get into the classic video game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a little part of the show where we like to pay homage to a game from yesteryear, a game from the past.
[SPEAKER_07]: And DarkSakura is not here tonight to do this, so this is the part where Loki and I will fill in.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Loki, I guess we're going to do your game tonight, because I did it last time.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Loki is going to pick a game for us this week, a classic video game that he thinks...
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody out there on the internet who listens to our show should be playing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, what is the classic video game of the week this week?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But actually, I just came up with one last minute.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray for me!
[SPEAKER_06]: No, actually, I want to pay homage to... It's not even that old.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I hate thinking that a PlayStation 1 game is considered retro now.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think one of the greatest in this game series, except for maybe...
[SPEAKER_06]: Twisted Metal Black, but Twisted Metal 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Twisted Metal 2, as it was known in Europe, as Twisted Metal 2 World Tour.
[SPEAKER_06]: The second game in the Vehicle Combat series, Twisted Metal, still one of my favorite games, and they've remade it a few different times.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the PSP, they had Twisted Metal 2 head-on, or Twisted Metal head-on, I guess it was called.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, basically this game, very over-the-top, just, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Paris, you can actually destroy the Eiffel Tower.
[SPEAKER_06]: LA, they had some ruins left over, I guess, from the previous Twisted Mel game.
[SPEAKER_06]: In, let's see here, New York, they had the rooftops, which I think was my favorite map of the entire game there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Antarctica, Glaciers, Icebergs, Hong Kong Crunch
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, there was some different characters that were added in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had Sweet Tooth, Dark Tooth, and Minion, which could be unlocked with different codes in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess Dark Tooth was only playable on the PC version, or if you had a cheat device for the PlayStation 1, you could play Dark Tooth that way, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: and he was a giant ice cream truck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, with a clown on top, because he was Sweet Tooth's father, if I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Victoria actually played this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I heard her speak up, going, I remember this game!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, because Darktooth was Charlie Kane, and then of course Sweettooth was Needles Kane, and he had the ice cream truck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of the other characters, Axel, which was a guy that was trapped in a vehicle, I guess, by his father with two giant tires, and so he was playing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then Grasshopper, which was a dune buggy, which apparently was Calypso's daughter, and Calypso, of course, was the guy that was running the entire tournament.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Mr. Grim, which is on a red motorcycle, and he consumes souls.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's kind of...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, I think that for Twisted Metal 2, they had some levels that they cut out that they brought back for Twisted Metal head-on.
[SPEAKER_06]: The PS2 version, they brought some that they had cancelled, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they were making, I don't know, more levels for Twisted Metal Black that were added into that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was kind of a remake of Twisted Metal 2 and the Twisted Metal Black engine, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, unfortunately, we still haven't seen another Twisted Metal game since Black.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't really count the PSP ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hey, you know, they were talking about remaking, and these are making a new one for PS3, and I think they should do it, because it was probably one of the best series that was on the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's my classic game there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Twisted Metal 2, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a good pick.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's old enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was pretty good for a last minute one, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it was good.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura's done Dreamcast games, and that was later in PS1.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you can tell that I totally remember all the backstory on this, because I totally butchered everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was the last minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: You did good.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's going to do it for Part A of Orange Launch Radio, but that doesn't mean the show's over.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're just going to take a break, and we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's plenty more where this came from.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your calls as well we'll get to a little later on in the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have some more news in the next segment.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to be talking about...
[SPEAKER_07]: Some updates with the Pandora battery, the controversial device for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also talk about some other PSP news.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: As well as a very controversial Nintendo patent that was discovered this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was something I kind of referred to earlier to try and...
[SPEAKER_07]: and help those people that are really bad at video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: But is it a good thing or is it going to be a bad thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, with all the talk about Silent Hill this week, for the live listeners, I'm going to play some music from Silent Hill Games because who doesn't love the Silent Hill music?
[SPEAKER_07]: But for those of you listening to the podcast, you don't get that because we're not allowed to play copyright music.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we'll be right back in just a few seconds for you guys on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: For those of you listening live, we'll be back in a few minutes here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we're back with more of Orange Lounge Radio on this Part B of our podcast, taping live here on January the 18th of 2009.
[SPEAKER_07]: To those of you guys who are just tuning in live on allgames.com, thank you guys for tuning in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tonight's kind of a weird night.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura is not here.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's on vacation just before school starts.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we brought in two girls to replace her.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: So anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: But no more flirting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Back to business.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're back to work here on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got more gaming news to talk about.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Loki, why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you starting us off?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: All righty then.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guitar Hero Metallica has been announced by Metallica that it is coming out in the U.S., or North America, I guess, March 29th.
[SPEAKER_06]: May, pretty much everywhere else.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's interesting, though, is the Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 versions are coming out on the 29th, but the PS2 and the Wii version, though, are coming sometime this spring, most likely early May.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is according to the band's website.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, it's going to have Expert Plus, 28 songs from the group's discography, as well as other tracks from Alice in Chains, The Food Fires, Slayer, Machine Head, Queen.
[SPEAKER_06]: and stuff like that what's interesting though this is a little bit late news here but they're going to have a special pre-order bonus actually being done through GameStop which is surprising they're going to be giving away with Guitar Hero Metallica another drum pedal because apparently you're going to need to have two pedals for the kick drum to be able to play some of those songs or you're probably going to want to have two kick pedals
[SPEAKER_06]: First of many.
[SPEAKER_06]: How long before the series jumps the shark?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: Done!
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Sony is going to be delivering, of course, more PSP and PlayStation 1 old titles on PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_07]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: There is a PSP game that just came out, I believe, this week on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Ultimate Ghosts and Goblins.
[SPEAKER_07]: I believe Jamie spoke very highly of this game when she was here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of a put-together compilation of some of the old Ghosts and Goblins titles.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's now available for download for $20.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't play it on the PlayStation 3 because it was a PSP game, but you can use your little transfer device and put it on your PSP if you have a large storage stick for your PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you have a large stick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Light Blue Tool, which is their service mode battery that they've made, is just basically a fancy name for the Pandora battery.
[SPEAKER_06]: They basically stole the idea for it and decided they were going to put it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, due to legal action by Sony Computer Entertainment Europe, they are not able to put out said battery.
[SPEAKER_06]: And...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they will not be releasing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's okay, because if you remember that there is an exploit now that's being used that will eventually allow the PSP-3000 to be hacked using GripShift.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that is coming along nicely.
[SPEAKER_06]: They already have some homebrew games available for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And soon enough, a homebrew and firmware loader.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you think will happen as a result of the lawsuit?
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not too difficult if you just follow the instructions, but the fact that they were kind of making this and claiming it as their own is kind of a rip-off because they did not come up with this idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dothack Games
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, I think they had two different series.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had the .hack series and there was .hack.gu, which was the later series.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now .hack.link was announced by Famitsu Magazine as coming to the PSP in 2009.
[SPEAKER_07]: So now it's going from PlayStation 2 to PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: The interesting thing, though, they're saying is that, you know, part of what made .hack kind of interesting is that it was sort of like an MMO, but it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a single-player experience that was like an MMO, if that makes any sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, you know, all the characters...
[SPEAKER_07]: DotHack is making a comeback.
[SPEAKER_07]: on the PSP
[SPEAKER_06]: and some of the stuff that they were suggesting here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Possible features include smaller yet retain most of the current PSP screen size, offered social networking functionality in the cross-media bar, included a keyboard for easier internet browsing and communication,
[SPEAKER_06]: Offered Bluetooth wireless support for easy pairing with other devices, had a touchscreen, had an improved screen for more dynamic graphic displays, offered the ability to find others near you who want to connect for online gaming, offered an e-comic book or book download service through the PlayStation Network, and included a hard drive for memory storage.
[SPEAKER_06]: and some other things.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were also talking about a built-in GPS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a feeling that they're going to do a touchscreen at the next one.
[SPEAKER_06]: They kind of have to at this point, if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Motion Censoring.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know though if they would just put a touch screen on a new PSP or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of these, I mean, other than like social networking, that wouldn't be too bad, or like a book download service.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you can do e-books right now through Homebrew stuff, so that could be done now.
[SPEAKER_06]: and even the ability to find others near you that want to connect for an online game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really see that as kind of a necessity because that would require a lot of hotspots and stuff like that and it wouldn't really make sense that you would need to know if there's someone nearby to connect with because you're connecting with anybody over the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it doesn't really matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe Bluetooth support for like...
[SPEAKER_06]: Using, like, say, your 6-axis controller might be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's read some comments from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chat.orange.trader.com We've had a lot of PSP different stories.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to kind of read through some of these because lots of diverse comments from our chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Redertainment says, Why is Datel getting sued for selling something that you can hack the PSP with?
[SPEAKER_07]: People who sell rocks don't get sued for possibly causing car break-ins.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this is the case with a lot of these companies that get sued, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it has to do with infringing on some sort of stuff, probably information that was written on the ROM of the battery.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the actual batteries that Sony uses actually have data written onto them.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if, for example, they use that to reverse engineer something to create a program, that would violate copyrights and then they could stop them, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also probably, you know, Datel's not really a large company, and Sony is a lot bigger, and they could probably bully them into doing whatever they want.
[SPEAKER_06]: But more likely the prior, that they actually reverse-engineered something, and because of that, you know, it's not licensed, so they've got to put a stop to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, some other things I want to read here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Giovedea, who's very excited about a new .hack game coming out, says, I wish those fuckers would have brought the actual .hack MMO over, even if it sucked balls.
[SPEAKER_07]: And X-Link confirms there was a .hack MMO in Japan, but it was shut down.
[SPEAKER_07]: D5T says .hack Link for the PSP is going to be the last game, FYI.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I don't know if it's going to... I guess not a series, because all the other .hack games were in series.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the first one had four games, the other one had three.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of weird that this would be a one-off game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully it's a lot of game, because .hack got a big... I guess a very cult-type game.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a lot of people who've never heard of these games, but then I think there's enough of our audience who like the anime and all that stuff, too, that I'm sure know about these games and are pretty excited about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, Monster Hunter, they're trying to basically recreate Monster Hunter over, you know, find anything that would work as a Monster Hunter game, because...
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are insanely popular in Japan right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially the new Monster Hunter game coming out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to probably take off really well.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're trying to find more stuff that's kind of similar to Monster Hunter.
[SPEAKER_06]: They try to make their game more like Monster Hunter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then maybe they'll try to get that same type of appeal that that game had.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was some other game that they were trying to make like Monster Hunter 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some other series game that they're changing up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting speculation in chat, too, by Alpha Cananagram says, maybe .hack//Link has DLC.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: It was apparently a very popular after school hangout.
[SPEAKER_07]: It had games, snacks, cards, clothing of all things.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it was kind of like a little hodgepodge of cool stuff, sounds like, a place for kids to go hang out.
[SPEAKER_07]: The proprietors were Bob and Gina Pearson.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently a $250 annual tax per machine on these games, they had to get rid of the 10 games that they had.
[SPEAKER_07]: Glow in the Dark Air Hockey, NASCAR Racing, Ms.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pac-Man all bit the dust because of this new tax in the town.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's a quote from one of the owners.
[SPEAKER_07]: We didn't renew the licenses because the machines didn't even make what you charge in these astronomical fees.
[SPEAKER_07]: The game companies tell us this is one of the highest fees in Illinois.
[SPEAKER_07]: We wonder if the village really researched how big this should be or if they just slapped a number on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We had become a pretty big hangout for kids after school and weekends but not having the video games this year has made a big impact in just the first two weeks.
[SPEAKER_07]: So apparently somebody who works for the town told the local news that they set the fee high with the understanding that the game machine distribution companies would actually pay the fees.
[SPEAKER_07]: But one of the proprietors said that only happens when you actually serve alcohol in the establishment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, so what was the purpose of this tax or whatever it was supposed to be?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to get money.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess, why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like the most random thing ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and by the way...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Let alone, you know, enough... I don't know of many at all that wouldn't be independently owned.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe at that pool place I've never been to up the street.
[SPEAKER_02]: They probably have some.
[SPEAKER_02]: But see, that's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's random and arbitrary.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, why... Oh, yeah, and all of a sudden, let's just pull this out of our ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: There has to be something behind it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it sounds like...
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: you're paying taxes on your revenue that you bring in so why tax it again there has to be something behind it there has to be maybe it was like targeted at that place or something are the places like this where kids like hang out maybe they think they're gonna become like delinquent or something if they spend their time doing that instead of like other stuff
[SPEAKER_07]: TigerClaw says, if you read between the lines, there was this way of getting rid of video games in these places so kids go home and do their homework.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, TigerClaw.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of disagree.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think some of these kids, if they don't have another place to go, they're going to turn to graffiti and murder.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: But more of the latter.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you know what I'm talking about?
[SPEAKER_02]: At least in these types of places, it's... Yeah, that's exactly what these establishments are there for.
[SPEAKER_02]: If parents aren't enforcing their kids to do their homework and stuff, they're going and at least playing video games or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not out on the street or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I just think that's kind of...
[SPEAKER_07]: In other words, kids hanging out at this place is because their parents aren't making them go home and do their homework.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if they're not here at this place hanging out, they'll be somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they're not going to be going home.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not going to go home.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, shucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: No more Ms.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pac-Man for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess I'll go do homework.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good golly, because that's what my brothers and I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our parents didn't give a shit if we came home and did our homework after school, so we went to the arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: We probably would have become druggies and murderous convicts were it not for video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just kind of wacky.
[SPEAKER_07]: SSJ100Matt says, so things are going to turn into Jet Set Radio, basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all going to start in Hampshire.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're all going to strap on rollerblades and go around and spray paint shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, kind of...
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe we should try to email these people and get them on the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: These are the types of stories I want to dig into.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you going to be like Call Rob or whatever, not the local show?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like the local news and stuff?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: All the other shows, they're trying to get the one-up guys and all that on their show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm over all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get these little niche stories and get them on the show and talk about why was your town out to screw you?
[SPEAKER_10]: We want answers.
[SPEAKER_10]: We demand to know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Asking questions, getting answers.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're never going to leave you with answers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to make an impact.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, do you have some other news for us?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe happier news?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe this is why they're getting rid of the arcades for games like Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Mortal Kombat killer has gotten 36 years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lamar Roberts, the teenager convicted of beating to death a 7-year-old, will be sentenced to 36 years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, this happened in 2007,
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess...
[SPEAKER_06]: They beat up Zoe Garcia, a 7-year-old who was described by prosecutors and law enforcement in Greeley, Colorado.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were beating her up as a reenactment of the fight moves from Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it says Robert and his 17-year-old girlfriend were supposedly supposed to be babysitting the child.
[SPEAKER_06]: They uppercutted a baby?
[SPEAKER_06]: And said the two kicked, hit, and slammed his half-sister to the floor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did they confuse their babality with a fatality?
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't even joke.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, that is awful, and I probably shouldn't have said that, but wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: They must be stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, only 36 years?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just 36 years?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_07]: Are prisons that hard up for cash?
[SPEAKER_02]: XBOX TACO ASSAILANTS
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, apparently law enforcement near Orlando, Florida... This is one of the stories that I've read so far, so it's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have in custody a 19-year-old who refused to stop playing games to join his family for dinner and threw a taco at his mother after she unplugged his Xbox.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, this was reported as a domestic disturbance and is...
[SPEAKER_06]: And apparently there is some name calling that says, seems his mom went upstairs and demanded he stop playing that Sega or Atari or whatever you call it and come down to be a contributing member of the family.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he was all, whatever, bitch, she said.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he flung the tacos.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is this for real?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, he says they actually have a screen capture from the news thing and he's making a weird little face on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: WFLTV is the news station covering it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she says she was going to let him sit in his jail cell for a few days and teach him a lesson.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need to show no mercy to this kid.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what they should do as punishment is make him work at Taco Bell and see what exactly it takes to get in to make a taco because I don't know anybody who's ever worked at Taco Bell that really enjoyed their job.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the quote from Dina.
[SPEAKER_06]: A few minutes later, Dina says she was in the kitchen cleaning and cooking tacos for dinner when Zachary showed up.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's when she says he slapped her arm and threw a taco in her face.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said no fucking tomatoes!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's taco side!
[SPEAKER_06]: No one commits taco side!
[SPEAKER_06]: I can imagine Eric right now like, nooooo!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, and finally, this is a little bit more recent.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a 17-year-old Daniel Petrick of Ohio.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's been found guilty of shooting both of his parents, which led to the death of his mother.
[SPEAKER_06]: His dad survived.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, he has been found guilty.
[SPEAKER_06]: This was because they took away Halo from him, Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's a 15-year-old, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: And...
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a surprise for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Close your eyes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he shot them both in the face.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: With a taco.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is so bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to say this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know this is like a horrible story.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to go back to the taco thing because this is one we could actually laugh at, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: The other ones are terrible, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: But comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: D5T says, if I went to jail every time I threw food at my mom.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm thinking, my mom and I did get into a fight over M&M's once when I was younger.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: You didn't throw them, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: You broke the bag.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't throw them, but it was a different story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Deekman says, I see nothing wrong with tacos getting thrown in my face.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, if you open... It could be like a game if you open your mouth trying to catch them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, but here is the huge, huge news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and then here's the best part about the Halo murder thing apparently the judge James Burge told the courtroom it's my firm belief as a human being and not just as a jurist that Daniel does suffer from a serious defect of the mind and apparently believes
[SPEAKER_06]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: He believes that games are somehow involved.
[SPEAKER_06]: He says, I firmly believe Daniel had no idea at the time he hatched this plot that if he killed his parents, they would be dead forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: That he was so far into the Halo 3 world that he separated himself from reality.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would he be like that Kali from earlier?
[SPEAKER_06]: So would they like respawn?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like parents respawn?
[SPEAKER_09]: It would be like that Kali from earlier.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know?
[SPEAKER_09]: It died and came back to life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mom?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, this is... There's a special place in hell where this show is waiting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know who's stupider, that kid or that juror.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's a judge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, disbarred.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's pretty ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I'm sure that kid's stupid, but I don't know if he's that stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I think he knew exactly what he was doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But now he figured out, I gotta go to jail forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm insane!
[SPEAKER_06]: Please don't kill me.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the face.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the face.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even know what to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: This isn't even really a story about video games at this point.
[SPEAKER_07]: This kid obviously has a ton of issues.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can we just talk about the Taco Kid some more?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, the Taco Kid's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I just wanted to point out that, you know, here live in studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, my titty.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm now the snickerdoodle assailant.
Open your mouth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_02]: You messed with my cookie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pick it up and eat it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been on my boobie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll eat your cookie.
[SPEAKER_07]: I threw a snickerdoodle and it hit Irene in the boob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, eat my cookie, Victoria.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was going to hurt, too, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make it flat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's deliciously painful.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, look, we're going to dedicate a certain segment of our show we do here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Love you.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to dedicate a certain part of our show here we do every week to these guys who are ruining the image of video gamers everywhere with their stupidity, and it's a segment called the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Since we don't have DarkSakura tonight to start us off, we'll let Loki start us off with the FUs of the week today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck you, Rockstar Games, for making a really crappy port of Grand Theft Auto 4 on the PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no reason whatsoever that the game should work for a while, then all of a sudden just stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't install anything, I didn't change anything, it just said, I'm not working no more.
[SPEAKER_06]: And just stopped working, now I reinstall it, I've uninstalled everything, including secure ROM,
[SPEAKER_06]: all my video drivers every little bit of crap that would possibly affect this game I've uninstalled it, reinstalled it, nothing it's just broken this is bullshit, why should I pay for an actual game and have it not work that's it, never doing it again I am never buying a PC game ever again especially Rockstar Games never again don't do it my FU of the week, if you're done
[SPEAKER_07]: My few of the week goes to my tooth, because it hurts.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I have to go to the dentist tomorrow, and I just... I don't like going to the dentist.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I've mentioned this on the show before.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like going to a used car salesman, because then they're going to tell me, oh, you need to have this done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and by the way, you need to get this done.
[SPEAKER_07]: You need to replace this crown.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to cost this much money.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's like...
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought you had an awesome dentist, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do that crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, you want to hear something funny?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm horrible when it comes to oral hygiene.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, they tell me to floss.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, yeah, I'll floss, and I totally forget.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, okay, so, yeah, nobody flosses.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, anyways, they keep telling me, yeah, you gotta floss because your gums are all, you know, they're gonna get fucked up and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I haven't flossed for years since I saw them last, and they said that it looked better.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, yeah, sure, I've been flossing all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well, it looks like it's doing a good job.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yes, they're full of shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's basically it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've seen more unicorns than people flossing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, nobody flosses.
[SPEAKER_07]: SSJ100Matt wants to point out that his dad's a dentist, but he's not a dentist.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look, if I lived in New York City, I would happily go to your dad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I need a friend who's a dentist.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a friend who's a dentist.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, he started his own practice.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to go see them because I want to go see somebody I trust.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you could go to a dental school.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least they're honest.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what poor people do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least we ain't paying for every shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've all been there, Victoria.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've all been there, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: You're a young 21 still.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're in that phase.
[SPEAKER_10]: A young, beautiful, single 21-year-old gal.
[SPEAKER_07]: With big titties.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quit trying to pimp me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to say there is somebody in chat right now with the nickname that says, I love Victoria.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aww, I hurt you too, whoever you are.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so my FU of the week goes to my tooth.
[SPEAKER_07]: Victoria, do you have any FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_09]: My FU of the week is to the person who didn't turn my keys in.
[SPEAKER_09]: whoever found my keys at work and didn't turn them in because I've been locked out of my apartment for the past three fucking days not really, that's the biggest FU of the week that I have and to my phone that's flashing an evil red color at me because it needs to be charged that's it and RicePrincess, do you have any FUs?
[SPEAKER_07]: yeah, FU to you for hitting my titty you wasted a snickerdoodle you liked it a little bit I'll give it to John when he gets back I'll put it on a plate and say we saved you a snickerdoodle
[SPEAKER_02]: Just, you know, brush off the little bit of dust.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I'll do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, if he ever finds out it touched my boob, he'll die.
[SPEAKER_02]: He'll be like, oh my god, I had a woman's breast in my mouth.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to put it back on the plate when no one's looking.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then it's like a game of Russian snickerdoodle roulette.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of these was on Irene's boobie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you want to eat one and take a chance?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or do you want to possibly inadvertently lick her boob?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's not talk about licking my boob.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, that's going to do it for the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_07]: On that note...
[SPEAKER_07]: So, let's get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is actually some big news that came out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: A patent that was revealed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, this is what I was kind of talking to Victoria a little bit about before.
[SPEAKER_07]: She was talking about how video games get too hard and she gets too frustrated and throws a controller, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's what's interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, Miyamoto has filed a patent.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I don't know if it's him or his company or whatever, but basically Nintendo has filed a patent and it has been discovered for a computable, readable storage medium.
[SPEAKER_07]: But...
[SPEAKER_07]: What the medium is, is basically kind of a hint system.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the game that they kind of show pictures of is a work in progress called Legend of OO, which could possibly be a Legend of Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's the interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: This patent is very, very, very wordy, kind of goes on.
[SPEAKER_07]: It talks about these different gameplay features that include...
[SPEAKER_07]: Hint videos that are actually already there inside the game that would unlock if you've been stuck on a puzzle for so long, then a hint video will show up.
[SPEAKER_07]: A mode called the Digest, which will actually just show the game's cinematics and gameplay sequences just as a movie, and you can take control at any point you want.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then a Scene menu, which lets you choose exactly where you want to go into the story.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's kind of like this extreme hybrid of mixing a video game with DVD features, almost.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then you just add on to this the fact that Miyamoto has said before that he wants to make Zelda Wii titles more accessible to a broad audience.
[SPEAKER_07]: Could this actually be something that they are going to implement in a future Zelda title?
[SPEAKER_02]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_07]: But what do you think of that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, is that dumbing down the game too much?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that taking the game out of the video game?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's kind of... For us, the hardcore gamers, the gamers who've been playing games all of our life, we're probably not going to be big fans of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, it's going to bring new people into games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: So let me ask Victoria, even though she's typing away on the laptop at somebody else right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: What if they had a game, like one of these games you get really frustrated at, but you can just say you throw the controller because it's too hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: What if suddenly the game said, hey, it looks like you're stuck.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me show you a video of how to get past this part.
[SPEAKER_07]: Would that make the game more appealing to you?
[SPEAKER_09]: It would probably help, but I'd probably get annoyed because I wouldn't be able to be like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_09]: How do I get up there?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's usually my problem with games is I have to get up somewhere and, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: What if the game said, press this button and I'll take you past this point?
[SPEAKER_09]: Then I'll play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then I'll be like, all right, bring it, bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: What would draw you to that, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: What would draw you to play the game if there's no challenge?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just read something funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: What was the question?
[SPEAKER_07]: What would draw, if you could just hit the button and skip that part to get up the ledge or get to where you need to go, you know, fast forward or whatever, what's the draw to the game to you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, then I just, I think it'd make it easier for me to play it because I'm not very video game savvy as I've, you know, said already, but I just think it would make it, I think it'd make it easier for me to play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think, you know, me and the four-year-olds who can't, you know, play video games very well, I'm assuming there are four-year-olds out there who can't play video games very well.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, I think that's the biggest appeal.
[SPEAKER_09]: You just say, oh, you two can play video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't have to be as awesome as Rob or Matt or Irene to play video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is funny because people assume because we host this show that we're actually good at video games, but that's so not true.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've seen you play video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've seen me play Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, he's pretty badass at Rock Band, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Loki, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's my issue with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If the game is designed well in the beginning, you shouldn't have problems figuring out what you need to do because it gradually teaches you the skills in the game that you need to learn and teaches you how to solve different puzzles and then says, go do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you should know how to do it if it's been done right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, if you're going to put together a game that's poorly done, then yeah, you're going to need this stupid cheat system and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think it's a waste of time anyways because it would be like showing...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's a horrible idea and I see what they're trying to do because they're still having this dilemma.
[SPEAKER_06]: How do we sell games to people that only want to play Wii Sports and now Wii Fit?
[SPEAKER_06]: How do we sell games to them?
[SPEAKER_06]: And they don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is a problem because they're never going to figure this out, this console generation, and they're going to
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a feeling they're going to sell millions of systems, but they're not going to sell millions of games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's a problem because the only things they're selling right now are the things that they're making hard to find.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because trust me, I'm sorry, Mario Kart's been out since last April.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're coming upon almost a year of it being out.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no fucking reason that should be a shortage right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a game and a goddamn steering wheel.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a piece of plastic.
[SPEAKER_06]: They make plastic toys like crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're in supermarkets everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a piece of fucking plastic.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there's no reason that the stuff is, they're selling out of it because they can't make enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, they're not making enough on purpose so that there's not enough on the market.
[SPEAKER_06]: So demand's always high.
[SPEAKER_06]: So people are always looking for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Wii Fit's always popular because people think, oh my God, it's out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: But once they buy it, like I do, you go, oh my God, I'm not using this thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have an argument for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number one, we have...
[SPEAKER_02]: Not only strategy guides, but we have a huge website dedicated to, you know, FAQs and walkthroughs and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, obviously, people are going to need help with games.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why those exist.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number two, there are going to be parts of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, not every part of every game is hard, but there are going to be very hard parts.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember a part in Resident Evil 4 that I just could not get past, and I wish I could have done that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just press a button and just gotten through that one small section of the game, and then continued.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: I personally probably would not use it to just skip through every part of the game, but if I have a chance to get through a hard part of the game, bring it on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: This has been done before, not necessarily to the fact that there's stuff that you can skip parts of the game, but
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: And that may turn away people from playing those games, but you're not going to buy the game in the first place if you aren't remotely interested in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like someone spoiling the ending for a movie or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why is...
[SPEAKER_06]: For example, The Sixth Sense or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why is it that his wife doesn't see him?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's because he's dead!
[SPEAKER_06]: Spoilers!
[SPEAKER_06]: If someone spoiled that for you so that you figure out the puzzle there, it ruins it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, see, gamers like us, regular gamers that have hand-eye coordination and all that stuff, we're not going to want to skip over the story parts.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to want to play the game as is.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there are people who suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just plain, flat-out suck at video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just can't make their character jump or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: They can't put two and two together.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to want to be kind of like a...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to say my piece because I haven't said anything on this yet and I haven't stated my opinion and you know I'm one of Nintendo's biggest critics as of like 2008 and everything Nintendo's kind of been pissing me off a lot lately that being said I actually think this is a really good idea
[SPEAKER_07]: For Nintendo and its audience, I think this is a really good idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: As long as they make a feature to turn it off and you hit the nail on the head.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is for those people that like to watch other people play video games because they're too intimidated.
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't want to really play them themselves.
[SPEAKER_07]: because of the fact that they feel like they suck at video games, they can't get past these hard parts, they want to just get past this stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think a game like Zelda, especially, that has such pretty awesome cinematics, these things that you get into, the towns, and the story behind these games, I think it actually is going to work really well.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of think about how many times we've kind of hoped that there was a game like Final Fantasy X or something, where you could just like, I don't want to grind, I don't want to do this dungeon, I just want to run past all the monsters,
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to equip the run boots on my character so I can just run really fast through the dungeon so I don't have to grind here because I just want to get to the next part of the story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you know how many games I've quit because I couldn't get past one certain part?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fucking Alundra.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, that game pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_02]: I spent so long trying to do one puzzle I could just never get it so I quit the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: My thing though is
[SPEAKER_07]: I think as we start to blur the line even more and more as games become more and more realistic between games and movies, this actually kind of seems like a logical progression to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: These video games are slowly becoming Blu-ray movies, in a way.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's fascinating.
[SPEAKER_07]: And again, for the hardcore gamers, that can be a little off-putting at first, but I don't think this necessarily means that games that you and I enjoy are going to go away.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think this is just something they're going to start in Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's a very Nintendo thing to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not surprising at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, sorry, Matt.
[SPEAKER_06]: My thing is, is that a fault of the fact that you can't finish something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that a fault of the person or is that a fault of the game design?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's a fault of the game design.
[SPEAKER_06]: The fact that they made that many random battles.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, they've tweaked it in future Final Fantasy games where there aren't that many random battles.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they've gone back and fixed different things like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because people complained about it and they listened to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't think that necessarily...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a bad thing that there should be some difficulty in there because it makes it worthwhile to figure it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to just go from story to story to story, seriously, go read a book.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go watch a movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, of course, but they're making it an option for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, work at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you really want a sense of accomplishment from beating this game, do it normal.
[SPEAKER_02]: But for those people who don't want to, they're giving them the option.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just have a problem, though, with someone pushing a button, having the game play itself, beginning to end, and just...
[SPEAKER_06]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's what you can't do with a movie, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's going to be some people like this.
[SPEAKER_07]: All they're going to do in a Zelda game is go around and talk to the villagers and then fast forward through the action sequences and dungeons of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they're going to feel like a part of the game and they feel that more emotional attachment because it was more interactive and they just walked around and talked to villagers and that's all they ever did.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're going to be like, this is the greatest game I've ever played.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what's also awesome about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: The fact that they're going to be done with the game now and they have to buy something else.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's their own choice.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's their prerogative.
[SPEAKER_02]: They can do that if they want to.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you can go on to themoviespoiler.net and look at the ending to all your movies without having to pay $100.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to say this here and now.
[SPEAKER_06]: This game, whenever it does come out with this feature, I'm not buying it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: This feature right here ruined it for me, and the fact that they're putting it in this game, I am not buying this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even though it's optional?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't give a shit, I'm not buying it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There have been plenty of kids, plenty of people that have figured out the Xbox controllers, figured out the PlayStation 2 controllers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd like to meet them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Figured out how to use the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's people that still don't know how to use the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless you come out with a game that's one fucking controller that's a big giant button that says, push me, and even then they're not going to figure it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to throw it on the floor and go, I don't know how to play this.
[SPEAKER_06]: These people do not need to be playing games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't care if you want to introduce them in the games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They think they need to be playing games, but they do not need to be playing games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And keep them away from my goddamn games!
[SPEAKER_07]: We 2.0, push me
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no, I was just gonna say, I, the way I see it, I liken it to, um, having an easy, normal, and hard mode in a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you just, there's gonna be, like, dumb fuck mode, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, don't know how to do anything in the game, just gonna watch it play itself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just another mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not surprised it's the Wii, you know, great.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're gonna have this feature, but I bet you anything they're gonna be able to turn it off.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know why?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that's a feature, and Nintendo doesn't add features that people want.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: we're getting back into that Matt we don't need to have that argument on this show no seriously
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not going to have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a second half to this I want Loki to get into here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, there's a second half.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, the game developers were asked to comment on this.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have different things.
[SPEAKER_06]: For example, Ben Matz from Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was saying he read through it quickly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not surely they fully understand the...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's kind of interesting because Ubisoft kind of already started going this direction where, you know, you don't die.
[SPEAKER_07]: The chick always saves you.
[SPEAKER_07]: And in every battle, at least that I've played so far, it pretty much tells you how to fight it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you just press buttons and it does cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, like, it's not a bad game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really not.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a lot of fun with the new Prince of Persia.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can I read this in chat real quick?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, this is too good.
[SPEAKER_07]: GS68 says, I guess talking about getting irritated at games, my face turns beet red, I throw my controller on the ground, start swearing, fucking game, long chains, swear to never play a shooting game again.
[SPEAKER_07]: And SakuraMax follows up and says, and then you throw a taco at someone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Todd Howard from Bethesda says that most people stop playing certain games because they get frustrated or confused by what the game wants them to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: It becomes work and frustration as opposed to playtime.
[SPEAKER_06]: This idea clearly tries to alleviate that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's much like passing the controller to someone that knows the game really well so that you can move ahead or simply enjoy the story.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a classic challenge or entertain issue that designers will often deal with.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, and then finally, uh, let's see here, Jonathan Blow from, um, the creator of Braid says, based on just reading your posting, I don't know, I mean, it's an okay idea for a developer to have a way to show you through various parts of the game, I guess, to show you the side quests that you missed or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd like to see someone try that, uh, but as a general, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Paradigm.
[SPEAKER_06]: For playing games, there are a lot of problems.
[SPEAKER_06]: The defining characteristics of a game is that you play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if in order for games to be accessible to a wide audience, we need to make sure that so that most people can skip over the playing part of it, then what that really means is that our medium sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you have...
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have to elude the basic property of your medium to make experiences in the medium desirable, then the medium itself is questionable at a very deep level.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently our stream went down for the live listeners.
[SPEAKER_07]: The podcast listeners won't notice the thing because we've been recording the whole time, but our stream went down in the middle of you reading that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what's going on tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's some weird things with our internet stream.
[SPEAKER_07]: But somebody in the chat room had to say, who threw a taco at the stream?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, that's never going to get old.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry to derail the other thing you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: The live listeners didn't even hear what you were just saying, which is unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of some varied opinions from developers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, definitely it's all over the place, but I think it's something that's only going to be used in Nintendo games anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not something that they're requiring, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder if any of these developers are secretly already working on something for this new system.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I'm curious about.
[SPEAKER_07]: I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You think this is a Nintendo-only thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think this is something they're going to push, and it's probably going to be one game, and I don't think you'll see it ever again.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really don't think... I mean, honestly, with this in here, the problem is if this is... We're expecting this to be implemented in a Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And really, are you going to be able to tell what kind of an impact this had on a Zelda game?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, this is a title that's going to sell like crazy anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I would think that they would want this something on, you know, something that doesn't sell very well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, even Mario Galaxy didn't sell that well.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, maybe something like that is where we can see an actual impact on this.
[SPEAKER_06]: But with Zelda, it's just going to sell like crazy and be like, oh, it worked.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I mean, it's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's...
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just going to sell tons of copies anyways because people are dumb and they'll buy whatever people tell them is good.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Zelda is going to get tens out of ten because...
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a good franchise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because there's fanboys out there that are reviewing that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And even though, like, you know, Twilight Princess, in my opinion, I don't think that's a 10 out of 10 game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or not even an 9 out of 10 game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was the first Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, the GameCube one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or the, not the GameCube, the Nintendo 64 ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't care for it too much either.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the... I just was not interested.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just didn't hold my interest in...
[SPEAKER_06]: That's sad because I'm really interested in the Zoli games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but they don't have an objective perspective on the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perfectly.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, there's going to be like Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, 10 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, Gears of War, 10 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they don't even have to work on it anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's guaranteed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's what you do.
[SPEAKER_02]: You build up a franchise and you get to the point where it's like, you know, you can do whatever and people are still going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's huge.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, then.
[SPEAKER_07]: Check out some emails from the listeners.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every week we invite you to send us emails at mailbag at orangelunchradio.com and usually DarkSakura opens up the mailbag and reads the emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, she's not here tonight, so I am filling in.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we actually have quite a few emails tonight, so I want to try and get through these as fast as I can.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's read this first email.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's from Chaz.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, OLR gang.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm a long-time listener of the show, but it's my first time writing in.
[SPEAKER_07]: I listen to you all every Monday at my desk while hard at work here in the frozen tundra known as Chicago.
[SPEAKER_07]: I listen to a lot of the other video game podcasts out there, and OLR is by far the best.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really have much to say in the way of video games today, but consider this my love letter to the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: How hard does OLR rock?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me count the ways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Number three, real gamers with real opinions.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nothing commercial here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's one of the things we pride ourselves on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we're definitely not commercial, based on the comments and, like, crap that we... Brought to you by Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, have you checked out GameTap this week?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Number two, awesome segments.
[SPEAKER_07]: Classic Game of the Week and FUs of the Week rock my world.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Number one, good friends with great chemistry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki with his blistering honesty, Jamie's hilarious interludes, and Rob's fun-loving and sincere take on gaming culture.
[SPEAKER_07]: These are just a few of the reasons I am and will continue to be an OLR fanboy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, on a personal note, I'd like to give a special shout-out to Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's so great and so important to have an openly gay gamer's voice being heard in the community.
[SPEAKER_07]: As a gay man myself, you know as well as I do how severely underrepresented and occasionally maligned gay sexuality has been portrayed through the games we've played and how rampant homophobia continues to be in the online gaming sphere.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for letting listeners know your stand on these issues.
[SPEAKER_07]: It means a lot to me and also to those who are unable for whatever reason to speak up for themselves.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep up the great work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, is he single?
[SPEAKER_02]: And not a minor?
[SPEAKER_02]: Shush.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shush.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that was very nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it's letters like those that make me feel good about doing this show for free for seven years.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, honestly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tear, tear.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, when one says it's right, it's tough.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really tough sometimes because, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, I'm saying, you know, the nice thing is being gay is getting more and more accepted.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're getting there.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, even though Prop 8 in California didn't pass, it was just, yeah, I know, I know, Victoria, don't get me started.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a very slim margin compared to Prop 22 of several years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're getting there.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, more and more, especially in the youth, no more gay people, what have you.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's funny because in the gay world, it's like, oh, you play video games?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's like a kid thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, why don't you listen to Madonna or do fashion shows?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, seriously, you know, like, it's hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, there was a long time where I didn't feel comfortable when I met guys for the first time, like, telling them, yeah, I do an online radio show about video games on the weekends because it's like, whoa, nerd alert, but now I don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm to that point where I've kind of seen there's enough out there that, you know, there's people out there that
[SPEAKER_07]: are going to like me for both elements, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, I don't want to get too into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can relate to you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: How so?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because girl gamers, I mean, like, you know, a lot of them are kind of, I guess, not really tomboyish, but they kind of shun, like, female convention.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, not all of them are bottle blondes that get their nails done every day and wear a lot of makeup, so it's kind of the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting perspective.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's get to another email.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, okay, this kind of ties into a story we reported on earlier, but obviously we weren't here last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Spazinator writes in, Hey everyone, I thought I'd email you folks about some news that I received the other day that you might want to share.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have heard via both 1up.com, Greenspeak.com, and G4 that Ziff Davis has sold the 1up network of sites along with EGM to UGO, not to be confused with Yu-Gi-Oh!, for some undisclosed sum.
[SPEAKER_07]: Subsequently, Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_07]: is, now I want to say Yu-Gi-Oh!,
[SPEAKER_07]: has fired approximately 30 1UP employees, including some of the more well-known and popular personalities.
[SPEAKER_07]: Additionally, EGM has been officially killed off, and although no one mentioned them specifically, it looks like the audio and video podcasts have been axed as well, including 1UP FM, Retronauts, and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_07]: On a personal note, I really feel bad for those that got the ax earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: The ones I recognize, I know they produce top-notch material, whether it be for the sites, podcasts, or the magazines, and inject their own personality into said material to keep it from going stale.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope for the best for them, but given the particularly craptastic economy as of late, I'm afraid there's the potential they may leave the video games journalism biz.
[SPEAKER_07]: If that's the case, the industry would suffer a great loss.
[SPEAKER_07]: Additionally, it really sickens me that they killed off EGM, a long as hell running magazine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't it bad enough that OPM was killed in 06 and Game for Windows earlier this year?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, come on, websites are fine and dandy, but magazines still have a place though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Case in point, which would you rather bring to the can?
[SPEAKER_07]: A mag or a laptop?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or worse, yes, a desktop.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow, it's like this guy read my mind from earlier.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not only that, but for some people such as myself, we like the feel of holding a mag in our hands.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hell, I still have every single solitary issue of OPM, original PlayStation Magazine, all 112 and every single issue of EGM since my OPM subscription rolled over to EGM.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was wondering, what are your opinions on this?
[SPEAKER_07]: I know that based on user-generated comments on various sites, blogs, etc., that most people are uber-pissed and vowed never to visit 1up.com again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Additionally, what other podcasts, websites, and mags would you recommend to fill the void?
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, I want to avoid GameSpot because of their reputation and credibility has been severely tarnished early last year over that Army of Two firing debacle.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for the email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously, we talked about this a little bit earlier in the show, but the point that he brought up that I thought was interesting was that last paragraph was based on everybody complaining, vowing never to visit 1up.com and all this stuff again.
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: EGM has really gone through a lot of changes since the beginning.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do a lot of people that worked there in the first couple years work there now?
[SPEAKER_07]: Very, very few.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I know that because most of the people working at 1up.com were in their early 30s or late 20s.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they would have been like teenagers when the magazines first came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: These magazines have already changed the guards a few times.
[SPEAKER_07]: So my question back to you guys is, yes, these guys integrated their personalities into the show and everything, which in turn probably ended up being bad for 1up.com because this would have never happened had they never had those podcasts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: If they never had those podcasts, if they never built up that personality, it's kind of like a double-edged sword.
[SPEAKER_07]: It probably really helped sell their site, but at the same time, now they're having to deal with this.
[SPEAKER_07]: What if you'd never really gotten to know those writers as well as you did?
[SPEAKER_07]: Would you have cared so much about this news?
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I bet this kind of stuff has happened before.
[SPEAKER_07]: You didn't care because you didn't feel that connection to them from reading their Twitters, looking at their podcasts, so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: There's what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Gamercast Network, I think they're called.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially if you like Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a lot of Xbox-centric shows over there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look for some of the networks of shows.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that's kind of what 1UP was, was a network, except it was a little different because they were all still produced in-house.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whereas, I think in the case of all games, Gamercast and whatever other networks you can think of.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's the other one?
[SPEAKER_07]: Platform Nation, I think, is another one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is Evil Avatar a network?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, all these kind of networks are
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the difference is that 1UP produced all those in-house.
[SPEAKER_07]: These are more, everybody produces their own little silo show and they come together on these networks.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, check out.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's lots of people that love games that would love to talk about them with you out there on the internets.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, obviously, if you still feel connected to the 1UP guys, it sounds like they're doing their own show.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, maybe it'll last for them.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Platform Nation is the... I said them right?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, just for the live listeners only, and I apologize, I'm too lazy to edit this kind of stuff out of the podcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently the stream is skipping now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sounds like a CD that's skipping or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not on our end, guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have had cable issues.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did not get to go to a WoW raid on Thursday because of Comcast cable issues.
[SPEAKER_09]: God forbid you miss your story of the castle.
[SPEAKER_07]: For real.
[SPEAKER_07]: And by the way, it was the dragon battle, Malygos, that I missed.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I was the only one attuned for it so the whole guild didn't get to go because I couldn't sign on because of Comcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it was big drama.
[SPEAKER_07]: Big drama.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyway, I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if it's us.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if it's the server.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something's up.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the podcast will be up in its entirety along with last week's podcast this week on the stream.
[SPEAKER_04]: Promise.
[SPEAKER_07]: More emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except I just closed the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whoops.
[SPEAKER_02]: Way to go, Ron.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else you guys want to say on that last email?
[SPEAKER_07]: About other...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you touched everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: When the line reaches the end, it continues on the other half of the screen.
[SPEAKER_07]: I feel that this game is the right step for the rhythm game genre.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's always two to three people waiting to play the game at Sunnyvale Golf Land, which shows that Technica just might keep arcades going somewhat longer.
[SPEAKER_07]: I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I hate to be the pessimist, but one game ain't gonna happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, I appreciate your enthusiasm.
[SPEAKER_07]: The touchscreen in the EBA meets luminous gameplay allows for more freedom of movement and play styles as opposed to, say, Beatmania 2DX or DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen players use one hand, both hands, one or two fingers, all of their fingers, and so on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, being a touch-the-notes game as opposed to hit notes as they pass a red line game, it's harder to sight-read a song.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen otherwise good players fail a song because of the offbeat notes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Songs that are faster tend to be also harder than slow songs because the notes are more spaced out and you have less time to survey the notes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm hoping something good comes out of having a card.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have one myself, and so far it's only apparent features are modifiers, which you use max points on, and Platinum Crew mode, which is some sort of online mode I'll discuss later when it's activated.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, our machine is looking to get an update in a few days.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully we'll get some new songs about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also a minor but nice touch, there's a headphone jack below the touchscreen.
[SPEAKER_07]: If it's hard to hear the game, using headphones can help.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe I'll see some of you at Sviggle.
[SPEAKER_07]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: This email was brought to you by Beat Rock 3 from Papa Music, home of the never-ending Falling Books.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to try this touch game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I'm supposed to be in South Bay February 7th anyway, and I'm taking Victoria with me.
[SPEAKER_07]: So maybe I'll take Victoria to the arcade because we have Rocky in the South Bay on the 7th.
[SPEAKER_07]: So maybe we can swing by and check out this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't you want to go play video games, Victoria?
[SPEAKER_09]: OMG, totally.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: She just rolled her eyes.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't want to play DDR, Victoria?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm an epic fail at DDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Am I fat ass on the damn thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, on easy, I'm like, oh girl!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh girl!
[SPEAKER_09]: I need a break!
[SPEAKER_07]: You can play pinball or something that's less stressful.
[SPEAKER_07]: Holla!
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, Victoria's ass is not fat, it's just round.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like big butts and I cannot lie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I don't think Victoria's fat, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, she's not at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's beautiful and single.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stop trying to pimp me, Irene.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me read another email here from...
[SPEAKER_07]: RJ, because I don't see another signature here, so I'm just going to say RJ.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, OLR, I'm using my lovely iTouch to send this email, so be warned, Jamie, if the grammar Nazi bar is high.
[SPEAKER_07]: You lucked out.
[SPEAKER_07]: You read me tonight, and I have terrible grammar, so I don't judge the others.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've just finished Infinite Undiscovery and Lost Odyssey, and I'm planning on getting The Last Remnant next, which I've heard is a slightly generic story, but a robust and interesting battle system, so I'll tell you what I've experienced next time.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Nevertheless, both leave you satisfied at the end and don't suffer from rehashed plot points.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you wish, story is better.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lost Odyssey is and has superb presentation.
[SPEAKER_07]: With Infinite Undiscovery gameplay, in my opinion, fun yet repetitive at parts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't hesitate on getting either.
[SPEAKER_07]: So interesting because I gave up on Infinite Undiscovery because the beginning is terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: PS, Rob, Queen was the better 70s band than ABBA
[SPEAKER_07]: I love Queen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Queen is amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Queen is amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Freddie Mercury was... I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Freddie Mercury is a god.
[SPEAKER_07]: Freddie Mercury was a god, really.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Abba's still number one.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Queen is like seriously two or three.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Two or maybe three.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe two or three.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Bowie's kind of... Oh, from Labyrinth.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's my thoughts on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And just a couple more here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, I know we have a lot of emails tonight, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't have a lot of...
[SPEAKER_07]: This one's for Fart Princess, which we haven't called it that tonight, but Fart Princess.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, since Rice or Fart Princess, which, by the way, can I say this about Fart Princess real quick?
[SPEAKER_07]: I was on WoW last night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, do you have to bring this up?
[SPEAKER_02]: Boo!
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: And for an hour, she was talking about farts in guild chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was not an hour, it was like five minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: It felt like an hour.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was incidental.
[SPEAKER_07]: You were talking about farts for an hour.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Vlad kept talking to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: So obviously someone was interested in what I had to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: Since Rice Princess is here tonight, this is from Amaze Satsuma, I'll go ahead and ask, how did you all like the latest Battlestar Galactica episode?
[SPEAKER_07]: We all know the BSG talk is in, was going to happen sooner or later with her here, so I thought I'd give it a helping hand.
[SPEAKER_07]: No spoilers, I haven't watched it yet because I'm still on season 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: This doesn't spoil anything, but I am depressed beyond belief.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to elaborate more, but I can't because then I'll start getting into the spoilers.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope that's not a spoiler, but I'm hoping that it wasn't an actual revelation of the final Cylon, that it was just speculation on behalf of one of the characters in the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I think it pretty much is confirmation that it is the last Cylon, but if that is the last Cylon, I'll be upset.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: We won't say any more.
[SPEAKER_02]: No BSG.
[SPEAKER_07]: One other email from our old buddy DMN who wants to update you on the March Madness competition that's going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember this was the controversial one last year where Super Metroid beat Chrono Trigger and I got hate mail for a year because of it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, as you deserve.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here is your chance to write what has been wronged.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can send your top 25 to...
[SPEAKER_07]: Breast Lull, I guess is his name.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there's a specific email address you actually want to send those to.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know it's a Gmail address.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me look it up real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is the last week to do so, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's like six days left.
[SPEAKER_07]: uslmadness, all one word, at gmail.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: You want to send those into Breast Lull as fast as you can because you only have six days left.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the rundown of the top 25 so far.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep in mind, this is only determining the seeds for the head-to-head competitions that will happen later on.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is not...
[SPEAKER_07]: 25.
[SPEAKER_07]: Paper Mario 24.
[SPEAKER_07]: Earthbound 23.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mega Man 2 22.
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Mario Galaxy 21.
[SPEAKER_07]: World of Warcraft 20.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ace Attorney 19.
[SPEAKER_07]: Street Fighter 3 18.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tetris Attack and Puzzle League 17.
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Mario World 16.
[SPEAKER_07]: Legend of Zelda
[SPEAKER_07]: 15 Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1, 14 Castlevania Symphony of the Night, 13 Final Fantasy 7, 12 Super Mario RPG, 11 Street Fighter 2, 10 Tetris, 9 Pokemon, 8 Dance Dance Revolution, 7 Super Metroid, at 7, excuse me, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_07]: 6.
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Mario 3 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy 6 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Ocarina of Time 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Link to the Past 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chrono Trigger And the current number one game of all time, according to people who have emailed, Big Rigs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rock Band is the number one game of all time.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you consider that music game fans is our roots, I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you would disagree, here's your chance to send in your list to make Super Metroid number one so it gets a little higher.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why the fuck is Pokemon on there?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't like Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you disagree, again, get those lists in.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have six days left.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because they're closing the polls.
[SPEAKER_07]: So are you going to send in a list?
[SPEAKER_07]: Your top 25 of all time?
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I already know my... I'm secure in my decision.
[SPEAKER_02]: My top five games of all time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't need to validate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, just stuck up, bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, that's going to do it for the emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com if you'd like to send your own email in for reading.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speak English!
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank God Jamie's not here, I would have just got a fail award.
[SPEAKER_02]: She would have thrown a taco at you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Back to some gaming news, and then we're going to take some calls on the Skype line at 1-877- You mean Victoria's going to take calls?
[SPEAKER_07]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: In a little bit, we still have some stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: This week on Xbox Live Arcade, we'll be getting the brand new game, The Maw.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the Maw is being put out by Twisted Pixels.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an adventure platformer that places you in the role of Frank, an alien stranded on a strange planet with the Maw, a strange blob-like creature that acts like his only friend and ultimate weapon all at the same time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And let's see, it will be available for 800 Microsoft Points.
[SPEAKER_06]: It will be out on the 21st.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if I remember correctly, I think the Maw was...
[SPEAKER_06]: it was a winner of some award during PAX but I can't remember what it was
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Was it one of those indie games that was featured in the center?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember hearing about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fable 2, which I'm finally going to get a chance to play this week because Loki helped me get hooked up with a copy of Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm going to check that out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I know this is a game that DarkSakura has been playing a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't seen her on Xbox Live a lot until this game came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And apparently she's been playing with OLR people and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm going to get on there and finally get to play some Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're not a big fan?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually have to go back and play because I want to finish it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's short.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm thinking about getting the download content though for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then I can start Fallout 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or maybe Lost Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_06]: I might have to go back to Lost Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I think I'm going to check out Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: I might even play it tonight and force Victoria to watch some of it with me.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Victoria?
[SPEAKER_07]: I just caught Victoria's attention.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to play some Fable 2 tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a video game.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's going, yippee.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll have my laptop.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can chat with your hoes on AOL.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can marry people of the same sex or have multiple husbands and wives.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been watching Sauce, or Tiara, whatever you want to call her.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's been on this show a couple times.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been watching her tweets that have been updating us on the progress of her.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sounds like she's having a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think she has two husbands and a wife and a child named Optimus Prime.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I want to check this out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, anyhow, speaking of Fable 2, the download content, not Whole Island, finally came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, there's a weapon in it called HAL's Rifle.
[SPEAKER_07]: The funny thing about it, it looks exactly like the assault rifle from Halo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_07]: HAL?
[SPEAKER_07]: Halo?
[SPEAKER_07]: 59 damage per shot, 24 shots per clip, and it has an empty augment slot.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, basically, they kind of made a little Halo lol joke in the download content.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, lol.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Redertainment says, Sky, why are you forcing Victoria to do things?
[SPEAKER_07]: What is she, your girlfriend?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, but kind of.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, she's like one of my hags.
[SPEAKER_07]: And she has to crash here all weekend.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got two of my hags here tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm very special.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the least I could do for him letting me stay here and not sleep in my car.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the least that she can do as his hag.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have hag duties, you know, that we have to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is some of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: What did they say?
[SPEAKER_09]: If the hag don't like you, the fag... If the hag hates you, the fag don't date you.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that goes the other way around, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: It does.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to approve if anyone Victoria or Irene dates.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is true.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to approve.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, don't ask that on the radio, for God's sake.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I didn't, I would have said something already.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you, Irene, have been your man a long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been with my man.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if I disapproved, I would have said something a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: You would have bitch slapped the shit out of him.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would have bitch slapped you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, because Irene makes no qualms if she dislikes somebody I'm dating.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, we know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now he was saying that she wants to get a second wife to do all the cleaning and cooking because she doesn't do any of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, anyhow, I'm sorry, we got derailed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Matt, if you become a gay man, that will be easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you'll get a bunch of hags who will do that for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why can't I have straight hags?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there's no such thing as a straight hag.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you ridiculous?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I am going to pioneer this.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't have your cake and eat it too, Matt.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I can.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else do you do with cake?
[SPEAKER_07]: You should take applications.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, you have a radio show.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should solicit applications for some straight hags.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nah, because, see, street hags, that's actual real hags, and no one likes real hags.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should just put on the application, four-toothed minimum.
[SPEAKER_02]: No fat chicks.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, SSJ100Matt says, Loki needs to find a girl who's into airsoft.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait a minute, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're not trying to set him up on a date.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's very happily married.
[SPEAKER_07]: Him and Nellie get along fabulously.
[SPEAKER_02]: He just wants a maid that works for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: for Nellie to nag so that she gets it out of her system before you get home.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, thank God.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of the airsoft stuff... It doesn't even have to be a woman.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't been good when it comes to the airsoft stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that, sorry, OLR Studio Drama, you know how we tape in the garage basically, very thin wall.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I can hear the neighbor like yelling at a dog or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: We can hear it all the way here in the garage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, I hope he's not throwing his weed out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think somebody just threw a taco across the street at the dog.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll be back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm hungry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Back to game news here.
[SPEAKER_06]: We talked about last week how there was a game that possibly will get removed off of the App Store relatively soon if Nintendo caught wind of it, and that was the Game & Watch game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, now there's another Nintendo game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Duck Hunt is now available for $1.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn, I forgot to download the Game & Watch game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't know if it's... It might still be up there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you just better check.
[SPEAKER_06]: Duck Hunt is available now for a dollar.
[SPEAKER_02]: One dollar.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, one dollar.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you have everything in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ducks and no annoying dog.
[SPEAKER_06]: You move the cursor around and shoot ducks.
[SPEAKER_02]: All for a dollar.
[SPEAKER_06]: All for a dollar.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a bargain.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the laughing dog isn't in it, so what the hell's the point?
[SPEAKER_02]: You shoot ducks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, maybe they didn't like the dog.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, who cares?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hence the reason he prefaced that statement with annoying.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, sorry, I'm looking for the Game & Watch games right now to see if they're there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they're there.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was the name of it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um... Crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: I searched for Game & Watch and didn't find anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here, just one second.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can find it for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is... It's not called Game & Watch.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called... Alright, you look while I talk about the next story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's GW Chef, GW Parachute, GW Fire.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just look for GW.
[SPEAKER_07]: GW, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I'll look at that after I read you this story because this is pretty exciting, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: I love the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't you love the Commodore 64?
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of it, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you remember, if I start talking this, you are standing in front of a White House.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is a mailbox here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that Zork?
[SPEAKER_07]: It is Zork!
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly right.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have been eaten by a Gru.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I knew you were going to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, and obviously Zork actually had a couple other games that came out later, like Zork Grand Inquisitor.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were kind of cute, funny games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, apparently Zork is coming back as an MMO.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Legends of Zork.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wiggity what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Joel Online is resurrecting the Zork franchise.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a game called Legends of Zork.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a casual browser-based MMO.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think it's up just yet, but they actually were interviewed by Grandma Sutra recently, and they have mentioned that the game is going to feature microtransactions.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can play it on the computer or the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: What are you so upset about?
[SPEAKER_07]: My phone just died.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Victoria's phone died.
[SPEAKER_07]: Big drama.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe we could bring it back to life.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm wondering how fast it's going to be before people get eaten by a Gru.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to push Irene in front of a Gru.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to push you off the edge of something from Impossible Mission.
[SPEAKER_07]: I almost did that for the classic game tonight, but it was Loki's turn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my gosh, I love that game so much.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was Loki's turn.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I actually found another Commodore 64 game I wanted to do first before Impossible Mission.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to get the sound bites from that game and use it like sometimes in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stay a while, stay forever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that game so much, but I couldn't ever play it because I was only like 10.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I never realized what it was he was saying in the beginning of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another visitor.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stay a while, stay forever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else does he say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Get him my robots or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on to the next story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Two more stories before we open up the sky blind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hurry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there's other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: We talked about Klonoa coming out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually been out on the Wii already in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, of course, will be coming out over here pretty soon, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been announced that sometime in 2009 it will be available.
[SPEAKER_06]: or possibly April.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then it might move.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: April 4th.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, not April 4th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a great day to release stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: April 4th.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, when these games come out, you can rent them at Game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Game is not here in the US.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you're looking confused, like, what the hell is Game?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually a big competitor for the GameStop EB behemoth over in Europe, and it's also in Australia and parts of Asia.
[SPEAKER_07]: They actually are only in the business of selling new and used games right now, but soon they are going to rent games.
[SPEAKER_07]: They partnered up with a group called Swap Game, so they're going to be offering folks over in the UK the option of paying a monthly subscription fee that will allow them to rent two games at a time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like a GameStop employee.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, interesting business model, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think that's going to make them a lot of money?
[SPEAKER_07]: Rental, it couldn't hurt.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I think it, well...
[SPEAKER_07]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of those sites are making money.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they're going to do a mail service where they're going to mail out the games or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just thinking that if I ever opened up a game store, I'd want to name it Store.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, because let's just get it as broad as possible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Store.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good luck getting any new releases, though, from a place like this.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I always wondered, like, because movie rental stores always rent games, but it never made sense that game stores never rented games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like...
[SPEAKER_02]: GameCrazy.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think of GameCrazy as not like an independent thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think of them as like part of Hollywood video.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you know, that's a movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: And GameStop wouldn't do it because they would cut into their used game sales because, you know, why bother paying $30 for, you know, a $40 game or something like that when they can rent it for $7 and beat it?
[SPEAKER_02]: They could still do the buybacks of the used games and then rent out those games as a buyback.
[SPEAKER_06]: And besides, those games they consider new.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember, they put a little sticker on them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Misty in chat says it sounds more immediate than Gamefly if it weren't a mail-based return system.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: And some people don't like to do the mail thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, Netflix is huge, but they're still blockbuster because sometimes, you know, just like even last night, Victoria was over, I was here, bored, done with WoW, let's watch a movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: But
[SPEAKER_07]: Game Rentals
[SPEAKER_06]: available over Xbox Live or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You download the game and you have it for seven days or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably just a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_07]: If they could make money off renting the game then selling the game, that would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be a smart business move.
[SPEAKER_07]: Next.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, that's it for stories tonight We're going to get into some last minute stories But first we want to take your calls on the Skype line 1-877-GAME-OLR Or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio If you have the Skype program and want to talk to us that way Let's go to the phone and take some calls Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, it's Ranma, what's up everyone?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, not much, how you doing Ranma?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm doing good So I've got a couple of things I want to discuss Alright
[SPEAKER_03]: I got a quick question for you, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: When was the last time you bought EGM?
[SPEAKER_07]: about a couple of months ago I still had a subscription okay that's cool I'm just curious because I bet there's some people that are sad you know I was sad to see EGM go but I haven't bought it in like 10 years you know what I mean so but I'm just kind of curious on what side of the fence you're on there so you were still a regular reader of it so okay you're sad to see it go
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was that, Die Hard, Game Fan, and GamePro.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those were the three magazines I read all throughout high school.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was it for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't GamePro still around?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's still around, but Die Hard, Game Fan died after like two or three years.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that because at the time, it was the only magazine available that had an in-depth review about import video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Weird, obscure fact about GamePro.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got to say this.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is what a nerd I am.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if you remember way back in the day.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you read GamePro for a long time, you'll remember this.
[SPEAKER_07]: A long, long time ago, they had a contest to get, I think it was 250 people, or maybe it was 50 or 250 people that were going to be part of an exclusive club that would get to write reviews for games or something like that for possible inclusion in the magazine or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: This was a long time ago, so bear with me.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this is what I remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was in the fourth grade or fifth grade or something, and I wrote in a letter.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got picked as one of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, in fourth grade.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they never did anything with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never got anything else other than the letter that said, you know, congratulations, you got selected, and then they never did anything with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, it's just funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, just a rant.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whenever I think of GamePro, I think of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: From when I was like, maybe it was a little late, like sixth grade, but I was young.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know I was young.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dork.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, some of those magazines are still around, but I sadly don't think this will be the last one to fold.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I wouldn't be surprised if any more fold because, honestly, I mean, as many video gaming sites there are, it's getting to the point where it's like video gaming industry with news and stuff is getting very saturated.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like every other site someone has a video game review site or blog or something like that, whereas me, I'm on the opposite spectrum for what I cover.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of hard to get that kind of information.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else did you want to talk about tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I have a couple of things I wanted to discuss, but I totally forgot.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I will do a brief review about The Last Remnant.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a game I just picked up yesterday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, yes, please do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, it plays like Final Fantasy XII, but when it comes to the battle sequences, it turns into a complete tactical-style game, which I'm really enjoying a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: What about the story?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've heard kind of mixed reviews on this game, so I'm kind of curious.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I remember correctly, the story is about a brother and sister who are going to meet up with their parents, but the sister is kidnapped, and he goes through his travels to find his sister, and you're discovering what these last remnants are, or these relics, for all types of different types of power that you can get.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: And right now, I'm like four or five hours in, and just like a regular tactics game, if you're not fully prepared, you will get killed on the first quest.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: So is this something for like a hardcore tactical game fan only or can anyone get into it or what?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're not really into tactics games but there are some tactical games that are very simple and you want something simple like that, this would be a good game to pick up.
[SPEAKER_03]: But to be perfectly honest, I wouldn't pay the $59.99 retail price tag for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got it on sale for $39.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say when you see it for $39, then pick it up then.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well anything else you want to share with our listeners today?
[SPEAKER_03]: Now I remember one more thing and I'll get out of here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember a long time ago I sent in a letter, an email about which games I should get for my 360?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um... Yes, I think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I actually picked up each of the games that you guys recommended for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_03]: I finally got around to doing so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, what did you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay...
[SPEAKER_03]: BlueDragon I'm still playing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really enjoy that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loving Saints Row and I'm loving Crackdown and Marvel Ultimate Alliance is definitely a fun party game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cool, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm glad our reviews did some good.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys are awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: What can I tell you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I do love you.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's almost like we pay you to say that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just wait until you come out here again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, hopefully soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is one of my goals for 09 to get back to New York City.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just probably won't happen until later in the year.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be waiting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, Orange Lounge Radio land.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is Jason coming to you with one less tooth in his mouth.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, hey, I know we've both been having dental drama this week, except yours sounds a little more severe, so I'm really sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, mine went a little bit crazy, but my mouth's been fine ever since Thursday.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what it's all about, then.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, isn't it the worst?
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I don't want to think about my mouth, because then it's just going to hurt more.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, I don't know if you've seen, have you seen what Deakman's done for the OLR beta?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, he was giving it to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: He showed me the link just a couple minutes ago, and I was...
[SPEAKER_05]: and Run with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a lot more attractive pretty instantly, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: He did a nice job.
[SPEAKER_07]: I gotta get you kids to work together behind the scenes to help make it happen so we can launch the new website because I'm all excited now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, we gotta show it to Jamie though.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's not here tonight to give it her okay, but she'll love it too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know she will.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's not gonna be... How can you look at the current site and go, oh, the current site's better.
[SPEAKER_07]: You really can't.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the new site's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I cannot
[SPEAKER_05]: I can agree with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pac-Man?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, he changed it, I think, to a Space Invader now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because somebody else uses a little... Like, the Pac-Man is right next to this little radio-looking thing, and it looks way too similar to another show's logo.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I was like, eh, we don't want to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we don't want to ruffle any feathers.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I suggested a Space Invader, and I guess he ran with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't seen the new logo yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway... I just completely lost you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't tell me I just completely lost you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we'll open up... No, I'm here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you hear us?
[SPEAKER_07]: Are we having internet issues going on?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I blame you and nobody else.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did not dump him.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, Jason, if you can hear me, why don't you tell us what you really called in for tonight before I hijacked website talk.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't hear me now, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, there's my echo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, two questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a question from Ryan, but she's too shy to get on the microphone because she's like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: How long did EGM 2 last?
[SPEAKER_07]: EGM2!
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right!
[SPEAKER_07]: They had a spin-off magazine for a little while, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: Famitsu was a weekly magazine, so they felt, I think for a short time there, that there was going to be like... Didn't EGM2 come out in the middle of the month or something?
[SPEAKER_07]: To offset it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I never... She had it.
[SPEAKER_05]: FYI, you went off the air again.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was not very long.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe a year.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: Just ignore the complaints about the stream in chat, Jason.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to just keep going with the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have it in the background, and I noticed a very specific loop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So about a year.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm definitely not the source.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: EGM2 ran from July 1994 to July 1998.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it was actually four years.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was way off.
[SPEAKER_05]: She had a subscription to both and I've never heard of it but she wanted to know so I am making you people do it for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got that from Wikipedia and I believe everything I read on Wikipedia so there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's just because I'm older than Jason.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Silent Hill 2 Restless Dreams.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's apparently something on the PS2.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: They released a little later on.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if it was on the PS2, but there was two versions of Silent Hill 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: The second version, Restless Dreams, has an additional scenario where, don't you play as Maria or something?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really short.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's short.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not like you're getting a whole second game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like another little quick scenario that just gives some additional insight to the story.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it was like a little bonus disc add-on that they released slightly later.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like a bonus chapter.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wouldn't even think of it as a full game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very short.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not even really a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even think you really do much.
[SPEAKER_02]: You do one thing and that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Restless Dreams, I believe, was originally for the Xbox expansion.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I think they re-released it on the PS2 with the Restless Dreams thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went through and I replayed all the Metal Gear Solids and then that led up to the time that we got the PS3 and I played Metal Gear Solid 4 all the way through and our next run through series is Silent Hill and I'm barring the dental madness I've been playing through Silent Hill 1 and I think I might be finishing that off tonight and since obviously Silent Hill 2 is the next one in line and I came across that I had never heard of it before
[SPEAKER_02]: You'll like Silent Hill 2 a lot!
[SPEAKER_05]: She was wondering if we were just going to skip the first one and as much as I want to because the game plays like hell and it really looks really bad I don't know if it's the PS2 doing something back in Pat but it has some really weird effects on our TV We were both thinking of just skipping the first one but she doesn't remember much of it and I fell asleep through some of it when I wasn't the one who played it in the first place so I kind of wanted to go through it the whole way and see it
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm admittedly using a walkthrough all the way through it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that hint system is actually viable to some situations, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm cheating all the way through it, but I'm getting the entire story in the manner it was supposed to be presented to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I'm playing the game to some extent so that's kind of enough for me nice yeah yeah and you want to play through one because it's not necessary but it's good to play through one when you play through three because it'll kind of give some insight into three's story also so I watched Silent Hill the movie what do I need to play the game for because it's
[SPEAKER_07]: Because if you're like Victoria, you'll think it's crap unless you give some insight to the series.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I have to admit, if I'd never played the games, I would have thought the movie was kind of random.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: What the hell is this pyramid thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Really, the movie was made for the fans.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really wish they would do this sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: On that same line.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the better video game movies, amazingly enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: My favorite video game movie, I ain't even gonna lie.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of want to watch it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do too, I've been wanting
[SPEAKER_07]: We should go get it on Blu-ray and then watch it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it on Netflix?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because then we could party watch it or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't have that built in yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think they have that feature built in yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'd call each other and try to press play at the same time and do it that way or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do it on Justin.TV or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jason, we've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take some more calls.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for all you do for the website too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Between you and Deakman...
[SPEAKER_07]: 2009 is going to be the best year ever for our website.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: I sure as hell hope so.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's been long enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am so excited because I'm all jazzed to write again for the website and I know TR has been wanting to do reviews.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're actually going to have a functional website and I'm so excited I could tinkle.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're jazzed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so we're going to let you go, Jason.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give me a month to move as we're closing on Tuesday and then I'll do my best to be really on top of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You got it, buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_07]: See you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dang, we got calls coming in back to back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think this is going to be the last one, though, because we're running kind of long tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's GS68.
[SPEAKER_00]: So about the whole hint system of how the game pretty much plays for you, there's always something like that in arcade games.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's called unlimited continues.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, but you have to feed it a quarter every time you want to continue.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, but at home, if you have free play, you just keep pressing start and you eventually get to the end of the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, no need to use any skill.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like playing the Ninja Turtles game on the Xbox, you can just get all the continues you want?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, or unlocking free play in Ikaruga.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can even just let the bosses time out.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's true, but you know, I also think of the old, you know what you're talking about, kind of reminds me of, could anyone, and I gotta ask Loki this, I've gotta ask Loki this, could you actually beat Contra on the NES without up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A, start?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's fucking hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's the point, though, you have to be good at it to, it can be done.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just that, you know, I need to play it more.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to play more to be able to learn the patterns and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's the whole point.
[SPEAKER_06]: It shouldn't be just like, oh, look at this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because even when we did that, we still didn't beat it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was fucking hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: The continue system was kind of an antiquated method to have gamers feed quarters into the machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the whole point.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to start all over again, unless you put it in a quarter, and then it just carried over onto consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what people were used to.
[SPEAKER_00]: I suppose it's like,
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know if the internet is acting up again, but you're kind of cutting in a little bit in and out.
[SPEAKER_00]: So go ahead and say what you wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was going to bring up DJ Max Black Square, which I got this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, it's alright, I guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, the songs are pretty good, and they're pretty hard, but I hate the club tour mood, because some of the missions are, like, really stupid hard.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then one feature, and then there's two other features that really piss me off.
[SPEAKER_00]: One, sometimes, the... Andy just dropped.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, no, you there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is this, I'm gonna ask real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're having these weird problems tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is this the American version that you're talking about, or is this the new one that came out in Korea?
[SPEAKER_07]: Korea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, basically sometimes the music will cut out and continue, but it will lag really badly.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or it'll lag like a few seconds.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are there any crazy-ass videos like there were in the earlier games?
[SPEAKER_00]: Sure, the physics in the office is all the correct feature.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, if you press...
[SPEAKER_00]: I wonder why they don't do DJ Max on the DS They are, and it is the arcade one that they don't do on the DS Arcade one, like, sometimes
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Max One of my friends is really into it and keeps begging me to check it out, so I probably will at some point.
[SPEAKER_07]: at least when it comes out in America but I do want to try this arcade version that's at Sunnyvale Golfland hopefully it's not gone I guess GS68 was saying in chat earlier that it looks like it's probably going to be gone by the time I get there so that would suck because I guess it's in this weird beta test or whatever so we'll see anyhow Loki do you have any last minute stories for us before we wrap up the show yes that's what I've been doing
[SPEAKER_06]: Some interesting ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apple has actually rejected a game from Yut Saito.
[SPEAKER_06]: You remember him from the Seaman series.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, he had a game coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it was like Seaman 2 on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was Gabo.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a spiritual successor to Seaman, but with a caveman instead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, they said due to unpleasant gameplay, they axed the game and they're not allowed to put it on the App Store.
[SPEAKER_07]: I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a lot of crap on the App Store, so I'm kind of surprised, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is why apples suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just had to work that in there, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: This isn't really a gaming story, but it has a game addict with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, there's a game addict in Beijing who was 23 years old and was rushed to a hospital after swallowing five pieces of saw blades in order to attempt to commit suicide.
[SPEAKER_06]: and apparently he had been talking incoherently about how to win his favorite computer games after being sent to a Beijing hospital ICU.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that was another one of those cases where he was a gamer and that's about the extent that it was related to video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: This guy had issues way beyond video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I just want to talk about swallowing saw blades and that was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty extreme.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty extreme, I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_06]: House of the Dead Overkill
[SPEAKER_06]: 1299 euros or pounds or something like that I think it's euros and it's um part of they're also going to have a big bang box um set that's going to have both that and uh two of those guns which they're calling the hand cannons and they look like pretty sweet guns so that's kind of cool um
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is pretty big news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Fantasy XIII is coming to Japan in 2009.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, we'll be making it out overseas and everywhere else April 2010.
[SPEAKER_06]: So April 2010 is the earliest that we'll see Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, I hope that we'll see it a lot sooner because I will be importing the Blu-ray Special Edition for Advent Children.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want that so bad, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: If we have to wait until 2010, then we have to wait until 2010.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess it's not surprising.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just a little disappointing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially because we do these things on the OLR forums, the annual predictions.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob with 2Bees does this thread every year, and he does a really good job tabulating and everything, and everybody makes their predictions for the year, and we see how many of them come true.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've already lost on two of my predictions.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said there'd be a new Rock Band game this year.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's not going to be, they've already said, because of the Beatles game, which makes sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: I should have been smarter and known that, that they don't need a new Rock Band game with the Beatles game.
[SPEAKER_07]: and also now this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said that Final Fantasy XIII would finally come out this Christmas and now it looks like it's going to be next year.
[SPEAKER_07]: I might get half credit for the Japanese release date though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and like I said, I'll try to import the Blu-ray for Advent Children because it's going to have a demo on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I totally wanted to check that out too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I might even import it for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the demo is supposed to be like two hours long, they said.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: CES09.
[SPEAKER_06]: Microsoft has been... Apparently was talking to somebody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: and let's see here also there's going to be a special edition Final Fantasy 7 Advent Children PS3 coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's in cloud black and it's got a nice little symbol there etched into the front of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's one of the 160 gigabyte PS3s.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll also come with it's got a Final Fantasy 13 trail version set which is with
[SPEAKER_06]: The Final Fantasy XIII demo, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then Final Fantasy VII Advent Children Complete Blu-ray Disc Set.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which will be available for 49,980 yen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Approximately $551 US.
[SPEAKER_06]: And... Very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And apparently...
[SPEAKER_06]: FFVII Advent Children Complete English Language Options
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is some funny stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Duke Nukem Critical Hour is coming along quite well, says 3D Realms.
[SPEAKER_06]: You may not remember what these are, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: Critical Hour was the game that they're putting out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a new game trilogy, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're also having some on the DS as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: But all I have to say is, finish Duke Nukem forever first!
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop going on to new things!
[SPEAKER_06]: Finish one, then you get to work on new games.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then the last thing EA is prepping a new game called Spore Hero and of course it will be related to Spore it's coming out on Wii and DS alright
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to go ahead and start to wrap up the show then and get everybody's final thought and get on out of here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately, our stream is crashing left and right and we're starting to lose listeners because of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I think that's a sign that we've probably been running too long.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're going to go ahead and wrap up for tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: But first, we're going to go get around everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I do want to say thank you very much for listening to Orange Lounge Radio this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you've enjoyed what you've heard, please tell two friends about our show.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's how we spread the word about our show and get it out there, the little program that we do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm Victoria and I'm young and I'm single and I'm sexy I'm beautiful
[SPEAKER_07]: and giving her opinion and everything, especially in the first part of the show, although she started to tune out during the second half of the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: So thank you, Victoria.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rice Princess, thank you for being here tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you said quite a bit tonight, especially in regards to Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: So thank you for your input as always.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: And do you have any final thoughts for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to know when the website's going live.
[SPEAKER_07]: The website, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't get too excited.
[SPEAKER_07]: It might not be until next month.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got to make sure Deepman and Jason get it worked out.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we will try to get it up fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will do whatever I can to get it working.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's cold in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, I haven't been running the heater.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's getting cold in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: And my final thought is I need some Orogel.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Boo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cry.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you guys once again for staying with us all night long, especially you live listeners that have suffered through several outages tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you guys as always for your support of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know we would just not do this if it weren't for you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, thank you, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have an amazing week.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see you again next week with Jamie back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next week!