[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, December 14th, 2008.
[SPEAKER_00]: Commodore 64 game returns to the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nintendo faces yet another Wii lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Could a Rez sequel be in the works?
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura Jamie Summers
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Let us in in our snow, I mean rain.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, Techmaster Loki is also joining us tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Good.
[SPEAKER_07]: As he does every week here for the past 305 some odd weeks.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's where we're at tonight, episode 305.
[SPEAKER_07]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: But you can't interact with the Video Game Awards.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do they even let people... I mean, I don't really follow it, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do they actually let people vote on it, or is it picked by experts?
[SPEAKER_07]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they may have, like, voting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe someone in our chat room knows.
[SPEAKER_05]: For at least probably one category or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, but here, they get to interact with us.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, the Video Game Awards doesn't let the audience interact with them, really.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, except the hooping and hollering.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well we're going to get started with the show tonight and we always like to start off with a little bit of how was your gaming week So DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Tatsunoko vs. Capcom and it was freaking fangasm-tastic And I played Raiden Fighters 2 at the Jaspers around the corner from your house and up the road I didn't know they had that, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I played some Ragnarok, and I tried to play some Order of Ecclesia, but I was like, meh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, Tetsunoko vs. Capcom, you've been very excited about this game for a while, so when you give this game a positive review, are you giving it a positive review because it's actually a good fighting game, or are you just giving it a positive review because it tickles your fan senses?
[SPEAKER_02]: Both.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially since I can play as the almighty combo of Ken and June, I'm very, very happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkTetsuya I think it's paid for ahead of time
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft says some of the categories are user voted Amaze Satsuma says video game awards have no ferrets that's why I'm watching OLR or I guess you'd be listening to it because sadly our video camera is broken just to give you an update on JustinTV we're going to be off JustinTV until 2009
[SPEAKER_07]: I was gonna say, I could bring in the PlayStation Eye, I think, has drivers.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, how was your gaming week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: My gaming week was alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played Animal Crossing and watched a lot of my wife playing Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, yeah, it's Animal Crossing and I don't know why I still play it, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then...
[SPEAKER_05]: I played some more Mirror's Edge, and that's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still very hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does the demo give you a good sense of that game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I actually tried playing the demo for that a little bit this week, and it was... It sort of does.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it gets a lot harder because I think a lot of it... Luckily, you can't really die.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just keep falling off the building and respawning and starting again and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's a lot of parts in the game that I didn't know where I was supposed to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: The reason why I actually played some Earth Defense Force is because I had gotten some Christmas bonuses and I was thinking about buying an Import 360 to play Japanese games, but then I actually looked at what Japanese games come out over there that I would be interested in, and there's like three, and I'm like, no, not worth it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Earth Defense Force was one of those, and I was like, oh yeah, I forgot about Earth Defense Force.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, not really, but I had to play it some more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, and then finally I played, um, Tatsunoko vs. Capcom, and yes, it is an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, it actually is a game that makes me excited about fighting games again, um, because it plays, I mean, I'm not really one to talk about fighting games because I don't play enough of them, and
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, here's my question about Tatsunoko vs. Capcom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because from my perspective, I don't know much about the Tatsunoko universe.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is it that makes this game so fun?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I'm kind of surprised that you guys are giving it such glowing reviews.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I kind of expected this game to just be like a...
[SPEAKER_07]: Slap the characters on it and run with it type thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Instant cash cow.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you guys both are enjoying this.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of surprising me.
[SPEAKER_05]: For me, it's a little bit simpler to play because it doesn't have all the kick and punch buttons.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now it's all just light, medium, heavy attack buttons.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then you have one button to switch characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: But...
[SPEAKER_05]: It seems a lot easier for me to play, and then also, it just kind of feels like Marvel vs. Capcom, which I love that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, the characters, you know, I don't know who have to... I mean, I recognize some of them from the titles of their series and stuff, but, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know who any of them are.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't watched the series and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I just know a few of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I do think that the character choices are a bit sparse because it's like one per game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have, you know, going there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Street Fighter wise, you know, from Street Fighter 2, you have Ryu and Cheng Li and that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then for Street Fighter 3 they have like one character from that and one character from Darkstalkers so it's very very limited in that sense but I mean there are quite a few characters I think there's like 32 altogether or something like that but it just seems kind of sparse in that sense but it's just fun I don't know and just the presentation of it's really fluid it's really smooth it plays well on the Wii which is saying much um
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty much why.
[SPEAKER_07]: A comment from ShadowCharlie in chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: What would make it more interesting is that it comes to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any hopes for this game coming to the U.S.?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's not going to happen because of the licensing of the Tatsuno characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: What I'd like to see is if they couldn't bring it over here, then do maybe another Marvel vs. Capcom or do Capcom vs. something else and use the same engine and just do new characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Reskin the characters?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_02]: Capcom vs. Mr. T?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they're all 3D this time, which is kind of neat, because it's Marvel vs. Capcom, but it is 3D.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's like Street Fighter 4 3D, where it's 3D but 2D type thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I don't know, maybe pick another anime character.
[SPEAKER_05]: All ADV and Pioneer are redistributors.
[SPEAKER_01]: The thing is that none of these companies really have American licenses.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then fine!
[SPEAKER_05]: Disney vs. Capcom!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that'd really happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft suggests Cartoon Network versus Capcom.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would actually, though, be the closest thing we could actually get to some sort of animated series on TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nickelodeon versus Capcom.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, Warner Brothers versus Capcom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, the Animaniacs would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about just Capcom versus Capcom?
[SPEAKER_02]: Freakazoid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody said that in chat, just as I said that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Capcom versus Capcom.
[SPEAKER_05]: They already have that, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't remember what it's called now.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, actually, that was a game that was scrapped.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they had... It was a Capcom... It was a fighting game they even ported to the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like a mega mix of characters from all these different Capcom games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not sure how to pronounce this name.
[SPEAKER_07]: Leo Shen, I think, or Leo Xen?
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably Leo Shen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Leo Shen says, your mom versus Capcom.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what Sauce said.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, so it sounds like you guys have been having fun with this game one way or another.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it... Yeah, studio... Yeah, I...
[SPEAKER_05]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just it's probably not going to come out over here, which is unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they could still use the engine for something else.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's what I think they should do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Frisbee says, Capcom versus the world.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they could do another like Street Fighter versus Capcom thing, but just make a sequel to that or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they can just use their own characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Capcom Fighting Evolution was the one I was thinking of.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nando in chat says, Harpo Productions versus Capcom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you imagine that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oprah versus Capcom.
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Grand Theft Auto 4 on PC and it's still it's weird because I tried upgrading the RAM on my PC to 4 gigs even though Windows can only see like 2 of it but I was going to do it anyways and I had a bad run with bad RAM from Fry's apparently Fry's they keep taking back my defective RAM as just a stock return and so they have like 4 that they keep swapping out
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though it's defective.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I stopped buying RAM there because it's pointless and it would have been too much of a pain in the ass to see it on my computer.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that being said, I haven't really been playing too much of Grand Theft Auto 4 since it's still kind of buggy even though they patched it a little bit to fix some stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't support SLI yet and that kind of pisses me off because I spent the money for an extra video card.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want the games to fucking see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I mean, come on, it's like a standard nowadays.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just lazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn lazy is what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well if that's it for your gaming week, then my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of a lot of the same usual stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've obviously been playing a lot of The Wrath of the Lich King.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have done a big, big thing in WoW this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I respect, for a long-term basis, because we're so short on healers, just on the server in general, not just our guild, but the server.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm no longer a boomkin.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I checked out Meteos Wars.
[SPEAKER_07]: I only checked out the demo, so I don't want to really review a full game based strictly off the demo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Graphics were a little minimalist in the stage I played.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, it's a fairly faithful translation.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was wondering how you would have the speed of the stylus in a game like Meteos Wars, but the way they did it was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Instead of sliding the pieces up and down, you use triangle to move a piece up a row really fast, and you use, what, X?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, triangles would be a PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, X.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what you'd really call that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I grew up in a day where it was all 2D.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mario Bros., Super Mario World, and all this, and even the old school Prince of Persia is 2D.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's taken me a long time to really get used to 3D.
[SPEAKER_07]: I even still have problems with Mario 64, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: But the thing I like about Prince of Persia is that they've done things in this game that make it really accessible to noobs, because the game really holds your hand for a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: and what I also like about it is that even if you fall off a cliff, you don't really die you have the chick as a crutch to kind of save you and I think a lot of hardcore gamers have been really turned off by that but for me, I've kind of appreciated it and it's kind of made me want to continue to play because I don't lose massive amounts of time because I don't know how to turn the freaking camera and that's what Tigerclaw says Sky, what about the fact that you cannot die in the game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: and I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Progress still feels a lot like challenge to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to collect things and you don't have to collect everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: You get light seeds and you don't have to collect them all to progress to new areas but you get a sense of accomplishment for collecting them all.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they've done other little things with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Achievements are really, really easy, though, too, I noticed.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least, or the trophies or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I noticed I unlocked a silver trophy real easy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't have to do hardly anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, that was pretty much it for new games I played this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm hoping I'll probably actually play Prince of Persia a lot more, try to play it through to completion.
[SPEAKER_07]: They thought it was a Final Fantasy game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm like, no, there's no, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to ask you, did you try out Home?
[SPEAKER_07]: Did I try what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Home.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, home is one of those things that I think it was a really great idea, but this execution that we're seeing of it is kind of not that great.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, God, if you think Xbox Live is bad, the minute I logged into home, I just started hearing every naughty word in the book.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, just everything you'd hear on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I didn't even know that you could use microphones on Sony Home, but apparently you can.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, yeah, you know, it's like, and again, it was also one of those things where it kind of caused, you know, the non-game playing people who come through this house to kind of look at the TV and go, what is this?
[SPEAKER_07]: This looks kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, they were watching me in the bowling alley, like, and you know, all the stuff in the bowling alley is really stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I tried playing one of the games in there, which was basically an overdone version of Breakout, you know, like just a redone version of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's all free, you have to remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can't expect that it's going to be anything that great, because they're going to nickel and dime you, like they're trying to do with the costumes and everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: This all being said, I do think there's potential here for something cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think there is networking potential within home.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kind of excited for the clubhouses to come out because I would like for us to have an OLR clubhouse where we could boot idiots and things like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we could have a lot of fun with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's my thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right now, it's...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just this clusterfuck of strangeness.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, honestly, it's what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how else to explain it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think it's fair for them to be advertising this as a feature of the PlayStation 3 since it is only in beta right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, they've been having it in commercials since, what, last year?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I think that's kind of unfair.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will answer that question, but let me address this because I got a private message.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is home?
[SPEAKER_07]: For those of us that aren't as familiar with this, basically home is like a virtual world.
[SPEAKER_07]: These types of things were especially big back in the late 90s and then kind of caught a second wind with Second Life.
[SPEAKER_07]: But when the whole virtual reality thing first came out, they used to have these chat programs where you could be like a little virtual avatar and you walk around a virtual world.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Second Life kind of really took that to the next level on the PCs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, this is kind of Sony's version of Second Life where you create a little version of yourself.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, you can think of me, I guess, but it's a lot more realistic.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you literally, using your controllers, walk around an open area where there's other people dancing or talking or interacting with each other.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then you can go into like a bowling alley and you can walk up to a bowling machine if they're not all full, which they usually are.
[SPEAKER_07]: and play bowling with other people and interact with them that way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or you could walk up to an arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's kind of like, you know, it's like a virtual life.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's kind of like a game, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if that makes any sense at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's their idea to try a new networking thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: VXChaseNextV in chat says, Second life is a construct.
[SPEAKER_07]: Home is a construct.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so now what was your question?
[SPEAKER_07]: Home, is it fair to advertise it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's obvious that Sony wanted to do a lot more with this.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not implemented yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not sure what's taken them so long.
[SPEAKER_07]: But maybe it's just like, again, it's one of those things where the ideas are coming faster than the reality of being able to program it in.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, technically, yeah, they can advertise it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would equate it to when they advertise video games with nothing but the cutscenes from the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's in beta.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not even done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't Gmail still in beta?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but it's functional.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would say it's close to being functional, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'd be like putting out a demo of a game or something like that and then advertising that in a commercial for the PlayStation or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, play Killzone 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, except it's not out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a demo or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, it's a little misleading.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not that anyone really gives a crap about their commercials, since I think the sales numbers speak for themselves, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just think it's kind of misleading.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think there's potential in Home, but it has yet to be unlocked.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, the only other thing I want to say about Home is that it's a little confusing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, the things about the Xbox, especially the Nintendo one...
[SPEAKER_07]: Those are very easy to just kind of pop into and go, and obviously neither system has done something as ambitious as Home, but Home's kind of complicated.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, it took me a minute to really kind of work through the menus and everything, and it really is, it's even more tough when not everything's available yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the other kind of bummer about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Jason wants to correct that Gmail is no longer in beta.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gmail is official.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gmail Labs is beta add-ons.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: SSJ100Matt says, it's like calling Windows 3.1.1 a game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Home isn't really a game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like folding at home is not really a game either.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a simulation.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's a thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I guess you could say it's a simulation.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, let's get into some gaming news after we talk about some housekeeping real quick, of which we don't have a whole lot of tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just, you know, always check us out on MySpace at Orange Launch Radio or Facebook at the OL Army.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our Twitter is OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're also on LiveJournal, Community Orange Lounge, and we always try to keep you up to date on the latest and greatest.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although, it's been kind of a busy past few months, so a lot of our internet presence has really slowed down, so sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we're still trying to keep it going with the show and do what we always do, and hopefully 2009 will be a little better.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe it'll be warmer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, also, one thing you gotta see in home is that when you go into the theater, you just get to see an extended Twilight trailer playing on the screen over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't seen it, nor probably will I. It's very Mystery Science 3000-able.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the type of stuff they should be using home for.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, that's why I say there's potential there.
[SPEAKER_07]: That doesn't necessarily mean Sony's gonna ever unlock it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's potential.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get into some gaming news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Start us off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of Sony, Sony has been seeing some hard times, and they're actually cutting plants and with that slashing 8,000 jobs.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is all supposed to happen between now and April of 2010, and Sony will cut about 5% of their electronics divisions and close a tenth of its manufacturing sites.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not good, especially in this tough economy.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it just because PS3s haven't been selling well?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or is it that now they don't need these people because the PS3 is already out?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's just because they haven't been selling well.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's no need to have these extra plants producing more systems if they're not selling out.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not having an issue with selling out at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although,
[SPEAKER_05]: They are at times hard to find just because they keep phasing out SKUs left and right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: This year alone there's been four different SKUs for the PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that's kind of crazy right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's four new SKUs and that's not even including the ones that we came in this year with.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is kind of related, but it kind of goes back to what we were talking about with Home.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really want to read this comment because it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Frisbee says in chat,
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of strange.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: But see, that's kind of cool with the whole BD Live thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow, what an interesting movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's really the only word I can use to describe it as interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Certain people are kind of dicks.
[SPEAKER_07]: The drama is still playing out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, how far do I want to get into this on the show?
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially when we were just talking about something completely different, and I apologize.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's very sad that people lost their jobs, but unfortunately we don't know much more than that at this time about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So here we are on this whole other subject.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: You gotta kind of wonder, like with this movie, how biased is it trying to be?
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm not trying to say that Billy Mitchell is not likely the pompous ass he made himself to be in the movie, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's something about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something about the fact that they had all these cameras in just the right places at just the right times when all these things were going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's something about it that says there's some type of...
[SPEAKER_07]: Editing stuff going on here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then at the same time, I know a lot of our folks listen to the other shows on All Games and you've probably heard all this crap about the Twin Galaxies and Mr. Awesome's been on All Games off and on throughout the years and all this crap going on with Twin Galaxies.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just kind of goes to show you this drama has been going on for years and is continuing even still today.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not just with Donkey Kong, but with the official scores in general.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's just kind of...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, he's like, well, not the Steve Wiebe guy that seems, you know, pretty cool or whatever, and his family's pretty funny, but most of the people in the movie are very sad individuals, like Billy and his lackeys and, you know, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm kind of like, well... But Billy Mitchell actually owns his own business and, you know, makes his... I'm saying he's still an ass, but, you know, but he's a successful businessman.
[SPEAKER_07]: The King of Kong was a very good movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: He sent the tape in and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a camera at his house when he sends in the tape.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a camera there.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a camera with Grandma at the airport.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kind of like, this seems all way too pre-planned for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was the only problem I had with the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: This documentary was really well done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, almost too well done.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I also didn't see him as being...
[SPEAKER_02]: Very, uh, excuse me, being rather pompous enough to want to tape everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's the thing, here's what I was going to say, and this is what I was kind of going to tell my roommate about too.
[SPEAKER_07]: You see these kind of pompous asses in lots of sports.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, you ever watch some of these football press conferences or wrestling or boxing?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, some of us cheer on these pompous assholes in wrestling, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, in a way, I don't hate the guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: He did come off like a pompous ass in the movie, but maybe there's more to him than that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then you look at some of these side stories going on like the whole Mr. Awesome Missile Command I never realized and keep in mind I've been watching this whole thing play out on all games I never realized that he had the direct impact on that movie by sending the guy the Donkey Kong board that he did and just to kind of see like literally I was just kind of like wow a lot of this makes sense now what I've been hearing on all games like damn these people and their drama overscores but I don't know
[SPEAKER_07]: All they've got.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't fault them for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think they're sad people.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's what they're into.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It hurts my head to think about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It almost makes you wonder, it's like, okay, so say you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know who I blame even more to?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the fucking Guinness Book of World Records, because they're not helping things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now putting out this stupid gaming book and stuff, they're just egging it on.
[SPEAKER_05]: And not only that, but they have stupid records in there, like people that claim to have the highest score in DDR, a game that I don't think you can have a high score in.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, so subjective
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: and you know I understand you know I understand why people get all into it because like you know I think one guy who was like a friend of Steve Levy or something said it said it best in the movie this guy my friend Steve is the best in the world at something in the entire world and true it might be Donkey Kong but he's the best in the world
[SPEAKER_07]: I can see why people get so passionate over that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you see him play through the kill screen?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've seen a kill screen once.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was little.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: A total tangent that took up more time than the... It's a cool tangent.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's gaming and not food.
[SPEAKER_07]: Much sadder story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of food though, I ate at Olive Garden today.
[SPEAKER_07]: Home of the NeverEnding Breadsticks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry I didn't invite you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a last minute thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that's the first time I've had it since the surgery.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bad tangent, especially following a story about such horrible layoffs as Sony.
[SPEAKER_07]: But unfortunately, we don't have a lot more to tell you there.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, let's talk about sales, and maybe this might help explain kind of the Sony layoffs and so on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of the November numbers from MPD are in, talking about the sales.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the Wii in November sold 2.04 million units, probably no one's surprised.
[SPEAKER_07]: The DS in second place, 1.57 million units.
[SPEAKER_07]: Xbox 360, 836K.
[SPEAKER_07]: PSP 421k PS3 378k Playstation 2 is finally in last place 206k so this might finally be the PS2 kind of walking out the door here but it's kind of strange that the PS3 you know is the PS2 is definitely on it's way out it's not I'd say maybe by the end of next year because I mean looking just at what the releases are like for example in February
[SPEAKER_05]: There are three games coming out for the PS2, and that is it.
[SPEAKER_05]: In January, I think two or three also coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's getting a lot less...
[SPEAKER_05]: FloatwalkinChat says people buy PSP still?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, because it isn't just a game system, but it's the whole movies and internet and MP3s in your pocket.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they are released.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sadly enough, a lot of the publishers are just not making PSP games anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: The amount of games coming out is really sad, and it's not a good sign.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why do you think everyone jumped ship suddenly?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't imagine Zahar the program for it, but they don't sell very well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Their versions aren't very good.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't have the install base for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: People are playing DSs more.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a lot of good PSP games, it's just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I wonder if the Final Fantasy VII remake that people always have big boners talking about on the PlayStation 3, like, you know, big fangasm, you know, talking about they want it to happen on PlayStation 3, I wonder if they wouldn't do something like that for PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't think it'd be very good.
[SPEAKER_05]: They could bring the, like, Final Fantasy VII, maybe redo some of the graphics a little bit, and...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: which, you know, kind of contradicts that story we had a couple weeks ago that wasn't selling very well because it was the 10th best-selling game in November.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe it didn't hit the millions and millions expectations, but the 10th best-selling game out of everything that's out there, that's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, and then also I think the last report we saw for the MPD numbers, it was only out for like a week, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can probably have explanations for most of these.
[SPEAKER_07]: Number 9 was Resistance 2 on the PlayStation 3, which is PS3's one of their big titles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Number 8 was Left 4 Dead on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really need to pick that game up.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game's been performing above expectations, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Number 7 was Guitar Hero World Tour on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Call of Duty World of War on the PS3 Mario Kart on the Wii
[SPEAKER_05]: Number four, Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also another thing that's very short and hard to find.
[SPEAKER_05]: Number three, Wii Play with the remote.
[SPEAKER_05]: If people just sell that like a remote, hey, you get a $10 game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then that's got to be why this game is still topping the charts.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: It's got to be it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Number two, Call of Duty World of War, the 360 version.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then number one would be Gears of War 2 on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I should point out, if you add up the two Call of Duty World of Wars across 360 and PS3, that would be number one, not Gears of War 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Gears of War 2 being Xbox 360 exclusive only has the one system to consider.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, just an interesting list.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your November NPD numbers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, for people like me who have an iPhone, there is some fun out there, although I've been hearing mixed reviews on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is I Love Katamari, which is actually I Love Katamari on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's $7.99, and you can either play it on the iPhone or the iPod Touch.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's 82 meg, has a story, time attack, eternal and exact size.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it apparently suffers really bad from the iPhone's poor frame rate for games but I figured I might download it eventually.
[SPEAKER_02]: The last game I actually paid for was Pole Position.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to check it out, but then I read the reviews, and they all were bitching about the frame rate, and I was like, okay, maybe this isn't so cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but that's just iPhone games anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: You look at any review on an iPhone game, they're going to talk about the frame rate unless it's something, you know, dinky like Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or Labyrinth, which is what I play all the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't matter, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I don't think...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's like bitching about the framerate on any system.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't see that that's a reason to even put out a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then, oh, I can't get the framerate up where I need to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then you can't release the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: That means you can't get it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to make some sort of missions for...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know whether it be like you just use cell shading, really flat textures so that the size of the textures isn't really big and so it's able to render it faster, or I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're trying to push the iPhone as this big gaming platform, and yeah, unfortunately to me that's almost like pushing the N-Gage as a big gaming platform.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: First of all, games look a bajillion times better on the iPhone than they did on the N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I had a great gaming taco.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand this.
[SPEAKER_02]: On top of that, there's so much more functionality with the iPhone that comparing it to that waste of electronics that was the N-Gage is seriously like comparing...
[SPEAKER_02]: I would have to say a Blackberry with one of those old car phones that you had to attach to your cigarette lighter and was the size of your head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's my thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're trying to be a gaming platform.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what they keep saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're one of the best gaming platforms out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how they can claim that, but they are.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's funny, if Nintendo had almost taken the same idea and just done almost like what XNA is doing and opened that up to people to release apps for the DS, can you imagine how much money they'd make?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's the same thing there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't even really call them a gaming platform anyways because for me, a game console is something that you can actually buy games for, not necessarily just digital downloads.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know that's the future of stuff, but
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just not seeing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's more casual.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it's ever going to take the place of a handheld game system.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to read this comment real quick from AlphaCananagram in chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love Katamari in its current build.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the worst eight bucks I've spent.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's neat but slow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Listener review of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so some other cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: We talked about this a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, Home has finally made its way out, or at least the beta of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is a 77 meg download.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, you do need to have, I believe, three gigs dedicated to...
[SPEAKER_05]: to this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, when you start it up, it says that you have to dedicate three gigs of your drive to the game, and it says okay, and then you basically, it partitions off a part of the drive for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what it's doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It reserves part of the drive.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's because you're downloading new areas as you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can go in there and download new stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not sure what it's all used for.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if it's caching data or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's storage of the actual areas and stuff like that, probably the videos.
[SPEAKER_07]: The areas aren't that
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe it was so that you don't download stuff you don't need, but I just figured the three gigs was some type of cache information.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's probably so that their servers don't crash from everybody downloading it all at once, and that way it saves them a little bit of time, and that way every time it goes in there, it checks to see if there's any updates to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of like, remember how AOL was?
[SPEAKER_05]: How you'd go to different pages and you'd download updates?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it is available right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, there are issues, and obviously...
[SPEAKER_05]: They've been having trouble with it staying online and they've had to actually shut down the PlayStation Network for about an hour to fix stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so it's definitely acting like it was in beta.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's available to check out and it's been a long time coming.
[SPEAKER_07]: Weren't they having a lot of issues on launch day with the downloads?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I heard, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, I got in there very easily, but I didn't remember it was out until like late in the evening.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I'd been watching a movie and I was like, oh yeah, I want to download Home.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm not going to try it for a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just haven't gotten, I'm not really gung-ho to jump into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just kind of, eh.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is like the avatars for me, you know, just like on the new Xbox experience or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was kind of neat, made my avatar, that's it, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Question from chatroom, Tigerclaw asks, Interesting, does it let you walk around the world?
[SPEAKER_07]: Does it download in the backgrounds and stuff?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of annoying when you're walking in an environment that appears empty and then about a minute later everything suddenly appears and you appear to have run into a wall.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it doesn't do that with the environments.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why you have to download everything before you go in.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it doesn't actually download the environment as you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: What will download as you go, like the movie that's playing in the movie theater, like the Twilight trailer or whatever...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: But, I don't know, there's really not a lot of point to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, see, but remember when Home was going to let me show whatever movie I wanted to on my screen in my home?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, remember that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: We were supposed to have that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, that would have been cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I think they got rid of that because of, you know, licensing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, because you'd think people would put up, you know, porn and what have you, but... No, I think they weren't even caring about porn.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were caring about people putting up, like, say... Okay, so copyrighted porn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, but imagine if we could have had an OLR clubhouse and we could have shot, like, some video just for fun, you know, that could loop in the clubhouse or something that we could have had in there just for fun and, like, change it out once a week or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, that would be great, and that's potential, but I just know that's not going to happen for years.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, is that something, like, kind of like, um... What is it, uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have to be logged into your account or something like that for someone to be able to jump into your clubhouse?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know because clubs aren't available yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you're going to have to pay for them when they do come out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if it's just a small fee, I don't mind paying it just to kind of screw around with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I think there's potential to kind of have the community there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we're all about community here at OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I want to know a little more about what...
[SPEAKER_07]: You can actually do with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it seems like it's going to be a little limiting.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I don't know if I would have to be on or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the PS3 is also one of those systems you can kind of just leave on.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't make any noise or nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you could hook up a PS3 in here and then broadcast our show into that clubhouse and have us on the TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I was thinking!
[SPEAKER_07]: Wouldn't that be an awesome potential?
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, if we could actually, because if you can talk through your headset, then that thing supports streaming audio, and I'm sure there would be a way that during the duration of the show we could just shut everyone else up.
[SPEAKER_07]: We shouldn't be giving away all our ideas.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other podcasts are going to steal them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wouldn't be the first time.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, that's kind of like the idea I would want to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, there's potential there, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jason says, you can create a club in home and it'll cost $5.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you actually do that now?
[SPEAKER_07]: When I tried to look at it, you couldn't do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did they actually open that up and I just couldn't figure it out?
[SPEAKER_07]: TigerClaw says, this is why Second Life does it better.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can actually create a club, invite people to come over, and the club will actually play music in the background by streaming a shoutcast stream into it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe we should have put a thing in Second Life a long time ago, but it was kind of expensive, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Second Life.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to touch that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like dirty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Home's not much better then.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's not much better, but it's like the new gas station bathroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a brand new gas station.
[SPEAKER_05]: The bathroom hasn't quite gotten all disease ridden yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's talk about other PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: What could have been, and according to 1Up, apparently what happened, Final Fantasy XI, you know, kind of interesting that it came out on the Xbox 360, but it never really came out on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, true, you could do the PS2 backwards compatibility, but even then...
[SPEAKER_07]: Sometimes the hard drive issues will kind of get in the way, I think, depending on what system you owned, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then you can download a patch that would allow you to play it from the PS2 version on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: But at some point they were going to release, I guess, a nicer version, I guess you could say, on the PlayStation 3, probably one with all the expansions included and what have you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, apparently it was supposed to happen, but apparently the Sony representative that Square was working with
[SPEAKER_07]: They were working with Hiromichi Tanaka, I guess, just quit.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they never really resumed talks, which is kind of strange.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh well, Final Fantasy XI is still getting three new expansions next year, but not through the traditional retail channels.
[SPEAKER_07]: They will all be downloadable story expansions.
[SPEAKER_07]: No new classes, none of that stuff, just story and quest expansions, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I assume zone expansions too.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yep, Final Fantasy XI on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was an idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you wondered why it wasn't there, somebody else must have been thinking the same thing, but then they just gave up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they didn't care like some of us.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kind of over Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're in another addiction now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I have WoW now.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I would like to revisit Final Fantasy XI someday when it gets redone and has a new, like Final Fantasy XI 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: They did X-2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why can't they do X-11 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they have good taste sometimes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, shush.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, here's something that should excite a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know there's a lot of our listeners out there who are fans of Fallout 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, for the PC, Bethesda actually brought out a PC tool set for Fallout 3 so that you can...
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess create your own levels.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can modify and edit buildings, landscapes, dialogue characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, you can just change it all up into your own game pretty much.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki's not all over this.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was called the Garden of Eden Creation Kit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really mod games anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wait for other people to mod them and then add to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can download it off of the Fallout 3 website.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's 8.47 megabytes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want someone to do the wondrous thing that someone has done with the Half-Life editor and make me a Hypercube version of Fallout 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would like to see one where the world ended because of something Jamie did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make a Maniac Mansion!
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, you totally could.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, actually, I was going to say, other than all the cool stuff for Half-Life, Grand Theft Auto 4, they have some of the first mods out there for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, the game actually doesn't allow you to run files that are modified, but someone's found a way around it, like it was cake or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they've made pistols that fire rockets, which are pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then also pistols and machine guns that have...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: is some brand new download content, and that'll be coming soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's kind of neat about the download content, though, is they're going to be raising the level cap on it, and you'll actually be able to... I don't know what level they're going to raise it to, but I know right now it's pretty limited.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's like 30 or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fightin' Alaska Fightin' Alaska Fightin' Alaska
[SPEAKER_05]: 4-5 hours long, 800 Microsoft Points
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, well, shifting gears here a little bit, talking about a different type of quest.
[SPEAKER_07]: I promised there'd be a story on WoW tonight, and it's not really the type of story you might be expecting.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually something game politics ran, so you know it's going to involve controversy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something political.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has to do with World of Warcraft, and they are actually re-re-re-
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a quest where you basically torture a prisoner to get information out of him to move on.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is what Richard Bartell said about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, you have to take some type of cowpoke and zap a prisoner until he talks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not at all happy with this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was expecting for there to be some way to tell the guy who gave you the quest that no, actually, I don't want to torture a prisoner, but there didn't seem to be any way to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Worse, the quest is part of a chain you need to complete to gain access to the Nexus, which is the first instance you encounter if you start at the west of the continent as I did.
[SPEAKER_07]: So either you play along and zap the guy or you don't get to go to the Nexus.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a game!
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm kind of, I'm just kind of a little bit in disbelief because it's like, well, A, he's completely misstating the thing about you have to do this quest to enter the Nexus.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not true.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can enter the Nexus whenever, you know, you can get summoned there.
[SPEAKER_07]: You just don't get the quest line or what have you.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you don't, I mean, there's like 50,000 quests now and I'm obviously overstating that.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's lots and lots of quests in Wrath of the Lich King.
[SPEAKER_07]: Trust me, you can level your character to 80 and only play through like 4 of the zones.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's like 7 or 8 zones.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you could skip this all together.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could start on the East Continent or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyway, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even if you couldn't skip this and it was a part of the game, I mean, do you write angry letters every time you watch an episode of 24 and he tortures a prisoner?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or every time you watch a movie?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or every time somebody wrote a torture scene in a mud game somewhere on the internet, which I'm sure exists somewhere?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, hello?
[SPEAKER_07]: What is it we always say here that you started here, Jay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Learn to be offended!
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fucking people.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's just a game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, if you want to, you just go to the quest and you click Abandoned Quest and there, you don't have to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: How hard was that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, the kind of ignorance stated here, even if this guy is a big deal for what he did, it was kind of a silly thing to state here.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, I'm just going to do the angsty FUs part of the show right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care if this is political.
[SPEAKER_02]: A big blaming fuck you to George Bush.
[SPEAKER_02]: For all of the series of legislation he's just passed during his last blessed day, you know, the end of his, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also for passing a law that pretty much lets any doctor not perform any kind of procedure based on moral, personal ethics, not necessarily the overall ethics of the community that they represent.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it's really disgusting a lot of it is from as far as I could tell unconstitutional and I'm sure quite a bit of it can be overturned under congressional review which is the one good thing that Newt Gingrich ever did apart from being hilarious on TV
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say F you to
[SPEAKER_05]: Take 2 for putting out a crappy version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I should say a buggy version of Grand Theft Auto 4 on the PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: The fact that I've got to still wait for patches before they support something that most modern games support now is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, I just hate having to wait before a game to work correctly.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I'm spending the money to buy the game, why does it have to be weeks later that I get a game that actually works?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_07]: My F.U.
[SPEAKER_07]: of the week goes to potstickers because they're really addicting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just can't stop eating potstickers.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like the food I've been craving.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anytime I go out to a restaurant that might have them, I have to get potstickers because they're so freaking addicting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I feel like I'm pregnant or something and craving things I don't usually crave before.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that food is potstickers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, it's so random, but that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're growing a gas baby.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_07]: So F you to potstickers for being so non-malicious.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I've learned you can get potstickers lots of different places.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty surprising, and I've probably sampled them everywhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, hey, let's move back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's try to get this show actually back on the track of gaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dragon Quest X is going to be on Wii
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's also going to be, as far as I'm aware, the first of the Dragon Quest games on the Wii, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the Japanese release date, by the way, for Dragon Quest IX is going to be March 28th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's going to be 5980 yen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other cool stuff that will be...
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, now, apparently, a used copy of the game Scrabble, which apparently learns words based on stuff that you add in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: This kid actually was playing it, and apparently Scrabble beat him on a triple word score with the word fuckers.
[SPEAKER_05]: and apparently the mother of... That's what I call my DS when it beats me at a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fucker!
[SPEAKER_05]: The mother, I guess, apparently, Tonya, she had bought this game for her son, Ethan, and it was a pre-owned copy, I guess, of Ubisoft Scrabble, which I didn't realize... I don't think they have that over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish they did, because Scrabble's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: DS Over His Shoulder
[SPEAKER_07]: How else did she find out about it?
[SPEAKER_05]: So apparently, you know, this, you know, is coming from, I guess... You know what she should have done is simply challenged the word.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I don't think you'd be able to find it in the official Scrabble dictionary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, apparently, this is coming from a tabloid, Daily Mail.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, they're hosts of a bunch of useless articles.
[SPEAKER_01]: So reliable?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ubisoft is saying that she should have used the game's junior settings, because I guess Fuckers isn't in the junior version of Scrabble, and Nintendo, of course, doesn't want anything to do with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why we'll just use, you know, Lil' Fucker.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_05]: J100 Matt in chat says, why do these fucking kids need to tell their parents that their games are cursing at them?
[SPEAKER_05]: I would laugh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would think that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would show it to my friends.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what you're supposed to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at my boy, dude.
[SPEAKER_05]: He spelled tits on triple word.
[SPEAKER_05]: Instead of little Ethan going, Mommy, Mommy, my game swore at me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm telling.
[SPEAKER_05]: Little punk kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think there's actually a version of Scrabble.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you want to know, she's totally grooming him to be a little wuss anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: Him and his pink DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, here.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, there's some type of Scrabbles.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know how every board game has their own house rules?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like in Monopoly, you might have a house rule where all the tax money goes into a free parking jackpot for when you land on free parking, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I think there's some house rules for Scrabbles where dirty words automatically are triple word score.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it encourages people to use bad words.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, we do that all the time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_05]: We even played Ebonics Scrabble one time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: If it sounded like a word, it was a word.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd like to play that sometime.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_07]: One game I was mad when they discontinued many years ago and made me yell, Fuckers, was when they got rid of the Great Giana Sisters.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1987 was the year that this game was originally released, and it was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was on the Commodore 64, but the problem was, it looked and felt just like Mario.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although, if you actually played it, there was a lot of differences.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, for instance, hello, in the Great Giana Sisters, you actually fight a giant enemy crab at the end of the second level.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, this predates even the PlayStation 3, but unfortunately...
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to have over 80 levels, and apparently the DS microphone is going to play into the game somehow, and they'll actually use the touchscreen and everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, one of the great things about the original game was the soundtrack, and the new version, Chris Hilsbeck, is coming back to do remixed versions of the original soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is one of those games where, you know, if you've never played this game, maybe some week we'll highlight it as a classic game of the week down the road.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's one of those games you definitely should check out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure there's clips on YouTube of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And just, you know, you can see its similarities to Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a fun game, especially for that era.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it doesn't really hold up against today's games, which is why I'm interested to see kind of what they do to it on the...
[SPEAKER_07]: DS version, how they're going to make it unique.
[SPEAKER_07]: But based on the screenshots, it looks a lot different.
[SPEAKER_07]: It definitely doesn't look like Mario anymore, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, moving forward, it looks like we've actually got some release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: How does that sound?
[SPEAKER_07]: Release dates!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it is December, so what else can we expect?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me go ahead and take a look.
[SPEAKER_07]: For the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly, for the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, it's Crash Commando and Sonic Unleashed.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's really it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to be a little bit more excited, but I guess not.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't say things are much better in the US, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are a few things coming out, so it's not that bad, but it's certainly not in November or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: This week, though, some of the highlights.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rise of the Argonauts will be coming out on all systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, this week, we've got the release of some DS games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kate West, The Vanishing Files...
[SPEAKER_05]: We've also got Mystery PI, Portrait of a Thief
[SPEAKER_05]: and Dreamer Horse Training.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, goddammit, there's not enough horse training games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Puppy Training, which has a really cute cover.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Slingo Quest, also coming out from DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a mumbo-jumbo casual game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Neopets Puzzle Adventure, ripping off Puzzle Quest there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And let's see...
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of crappy DS games this week, man, I swear.
[SPEAKER_05]: Australia Zoo Quest, which is a puzzle game and for some reason has Saberwin on the cover.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, crikey indeed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Learn Math for grades 1 through 4, a math learning game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Driver's Ed Portable on DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, you can learn how to drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: and other things other than DS games.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a few Destiny or Wii games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Summer Sports 2, Island Sports Party, their party game, and Wurjong Party.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a Mahjong party game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Rock Band 2 on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game-only version will be coming out on the 18th.
[SPEAKER_05]: and, uh, I just gotta mention this on the 19th, Calvin Tucker's Redneck Jamboree.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, goody.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you know, if you want a busy week for game releases, you need to look at Japan, because there's tons of stuff coming out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, granted, a lot of it is localized versions of stuff we've already had here in the US, but let me talk about what's coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Starting with 360, we have just that.
[SPEAKER_07]: A big release for Japan would be Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: The localized version is coming out this week, December 18th.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lego Batman, Need for Speed Undercover, and Prince of Persia also all being released on the 360 in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also a game local for Japan, Gundam Musou 2 comes out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this game is a shooter that looks to be probably based on Gundam.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep, robots with guns.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dynasty Warriors Gundam 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game is coming on the Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on to the PlayStation 3, many of those same titles.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's also Gundam Musou 2 comes out there as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lego Batman, Medal of Honor gets a price drop, as does the Godfather and Armored Core.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what you've got to look forward to on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although I do want to point out there's also a wireless keypad available now in Japan if you want to check that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, on the Wii, they have a game called Let's Tap.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's coming out from Sega in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the one where it's the game that penguins can play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: A game that even penguins can play.
[SPEAKER_05]: You set the Wiimote on the box and you tap the box.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't actually use the controller at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's all these little visualizers and things.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're bringing that over here, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Bleach vs. Crusade Dance Dance Revolution Furu Furu Party Elebits Price Reduction
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, going on the PlayStation 2, a little game called Beatmania 2DX gets its 15th game in the series on PlayStation 2 this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Troopers comes out on December 18th.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not the 15th game on the PlayStation, however, because they didn't start with... They started on 3rd style.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this would be the 12th game on the PlayStation 2 in the 2DX series.
[SPEAKER_07]: In Japan only, that's not even counting the one we got in the U.S.,
[SPEAKER_07]: Fate Unlimited Codes is also coming out on the Playstation 2 as well as another version of Gundam Musou 2 for the Playstation 2 and Pachinko Series Volume 13 Neon Genesis Evangelion yet another one
[SPEAKER_01]: Princess Ballerina
[SPEAKER_07]: Yumei Miru, 4Gen, no, Primadonna.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't you like Primadonnas?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, but I'm watching Bush get a shoe thrown at him and that's pretty fucking funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Top it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lego Batman also comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gensu Suikoden Tier Kreese comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be the Suikoden's strategical title.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's a busy week in DS world.
[SPEAKER_07]: And as far as the PSP goes, all the other systems are getting love.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why not the PSP?
[SPEAKER_07]: And yes, Final Fantasy Dissida.
[SPEAKER_07]: Star Wars The Clone Wars
[SPEAKER_07]: Need for Speed Undercover, Samurai Shodown Anthology, Ultimate Board Game Collection, all on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very busy week in Japan for releases.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's move on with more news.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then we're going to take a quick break here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there is a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_02]: This actually has to do with some...
[SPEAKER_02]: with something having to do with Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I think it already happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a social club event put out by Rockstar for Midnight Club Los Angeles and Grand Theft Auto 4 that was going on Xbox Live and PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were supposed to have a little contest as in a video editor contest for GTA 4 PC and
[SPEAKER_02]: and then for topping the Midnight Club Ocean to LA time trial and there were supposed to be prizes available for both.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was though already going on and I do believe it was from 5 to 9 UK time actually I think today so already gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good luck to whoever won.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: um some other fun stuff um prototype um you may remember this game being kind of like an open world uh crackdown meets you know kind of mutants type of thing um
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: And there was all sorts of different gameplay videos and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, that was supposed to be stuff that they were showing off at CES.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, you know, a few, I guess a day later or so, the whole was covered back up and the countdown back to CES was put back on the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the funny thing is about all that, that's what they want you to think, you see.
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole...
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole leak was a hoax, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Perpetrated... Do people know that?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Perpetrated by... So wait, you're saying the game blogs all got punk this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, they all got punk this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Perpetrated by their marketing team.
[SPEAKER_07]: And how do you know this?
[SPEAKER_05]: You're making this up.
[SPEAKER_05]: You make this shit up.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't make this shit up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know this because they sent out an email boasting about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's all a ruse.
[SPEAKER_05]: To who?
[SPEAKER_07]: To you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why would Activision send you an email boasting about it?
[SPEAKER_05]: They send it to all of their retail partners to let their customers know because they're trying to drive up buzz for prototyping because...
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody loves leaked assets, and so they're going to start talking about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it was just a release of assets, it might not have been getting as much attention.
[SPEAKER_05]: But since it was something forbidden, people are interested in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it worked.
[SPEAKER_05]: It got them all to cover this leak and got all the information out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: The videos were ranked pretty high in game trailers, and that's all good news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good buzz for them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because people want to see things they're not supposed to be seeing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it was a hoax the whole time.
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole time it was a hoax.
[SPEAKER_05]: They made it look like it was an FTP directory and everything, and they got you all.
[SPEAKER_07]: And people don't know this yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're the one telling them.
[SPEAKER_05]: People don't know it, but it doesn't really matter, because the game looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole thing is they're tricking the people that they normally work with in the media to cover their game.
[SPEAKER_07]: What are they... Surely these people are going to find out eventually if they haven't already.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think there's going to be retaliation?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think this stuff happens all the time, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, here's another thing, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Could they be saying now that, oh, yeah, we meant for that to happen, when maybe they didn't?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it was in great detail.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, you know who tipped them off that the site had been broken?
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, survey sites and stuff like that and you may think, hey, why aren't these publishers doing anything to stop these leaks?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometimes they're intentional and sometimes that's how they drive buzz for stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just a little bit of insight in the back workings of the...
[SPEAKER_05]: Game Publishing World
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, the game looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's going to be a really fun game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's definitely going to be something I pick up because it's like crackdown.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Definitely something I'll be playing.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, moving on before we take a break here on the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a pretty big bombshell.
[SPEAKER_07]: We should have probably said that earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not that big of a deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: A little reward to those who actually pay attention to the whole thing, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, reward for being persistent and working at things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not really gaming news, but kind of a gaming funny, I guess you could say.
[SPEAKER_07]: At Missouri State...
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: So knowing that, he realized, it's in the next room.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, well, not necessarily, but he knew it was 30 feet away.
[SPEAKER_07]: So through the process of elimination, what he did, he actually went to the 4th, 5th, and 6th floors and found that the controller still worked on the 4th floor, 5th floor, and 6th floor, but it would not work on the 3rd or 7th floor.
[SPEAKER_07]: So process of elimination, where was the Xbox?
[SPEAKER_07]: On the 5th floor, the middle one, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: So then he went to the fifth floor and using the... Because if you get too far from the Xbox, the thing will start blinking.
[SPEAKER_07]: So using the process of elimination, he found out where the center was.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was hot and cold.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was playing hot and cold with his controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it told him exactly where the stolen Xbox was.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they actually got the RA, the resident assistant, to go into the room where the stolen Xbox supposedly was.
[SPEAKER_07]: They found the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: And apparently, what's really funny about it is that the...
[SPEAKER_07]: The Thief wasn't around when they got it, so kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they know who lives there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting, interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, people actually do have a brain in college.
[SPEAKER_05]: People are retarded.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, some people have a brain in college.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, the person who stole it obviously doesn't have a brain.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're retarded.
[SPEAKER_05]: They'll be going home.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I'd be pressing charges, but that would be me, because, you know, I totally don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a stupid award.
[SPEAKER_02]: In a way.
[SPEAKER_02]: For the loser that stole it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, but the thing is, I more give props to the guy who used the investigative skills to figure it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's like a spy versus spy award.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I guess you could say.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of both at once.
[SPEAKER_07]: A good job.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of like, what do they call it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Good job, gumshoe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember Carmen Sandiego?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So he's the gumshoe of the week award.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, I almost actually bought that game on PC last year.
[SPEAKER_07]: What, Where in the World is Karma San Diego?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I found it at the thrift store.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't that one of those games you can do on GameTap?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm pretty sure it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have GameTap.
[SPEAKER_07]: The old school ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have ZSNES and Magic Engine and, oh, wait, I actually have the systems too.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: You okay there, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're just so excited, you're just throwing your microphone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, what should the kids be playing this week in the classic video game of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: The classic game of the week is Willow for the Nintendo Entertainment System.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what's hilarious?
[SPEAKER_07]: I was just thinking about this game today.
[SPEAKER_07]: I shit you not.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I was actually thinking, like, this game needs to be highlighted as the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I swear to God, like, before I read that you were picking it for tonight, it was amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you have to then skip about a minute 25 in the music, because it has the music I like, which is the actual kicking ass outside the village music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: See?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like some of the best video game music ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what other game is awesome that's also based off a movie?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Addams Family.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fester's Quest was shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Back to Willow.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game came out in 1989.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually came out for the Famicom first in 1988.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, it actually came out in 1989 on both systems, but the movie came out in 88.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically you play as Willow and you go by yourself.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it's kind of Zelda-ish, but not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's more like, um, kind of playing like Secret of Mana did, actually, but being a Nintendo NES game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, but it was put out by Capcom, so it's one of the cool things that Capcom has given us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why don't we have Willow in a Capcom game, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: There are also other... I'm thinking licensing for the movie is an issue.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm joking, right.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are also other games.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a computer game that came out on Amiga, Atari ST, and a DOS game that came out by a Midnight Entertainment Group, but it wasn't the same game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a different one.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyone who's thinking they've got it, you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to say, I'm surprised I never played that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's cool, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's also an arcade version, but it was action adventure, and again, it's not like this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one is an action RPG.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a pretty cool little game, and you can get, you know, basically your items and weapons and meet people from the game and go talk to stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's RPG, but it was Willow, and it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus, you know, it had acorns that turned people into stone.
[SPEAKER_02]: The end.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So do I. Alright, there it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Willow on the Nintendo Entertainment System.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's a complete walkthrough there on YouTube that we were kind of playing the music from there.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can just watch somebody blast through the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: They use cheat codes to do it, but you still get a pretty good feel for what the game looks like there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played the crap out of that game when it came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was one of those games I rented and we held onto it for like so long because I didn't want to take it back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you end up having to pay for it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, not...
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for listening.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_07]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spring?
[SPEAKER_05]: Summer?
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, sorry, let's get into some real news now, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, apparently a woman from Colorado thinks she has an expert opinion of Nintendo's neglect to provide adequate support for Wii remotes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, there is another...
[SPEAKER_05]: Class Action Lawsuit for Nintendo's lack of adequate straps for their Wii remotes.
[SPEAKER_05]: She claims that even though the new straps are thicker and they are the third version with a new plastic strap, they still fail to secure the Wii remote properly.
[SPEAKER_05]: to the user during strenuous use.
[SPEAKER_05]: Furthermore, the suit alleges that Nintendo has failed to report a single remote strap issue to the Consumer Product Safety Commission in their monthly reports, despite Nintendo's support documents prove the existence of said issues.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: For one, the straps are basically there so that you don't drop the remote on the ground.
[SPEAKER_05]: Furthermore, then they went to reinforce them because idiots don't realize that they are just meant to prevent you from dropping them on the ground.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so they even reinforced them enough to where if you let go accidentally, it probably won't break.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's no guarantee.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do they need to put a sticker on the Wiimote that says, please touch me gently?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, that's simply just a case of consumer stupidity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone needs to just duct tape her into someone's cellar.
[SPEAKER_07]: Will a judge throw this out, yes or no?
[SPEAKER_02]: Will a judge order her to be locked up in a cellar by duct tape?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, duct tape is great for everything, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Duct Tape will silence the stupid masses.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty cool, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, should point this out, even bigger for you DS people, Pokemon Platinum, if you're still into collecting them all, Pokemon Platinum, March 22nd.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Circuit City had it listed, but then they pulled it.
[SPEAKER_07]: If that doesn't confirm it, I don't know what does.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shadow or Fire Emblem, that date is close if not accurate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe at CES or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to announce some more games and stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe a little bit on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, CES is not a gaming show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know why people think these huge announcements are going to come out at CES.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they're going to announce them at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's only a few months off, so I would think CES being the next show... Nintendo can do their own thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: They can say, we got Reggie coming to a party.
[SPEAKER_07]: Miyamoto in the house.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the press will show up.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's the thing, though, Rob, is I think...
[SPEAKER_05]: That they would do something at CES because of the DSi.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, the DSi coming out next year at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that's a technology thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: They may incorporate all into that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just a guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I suppose that's an educated guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would say it's like a 7th grade level educated guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: You might be right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just kind of wanted to go to Consumer Electronics Show just for the laughs and giggles, but I won't be able to go this year, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do know that there are going to be gaming people there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, there's like, I got a, you know, obviously I'm not going to CES, but I got an invite for anybody that's, you know, game retailers or our customers or whatever, if they were going to CES, that they can go sit through a Microsoft presentation and they're going to show them the upcoming stuff that they've got coming out for next year or like...
[SPEAKER_05]: and probably just Halo Wars at that point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: There will be some presence.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's getting bigger, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's not that far off, so we will see soon if they're going to announce these officially or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, something that is actually official is that there's going to be former members of Team Ninja and those who worked on Brawl doing a new Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles fighter going to be on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: hoping that they can pull it off I mean that would be really cool I actually did like the old 2D TMNT tournament fighters that was kind of a fun game so hopefully this will have actually I hope it has some of the characters from that series I think it would be fun
[SPEAKER_05]: Team Ninja equals April with Breast Physics
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Halo Wars has been announced to be coming out now on March 3rd.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um, kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a lot of stuff coming out right there in March, especially since I think a week before that you have Killzone 2 on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, now of course Halo Wars is the RTS, um, kind of prequel to the whole Halo series.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they've got, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: and apparently coming out in Africa, Europe, and the Middle East the day after.
[SPEAKER_05]: Almost a worldwide release there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be interesting to see how that is because I know it's probably not going to do as well as a normal Halo game because it's not a first person shooter.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it has a Halo name on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does have a Halo name on it and there are a lot of RTS fans out there so they're hoping to kind of be like a StarCraft but
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's tough.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take this all with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's nice to know, especially because I guess it did pretty well on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's nice to hear there's interest there again.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just hope whatever this is doesn't come out on Wii, that it is another HD game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, kind of some other things going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, whatever Mystery Project LMNO that was going on at EA, apparently that is now on ice right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I shouldn't say gone forever, but just on hold because of all the layoffs that were going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I mean, heck, what do you call this Halo 3 Dark, or no, it has a new name now, all the random numbers and letters or whatever, it's just Halo 4, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you have it, some rumors out of Electronic Gaming Monthly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take with grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we have a little bit more rumor, more like a hint, is that there could quite possibly be Halo 2, not Halo 2, Fable 2, available as a full digital download.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was basically when asked if...
[SPEAKER_02]: If there would be, the quote is, I can't say anything else on it, I would be killed to death.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I think that's pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's interesting because that would be the first, at least on the Xbox 360, sorry, the PS3 already did this with the Burnout game, but on the 360 where you would have a full
[SPEAKER_07]: GameSpot swears they're not worried.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, GameStop.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's definitely not taking away too much from buying games.
[SPEAKER_05]: If anything, you look at the special editions and the special edition sales.
[SPEAKER_05]: People love their special editions and they keep getting more creative and putting more crap in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, in the case of Fable 2, maybe not so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: They start taking stuff out.
[SPEAKER_05]: For everything else, though, they're still getting people to buy these special editions for...
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, look at the Legendary Edition stuff of Halo 3 and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which, by the way, I saw at Fry's this weekend for $59.99.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, people bought a lot of those and they weren't selling as hot as people thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Same with those Halo 3 consoles too.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, I mean, it's definitely going to head that way at some point where they'll allow you to download stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I think also people have to keep in mind...
[SPEAKER_05]: is it really worth it downloading a game like that especially with like a 360 you know where your system might conk out on you then you got to get a new one then you have to find some way to be able to you know have it tied to your new system and also when you're done with it you can't sell it off used which is another thing but you know that for some people that might not be a big deal
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and you only have so much room.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, once your hard drive fills up, it fills up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of the bummer.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, sure, they can release a new hard drive, but those hard drives ain't cheap.
[SPEAKER_07]: I paid $150 for my 120GB hard drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, sadly enough, those hard drives, the actual parts, don't cost that much.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's the bad thing about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, they're just laptop hard drives through a special connector.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, don't remind me, because I'm going to get more mad.
[SPEAKER_05]: You keep talking, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: But hey!
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you remember, though, that is one plus, though, about the PS3, though, is they do let you upgrade your hard drive and you don't have to buy a special hard drive from them.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just any hard drive will do, which I think is the way that Microsoft should have gone with their hard drives, if you ask me, but what do I know?
[SPEAKER_07]: One thing, I will say this, you know, despite the hard time I gave the PlayStation 3, you know, for many, many years on this program, I will say this, I will admit this, playing Prince of Persia this week, it's been nice and quiet while I've been playing the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll give it that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, so other things coming Fable 2's way, of course, a brand new expansion, Not Whole Island, is going to be available to download on December 22nd.
[SPEAKER_05]: It will run you 800 Microsoft points, or that's $10 in real money.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Some interesting things along with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course it's going to add some new costumes, a bunch of new missions, and some other fun stuff including some more achievements as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are three achievements tied with this now.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's the collector, which is worth 25 gamer score if you acquire all the mystery items in the box of secret shop or see another hero doing so.
[SPEAKER_05]: The meteorologist, which is worth 50 gamer points.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to bring all of Knothole Island's weather problems under control or help another hero do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: and The Bibliophile, which is 25 gamer points.
[SPEAKER_05]: Find all the books detailing the history of Knothole Island or help another hero doing so.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I may pick this up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure yet because I haven't really gotten to Fable 2 that much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still want to go back to Lost Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't finished that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your wife sure did get to Fable 2, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, she...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, you probably should get all that shit hooked.
[SPEAKER_07]: Since we don't have the adjusted TV cam tonight, you might want to get all that hooked up before we... I will.
[SPEAKER_07]: The minute we go off air, we can just go into that and be done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Left 4 Dead is another one of those games I really need to check out at some point because I usually don't like first-person shooters that much.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's Valve and it's zombies.
[SPEAKER_07]: It might be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I've heard nothing but really good things about this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except for the fact that people have been cheating on the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: But guess what Valve did this week?
[SPEAKER_07]: They put the hammer down on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: You can still do it on your local games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right, you can still do the thing because it only fixes this when you're playing the live games online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically what they did is they used, there's a mod tool that you can, if you have a device to basically rip files off your hard drive, which they actually do sell them, they're like 50 bucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm thinking about picking one up because I need to buy useless crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can mod a file on there and it will allow you to do different cheats.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which might be fun, because I like to cheat in games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go cheatin'.
[SPEAKER_05]: for local games at least.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be a fun game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cheaters Presents, let's go cheatin'.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't mean like cheating on your relationship sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you hear, and I've seen this in our system, I know it's coming, Grey's Anatomy, the game, for Wii and the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the shit?
[SPEAKER_07]: What are you going to make a game out of for Grey's Anatomy?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're doing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They actually have the ESRB
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to stop time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me read this real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all from the ESRB description for Grey's Anatomy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a story-based role-playing game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says the storyline contains frequent references to sexual encounters between different characters and dialogue that contains sexual innuendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: For example, is there anyone in this hospital you're not going to sleep with and you want to have sex after surgery?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know about you, but that's not a sexual innuendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's you want to have sex after surgery.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some scenes take place soon after the characters have had sex.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dialogue also contains minor expletives, for example, hell and ass, and references to alcohol, like you, me, at a restaurant.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh no, hell and ass!
[SPEAKER_01]: I like the references to alcohol.
[SPEAKER_05]: This game looks like crap, but that'll be funny though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Grey's Anatomy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Grey's Anatomy, The Game, Amazing Hey, I gotta read some comments from the chat about you and Nelly and the way you play Animal Crossing because they had some comments here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft says, Animal Crossing, the game about time traveling and its effects.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Press Start says, Tom Nook is gonna break her legs.
[SPEAKER_07]: TigerClaw says, you better do what your wife says, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't want to have a divorce over the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: And SSJ100Matt wonders aloud, why does Nelly have to cockblock us?
[SPEAKER_07]: And SSJ100Matt also makes this very winner comment about the way you play Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkTetsuya asks if you got a blue phone box in your town.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dark Dead Studios says Rocky Horror Picture Show is on Xbox Live Netflix.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't even think to look for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you know that, and I'm not sure, I didn't know this until today, but you can actually change out what bed you have in your attic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: With any bed that you buy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, I'm totally putting the regal bed in my attic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish I could decorate my damn attic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm tired of my attic looking like wood.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just walk up to the bottom of your bed and hit A, and it will allow you to change it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There should just be... Oh, I like Misty says, she says, screw that, I want a TARDIS.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to have my house be a TARDIS.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kind of surprised they're not trying to nickel and dime us yet in Animal Crossing with releasing the stuff that you have to pay for that you can get.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bet Nellie would make them do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not that smart, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the problem, though, with... Because...
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the thing, is if they had that kind of content, it would be pay to unlock content.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if they had that in the game, someone would figure out how to hack it and unlock it already.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they'll do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or like maybe, okay, the old school Nintendo games, like maybe just have the ones that I have on my virtual console.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess that's kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_07]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They'd never do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Forget I said anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get to that statement of the show that we encourage you to participate with our show every week by sending us emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: And DarkSakura is going to open up the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, you are.
[SPEAKER_07]: You better.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's going to read a few of her favorite emails right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or I will subject her to watching...
[SPEAKER_07]: Manos, The Hands of Fate Manos, The Hands of Fate
[SPEAKER_07]: Number 11, I think it was, was some karate movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember the name of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll have to find it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the trick was the one dude had no arms and the other dude had no legs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they were actually karate fighting in the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to figure out what freaking movie it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe somebody in the chat will know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did they tie themselves together?
[SPEAKER_07]: Astounding.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to see this
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know who put it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to say this.
[SPEAKER_07]: The documentary itself wasn't that good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to see the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Screw the documentary.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just want to see the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why is not Manos the Hands of Fate on there?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that because they NST3K'd it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I will say Howard the Duck was on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Howard the Duck was on it?
[SPEAKER_07]: As was Ishtar.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Howard the Duck.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's one of my favorite.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was Xanadu on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Xanadu was on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: No!
[SPEAKER_07]: I love Xanadu.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I don't know how Manos the Hands of Fate wasn't on here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a pretty poorly done documentary.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe they only had access to one studio's films or something, but yeah, I gotta figure out what the name of that movie was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on, I'm getting it right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you say the name, I'll remember it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, DarkSakura, read some emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm gonna play music again, because we got on a tangent.
[SPEAKER_07]: Surprise!
[SPEAKER_05]: Fighting Life!
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: The Crippled Masters, that's what it was called.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about some emails?
[SPEAKER_02]: How about it?
[SPEAKER_02]: This comes from GS68.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, OLR crew.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wait, wait, stop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, sorry, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: You had your turn.
[SPEAKER_05]: In The Crippled Masters, they actually attach themselves to each other to create that person that I was saying they should do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says right here.
[SPEAKER_05]: The two men are disfigured by their evil leader.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says one man has his arms cut off, the other has his legs burned off with acid.
[SPEAKER_05]: The two men are enemies but struggling with being disabled.
[SPEAKER_05]: One day fighting each other, the wise old yoga master suggests they work together and start training with weapons and team up to help them with the help of a shoulder.
[SPEAKER_02]: YouTube trailers.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says with the help of a shoulder harness so that the man without the YouTube
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking at the trailer right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Three for the other man, and vice versa.
[SPEAKER_05]: Three words better than Voltron.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'm watching this scene where they cut his arms off.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no arms.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, you promised not to interrupt the emails now.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ew!
[SPEAKER_02]: God, that is disgusting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: One more time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I have a question, actually, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was The House Where Evil Dwells on there?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the movie... They had some really fucked up movie from the 70s, though, that was like just a total gore film and had titties and butts and blood and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember what the name was.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love The House Where Evil Dwells.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I have a little story about this, and then I'll do email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Promise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love what Actdeft said in chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: The crippled masters of independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that might be offensive, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: There are people that are actually handicapped.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are actually crippled masters out there who do podcasts.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you have to admit, it's an awesome idea for a movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not that the people have no... But the fact that it's like that... What was that movie with Richard Pryor and Gene Wilder?
[SPEAKER_07]: Where one was deaf and one was... See no evil, hear no evil.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like that, but karate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, sorry, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so this movie, I saw it when I was like six, something like that, and it was on Showtime, back when Showtime was new.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was at the time called The House Where Evil Dwells, and I had no idea that was the name of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just remembered that it's about these people that move to Japan, get possessed by ghosts, and end up killing each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, the ghosts killed each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I have been trying for years, I mean decades, to find this movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did not remember the name of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was so little, I didn't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I remembered scenes from it, including the ghost-possessed crabs chasing the girl at the tree.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is why evil alien crabs always, giant alien crabs always make me crack the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I always remember they go to roar sound.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, like, you hear, like, the... For lack of a better description, I guess, like, the Japanese ghost noise, you know, that sounds, like, really deep.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's Broken Neck Ghost Woman.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's more like...
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway... This show's terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: So... Shut up!
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so... So, um... Last... It's like, I think six months ago, I finally, finally found a review of the damn movie, found the name of it, and bought it on Amazon for five bucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm making you watch it with me.
[SPEAKER_01]: No!
[SPEAKER_01]: You want to use that to do with me?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, but we have to find the cheerleader movie that was on that list and watch that too, because that looked amazing!
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to see a cheerleader movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do we get to know?
[SPEAKER_07]: Can we do email now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you totally need to see this movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: God.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, first email from GS68.
[SPEAKER_02]: GS68.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, OLR crew!
[SPEAKER_02]: If you've already covered what I just brought up in the subject line, just ignore this email.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, Sunnyvale Golfland is holding a location test for the North American version of DJ Max Technica sometime next week, somewhere in the December 17th to 19th range, and I thought I'd share this with you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kudos to Corey Virtue from Bimani Style for bringing this up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm texting Shane right now to get a reaction out of him because I don't know anyone that loves this game more than him and he's going to be pissed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I encourage people living in NorCal who are interested in Technica to come check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: GS68.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: This email was brought to you by Tetris the Grandmaster, home of the ending Tetrominoes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I... Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, DJ Max.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you seen this new one yet?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm curious to check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shane made me watch YouTubes of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't look anything like the PSP one to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just the same music.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd be curious to check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have any plans next weekend.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cancel them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to Old Folsom and eating good food and shopping.
[SPEAKER_07]: We can eat good food and shop in the bay and play DJ Max.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who are you going with?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: So, moving forward, um, hey guys, Loki, a few episodes back you said that Wii music is for five-year-olds.
[SPEAKER_02]: I object.
[SPEAKER_02]: My recently turned six brother loves to play video games, and not only games, he plays Guitar Hero 3 and Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_02]: He strums and he yells at me to press the buttons while we work our way through Slow Ride.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's your lol for the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sky, put the podcast up faster.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope I pass the grammar Nazi test.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Geekboy2424.
[SPEAKER_02]: Think of it this way.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're going to get an awesome Christmas present pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: You put it in an ellipsis where you're not supposed to, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're supposed to use two dashes, not an ellipsis.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll take care of that later.
[SPEAKER_02]: SuperHappyFuntimeShow
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate that show.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please find attached our Christmas to you all at OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not sending analog versions out as we're trying to save the planet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a great Christmas and New Year and we'll see you on the other side, whatever that means.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a very creative idea to do your Christmas cards digitally.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I would like to see some holiday cards.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't want to say Christmas because that's insensitive.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want Christmas cards!
[SPEAKER_02]: I want it fucking loaded with baby Jesus.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, then fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: We would like to get your digital... For this week's mailbag, we would like to challenge you to send us Christmas cards, and they better be about Christmas.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Jesus and Santa and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless you want to do them about original Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's with, you know, Yule Logs burning and candles on trees and druids sacrificing things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fine, look, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: We want your Christmas cards via email this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: So mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: and your banners for the PSP website dammit
[SPEAKER_02]: It was.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was very nice and we appreciate it very much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually mailed all four real Christmas cards this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they were pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it for emails, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope, we got some spam.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you, allconfirm at ebay.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: You shit.
Done?
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to send us emails, mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com Back to the gaming news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got some other interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a game that I was playing quite a bit right after it came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of put it off now since...
[SPEAKER_05]: I have other things to be playing, but I want to go back, and maybe this will entice me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mercenaries 2 is getting some new download content.
[SPEAKER_05]: They kind of teased this a little bit a while ago with their Obama and Sarah Palin characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this is all going to be part of the Blow It Up Again download content pack.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is going to be free, and...
[SPEAKER_05]: It is going to contain a bunch of cool stuff, including some new modes.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to have four new game types, including there was one that looked like a death race or something like that, and some other fun explosion-based games, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And apparently it will be coming out on the Marketplace December 16th.
[SPEAKER_05]: PS3 owners
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if you want to continue to expand games that you might own, Guitar Hero World Tour is going to be offering five free download tracks, but only if you own the guitar bundle of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So not buying the game by itself, not buying the big band box, just buying guitar and game by itself.
[SPEAKER_07]: Supposedly you're going to be getting five free songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: And here's the thing, it's not five pre-selected songs like it was a rock band.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll just get to choose five free downloadable tracks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what's... I actually almost bought Guitar Hero World Tour.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just... Every song in the song list that I really, really wanted to play was pretty much already in Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I just... I feel bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel like Rock Band's so much better than Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's so much more versatile.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has a lot more tracks to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: We met some real nice people that worked on Guitar Hero at PAX.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_02]: But one thing I am... One thing I am excited about, though, is the music mixer.
[SPEAKER_02]: The studio mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's limited.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe when it comes down in price a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the price is one thing I'm having a hard time justifying.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do really need a new guitar, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, I was playing the No Doubt stuff in Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe if they get better downloads, too, I'd be on board.
[SPEAKER_07]: No Doubt has that album, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: And my roommate was watching me play it and was like, yeah, it's too bad you don't have a second guitar.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually want to play Rock Band right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm like, oh, I need to get a second guitar anyway, because I'm still using the Explorer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Still.
[SPEAKER_07]: And TigerClaw says, why buy the game when SingStar ABBA was all you cared for?
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't believe I left that out of my gaming week, but I did play SingStar ABBA last night.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep, yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, this is definitely for the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: In February, Rise of the Argonauts is going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an action roleplay game that's being put out by Codemasters.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's already out on PC, PS3, and Xbox 360 everywhere else in Europe.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, the UK version had some problems with actually having space for the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It really was only a retail issue.
[SPEAKER_02]: The publisher actually said that they tried to get it into retail in the UK along with the others, but it was so busy they could not get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do it so they actually delayed the UK launch, simply for retail reasons.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually supposed to be out in the US on February 16th, and everybody else as of Friday.
Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: You may remember back... Man, I can't believe it's already been over a year, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: BioShock.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had some limited editions that came out that had the BioShock Big Daddy figurine with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, now to go with the Big Daddy is a little sister.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you'll actually be able to purchase these.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they're from the Cult of Rapture.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure if they're actually being sold through the website or not.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, it's going to be a little sister figurine that will go along with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: And
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: But what's cool about this, the mobile game actually supports local matches via Bluetooth And, remember the awesome game Pac-Man Versus, and what was so awesome about that, you could play as the ghost You can do that in this mobile version as well Now here's the thing, there is that kind of like fog or limited vision on the mobile phone But, you know what, still kind of awesome So there you go, if you're a mobile gamer and looking for a game to get
[SPEAKER_07]: being able to play as the ghost definitely puts a whole new twist on Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's available right now in Europe and I'm sure we'll come over here soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Patience.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a virtue.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sadly, I'm not virtuous, but oh well, I have to be because I'm poor.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want it now, daddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you want the goose that lays the golden eggs?
[SPEAKER_07]: I want a goose that lays the golden egg.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's also a very stressful episode on Wondershowsen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Patience, patience, patience, patience, patience.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, I love Wondershowsen.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so sad that show didn't win.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Jamie, you are missing out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, if you're going to make me watch your crappy movie, I'm making you watch Wondershowsen.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a crappy movie, but it's fun crappy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the hot dog highway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Daddy!
[SPEAKER_05]: Mortimer!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: It will pick up on Wi-Fi signals that are nearby.
[SPEAKER_05]: And based on those Wi-Fi signals, it will kind of create treasures for you to be able to collect.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can actually walk around different places and find different treasures.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like a real-life treasure hunt, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might also remember that, I want to say, Metal Gear Solid Portable Ops did something similar to that effect as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, I think you could...
[SPEAKER_05]: and get different unlockable characters based on Wi-Fi spots.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if I like the fact that I have to walk around to find these Wi-Fi spots, but neat nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is this kind of like the whole geocaching thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sort of, but not quite as cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: TigerClaw says, I bet the treasures are actually just open Wi-Fi networks.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be a treasure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, one more story about an announcement, possible announcement coming to Consumer Electronics Show.
[SPEAKER_07]: This could be some big gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just a rumor.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, it's coming from a research analyst for the firm Global Equities.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, Microsoft could be unveiling a Zune phone at Consumer Electronics Show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, the Zune phone, you can guess what it's probably trying to compete with, but it's supposed to have motion enhancement features.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would actually have an accelerometer in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: A large multimedia screen in it and a keyboard, I guess, that is on the screen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, of course, the interesting thing about it is that, you know, although nothing is really said about gaming right away, you would think, especially with the way the other big phone is going, and especially because Microsoft has that tie-in to the 360, and they've always talked about that whole live anywhere thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they also showed off those downloadable X and A titles to the Zoom.
[SPEAKER_07]: This would be really a great bridge between all that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So especially with, you know, so many community, I mean, the community thing has really exploded out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And congrats to our buddy Aaron, who appears to still be in the top, like, 15 of the games on the community games amongst all the stuff that's out there right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Props to him, but that would be very interesting if all these X and Y games could suddenly be playable on the phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like they'd have this huge base of already made things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Excellent idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Although I would probably like doing that because it would come in handy sometimes.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it would all depend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe if they made a standalone Zoom player that also played games and you can download stuff, maybe not the phone, then I might be interested in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's not something I'm actually going to purchase as a phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Arama in chat says, Okay Microsoft, you already have smartphones and pocket PCs, phones that are on the market that's a whole lot better than iPhones.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't need a damn Zune phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, that does it for stories tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll get to some last minute stories in just a moment.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we are going to open up the Skype line right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to call and talk about the show tonight, please give us a call.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're only going to take a couple calls tonight because we want to make sure we have time after the show for the Justin TV thing with Tatsunoko and Capcom.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're going to try to abbreviate this so we get Loki home on time and not in trouble.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then I just... Well, I appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't need to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't want to stay up all night either.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's freaking cold in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is very cold in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, we're going to just take a couple quick calls while we're waiting for a call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, you want to do some last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a weird game that this...
[SPEAKER_05]: 3D Oz Funny Band
[SPEAKER_05]: and then also on that there are two sets of keys there's four keys on the bottom and three keys on the top kind of the base of the guitar and you flip the guitar over and there's six drum pads so that's kind of neat and the game itself kind of looks a little bit like you know Guitar Hero or Rock Band but what's kind of cool is the actual board that the notes scroll down is kind of curved so it's like kind of
[SPEAKER_05]: Suck that you can't play drums and guitar at the same time Not without it being very uncomfortable
[SPEAKER_05]: Something else that's coming out, Brutal Legend, of course, was shown off during the Video Game Awards show tonight, and EA is now bringing that game out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, this used to be one of the properties of NVIDIA before they got bought up by Activision, and now EA is putting out yet another game, a little bit different, not going to see Brutal Legend 2010 or something like that, but neat nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then we were talking a little bit before about DJ Max Technica.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, DJ Max Technica is actually coming to the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're going to be doing a DS game that's going to also have some DSi features as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to also use the DSi camera and have storage support, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: But very cool to see that this is going to be coming to the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess it would be perfect since it's a touchscreen game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the PSP versions have done very well as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, now we're finally getting calls, because apparently our Skype was on Don't Disturb or something, and I finally figured that out, thanks to a chat comment, and reset it, and now we've got a call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is Jason.
[SPEAKER_07]: I come from the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was getting a little worried that no one was going to call tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, that's a little embarrassing, but then I realized... You were online the whole time, ever since you came on to do the, uh, the toss-over with, uh, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I usually turn it off for the first hour and a half that I got lazy tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, what's up, Jason?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, not too much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just chilling in three-degree weather.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just chilling.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what it feels like here, even though you'd probably kill us if we told you how cold it actually is here.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'd probably be like, you fucking babies.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: This weather would have frozen me if I had still lived in Arizona at the time, so I can definitely understand.
[SPEAKER_07]: 47 degrees out, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whimps.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what a Colorado summer?
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, no, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's up, Jason?
[SPEAKER_07]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty close, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have had notes open ever since the start of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Home.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray, home.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's funny because when you said that this was something that was popular in the 90s, all of these memories came fluttering back.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was two things that stood out.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of them was a company called Worlds3D that... I remember Worlds3D.
[SPEAKER_06]: The sad thing is I've never actually used any of these 3D world products back then.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't have my own computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was young.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't know nearly as much as I do now.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Worlds 3D came out and tried to do this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if that's what ZDNet, you know, the precursor to Tech TV, if that's what ZDTV spotlighted at one point.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I remember seeing a 3D interface for web browsing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's slow.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a great interface for browsing the web.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're called web browsers.
[SPEAKER_06]: It presents everything in a great medium.
[SPEAKER_06]: What a concept.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you think home is just stupid, or what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby had it right, and I've said this to a couple people in the chat room, and I think you even echoed it at the same time.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want to compare it to Second Life, but you can't compare it to Second Life.
[SPEAKER_06]: Second Life is a game in the sense that you have production and you can play other people's production and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Home is an interface to, I mean, it's an alternative to the XMB, you could say, with the fact that they're trying to integrate partying and game launching and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it's a cross-media bar that says, fuck, shit, nah, and fat, you know, all that stuff, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's another interface.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's slow and it takes forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it just doesn't work as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: While that's natural, it doesn't work on the digital mediums.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not that smart.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you said you've been taking notes during the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else did you want to comment on?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just a lot of this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of the things that Rye pointed out was that
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: That was aggravating.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the worst thing I've ever seen in a game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you know that Prince of Persia is the first PlayStation 3 game I've bought that had to do the installation thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: And it kind of caught me off guard.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I was like, whoa, oh, hey, I forgot PS3 games do this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because all the other PS3 games I have, LittleBigPlanet didn't really do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it might have, but I totally didn't notice it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It did.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did it?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's small.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just didn't notice it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I was doing something wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: You notice that there's no more stories about those anymore?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's because every game does it now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was actually going to say and ask the same thing about LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember an install.
[SPEAKER_07]: It did it, but it's just kind of short.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so is the Prince of Persia one.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll notice the first time you play the game, it's slow to boot up.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I was like, oh, this shit's installing on my hard drive right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: And sure enough, every time I booted it since then, boop, comes right up.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's just so weird to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: But PC games have done this for years, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a PC!
[SPEAKER_06]: The difference between a PC is that you have to support a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: In a game console, developers should already know exactly what they need to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you can say the same thing for download content, but... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just seems really weird in the way that the PC is kind of graying out
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me say this, Jason.
[SPEAKER_07]: To me, it's weird, but it's not a deal-breaker.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I can put up with it, especially if it's just once at the beginning of the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would only be more pissed off if it kept happening throughout the whole thing, which it sounds like it happens in Metal Gear Solid 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's funny, because the first time it installs, it takes something like 10 or 20 minutes, I think, if memory serves correctly.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then every additional time it installs it takes about three minutes and I swear to God it's a three minute when we were playing through it and Wright was watching me play when we were playing through it and we would get to these stupid installs I would say it's a three minute Marlboro commercial because Old Snake is sitting there smoking away right in your face for three minutes and nothing else is going on
[SPEAKER_06]: He's just sitting there huffing and puffing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Comment from chat, Legend of Zaku says, Bullshit, PC games installed faster than PS3 games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got three words for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't count download time, download patches and updates.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, even the game itself spawns across like four CDs.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been too long.
[SPEAKER_07]: I understand the point he's trying to make, that some of those PC reinstalls are very long.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, Jason, I got to rush you along because we got to take some more calls.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is there anything else you want to comment on tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: As soon as it's actually flourishing, it's a preview.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Jason, when you open it up to the masses like Sony has, that's not how everybody's going to view it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because people are going to download this and go, this is home, this is bullshit, and they're not going to look at it again.
[SPEAKER_06]: They shrug it off as the whole beta thing, but... I mean, they pushed it to the cross-media bar.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It definitely popped up as soon as I found out that it was open for everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I stand by my comment, but I certainly understand yours.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jason, I think Home is going to be one of those things that's a lot cooler in a year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just like the PS3 itself, it's not going to realize its potential for a year.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a good point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lord knows we didn't buy our PS3 until recently because the library, we didn't care about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We didn't have a need for Blu-ray, which has also changed now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blu-ray movies, that is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, hey, it's your buddy from New York, Ranma Well, hello, buddy from New York, Ranma, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was cold earlier, but now I'm happy I'm home.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried to call you guys last week, but since SSJ100MAT told me you guys didn't have the 1-800 number, I had gone to an interesting... Yeah, we had issues last week, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: We had issues last week, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't we all have issues once in a while?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but I had gone to an interesting concert last week and called BlipFest 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: BlipFestival.org
[SPEAKER_07]: What convinced you to go out to the show?
[SPEAKER_03]: Chip Tunes
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if you heard these shows we did live at Penny Arcade Expo, but... I missed those.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder if Bobby's listening.
[SPEAKER_07]: He'll say it in chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there was a guy that actually came on who did chiptunes with his old school brick Game Boy, and he was pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he came in... And he was playing them, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: It wouldn't have been the last day, because we weren't there the last day because of our flight.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was the second day.
[SPEAKER_07]: So look for day two of the PAX podcast we did at All Games, and towards the end of the show is when the guy came on.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you get his name or something like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember it off the top of my head, sadly.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know we had it at the time, and I apologize.
[SPEAKER_07]: If Bobby's listening, he'll remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, a lot of the performers on stage were actually mixing, and with Game Boys, there was one artist up there, I think his name was Nordliff, or USK, actually had two Game Boys and basically switching back and forth through a mixer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: You had another group that I saw on Sunday called Starscream.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty much what they were doing was you had one person on the Game Boy and another person on drums.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was just like a non-stop dance party or what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It turned into like this awesome 8-bit electro rave and...
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was like a lot of crowd surfing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just great.
[SPEAKER_03]: It ran an hour late, but it was well worth it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because my favorite group was on stage, Anamanaguchi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, their background beats is 8-bit NES, and you have one on drums, a lead, a bassist, and another guitarist.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just couldn't remember what his part was.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I actually found it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, somebody in chat says it right, as I find it myself.
[SPEAKER_07]: But his name was Paul Owens, and he's the director of the movie Reformat the Planet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay, that artist wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, but that's, anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: When you said chiptunes, I just remember that particular performance was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is kind of a big part of how 8-Bit Weapon kind of got their sound.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love 8-Bit Weapon.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's funny that this stuff's gotten bigger and bigger.
[SPEAKER_03]: StarScream, Syphus, Nordloaf, and Anamanaguchi How much did this whole thing cost you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, it was $15.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a four-night event.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's $50 for all four nights.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you paid $60, you get a DVD of Blitz Festival 06.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just went for Sunday.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just picked up the 07 DVD, and I will tell you this.
[SPEAKER_03]: The way they remixed the music on that DVD, even if you have the volume almost near where no one can still hear it, it's still loud, and it's really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it sounds like you had fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wish our phone lines had been open last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: The Force is not strong with him, but, you know, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm staring at that screen, and happy fangirl.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll get to it after the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, we've got Tatsunoko vs. Capcom up on the screen now, finally.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to get to it soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ranma, we've got to let you go, though, so we can get one more call.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can I say one more thing, and then I can get out of here?
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, that song, it's Pitch Black.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's off the MC Frontline album, Secrets from the Future, so you know which one it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Got it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, did you get a chance to check out the new album?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's in my roommate's car, but I'll have to check it out soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very much worth it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll take one more call.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any other last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do we get them all?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, we didn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's music news stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pearl Jam's 10 album is coming to Rock Band in March.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was announced at the Spike VGA.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is like a ripper.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Akadepro, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm, uh, well, what is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm, well, as you haven't heard, I'm back in WoW, playing on the US server once again, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well, uh, well, I thought you were going to go off to this, that you can now change your, uh,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Troll Warlock
[SPEAKER_07]: The interesting... Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: The interesting thing is, is that, um... I don't play a warlock, obviously.
[SPEAKER_07]: The other interesting thing is, is that you can change the gender of your character.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can now give your character a sex change!
[SPEAKER_04]: Whee!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: And, well, here's the other thing, is that, well, as one sort of... Well, I don't know if you're supposed to be... But as one cross-dresser sort of like, since I'm not considering myself fully bone-training...
[SPEAKER_04]: I would say, but that doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_07]: We already play as girls already.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I play as a tauren female because who plays a tauren female?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll tell you, nobody plays a tauren female.
[SPEAKER_02]: You do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, me.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's probably like five on the entire server.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is this Sassy Pants?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I usually don't give out the character name on the server.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, no, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just don't want random tells.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, they can probably find it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just don't need the random emails of people saying, I looked up a character in the armory and she sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that would tell me exactly what they could do.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm in the process of leveling up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of warlocks, they work warlock.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got to level 30.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's damn nice that you get your mount at level 30 nowadays.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, it's amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: They've made a lot of great changes.
[SPEAKER_07]: One change I really like that they did is that now you have the heirlooms.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you have a level 80 character and if you save up your badges or wintergrass marks, you can buy these heirlooms and you can send them.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're bind to account, meaning you can send these items to any player on your account and they actually scale in level.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what's cool is that the shoulders heirlooms that you can buy scale in level so you can send them to your level 1 character and they get a 10% experience bonus gain in addition to the pretty awesome stats.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: That seems quite nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, other than that, I have nothing to remark about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I should point out, check out Left 4 Dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Left 4 Dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Left 4 Dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I play, when the demo was released, I got up to play it, but it really is something.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing you have to point out is that you really do need four people and all of them need to have mics, else there really isn't any fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I got to let you go because the chat wants less Warcraft and more Tatsunoko versus Capcom.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're going to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm pretty excited about that too.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, same.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for the call.
[SPEAKER_07]: We enjoy hearing from our listeners from afar.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do have commentary about Tatsunoko vs. Capcom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which would be?
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the music that they've put up for the characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: That for Ken, they give him the... Okay, gotcha my history.
[SPEAKER_02]: For the first 13 episodes of the series, it had a more sedate opening.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the da-de-da thing that everyone knows was the closing theme.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they switched it over because all the fans liked the big one better.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Ken gets that theme, but June gets the original opening, which I thought was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's it for me being a total Tatsunoko fangirl nerd.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Dan laughed at me because I was singing along with it while I was playing the other day.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to go around and get everybody's final thought and wrap up tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're at the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last minute story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back to Guitar Hero Metallica.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have a partial track list out from it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: On top of the Metallica songs, there's going to be some songs from other bands that worked with Metallica and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alice in Chains, No Excuses, Bob Seger, Turn the Page, Judas Priest, Hellbent for Leather, and
[SPEAKER_05]: Cyrus with Demon Cleaner, Leonard Skinner with Tuesday's Gone, Mastodon, Blood and Thunder, Michael Sheckler Group, Armed and Ready, Sam Hain, Mother of Mercy, and The Sword, Black River.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's also apparently some unannounced tracks by Slayer, Queen, and The Foo Fighters.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess this is all coming from the new Game Informer.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to have some info on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, the Metallica tracks in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enter Sandman, For Whom the Bell Tolls, Fuel, Hit the Lights, King Nothin', Master Puppets, and No Leaf Clovers, Nothing Else Matters, Sad But True, The Unforgiven, and Where I May Roam.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: and, um, let's see, some other stuff, download content coming to LittleBigPlanet, including a Santa costume you can get now, it'll be available free on, um, December 18th, and they're gonna have it in two parts, so you can make, uh, your Santa sack boys, and, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, WhiteShadow
[SPEAKER_02]: because if you know Gatchaman.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I forgot the whole stupid speech, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: More Gatchaman, less WoW.
[SPEAKER_07]: My final thought is WoW.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, WoW I love my new, I have a Tanooki suit hoodie that I have now that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wore it out last night and I got compliments on it, but the best part about it on the actual hoodie is little cat ears.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you actually look like, I'll go out and get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I don't have it out right now, but... I need to find one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll wear it out sometime when we go out to not go to the test location of DJ Max Technica.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, you know, you're like, I gotta go shopping, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get some shoes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is I gotta find Cageman's song.
[SPEAKER_05]: You better hurry.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in to and supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys are awesome, and thanks so, so, so much for your support.
[SPEAKER_07]: Without you guys, we just wouldn't be here.
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't have any major TV thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't get acknowledged to the Video Game Awards.
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't have tons of people listening to us.
[SPEAKER_07]: So just help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_07]: Leave a nice review on iTunes or some other website that ranks podcasts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell your friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_07]: Commercial free.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, sometimes the podcasts are slow to upload, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_07]: We love you.
[SPEAKER_07]: So have a good one, you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: And until next week, we will see you on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_00]: or allgames.com but we're probably right anyway see you next week