[SPEAKER_07]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Happy Holidays, y'all!
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are that podcast on the internet dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining me as always, say hello to Dark Santa, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Sakura, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I am.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing, um, crampy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ho, ho, ho.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bah, fucking humbug.
[SPEAKER_02]: Try having cramps around Christmas, you'll curse your uterus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did Santa bring you cramps for Christmas?
[SPEAKER_02]: That and a migraine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you were a bad girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck I was.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd rather have coal because then I could light it on fire and be warm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello as well to the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of Santa's elves joining us from North Pole.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's correct.
[SPEAKER_05]: Highly accurate.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything exciting planned for the holidays?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, then.
[SPEAKER_04]: You tell us about it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I will in just a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, okay, then.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you should already know what it is, but there's lots of stuff leading up to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, sometimes I play stupid for the sake of the listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: It gets you to retell the story, even though you might have already told me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometimes I don't know when you're pretending.
[SPEAKER_04]: Radio magic.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's commentary in the chat room, Rob, about you saying y'all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do they not like the y'all?
[SPEAKER_04]: Am I not allowed to say that?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can say it right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm from NorCal?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, what was I supposed to say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Y'all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Y'all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, depending on certain parts, you-ins.
[SPEAKER_04]: You-ins?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And J-Rod in chat wants to point out, my girlfriend also has cramps.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coincidence or evil plot?
[SPEAKER_04]: Coincidence.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're here to make your Christmas suffer a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could it be a conspiracy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are all the gamer chicks on one big cycle?
[SPEAKER_02]: Only unless we've all been hanging out in the same room for at least two months.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you know, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's your unwanted education.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh lordy.
[SPEAKER_02]: That if you get women living in the same place for long enough, their cycles will align.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I've heard it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I was making the joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: That all the gaming girls, you know, like somehow via Xbox Live, I don't know, have all gotten on the same cycle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Man, that must suck in college.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, actually, because... It's like, everybody hide!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the two... No, it was actually true for my dorm.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can bet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I had a suite.
[SPEAKER_02]: So me, my roommate, and our suite mate...
[SPEAKER_02]: We're all like, chocolate, wine, now!
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, we were poor, so it was, you know, Strawberry Hill or Apple Wine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mad Dog?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: We at least had the taste to get the tasty Boone's Farm stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Everclear.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it was Alabama, and you could get Everclear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, look, we're going to get into how was your gaming week as we always start off the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not how was your vagina, but how was your gaming week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Vagina Wars.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually turned on my DS and then turned it right off when I got a phone call and forgot to play again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played some Ragnarok, because I'm still playing!
[SPEAKER_02]: And I've decided that I might actually go back to World of Warcraft for just a little bit, just to see what the new expansion's like.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I really don't think I'll stick with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's more of a, eh, why not, while I'm waiting for the Star Trek MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to warn you, if you're not at least level 55 in World of Warcraft, you won't see anything in the new expansion.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all endgame content and a new class.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, sadly, there won't be a lot there for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to play a Draenei.
[SPEAKER_04]: Draeneis are fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And name her... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a name I was going to name her.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the Draenei women talk like Natasha from Rocky and Bullwinkle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boris Luke is moose in school.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's fearless leader, darling.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that would suit.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I am going to, in the next week, download Cho Inaki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I know what else it was!
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually sat and watched a playthrough of Abadox.
[SPEAKER_04]: And how was that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just as shitty as I remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I played more Grand Theft Auto on PC
[SPEAKER_05]: and I've actually started tweaking some stuff now because they've made it a little bit easier for you to actually edit stuff in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just kind of have to know what you're doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little bit like the cheat device was on the Grand Theft Auto on PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Similar type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have a file that you edit some of the amounts with.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, it's a lot easier on the PC version because everything is labeled for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I made a pistol that would catch a cop car and fire in one shot and that was funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, but just, um, some of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then the game crashed because I shot too many cars and caught them on fire.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently I didn't like that much fire at one time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, but it's kind of like finding a balance, you know, between, um, crazy shit and, uh... Between fuego and non...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, well, see, my next thing I want to do is, because you can make your gunfire have so much kickback to it, like if you shoot somebody, it'll knock them over, or you can make them, like, fly away and that type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I want to do that, but I also want to have the trainer where I have infinite health, so I can basically, you know, catapult myself with rockets, you know, across the map.
[SPEAKER_05]: That might be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, eventually I'll do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there aren't that many mods out there for it right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's like a drifting mod, a mod that changes the car names to, I guess, realistic cars.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, you know, the rocket pistol thing, which I was trying to do that myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the first time it glitched out where I actually couldn't select that pistol anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then I figured out what I was doing wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just not quite to where I need it to be yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: But soon it will be.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then of course more Grand Theft Auto 4 multiplayer at work and that's still fun and other than Grand Theft Auto I've been playing Dissida the new Final Fantasy fighting game and it's
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: in a gentle way that you appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's gentle rape.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just like, oh my god, this is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: That can't be rape if you're willing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So just say that maybe it's a bit of sadism.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be like a hot chick all of a sudden getting naked and thrusting herself upon you.
[SPEAKER_05]: But see, at first you're kind of like, whoa, whoa, whoa, what's going on here?
[SPEAKER_05]: But then you just go with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't know, I haven't had that happen
[SPEAKER_05]: Put it on the PS3 or something like that, and then also expand upon it, because Dissida is basically fighting, that's all it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have a little bit of cutscenes and stuff like that, but there's no actual roleplaying and running around and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they kept the fighting system in here, and say they did a Kingdom Hearts type of thing where you have all the different characters from the different games, they could really have a kickass game on their hands, but Dissida itself is going to be really awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Dark Knight in chat at chat.orange.com jokes Dissida, aka Urgeis2 No, it's not even close to Urgeis.
[SPEAKER_05]: No way.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not even remotely close.
[SPEAKER_04]: A.A.A.A.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, he has no name.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just the Warrior of Light.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Poop, if it's my cartridge.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's not Poop.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's cool, though, because as you level up the characters, they level up in all the other levels that they appear in as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I did have a party in Final Fantasy because I'm this mature.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it was Ass, Assy, Butt, and Poop.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the last time when we played it on, because I have the WonderSwan one in Japanese, I actually sat down and tried to figure out the names to put in it in Katakana, so we had Dan, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan made Eric for some reason, one of his buddies who's kind of not all that bright.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't remember who we named the last one.
[SPEAKER_02]: My Chrono Trigger cartridge actually still has my friend's save on it that has me and there's Luca.
[SPEAKER_05]: But seriously though, like, you know, not to interrupt or anything, this game could be like Kingdom Hearts, but without...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, it's in Japanese, so I can't read that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But maybe he did in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: All righty then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you've been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Played a little more Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why I'm still playing Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to come visit Nelly's Village.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the thing is, I tried... You know, I don't understand this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently you have to talk to some idiot in the town to get a friend code.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to talk to the guy at the gate.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how you've done it in all the last versions, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that's great, but why the hell do I have to talk to somebody who has a friend code assigned to the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that way it connects to Nintendo Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_02]: It also is different per player.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and so once you get it from Nintendo Wi-Fi, then you can access it whenever in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you just have to do it that one time.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I have to do that, but I haven't gone around to that yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Unpsychopedia is so strange.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's also a picture of one of the little aliens bursting out of someone's stomach.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's this picture taken by hospital staff one minute after Lavos was born.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cute little scamp, wasn't he?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think somebody in chat made a Lavos joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something about, oh, Dan Shadow says, you think that's fun?
[SPEAKER_04]: Try playing Chrono Trigger and name everyone Lavos.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what that's supposed to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, the only new game I played this week was the free game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love free games, and there was a free game that hit Xbox Live this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you all remember, but it's Doritos Dash of Destruction.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's an XNA game that somebody made, or it was a concept for a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It won some type of contest.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it was an XNA contest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Doritos made people try to come up with a concept for a game, and then they made a Doritos game.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you can play a T-Rex and chase said trucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's kind of an interesting little cat and mouse concept.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I've got to say, it's better than Yaris as far as free games go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this something I would have paid money for?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe $5.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's that cute little cat and mouse thing going on where you can play the truck, try and do the deliveries, or you can go in and out and try to eat the trucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that made it kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't think it's anything that's going to have a lasting value to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of the levels kind of look the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus you just would unexplainably get these power-ups that didn't seem to do a whole lot of anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the game was handing out achievements like candy.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was really one of those games where it was like, push start.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Texas Hold'em was free for a little while.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're marbles!
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, besides that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, like, what on the Xbox 360 did I lose?
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope it wasn't any of the rock band tracks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just not gonna notice they're gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or if it was, like, hopefully it was one of, like, the crappy ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can always re-download them.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about the original rock band songs, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, you'd have to re-download them unless you, um, sold them.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you sold it back, then you're kind of screwed there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually never did sell Rock Band back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still know people who still have Rock Band if you need it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't checked.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't checked to see what got corrupted.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I haven't played Rock Band since the transfer.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that was probably the largest chunk of my old hard drive was Rock Band songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I have a lot of Rock Band songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I have the Rock Band 1 exported, the entire No Doubt album, and just like at least 20 download songs on top of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I finally bought a...
[SPEAKER_05]: A hard drive transfer thing that's not part of Microsoft's transfer kit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually something to dump files to your hard drive and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: To get, well, on top of potential modding things, to basically move the two PopCap games saves that PopCap for some reason said, No, you can't transfer to a memory unit.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to be dicks about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, yeah, I love how on Twitter they're like, oh yeah, we're looking into that.
[SPEAKER_05]: He thinks we're looking into that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw you got a response, though, that was basically they couldn't figure it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, their response was like, you have to re-download the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, what the fuck does that have to do with my save file, stupid?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not, like, transferring the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm talking about the save file.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, wait a minute, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I theorized a couple weeks ago when this first came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe this is something that was kind of out of their control.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, they just... It's not out of their control.
[SPEAKER_05]: All the other games before and after them have allowed me to move the save files to a memory unit and, you know, move it to another hard drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: You may not be able to copy them to other profiles.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That makes perfect sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: But not being able to move it at all, that's retarded.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what else did that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hexic HD won't let you move this thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, screw you, Microsoft, and screw you, PopCap.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to do it anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will find a way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know we have people from PopCap that listen, so I hope... Well, then fine!
[SPEAKER_05]: Screw you both!
[SPEAKER_05]: Bejeweled 2 and Zuma...
[SPEAKER_05]: for whatever reason, your stupid save files won't move.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not the game, the game is fine, because I can delete it, download it, move it, whatever I need to do, but the save files will not move.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm assuming this is a big crisis in your house, because Zuma is like one of the only games your wife will play.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's not a big crisis, but it's annoying, because if my wife... It's the principle of the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, we put in a lot of time to Bejeweled 2, which I might add, the achievements are...
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn near impossible to get.
[SPEAKER_05]: But for whatever reason, we put a lot of time into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially Zuma.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zuma gets pretty hard too.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least that I can get some achievements in.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Jewel 2 is a bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, I don't want to lose all my progress in that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care if it's a crappy game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's still progress and I don't want to lose it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But in the fact that
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: S.S.J.
[SPEAKER_05]: 100 Matt wants to point out now if Nelly lost her Excite Truck save file then shit would hit the fan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, but it might give her another reason to play it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do want to say, though, since Matt brought up PopCap, I did play the new Bejeweled thing on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have like a Bejeweled tournament thing on Facebook where you get like a minute to get as many points as you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: And right now, I'm on the top of the leaderboard, at least of my friends list, because you can't see everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can see your friends list.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got 55,000 in one minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got really lucky with the chains.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I can say.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I thought that was kind of cute that they put that on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, so anything else for Gaming Weeks around?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody?
[SPEAKER_02]: I played rock band.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like the first one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that's what Julie got.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I have to say I've forgotten how much I hate the rock band guitars.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now I remember because it was forced upon me.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I hate them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're flimsy.
[SPEAKER_02]: They may be better for strumming, but most of the time the keys stick on both of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they wouldn't sync properly for the wireless one.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was just a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: And next time I go over there, I'm bringing my Guitar Hero controllers.
[SPEAKER_02]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did watch a lot of Netflix stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't the Netflix thing on 360 great?
[SPEAKER_04]: I watched a documentary this week because now Netflix... On penguins?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Netflix got smart and they added an HD category on their Watch Instantly thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I was looking at HD movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I watched a documentary because I've been all about the obscure documentaries on Netflix.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I watched an obscure documentary about...
[SPEAKER_04]: The people that dress up as superheroes on Hollywood Boulevard and post for pictures.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's called Confessions of a Superhero was the name of the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was interesting seeing the reasons why people did it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some did it because they were obsessed with their character.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people did it just for another job.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people did it because they have issues.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of issues.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, I want to come over and watch documentaries with you now that I don't have school.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except I have work.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the sad thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have work.
[SPEAKER_04]: But not every day.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to come watch documentaries with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, documentary night.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll try to see who can find the most obscure documentary.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because there are some obscure documentaries on Netflix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of documentaries, I got a screener copy of E!
[SPEAKER_05]: Athletes, which if I remember correctly, I think that's the film that Scott Rubin actually did some of the shooting for.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's about those two Counter-Strike teams.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they came to Eldorado Hills to do part of the tournament there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he was filming a second unit or whatever on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tiger Claw Confessions of a Superhero
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that sounds cruel, but I just didn't see... Her costume was decent, but I just didn't see... She did not look like Wonder Woman as much as Batman looked like Batman or Superman looked like Superman.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was only one Wonder Woman ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she was in the 70s.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she was freaking fantastic, and I really enjoyed seeing her in Sky High.
[SPEAKER_04]: You were going to say something, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought I've actually seen part of that show or something that had to do with those people that were on Hollywood Boulevard.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might.
[SPEAKER_04]: A hostile one in chat says, I've seen that doc.
[SPEAKER_04]: They even said that people were protective.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I'm the only one who can play Superman on this block.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_04]: Elmo wants some money for drugs!
[SPEAKER_04]: Give Elmo money!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby, the man who does the show before us, is doing his annual year-end special next week, and he's going to have some guests on his show and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: He might be starting a little early, and we might let him run a little late to help out.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Vito!
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a little.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that means, it made me realize, that means next week is our year-end show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't even thinking about it, but yeah, next week's the year-end show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you believe it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, because it comes the same time every year.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there will be no show on the week of January 11th.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is no show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to be in Hawaii.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will not be here the weekend of the 31st.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I'm going to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_02]: Presents.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should do our gift exchange.
[SPEAKER_04]: I may go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel bad, though, because I didn't get gifts today.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am doing something different and experimental this year for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I already gave you part of yours already.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I was going to say, I thought Prince of Persia was my gift.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, no, not Prince of Persia, Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Prince of Persia, that was a freebie.
[SPEAKER_04]: That too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you've already got me a gift, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but this is cool, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw this at the store and I had to get it for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, yay, gifts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry we don't have a camera tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: This sucks for TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't worry, HitStun, we will not cut off the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they go a little long, we'll deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Star Trek Pez Dispensers
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to, actually, I was, because the artwork is a different style, and so I wasn't looking at the character designs, I was reading Ragu no Raku on I was like, oh shit, because I read like an illiterate, you know, child.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: In Japanese.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gave Rob sparklies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, oh, I'm opening it right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, there's glitter and glitter and more glitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, this looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, it's like, oh, I've seen this in the store before.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the Press Your Luck DVD game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Play at home edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I was going to get you the prices right, but I didn't think you liked Drew Carey so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so it didn't have Bob Barker or, you know, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, but Press Your Luck is epic.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's old school.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I made sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it does have the new host, but seeing as the other one died.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's got the old whammy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it has the old whammy.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to play a DVD game or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Want to check that out?
[SPEAKER_04]: The box?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got, I got, I got, um, well, Matt, tell your president.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I couldn't think of what to get you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to read the card, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I tried to get you something useful.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty cool there, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I don't know what that book is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't want to open it, you know, so I don't know if that's a manual or like an art book or something that they threw in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to open it right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, but I figured, you know, Ragnarok
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Dark Knight brought up something about the Price is Right that reminded me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you see the, in chat room, did you see the talk about the guy on the Price is Right that nailed the showcase on the head?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the manual.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was joking about how I think that's a giant conspiracy.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's more in my life journal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hitstun says, does Ragnarok DS have any sort of online play?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a few players, like local.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is fantastic!
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you do your attacks and spellcasting by stylus control.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what a happy holiday we have here on Orange Lounge Radio this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except for me, I'm a Grinch, because I didn't give out presents tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's alright, don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm doing something different this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, nice!
[SPEAKER_02]: It has the skill trees in here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just didn't want to forget these all in my house and I started to get to the point now where I'm like, whose gift is that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Whose gift is that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh crap, I gotta get rid of these.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, woo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that we've all been bitten by Christmas spirit.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's two classes that are just for the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're gonna hear little tidbits about Ragnarok DS all night long.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, in fact, DJ Dark Knight in chat says Jamie wishes she could bring her online character to the DS game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, my characters are like over 120 something right now, so, because I'm playing on a private server.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I was going to say, plus you play on bootleg servers, so I don't think that would be a coach.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, Dark Knight's fucking hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like J-Rod, Star Trek, Pez, Spencer, what a thoughtful way to carry around your ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Star Trek Pest Dispensers
[SPEAKER_05]: I was like, dude, I gotta pick this up for Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I thought about getting you another Imagine game this year for the DS, but I figured I'd actually give you something useful instead of, you know... I'm putting pictures up in a second.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so, wait, is that going on your Twitter?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'll link the picture in the chat room because my Twitter's blocked from almost everybody, so... Oh, you can log into the OLR one if you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on and get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to go from such happy, joyous, wonderful news to not-so-great news tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want you to listen to the first stories in tonight's show and see if they all have something in common because it's kind of sad, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of a bummer we have to follow up such positive stuff with this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Factor 5 has closed its doors.
[SPEAKER_05]: The developer known for such games as Lair...
[SPEAKER_05]: and some better games as Star Wars Rogue Squadron and even like the Turrican series.
[SPEAKER_05]: And apparently they were being rumored to be working on the new Kid Icarus and Superman games.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they have closed their... Superman 128?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the Curse of Spider-Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, it's Superman, I tell you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a new Superman, not tying in with the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they have closed their doors, and it was supposedly confirmed by Matt Casamani from IGN, who had, I believe, received an email from...
[SPEAKER_05]: and Julian at Factor 5.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says, Hi Matt, how have you been?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wanted to contact you with some late-breaking news.
[SPEAKER_05]: We just learned Inside Sources that developer Factor 5 has officially closed the doors as of today.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's some pretty big news considering that those guys have been around for quite a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's definitely a real shame and I hope this information is helpful to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, you know who we have to blame for this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Lair?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Ronald Reagan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Reaganomics.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, that's one of the big contributors to our financial crisis right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, perhaps it continues on in these other stories we're getting into, such as about Electronic Arts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Electronic Arts had to cut 1,000 jobs and closed
[SPEAKER_04]: Black Box Studio in Vancouver is going to be merged with the EA Studio in nearby Burnaby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, so this is going to save the company $120 million annually, but costing them about $60 million in restructuring charges while this goes on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of a bummer for those folks that got laid off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to hear about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had some friends that worked at EA.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not people I talk to every day, so I don't know if anybody I know is affected by this, but still, my thoughts are with you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is very unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there actually is going for Midway too.
[SPEAKER_02]: The rumor was that they were going to be laying off around 160 people from the Chicago studio for the most part because of financial issues.
[SPEAKER_02]: The official word is that they're laying 25% off of its workforce.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's about 180 people.
[SPEAKER_02]: 130 people from Chicago and 45 from Austin.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Austin operation itself has closed.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there's supposed to be some other games that were unannounced that are being suspended.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're just trying to, I guess, mitigate whatever the costs are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently the Mortal Kombat team is safe.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can all sleep easy, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: and even more upsetting for me, Free Radical has closed shop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently their doors were locked and all the employees were locked out while the company was having some final meetings deciding what the fate of the company was going to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, Free Radical is known for the
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: The good news is, though, is they may not be out of work for long.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, some other companies are looking to purchase Free Radical and kind of absorb them into their, you know, developing firms.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's kind of good because I want to see TimeSplitters 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was kind of neat since they were, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess the new studio had been formed a few months before this whole, I guess, thing happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this was working out before everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe he kind of figured that this was going to happen anyways and so kind of a precautionary measure.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I'm wondering if this guy didn't kind of see the writing on the wall.
[SPEAKER_05]: GameGuru in chat says this is what happens when you don't support the console that won that's the Wii my friends wait a minute look at EA they just laid off a bunch of people they've been big supporters of the Wii right?
[SPEAKER_04]: even sort of yeah
[SPEAKER_04]: GameGuru says the economic crisis just accelerated the problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't really say Free Radical wasn't supporting the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've only made one game since the new consoles have come out, you know, Haze.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's not really fair.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, another company seems to be cutting back on staff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Asper is the name of the company and they are based out of Austin.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're probably most known for some of their porting work.
[SPEAKER_04]: They ported Call of Duty 4 and Sims 2 to the PC and the Mac respectively.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, so no comments out of Asper.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should note, though, that that story was just a rumor status only.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, it unfortunately would not be surprising considering all the other news we're hearing this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, in other words, they're like, oh, fuck, bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan got laid off in the money store.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that what happens?
[SPEAKER_02]: Similar?
[SPEAKER_02]: They just went in, found a bunch of people walking out with stuff, and so they're like, just pack your desks and go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: My gosh.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they bribed us to stay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's my question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this going to continue?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this was six in a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we going to see more throughout the next few weeks, or what's going to happen?
[SPEAKER_02]: Blame Reagan, blame Bush.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's next?
[SPEAKER_02]: and the Republicans.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, wait a minute, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's not get too political here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, seriously, if you look at it historically, the reason why we're in all this financial shit is because of Reagan's whole Reaganomics crap and the fact that people have decided just to screw us over instead of putting money back into the economy where it goes.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're spending money on a war we didn't need to spend money on.
[SPEAKER_02]: and all this other bullshit it just should have looked out what the country needs and go for the best thing and now as a result we're seeing and it's not just this there's other companies like I went to Old Folsom today and I say yesterday and at least a third of the old shops there were either closed or going out of business the coffee place I go to they close down without a word it's just you're seeing more and more businesses closing down it's not just in the video game industry
[SPEAKER_04]: Regardless of whatever path we took to get here, how are we going to get out?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess would be my question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is the end in sight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we going to get out of this anytime soon?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's it going to take?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we just need to buy more video games or what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's a lot more complex than that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, a lot of it is going to be consumers, you know, having more faith in the industries and, you know, putting their money into product.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's also going to mean that to be able to put money into the purchase of products, there need to be the jobs available.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's very much right now a catch 22.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn if you do, damn if you don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really going to take, I think, the companies being able to be in a financial position to where they can start hiring again and start putting out more product so that these people who now have fresh incomes can go out and put their money back into the money flow.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see what happens in 2009.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully it won't be much longer.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, all this news makes us very sad and upset and angry that all these great game studios are just closing their doors.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, some not so great, but they're all closing their doors.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just stinks.
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole thing stinks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so we dedicate the FU's of the week to those without a job this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: My first F.U.
[SPEAKER_02]: goes towards my girl bits for hurting me and causing me pain.
[SPEAKER_02]: Therefore, I have to turn around and hurt other people and cause them pain because they don't have to endure this type of thing, so we have to share it with them somehow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, an F.U.
[SPEAKER_02]: goes on behalf of one of my friends who didn't necessarily say this herself, but I'm passing it on for her to the lack of proper transplants for her dad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki,
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to rude people at the stores, especially at this time of year.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was some lady in front of us when we were trying to buy some, you know, gifts.
[SPEAKER_05]: And first off, she's taking forever with her transaction.
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: FU the rude people.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then there's a ton of people who can't drive correctly, especially now in the rain, so... Screw them, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, my FU of the week goes to the fact that I'm feeling pains in my side, and I don't know if I'm just imagining it, or if it's something weird happening again, or what have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll try to go to the doctor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it is my uterus, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, I don't know, like, I just get freaked out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been a hell of a year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want 2008 to go die in a fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: First of all, I would like to tell the entire chat room, don't wish assassination, that's your wishing murder on somebody.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, complete incapacitation of both Bush and Cheney would be fantastic if someone were to do that, because that would put Pelosi in charge until Obama takes over.
[SPEAKER_02]: She is the Speaker of the House.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I want to know, and my other FU goes to selfish people.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: In early 2009, we'll be receiving a brand new game from the creator of such wonderful games as Katamari Damacy and all the other sequels.
[SPEAKER_05]: Takahashi is releasing Nobi Nobi Boy on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had a few videos that came out this week for it, and I still don't know what the hell this game's about.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like you're this stretchy thing that...
[SPEAKER_05]: Try to hook a bunch of things up with your body and I don't know what exactly that's supposed to be for.
[SPEAKER_05]: But apparently you can stretch your body, you can devour things.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not really sure what exactly you do, but it's supposed to be coming out in Japan on January 29th for 800 yen.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the US probably around the same time, so early 2009.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but this looks really weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, even, like, Katamari, you know, you can watch a tree and then get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's, oh, you roll over things and your ball gets bigger.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is like a giant tube thing eating things and tying things up with its body.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't get what the point is.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds fantastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like Bizarro Snake.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is like a Bizarro Snake.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, you know, everyone's, like, all happy and stuff, and then he starts eating people, and it's like, oh my god, this isn't good at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eating people is great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nom, nom, nom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobby Nobby's made of people.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's people!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, LittleBigPlanet got some updates this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It got two patches back-to-back, 1.06 and 1.07.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1.06, now it upgraded the moderation feature of the game, which a lot of people would say was badly needed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, your unpublished levels can be edited by creators.
[SPEAKER_04]: They will not be erased forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, believe it or not,
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is just what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I clicked on the link in the chat room that was posted by TigerClaw.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I think we're covering later in the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, then never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I get.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, how about some different news about SingStar?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're doing wireless microphones that will be out next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're...
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually saying that there's going to be 100 trial packs also available to, I guess, just a number of different SingStar followers on their MySpace.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the packs are going to be two wireless microphones, USB receiver, a mini BUSB cable, and four AA batteries.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want one for SingStar ABBA, which, by the way...
[SPEAKER_04]: There is now a SingStar ABBA theme in the PlayStation Network store that you can download for your PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if we know it all yet, but it's coming out next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Here, that's coming out also in Europe, or may have already come out.
[SPEAKER_05]: SingStar Queen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice!
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard there was a Queen one coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm totally going to buy that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's coming out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_05]: That is exciting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Queen is all sorts of awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Queen is very awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to have the videos and everything, I bet, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Rob, what is your favorite Queen song?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I have to stick with the old Bohemian Rhapsody, but I do have a big love for Bicycle.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about you, Matt?
[SPEAKER_05]: Bohemian Rhapsody and No One Wants to Live Forever, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: My favorite would be Somebody to Love.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my favorite of all time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's a great song.
[SPEAKER_02]: My second is Killer Queen.
[SPEAKER_04]: These are all good songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait for this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know the only thing that would be better?
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be SingStar Journey.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know I had to say it.
[SPEAKER_05]: SingStar Heart.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, now, it would only be good... I think that they should just do a Queen Pack for Rock Band, because that would be a lot better.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do need to have SingStar Butt Rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: With Poison and Motley Crue and...
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they'd have to have Cinderella and Dokken and Night Ranger.
[SPEAKER_02]: And damn Yankees because of Ted Nugent.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ted Nugent!
[SPEAKER_05]: Everything's awesome and also from Sony.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pots upon 2 is out in Japan right now, but it will be coming to other regions in early 2009.
[SPEAKER_05]: February in probably North America.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um... Yeah, Patapon is actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't get to play a lot of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just kind of gave up on it after a while, but it was fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Definitely a unique little game, and, you know, I'd like to see more in that crazy style.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'd also like to see it, like, on other systems, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to have to always bring out the PSP to play this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Port that shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it'd look awesome on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Patapatapatapon!
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a very interesting little game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, I'm cold.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be even better if the buttons spelled out or sung out Damn Yankee songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I...
[SPEAKER_04]: Hate everything about your mother.
[SPEAKER_02]: That wasn't Damn Yankees.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm thinking Ugly Kid Joe.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking High Enough was Damn Yankees, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's fucking Ted Nugent.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ted Nugent eats meat and shoots guns.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like this man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw him on TV skinning a deer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ted Nugent's fucking hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, you won't be able to skin a deer in LittleBigPlanet, but you will get paint guns, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do have a challenge out there for you folks to make a level where you do skin a deer.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can probably do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to actually go back to Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: Queensryche is the shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although you misspelled it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because the lead singer of Queensryche is a trained opera singer.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he's just got this fantastic voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like to see Sackboy's House of Blood in...
[SPEAKER_04]: and LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see some really disturbing levels.
[SPEAKER_05]: One time, and I just never got around to actually trying to make anything in this game, but thought about it, making a Saw-themed level, but I couldn't figure out how I could do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is.
[SPEAKER_04]: But so why...
[SPEAKER_04]: Why then are there these new trophies?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because shouldn't I get to play it still if somebody else makes the level using it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or am I going to get locked out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: The Holiday Pack is now apparently out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was supposed to come out December 18th for $2.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's the Festive Level Pack, and it's supposed to contain two new costumes, some new material, new objects, six new decorations, and tons and tons and tons of new stickers.
[SPEAKER_04]: But however, with this pack, levels themselves are not apparently included.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they just have the stickers, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess you put this in your own levels or what have you because you can create new Christmas tree looking things and everything with the stickers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, speaking of stickers, when are we going to get that feature where I can put photos from the hard drive into the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's the other big thing we're waiting on.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it was in an advertisement.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's false advertising.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bitch, whine, moan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_05]: You're never going to get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: SuperStreetFighter 2 Turbo HD Remix
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, there's a lot of suckers out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got so many different versions of Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not even funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's 250,000 people sucking the cock of nostalgia.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically broken both day one and week one sales records and is slated to break 30-day sale records as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's supposed to be the...
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, according to Capcom, it's quoted as saying it's on its way to becoming the highest-grossing digital title ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Besides that, they had the good sense to use Udon Kru to do their art, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't sell one to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, unfortunately, this week, there aren't that many choices for you to go purchase stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it is the week of Christmas, and a lot of game publishers aren't exactly putting their games out this week because...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not a lot of time to purchase them.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there are a few that are putting out their games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, well, they're games, alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Candice Kane's Candy Factory on the DS is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, the Spore comic book creator.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really know if that's a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's more software, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's coming out nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Mystery PI Portrait of a Thief on DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I swear that I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, on the PlayStation 3, you also get Alone in the Dark.
[SPEAKER_04]: Far Cry 2 and Bioshock get their Japanese translations, as well as another port of Civ Revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: But also some other games.
[SPEAKER_04]: White Knight Chronicles is coming out this week, as well as another game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea what this is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's an actual gaming stick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, it's not a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like joystick.
[SPEAKER_04]: They call the... Don't laugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the Roid Stick DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: There were a couple games I missed, but I don't...
[SPEAKER_05]: Fun Fun Mini Golf on the Wii Tiki Towers on the Wii I think those are both download games and then Dreamer Horse Trainer and Dreamer Puppy Trainer on DS
[SPEAKER_04]: Peekman gets its Wii upgrade this week as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: or Pikmin, Pikmin, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that's that Biohazard Zero.
[SPEAKER_04]: That might be what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 2, Lego Batman comes out this week and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the handhelds, you have on the Nintendo DS...
[SPEAKER_04]: Biohazard, Deadly Silence, Happy My Sweets, Phantasy Star Zero, Sony PSP,
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Maxx Portable, Black Square Cherry Blossom Portable, Biohazard Degeneration I'm totally jealous.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our branch of my work that's in Dallas that houses most of our game reps Genius Products is bringing out that game Scratch to playtest for them You know that new DJing game that's supposed to be like Beatmania?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, with the Newmark turntables or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you can get some pictures or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's only in Dallas.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't give a crap about that stuff anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm totally excited to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's move on around the world with more releases.
[SPEAKER_02]: Two things for the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: The 23rd is Savage Moon on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And on the 26th, Boxing Day is 100 Classic Book Collection.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just not a big week in games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I reckon not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have to do the release dates no matter what, even if it's a slow week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And don't expect next week to be much better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's not.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know what is pretty big?
[SPEAKER_05]: The text in Banjo-Kazooie now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because there's that brand new patch for those people that own the 14-inch standard definition tube TVs.
[SPEAKER_05]: You now can read your text in Banjo-Kazooie and suffer through the dialogue of that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hurrah!
[SPEAKER_04]: So, um... Well, thank heavens, because, you know, I was just waiting for the... No, actually, a lot of people really were waiting for something like this to come out, because if you play it on the small TV, this game's next to impossible to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm spoiled with my HDTV, so I need to just stop taunting those that don't have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Correct?
[SPEAKER_04]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, we're just about to the end of Part A tonight, but hey, we've got to take some time to recognize gaming's classics, and that's what we do here in a segment we call the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, DarkSakura, what have you picked for this very special holiday week for the kids and adults out there to recognize this week in gaming?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've picked a bit of NES and Commodore 64 for you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Joy, in the form of Maniac Mansion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maniac Mansion is a weird little game.
[SPEAKER_04]: This music's from the NES version.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was originally on the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_02]: So where...
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually is the game that the Scum Engine was created for, the script creation utility for Maniac Mansion.
[SPEAKER_02]: And LucasArts used it for about 10 more years to keep playing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It also has Chuck LaPlante in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically, there were changes in the people that lived there, and then people that were in the hospital started disappearing, so then there were a bunch of people who decided to go into the house because a local cheerleader turned up missing, and they decided to go through the entire house, which is like this big...
[SPEAKER_02]: B-movie type horror house thing with tentacles and an evil genius and the pool.
[SPEAKER_02]: The pool is the best part.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has multiple endings.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can go through.
[SPEAKER_02]: It depends on who lives, who dies.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can have a perfect ending.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can have the adversary win.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can have them famous by publishing his autobiography.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can feed him to a plant.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: and you can get your players in the game killed and it has different red herrings in it and
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kind of different weird stuff in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The different characters in there is you have the sort of James Dean type character.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have a New Wave musician.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have a photographer.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have a novelist.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have a big nerd who's really scared.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay, nerd!
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got a punk rock girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got Surfer in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: They all have their different strengths and weaknesses.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I've played this, of course, on the NES, because that's what I had.
[SPEAKER_02]: The different versions there were, there was also a PC that also played...
[SPEAKER_02]: Apple II, Amiga, Atari ST, NES
[SPEAKER_02]: and there is actually an enhanced version with updated graphics that's out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it had a sitcom based on the series.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you ever remember watching that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I remember that!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh god, that was not very long, but yeah, I remember there was.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game was pretty big when it came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there was a fan remake that's called Maniac Mansion Deluxe that runs on Windows that has really...
[SPEAKER_02]: Enhanced Graphics and Music That was actually borrowed from Day of the Tentacle And it's supposed to fix a lot of bugs and inconsistencies And they put in some different changes to make it a little bit harder It's also playable in Day of the Tentacle Maniac Mansion And of course then there was It was really, really censored though on the NES There were a lot of stuff changed Um
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_02]: The guy, though, that ported it, Douglas Crockford, put out a memoir that was called The Expurgation of Maniac Mansion, which was basically him going, God, Nintendo, you suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: about how strict Nintendo was for what they could allow in the game and what they couldn't and about some things that he agreed with taking out like Edna having sexually themed threats to the characters and different things including the use of violence, non-violence and that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it was pretty heavily censored, like I said.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, like I was saying before, it was my favorite part of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whenever I would just get really tired of playing it and go to hell with this, I would go to the pool, drain it, and push the red button so that the house would explode.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just what I did every time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, I'm tired of playing!
[SPEAKER_02]: Explode!
[SPEAKER_02]: Game over.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't think the graphics on the NES version were that great compared to the computer one.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is strange, because I'm talking about a game on the Commodore 64, but... The Commodore 64 version was actually really nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I personally did not play it, but I have seen it played.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, like I said, I didn't have a Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a click-go-at-em.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to say, though, as far as this type of game goes on the NES, there is a game I do prefer, these point-and-click games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shadowgate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shadowgate was great!
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what part I would always get stuck at?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was where you went into the portal and you had a limited time with your... You had to actually have some item to make it through the portal.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're gonna need to do that in a future week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna have to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually never finished Shadowgate, but I love Shadowgate.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just interesting because you don't think about these point-and-click games a lot on the NES.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there were some really good ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um, yeah, this, it's a really good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, also, uh, some of the, uh, LucasArts, uh, I was just looking at the list of the different LucasArts, uh, um, titles that were supposed to go along with the SCUMM engine.
[SPEAKER_02]: And let me get back to that because I was just on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was, um, I think a couple of Monkey Island games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, uh, Labyrinth and Loom.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think I've covered Loom before.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is strange because I think Loom came out before Maniac Mansion, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was after.
[SPEAKER_02]: No?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it was after.
[SPEAKER_04]: Strange.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was after Monkey Island even, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, and actually one of the Sam and Max games was supposed to use it, but they cancelled it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sam & Max Freelance Police Full Throttle Payback Monkey Island 2, LeChuck's Revenge, Indiana Jones and the Fate of Atlantis
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If there's nothing else to add, then your classic game of the week is... Blow up the house!
[SPEAKER_04]: Maniac Mansion on the NES or Commodore 64, whatever system you prefer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maniac Mansion.
[SPEAKER_04]: And don't forget to drain the water from the pool and blow up the house!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's DarkSakura's favorite thing to do, correct?
[SPEAKER_04]: Indeed!
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we're going to take a quick break here on Orange Lounge Radio and do some music here.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when we come back, we have plenty more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, sorry, the podcast folks, you won't get to hear the music.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just the way it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, copyright rules and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we'll be back really soon with more of Orange Lounge Radio, more stories, hopefully a little bit happier than all the layoff stories we had in Part A. Do you think we can arrange that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Get some happier stuff in Part B tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we'll try.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, we're going to go ahead and take a break, and we will be right back.
[SPEAKER_04]: And welcome back to more of Orange Lounge Radio and this Part B of our podcast for this December the 21st of 2008.
[SPEAKER_04]: And happy holidays to you guys out there listening to the program.
[SPEAKER_04]: We talked a lot about different things going on in Part A. Unfortunately, a lot of really not-so-happy holidays going on for a lot of folks in the game industry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bummer to hear that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We talked also about some other news, including some sales stuff about HD Remix and some little Big Planet updates and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Still going to be $10.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently they ran into some unexpected technical difficulties.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least they didn't call it Balloon Knot Hole Island.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that would have been really bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be horrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why the delay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Unexpected technical difficulties.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever that's supposed to mean.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everyone took some time off for the holidays.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still don't think it's a good name to name it Knothole Island anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just makes me think of like a glory hole.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, haven't you ever heard of what a balloon knot is?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's supposed to be like an asshole.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you know what a balloon knot looks like?
[SPEAKER_02]: An asshole.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this one helps in San Diego.
[SPEAKER_04]: And every time I hear Knothole Island, I keep thinking of a balloon knothole and it's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, who wants to visit an island with a bunch of assholes?
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a house in San Diego that looks like a sphincter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make all the gay jokes you want, but that does not sound appealing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I'll move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to eat a bagel while I'm talking and making jokes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to stop eating cookies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tiger Claw says every time I hear Knothole I'm thinking of Sonic AM Moving on
[SPEAKER_04]: 800-point Microsoft point cards now have made their way into the retail marketplace.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, you could only get 1,600 Microsoft points before.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was $19.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now you can get 800 Microsoft point cards at retailers for $9.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, hey, that would be one whole cent cheaper than buying them online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, but you have to pay tax.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're screwed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then you have to consider there's tax.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's good if you want to give a gift or if, like, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't have a credit card and you're a little kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you want to buy it as a gift, but it's a stocking stuffer, so maybe $20 is too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just buy it online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I want?
[SPEAKER_05]: World Peace?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not World Peace.
[SPEAKER_05]: Screw World Peace.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they're not available in most stores is those PlayStation Network cards.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I hate the PlayStation Network and how they do their payments online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's a little silly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, speaking of PlayStation Network, because you brought it up and I forgot to mention earlier in the show, we talked about PlayStation Home last week and I said I was going to get an OLR club as soon as they opened it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I guess I missed it because I went back online later in the week and I saw where you could buy a clubhouse online.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just hard to find.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not interested in it because you have to invite people into the club and you can only invite up to like 30 people.
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of an OLR club is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a cool one, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have more than 30 people in our chat room tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We probably would have more people now than we do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was something that people would be able to search and go into at their leisure, but I don't see how it's promotion for the show to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then I'd have to buy all the furniture, so forget it!
[SPEAKER_04]: Until home gets cooler, I protest.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, there are probably only about 30 of our listeners that actually have a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at the sales numbers.
[SPEAKER_04]: SJ100Matt in our chat room wants to point out, I see PSN cards in Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Red Entertainment says, not only that, clubs cost money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fail.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was willing to, like, for five bucks, I would have done it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it's an experiment.
[SPEAKER_04]: How much was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Five bucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Five bucks?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it five bucks per month or year?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still considering it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right now it's $5 with no reoccurring fee, but Sony is going to implement them at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just didn't say when.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, home doesn't suck enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, do we have the trophy rooms and stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, like most things, it's extremely early.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure home will be better in a year, but by then we will have all forgotten.
[SPEAKER_05]: Home is extremely late as it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's no time for being early.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's late.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can go back to other stuff now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sega!
[SPEAKER_04]: What about them?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it looks like there's been some ESRB ratings put out, so that means that there are going to be a number of games on Xbox Live and PlayStation Network from Sega.
[SPEAKER_02]: There will be Sonic 3, Comic Zone, Phantasy Star 2, and Gunstar Heroes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Woo-hoo!
[SPEAKER_02]: which are supposed to be out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there were, I guess, other releases.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, the previous releases were Sonic the Hedgehog, Sonic 2, Golden Axe, Echo the Dolphin, and Streets of Rage 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait a minute, but isn't Sega putting out that thing of like 40 games for like 20 bucks or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think that Sega wants as much money as possible?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sega!
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they giving me anything special?
[SPEAKER_04]: More achievements?
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're gonna give you the option to blur it out so that it looks all, like, you know, HD-like.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just buy the $20 thing when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless they're actually remaking everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which I highly doubt that they are.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something else coming to Xbox Live Arcade, kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure a lot of people are familiar with the MMORPG DOFUS.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have a game, I think it's called Wakfu.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now the islands of Wakfu are going to be coming to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's like an MMO, but not.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: An adventure beat-em-up?
[SPEAKER_04]: An adventure beat-em-up.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an adventure slash beat-em-up all-style game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says it can be played in a two-player team mode and will reveal never-before-seen background content from the world of Dofus and Wakfu.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really, because to me, the entire world of Dofus and Wakfu are unseen and I have not played either one.
[SPEAKER_05]: But hey, it's a different type of game and that's always welcome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bochikawa in chat asks, Wakfu, is that like beating people senseless with a frying pan?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it is, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that would be a great game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: PowerSwitch and stuff, it's really funky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like the PowerSwitch, there's a little button that's off-center on it, so if you push it in the center of your faceplate, it won't exactly trigger it every time.
[SPEAKER_05]: You kind of have to push to the right of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, and the way the eject button works is kind of similar.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little push-button switch, so I wouldn't be surprised if it wore out.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, you can always, if you can't get it to eject that way, just, you know, hit the middle button and select eject disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: Great, Jrod in chat says, I used to have to do that and it ended up where the disk drive wouldn't read anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember, they won't warranty it unless it red rings, so that's when you take a blowtorch to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, look, there's some other options, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: The other options were to slow down the disc rotation speed, but that was rejected because it would have slowed down the game loading times.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we can understand that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, apparently, the other option was to install little bumpers that would have cost the company between $35 to $75 million additional dollars.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I would think little bumpers, wouldn't that be maybe like a buck?
[SPEAKER_04]: A machine?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it's literally that little.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had a fix a long time ago when people were writing a scratch thing that was available online.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'd buy these little... It looked like a CD, and you would put it in the drive and kind of push it up, and it would stick little pads on there that would keep the disc from jiggling.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because basically what happens is since the disc has so much play inside the drive, it'll end up bending back to where it rubs up against the laser, and that's what carves a nice little...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the thing is that... And the big thing that the document shows is that Microsoft, what they eventually decided to do, they appended the manual with a warning and offered a disk replacement program.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, that was their big fix.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I believe something about like a sticker on the door, too, that you have to pull off that warns them not to tilt the machine when you play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, this was deemed insufficient by company employees via an internal email.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's apparently what happened anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it is kind of... I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a stupid fix, and really they should have just added those little bumpers to it, because it wouldn't have cost them $75 million.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, how many consoles do they have out there?
[SPEAKER_05]: They have like almost 15,000, you know, 15 million consoles, or not even really that many, but like over 10 million consoles, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, they're saying $75 million, so that's $750 per console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or no, that's $75 million.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'd be $0.75 per console, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: No, my math's all wrong today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Either way, it's not going to cost that much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft in chat says, but who the fuck moves around a console when playing a game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, some people own pets like my cat who likes to jump on consoles and she may knock it over.
[SPEAKER_05]: Luckily, I'm smart enough to know if the cat's nearby the console, I will lay it flat on the ground instead of tipping up and that's a rare occasion.
[SPEAKER_02]: We just tuck ours away where she can't get to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I mean, someone can bump it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, a court get pulled or something and knock the console over.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, there's all sorts of stuff that can happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's rare, but there are cases, though, I've been hearing where people are just getting a groove carved into it just from leaving it
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever happened to that controller that was supposedly coming out that had a better D-pad?
[SPEAKER_05]: I never saw that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And why they would do that for a limited amount of time is retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a very good question.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea why they would do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Tigerclaw wants to say...
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft needs to fix the tray eject problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people are experiencing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not the only one.
[SPEAKER_04]: and Bobby Blackwolf wanted to work in a cheap plug for his upcoming new show.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said the first episode of Friday Night Gaming will address that issue directly on stage with a company that repairs consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently one little shtick they're going to do on their show is actually repair consoles live on air.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have the device to do it, let alone the patience or the skill necessary.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't want to do any more news, we're done, we're out of here Have a great night everybody Bye
[SPEAKER_04]: So mailbagorangepontradio.com Let's read some of those emails.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey OLR, this is Amasa Tsuma.
[SPEAKER_02]: My question to you is if you were able to throw an object at someone, what would that object be and who would you throw it at?
[SPEAKER_02]: Must be non-lethal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does this have something to do with the bush shoe thing this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: It must.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually would, if I could completely get away with it without, you know, the Secret Service trying to jump me or anything, I would throw something at Bush.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would throw basically the waste of a homeless person at him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Feces?
[SPEAKER_04]: Feces.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, over all waste.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And say that it was his fault.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's hypothetical.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that I would physically do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm not breaking any sort of constitutional law by saying it would be cool if that were to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I answer?
[SPEAKER_04]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That crazy, messed up, fags-go-to-hell guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that guy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Phelps.
[SPEAKER_04]: Phelps, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like to throw a cream pie at him, but what a waste of a yummy pie.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I will throw... Throw rainbow sparkles at him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Feces pie!
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's some shit cake.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here, Fred Phelps, have a shit cake.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: Millions of dollars at my cell.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would mean you'd have to have it to throw it at yourself first.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I would have to have a million dollars in my hand, which means I would have acquired millions of dollars.
[SPEAKER_05]: Win-win either way, I have to look at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that we've invented a new word on the show tonight, shit cake.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to use that in a sentence three times this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shitcake, shitcake, shitcake.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up and go eat shitcake.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, last week you asked for Christmas e-cards and I decided to make one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Since I suck at Photoshop, I made it using this Microsoft Flash app that uses your 360 avatars.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope you will enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the Joker avatar in front of a fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I saw that as his signature on another forum.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, crew of OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is I, Katakos, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reese, here to tell you and to anyone else who plays Stepmania that I have made a song for download.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'll just post a link in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: But are you guys slash girl impressed with the 2009 PSP games?
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, has anyone heard anything about Elder Scrolls Travels for PSP?
[SPEAKER_02]: and do you really think there will be not T-H-E-I-R, it should be T-H-E-R-E?
[SPEAKER_02]: He's typing on a PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spelling is spelling.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also, E and R are right next to each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: E and I are not.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it uses QWERTY.
[SPEAKER_02]: And do you think that there will be a little big planet for PSP?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hope you enjoy this song as much as I enjoy your show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reese, BC, Canada.
[SPEAKER_02]: My birthday is December 26th.
[SPEAKER_02]: LOL15Woo.
[SPEAKER_04]: PSP, PSP, PSP
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell me some of the titles I have to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Star Ocean 2nd, where the second Star Ocean game is coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Resistance Reptribution, LocoRoco 2, Poptapon 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's supposedly a Motorstorm game and a little Big Planet game coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to think of what else.
[SPEAKER_05]: Monochemia is coming out on PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where's Africa PSP?
[SPEAKER_05]: Where's Africa PS3?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true, wasn't that supposed to be out by now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they were picking up a National Geographic license I was this close to importing it And I was like, fuck that, I can't run over the animals So I said, no, I'm not buying that Uh, Dissida, when it comes out in English Yes, Dissida will be coming out over here in the summer Okay God, I can't wait to play that Um
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, it looks like a better year, definitely, because 2008 sucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, like, you look at the releases, there was just not a lot of releases, period.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, there were some good ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, the Midnight Club LA remix is supposed to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, Star Ocean, the first one, was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could go for some more of the Final Fantasy ports to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be pretty awesome, like, you know, maybe six.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did we get all the questions in that email?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I don't doubt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on to the next email.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just thought I would update you folks as to what's going on regarding the situation with my stolen PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is from Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yes, he called in last week or the week before to mention that it got stolen, and he wanted us to kind of put out the word for all our fans in Buffalo, of which I don't know how many we have, but we tried.
[SPEAKER_02]: To date, the Buffalo Police have not done anything about it, and let's face it, unless the PS3 was jelly-filled or covered in sprinkles, they aren't likely to look for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Frankly, I have no faith in them.
[SPEAKER_02]: My counseling agency has been helpful as a wet fart.
[SPEAKER_02]: Read, not at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd think that since the theft occurred there that they'd be eager to have this issue resolved just to cover their collective asses, but it looks like that isn't the case.
[SPEAKER_02]: As...
[SPEAKER_02]: I lost my place, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: As a related note, and if I neither mentioned it in the call or you haven't figured it out already, I brought my PS3 to my counseling agency for an informal party.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was supplying the entertainment, movies downloaded on PSN, karaoke, rock band, slash guitar hero, world tour style, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was stolen between 12.15 p.m.
[SPEAKER_02]: and 1.15 p.m.
[SPEAKER_02]: EST.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wouldn't that be a.m.? ?
[SPEAKER_02]: on AST on 11.19 when it was unattended.
[SPEAKER_02]: In all likelihood, I won't be getting my original system back, which is a shame.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had the 60GB model, which are impossible to find.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not only that, but I upgraded the internal HDD and bought a ton of stuff off of the PSN store.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anywho, luckily my SSI PAE is sitting on my rainy day fund and sent her a request for the adequate funds to replace the system with a used 80GB model and the same type of upgraded HDD that I had before.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll worry about the movies and TV shows that I bought at a later time and date.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry for the long as hell email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trust me, it's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I figured that you'd appreciate an update.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, thanks for letting us know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, stolen systems suck, and whoever stole your system needs to die in a fire, and let's just hope that karma comes around and bites this person in their big fat ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next email!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it's gaming related, but I would like a new computer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a new computer for the gaming, but I would just like a whole new setup for the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like a fancy new mix board, an easier way to publish a show on a faster computer without having to transfer it to my new one, which has kind of been slowing things down.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess it's technically gaming related.
[SPEAKER_04]: Technically, because it has to do with the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that would be my thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd want a fancy, I want a state-of-the-art computer recording studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I want.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want a DDRX machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty pricey.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: And new.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't say that there's too much that I would really want that I don't already have.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually want a PC Engine Duo RX and an arcade card so that I can play Sapphire.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I want a baby Pac-Man machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck yes!
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: The hell with the studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just bring me a baby Pac-Man machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I already have the pinball machine that I really want.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have my World Cup soccer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you believe that Dan actually asked me if I would trade it temporarily?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I can't go on a completely random tangent for a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is related, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: On Twitter, I follow some other podcasters, some other indie podcasters.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one of the podcasters I follow is one of the guys from Video Game Outsiders.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he posted to YouTube today.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess he picked up some new Popeye machine or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess what he does, he has, like how you amass a bunch of pinball machines in your house, he amasses a bunch of 80s stuff in his basement.
[SPEAKER_04]: A bunch of babies in his basement.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a bunch of babies.
[SPEAKER_01]: I found this baby at the mall.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to take it home and raise it to do my work.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, stop trying to start a podcast war.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can just see it now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can see they're going to read an email on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: The guys from OLR said that you have babies in your basement.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you have to say about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're crunchy.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and I have to admit, it's the first time I've ever really watched something like that another podcaster did where I was completely overcome with jealousy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like just total jealousy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was looking at it going, that is so cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am so fucking jealous.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want one of those fuckers so badly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even the baby Pac-Man sort of sucks ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the novelty.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the novelty of the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only successful incarnation of video and pinball has been Pinball 2000.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, now they're going to get... I can just see it now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You said you keep babies in your basement.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's Baby Pac-Man that he had in his basement that I was completely and utterly overcome with jealousy.
[SPEAKER_02]: He had babies.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I could find one of those machines cheap, you know I would put that shit in this garage.
[SPEAKER_02]: You wouldn't find one cheap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless it's completely destroyed and gutted.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan, come fix my Baby Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I don't know dick about pinball games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, OLR!
[SPEAKER_02]: Without much lag while I was there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I got home and started playing for a few hours, so my question is for Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: What server, or whatever it is it's called, do you play on?
[SPEAKER_02]: I play on the Garethos, did I spell that right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Server.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm level 9, and I wanted to know if it's worth buying and if I can switch server to play on with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, tell me a little about the game and some of the things that will convince me to buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to give you an answer you weren't expecting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because if I remember right, Cheeseburger is like 15 years old, 14, 15, like he's a younger listener of ours.
[SPEAKER_04]: My advice to you is not to buy World of Warcraft because you're still in school.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you get sucked into a game like World of Warcraft, it could affect your school.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you know in your heart and in your gut and in your mind that you can restrict yourself to playing this game one or two hours a day tops, then it might be okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: But honestly, it's the social element.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what really these games are all about.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could describe all about the quests and the classes and the magic and all this stuff, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're playing the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You see all that firsthand.
[SPEAKER_04]: The reason why people get addicted to this stuff is the social element.
[SPEAKER_04]: When I log on to the game and I say hello to the guild, everybody goes, Rob!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like walking into Cheers, the bar, and everybody yells, Norm!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the reward that you're going to get out of a game like Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: That being said...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my honest advice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ta-da!
[SPEAKER_02]: So that was it for emails?
[SPEAKER_02]: I said that, didn't I?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I wasn't listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Surprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, gee, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else is new?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just talk on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it for emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to send us an email, mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll get some more stuff from you later during the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how long we can go tonight because it's fucking freezing out here in the garage.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we will get some more stories first.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not as cold as it was last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still pretty fucking cold.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love this quilt.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so cold.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's rumors that the PSP is getting another revision.
[SPEAKER_05]: The PSP 4000 is apparently due out late 2009.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is coming to us from Eurogamer that reports their publishing sources.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sony is planning to launch a PSP2
[SPEAKER_05]: Where have I heard we have no plans for something before?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I know!
[SPEAKER_05]: On every other rumor that they have no plans on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, no plans for a price cut.
[SPEAKER_05]: No plans on releasing a 160GB system.
[SPEAKER_05]: No plans for doing something that's completely obvious.
[SPEAKER_05]: No plans to release a good system.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have no plans on ever becoming the number one console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, when you hear no plans...
[SPEAKER_05]: Hear them saying, it's like we are.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, just big deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: We know hardware revision's coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_04]: A sequel to a popular handheld system might happen, you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's what I thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, moving on over to Nintendo, who has been number one lately, although amongst the hardcore gamers, some of us are starting to feel a little jaded.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, this is something that some hardcore gamers will be into, but probably more for the casual crowd and the young folks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the early 2009 releases for Nintendo, of course, headlined by Pokemon Platinum on March 22nd.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is going to be a pretty big title on the Nintendo DS, even though, isn't it just the last two Pokemon?
[SPEAKER_04]: They do this all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: They
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Some other games that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles Echo of Time is supposed to actually come out this spring, so we'll see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, what else is supposed to come out here?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got a whole list.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is spring that they said that game would come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: March?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, probably the later the better.
[SPEAKER_04]: For them, not for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dragon Quest V. Is that on...
[SPEAKER_04]: Saga's Putting Out the House of the Dead Overkill on Wii in February Sonic and the Black Knight in March Mad World in March
[SPEAKER_04]: Ubisoft's got Tenchu in February and Broken Sword, Shadows of the Templars in March.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo, first party games, the only stuff they're putting out, Mario Power Tennis in March and Pikmin in March.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Wii, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, on the DS from Nintendo, Personal Trainer Math on January 12th, Fire Emblem Shadow Dragon on February 16th, and the before-mentioned Pokemon Platinum, which is kind of in line with their one title a month.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Ubisoft, Imagine Cheerleader, Imagine Family Doctor, Imagine Ice Champions, American Popstar, Road to Celebrity Cash Cow Pikmin
[SPEAKER_04]: I do want to point out, Konami is putting out a game on the Wii that some of you guys might care about.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Disney Grooves.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those that are still playing DDR after all these years.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100 Matt in chat says, Factor 5 goes down, but Sonic Team is still around.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's the justice?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's that for first quarter lineup.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, how about something very cool for all of our 8-bit fans?
[SPEAKER_04]: Which, by the way, thank you for the old-school Nintendo Entertainment System, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of like a second Christmas gift slash late birthday gift.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, also, thanks, Sauce, for agreeing to a trade that I got the better end of the deal of.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking at a video here on this site.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, that's what you're hearing in the background. ...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it seems like it's a hacked ROM of some sort, because the music in the background is strange.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't sound like Pac-Man at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might be trying to emulate the music from... Hmm, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, at any rate, there's no idea where you can find the ROM.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's from the Pac-Mania soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry if that was loud, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't loud to us in the studio, but I guess it came out very loud over the... But hey, whoever finds it, then let me know what you think of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, apparently the weird thing about this is that it's still unknown if this is like real or a concept thing, because no ROM has showed up out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the weird thing about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not something you can actually download for use in an emulator, but they say it's an actual 8-bit Nintendo game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: A game that is coming out on the DS, Grand Theft Auto Chinatown Wars, has been dated for March.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is weird because I thought it was dated before for January, but either way, it's coming out now March 17th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Grand Theft Auto Chinatown Wars will feature most of Liberty City.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they're cutting out Alderney from Grand Theft Auto 4, but most of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's going to kind of look a little bit like...
[SPEAKER_05]: The old Grand Theft Auto 1 and 2 games.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, kind of a top-down 3D type of game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's all cel-shaded.
[SPEAKER_05]: But still violent and pretty cool looking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay cool looking things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Europe will be getting the game three days later on March 20th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's good that it's not getting delayed so bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I can't wait to try the online multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, tons of people will be cheating in it because they can.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so here's something interesting going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what the hell you want to call this, but I don't know if you've heard about this project.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Bob's Game, and it's this guy who's spent a lot, a lot of time making a particular DS homebrew project.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's apparently going on protest.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's going to be spending 100 days locked in his room, locked and barricaded from the outside to protest how Nintendo has been treating his project.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: He needs a DS software development kit to get his game, which is... I guess what Bob made is some type of 2D adventure thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: He actually wants to sell it as a retail game, but Nintendo will not give him one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though Bob has apparently talked to Nintendo, done the application, told he was going to get an answer in a few months, and apparently 17 weeks have gone by, no answer, no kit has showed up.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, now what he's going to be planning is this 100-day sit-down protest.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he's doing a tantrum.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, he's throwing a fit.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: On the application, it said it would be six to eight weeks for a decision.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been 17.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says he's met all the requirements.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's a financially stable registered company with an FEIN, which I believe is a federal identification number, working from a commercial address.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he says that when Nintendo decides to approve the developer license, he will end his protest.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, you can actually watch on live webcam.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm actually going to go to the site right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like he's asleep.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you can see something on the board right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says Reggie on the monitor there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually his live confinement right now, but it looks like he's fast asleep or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or he left the room.
[SPEAKER_04]: But he's on day 12.
[SPEAKER_02]: How can he leave the room if he's not supposed to leave the room?
[SPEAKER_05]: It says he sleeps behind the camera.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's his potty?
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope that's all behind the camera too or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, he says he cannot leave the room.
[SPEAKER_04]: The door is locked and barricaded from the outside.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's sleeping behind the camera.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, there is a shower.
[SPEAKER_04]: Food is being delivered once a week by a friend.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is no internet access, television, or game consoles besides the ones he's developing on.
[SPEAKER_04]: He can receive and send email on his cell phone so he can get Nintendo's reply and update the site.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the LED counter will be incremented once a day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes it will display hints and secret messages.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yes, Jamie, he's throwing a tantrum.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's doing the equivalent of sticking his fingers in his ears and closing his eyes and going, Well, still though, what about the point that he's meeting all of Nintendo's requirements and Nintendo's dicking him?
[SPEAKER_04]: What about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: To play Devil's Advocate.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need more Imagine games.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't have time with this good adventure crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Need more Imagine and more pets.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it's got Imagine and pets in it, we can definitely do something with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and if it's a sim.
[SPEAKER_04]: More sim games.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100Matt says, Rob, you need to get an interview with this guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if I can.
[SPEAKER_04]: He has no phone, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no, he has a cell phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I can.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess I could try sending an email.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Misty in chat says, there's better ways to bitch about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so good luck, Bob, on your protest, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't die.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kind of fucking ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: And by kind of, I mean really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, this is very, very happy, happy news for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I have been wanting this game, and I played the other two, and it's freaking beautiful.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Klonoa Door to Phantom Isle is going to be coming out in North America.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that makes me giddy!
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's supposed to be out in Spring 2009.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: and the classic controller is also, you can use that too.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there is a rumor that the Klonoa 2 remake is on its way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Klonoa 2 is freaking hard, but I really, really, really, really, really love Klonoa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe this took so long to come out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: because the Klonoa developers locked themselves in a room for 100 days until Nintendo agreed to put out their game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, after much begging and pleading, apparently EA has decided to graciously allow players to be able to reinstall their copies of Spore
[SPEAKER_05]: Hurray!
[SPEAKER_05]: But unfortunately there's not a tool that's gotten me back interested in Spore again To which actually my cat knocked a disc on the floor in its case And I was like, eh, it's a good place for it Nice So do you let the cat rearrange all your furniture?
[SPEAKER_05]: She does that on her own She decides that she wants to cram herself in the tiny space that is between my monitor on the shelf And the top of my desk It's like...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your cat's name again?
[SPEAKER_04]: Stella.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, the RIAA.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently some kitties, some cute kittens went into the RIAA office and just they made them go aww and shucks because they decided to do something nice this holiday season.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are no longer going to sue individual file sharers or harass universities anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: but they'll be able to better control the congestion on their networks by applying this new little policy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some words from Ars Technica on the original report of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Suddenly ISPs gained a tremendous new tool.
[SPEAKER_04]: One study in the UK showed that most people sharing music would stop when made aware that their activity was being tracked and that they were not in fact anonymous.
[SPEAKER_04]: Should that hold true in the US, ISPs would presumably see massive decreases in P2P traffic.
[SPEAKER_04]: And whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not going to work very well, but hey, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pirate away, everybody!
[SPEAKER_04]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: You shouldn't pirate, because that's why all these people got laid off this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was all your fault.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's the RAAs coming after you for music.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if there's any companies that are going to say, nope, we're not participating.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go fuck yourself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, stop downloading music and start downloading movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jrod in chat says, I got a letter from my ISP about downloading HBO shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: It didn't stop my torrenting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I've never received any kind of cease and desist.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only letters I receive from my ICP is, we're raising your rates.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, if you're downloading TV shows, I mean, they were on TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, some other very interesting news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move away a little bit from the RIAA bastards.
[SPEAKER_02]: EA and Steam have decided to make sweet love.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's going to be EA games that are available through Steam's service which is Mass Effect Need for Speed Undercover and Spore and the Spore Creepy and Cute Parts Pack FIFA Manager 09 and Warhammer Online Age of Reckoning So that's going to be hanging out there So they're getting steamy?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're getting steamy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also others slated for there is Mirror's Edge, Command & Conquer, Red Alert 3, and Dead Space.
[SPEAKER_04]: But not Mick's steamy or else the RIA might sue them for sharing ABC shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing, never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you didn't get that joke, good for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who in this room doesn't watch TV?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even you watch some TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just don't watch TV like on TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: I watch DVDs after the fact.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will going to be watching a show as soon as it's got new episodes on.
[SPEAKER_02]: When it airs.
[SPEAKER_04]: See.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is Supernatural.
[SPEAKER_02]: American Idol.
[SPEAKER_02]: Supernatural.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if there's David Cook 2 on American Idol next year?
[SPEAKER_04]: Will you watch that?
[SPEAKER_02]: And keep in mind, I watched American Idol through YouTube.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well this year they're actually getting rid of or they're limiting the amount of the bad singers that they have on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: To that I say, great!
[SPEAKER_05]: Another show I don't have to watch anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, so apparently, you know, Crackdown 2 is a game that I wish would come out because Crackdown 1 was awesome and it does need a sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, of course, you know, Real Time Worlds, they're busy working on the game that I'm going to have to get back into MMOs for and that would be APB.
[SPEAKER_05]: But until that happens, people still wish for Crackdown 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, there was a rumor that Crackdown 2 was actually being developed by another company, Ruffian Games.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, that may not be the case anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: The studio head, Colin McDonald, actually said they would like to make the sequel for Crackdown, although to date they have not been offered from Microsoft for a Crackdown sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are having ongoing discussions with them, and they would feel really hurt if Microsoft went to some other studio to develop it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't there rumors that that's exactly what Microsoft did?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, there was, but they don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said that they would doubt that Microsoft would choose a startup on RTW's doorstep, Ruffian.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why they would choose them, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jrod in chat says, Crackdown!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you meant that bonus disc that came with the Halo 3 beta?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, that's the one.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game is awesome, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Way better than the Halo 3 beta.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, in reality, I probably did play more Crackdown than I did Halo 3, and I didn't even know the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crackdown was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was crack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Down.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: And what it does, it makes all the sights and the sounds of a winter fireplace via your Xbox 360 on the television.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like one of those, like you remember the old cassette tapes that was just nothing but the fire that you could play in the background during Christmas?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's basically what this is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't you mean a videotape?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what did they call it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like a virtual Yule log or something like that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Virtual fireplace.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what they call it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They still have those and they actually have Blu-rays now of virtual fireplaces.
[SPEAKER_04]: People buy this shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the amazing thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should make the official OLR Yule log and just make tons and tons of money off people's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Impulse Buys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently you can get the demo on your Xbox 360 and you can even get that on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just download it right away and you can get a little four minute demo.
[SPEAKER_04]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want the full version, it's 400 points.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I'm
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to give this guy a lot of shit because having talked to Aaron on a previous show who made Snake360 and talking to the community developers, I think there's a certain range of points that they can charge.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so probably 400 is all this guy can charge.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if he can charge less.
[SPEAKER_05]: No?
200.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bastard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to look at some video of this thing in action here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to actually play a little video.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, that is definitely a virtual log.
[SPEAKER_05]: To be honest, you could probably purchase a DVD for cheaper.
[SPEAKER_04]: Than five bucks?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you could probably go to the 99 cent store and get one of these DVDs.
[SPEAKER_05]: The 99 cent store has some pretty funny movies there.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, that would be really fun to make stocking stuffers with the 99 cent clearance center movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some absolute crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't even press a button.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be awesome if you pressed a button and you could throw a kitten in the fire and watch what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it is wrong, but funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: A reindeer.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's more festive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or Santa.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just watch Santa drop in the chimney into the fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, that would be worth 400 points.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or Christmas lemmings.
[SPEAKER_04]: As DarkTetsuyinChat says, or a ferret.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's been some new patches for some PC games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Far Cry 2 got a patch to fix their widescreen issues.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently it had the same thing that was wrong with Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Sony declares death to the clamshell Slow going
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it is Christmas week, for heaven's sake.
[SPEAKER_04]: But hey, or well, you know, coming up.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I am so excited about the clamshell news, because I think that packaging is horrible, evil stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, oh, grr.
[SPEAKER_04]: Clamshell packaging can go die in a fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really excited to hear.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to press a button and watch all my old clamshell packaging get burned in the fire, because that annoys me.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we're taking your calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been doing this a little bit too long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you believe next week is our last show of 2008?
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we will go into the year 2009, which would be our seventh year of podcasting, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or seventh year of doing this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess podcasting hasn't been around seven years, but you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're getting old.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next year, one of us will kill another live on air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just wait for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you spend $5 for a Yule Log game on the 360 where you could throw clamshell packages into the fire?
[SPEAKER_04]: I might.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just might be willing to spend that kind of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Except you wouldn't because you'd have to use the D-pad to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'm going to the chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, the phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's getting late and I haven't even cracked open the eggnog yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lodge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Legend of Zaku Hey Legend of Zaku, what's up?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing much, you know today's my birthday, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or for the next, um, less than 40 minutes Well, happy Hanukkah!
[SPEAKER_04]: And birthday Not Jewish That's alright You don't have to be Jewish to appreciate Hanukkah I get guilt I love those potato latkes though Hell yeah, one of my friends was supposed to make me some of those, that sounds delish
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mind, Zaku?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing but just trying to scurry up as much money as possible to get me something, at least one game for Christmas since the last game I bought was GTA 4 back in May, like April or May.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I'm unemployed right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to find work and I can't be pissing my money away on unnecessary things like that when the bills have to be paid first and foremost.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard that Prince of Persia dropped in price to $40.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where at?
[SPEAKER_03]: Everywhere?
[SPEAKER_03]: What, for the PC or 360?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, for PS3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, I'm trying to give my PC some love.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to ask, what one game are you thinking of buying?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you must have something in mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Left 4 Dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, Left 4 Dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why Left 4 Dead?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, because that's just like playing Half-Life with zombies, but with at least a subpar storyline with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I get to use my keyboard and mouse nice very cool I've heard a lot of good things about Left 4 Dead but I think that's another one of those games that I won't probably actually get to check out until next year just because I'm playing so much other crap like WoW yeah well I'm sorry to hear about the financial tough times but you know I mean I have plenty of money saved up I'm not worried about you know the bills but you know I can't burn that money that quickly that money has to last me until I find work right no that's understandable
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean, other companies are struggling.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you already had about two or three companies going under in one week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Six.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not necessarily going under, but doing layoffs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Six companies doing some type of closure or cutbacks this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know Factor 5, and I think
[SPEAKER_04]: Free Radical went belly up Yeah, we reported on it, I don't know if you were here at the very beginning of the show, but we kicked off the show Factor 5, EA, Midway, Free Radical, Asper, and Turbine all did some type of closure or layoff this week
[SPEAKER_04]: Looks like someone's not having a Christmas party this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, and it sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you used to work in, like, cell phone games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this time last year, I had a really nice Christmas party complete with, like, all-you-can-eat stuff, open bar, you know, Guitar Hero, SingStar right there on a nice big projection.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you surprised by what's happened?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's shitty all around.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: Ask anybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet you know at least three or four or five people that you know personally that are probably unemployed right now and are struggling to find work in this economy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I have so many skills right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: My experience is that I'm trying my best to secure work, but it's a clusterfuck because I'm not the only one fighting for that same job.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like hundreds upon thousands of other people fighting for that same position, especially here in New York.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is very, very tough out there right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is very tough.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're lucky you still have work, whereas I had to work as a contractor since early this year, since I got laid off from my full-time job.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was connected and I had resources, but they ran out over the summer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh no, I'm thankful to have a job.
[SPEAKER_04]: I stopped bitching about the promotion I was supposed to get because a while ago they were trying to give me a promotion at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I stopped bitching about it for now because I realized that I should just be lucky to have a job right now, so I'm just going to shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's better to have a job, better to be working than not be working at all like me right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Zaku, best of luck in your search, maybe for your birthday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody will give you a new job.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, hopefully if you want, you know, I could give you my resume, see what you could do with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then again, I live out, you know, here in New York, so it wouldn't make any sense if I'm sending it off, I'm sending it off, I'm sending it off, I'm sending it off, I'm sending it off, I'm sending it off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, which unfortunately I don't think I have the money to do right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the crap happened there?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was, we got like bad echo and Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think closed on me.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, wow, I swear we didn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the crap was that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Skype just crashed on us in studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got the error message and that happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's a robot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, first, no, dude, this is like the beginning of a scary movie right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: First we had the door blew open.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we have something happen with Zaku on the Skype line there.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the shit?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm scared to take another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it was anything you did, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I didn't do anything either.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the weird thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's take one more call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw something come up and I got excited.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you going to sleep, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good night, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura's going to sleep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_00]: Y'all must have had a one missed call moment.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_00]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_00]: Y'all must have had a one missed call moment or something when that happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what the hell's going on with Skype, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I need to upgrade, but I thought I just upgraded last week, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_00]: Talking about the layouts and whatnot, Free Radical, I can understand them shutting their doors and whatnot, because like I said, they had one buzz game and whatnot that didn't really make much money for them at all and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, I mean, you know, it's still unfortunate they won't get a chance to do a second one, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's true, and they said they were working on the TimeSplitter game, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, so, I mean, I can understand that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I understand that.
[SPEAKER_00]: As far as midwaying them, doing layouts and whatnot, that one's kind of hard to swallow because, I mean...
[SPEAKER_00]: The latest Mortal Kombat and whatnot, they've been making their money off of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did say the Mortal Kombat team was left intact.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mortal Kombat team was left intact, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and Midway's kind of had a rough year outside of Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, we don't really know how the other games have been selling yet, but some of their other high-profile titles did not follow through the way they should.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to be honest, I can't think of a lot of Midway games I've gotten really excited about this year, which is kind of a bummer.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I thought I would hear people talk about Blitz, but I don't even think I heard people talking about Blitz and everything like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nope, nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then EA, I mean, EA's kind of, you know, their year hasn't been that terrible yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: They did a lot of layoffs too, so it's kind of... And that is a big shocker to hear that EA, I figured, I made a comment earlier saying that if one of the big game manufacturing companies did have any layoffs, then we'd really be scratching our heads.
[SPEAKER_00]: If anything else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo, Sony, or Microsoft
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it was from their general company.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it was from their entertainment division.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but at least Microsoft and Sony, they have all those other divisions of their company.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're a huge, huge company.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not just about the games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Still, still.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I mean, it just... And then you think about it, Sega is like Sega having their bad luck streak with their games and whatnot, all the Sonic games and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_00]: They didn't find out problems with...
[SPEAKER_00]: Problems with their online gaming division and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm like, here we go.
[SPEAKER_00]: If Sega was to go, then I'd be a lost sheep.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would cry with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not just that, but just that all these companies are getting swallowed up by other companies, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_00]: Like Koei and Tecmo.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dark Knight, anything else on your mind before we let you go tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, just want to wish y'all guys a happy holidays and be safe and enjoy your presents and everything like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, phew.
[SPEAKER_00]: We will do.
[SPEAKER_00]: And see y'all in 09.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to play with my pest dispenser.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just open, close, open, close, open, close.
[SPEAKER_00]: All night long.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's Klingon's on a starboard belt, Captain.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care, Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a safe one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to close up the Skype line for now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry we didn't take a lot of calls tonight, but damn, it's cold out here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do want to give a quick plug before we close our doors tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to give a quick plug to our buddies over at Under Sedation Live, Travis Donovan and DMN.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, no, I think he's officially retired that title now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think he's Insanist officially now, John.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever his name is, he co-hosts the show over there Saturday nights on All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are putting together USOLR Madness 2009.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm being corrected by the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: His new name is Brest Lowell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: You can send in those emails with your top 25 games to uslmadness at gmail.com That's all one word.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you can look for more information on our forums at orangelaunceradio.com and I'm sure plenty of other information as well at Understation Live's website.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to do it though tonight for Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys so much for tuning into our show and supporting independent podcasting and independent radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We wouldn't do it without you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just looking at it out of, you know, huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a bad job, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's all really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's growing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm really... Mine just... The last time... Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_04]: The last time I looked at it, mine just said, tune into this show to hear about Rob's life, which I thought was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a link to my MySpace.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cute because I never update it anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will say this.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll do my final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll do Loki's final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought is shit cakes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that the different levels in this have different difficulties, so I'm skipping ahead to Final Fantasy 7.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to play them in order, but apparently Final Fantasy 1 is like a level 5 or 5 star, and that's kind of hard, because I got my ass kicked pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still kind of want to see a little more about this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have a... Oh, you can't use the video thing to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I tried that later, because there was an update that they allowed PlayStation Network software to do...
[SPEAKER_05]: to be able to output, but it's only classic PlayStation games, and that sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's bullshit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of classic PlayStation games, I got Castlevania Chronicles this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hey, we're going to close out the show now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys so much for downloading and supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't do my... I thought we did your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, then, DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's freaking cold in here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought your final thought was about your wiki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it was?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can talk about the cold.
[SPEAKER_02]: The cold froze my brain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you so much for downloading and supporting independent podcasting and shows like ours.
[SPEAKER_04]: We wouldn't be able to do it without you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tune in next week for our year-end special.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, I don't know if we're doing that much special for it because it's kind of on a weird day.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Bobby's doing a year-end special right before us.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we might just do a non-special year-end special.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, we will do listless.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can be sure of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see you next week here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_07]: or allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: See you next week!