[SPEAKER_06]: Tonight, Tekken 6 gets a date, Rock Band is set to go a little bit country, and is Cooking Mama taking up a new hobby?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are that video game show dedicated to all things video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_06]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Joining me as always, say hello to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome back.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what an amazing two weeks off it's been.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't rub it in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've had all this time off.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are a little late tonight in starting the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: This won't affect anybody listening to this on the podcast, except for the fact that podcasts have been going up extremely late lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's because we're all pregnant.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no, we're not all pregnant.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me introduce Tech Master Loki, who I hope is not pregnant.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you pregnant, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I am not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome, Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're starting a little late tonight, 7 o'clock Pacific, just because there's personal life things going on that have to... Real life, greater than gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob has PMS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I have PMS.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm having a baby.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also say hello to a special guest we have here tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie has brought one of her friends here to giggle with us tonight on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Say hello to Becky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Greetings.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have an online name you use, Becky, that you want people to call you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Beckers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Beckers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes me think of Beckham.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Beckers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow... Yeah, but he married a hoochie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Posh Spice is pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a hoochie!
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, Beckers... Her boobs don't move!
[SPEAKER_06]: Beckers, what type of video games do you enjoy?
[SPEAKER_06]: You play a lot of video games?
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you like?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I refuse.
[SPEAKER_06]: Refuse?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: How dare you refuse?
[SPEAKER_03]: I played some rock band.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been playing Castlevania Order of Ecclesia and I'm very pissed off at it right now so I took a break because it's fucking hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have the same problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to actually go back and re-level just on that first thing just because it's such a pain in the butt.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I got Animal Crossing and I have been beating my animals with the bug net.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I accidentally stole my shovel and stupid Nook, that butthead, won't get anyone in.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I was telling Nellie, because there's this one stupid rabbit in her town named Francine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know which one that is!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that she absolutely hates.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said that we have to form a hit squad and just have everybody at Bug Nets all of a sudden chase her down, like, get her trapped in one of those pitfalls and just all four people hitting her at the same time.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you know who fucking showed up in my village?
[SPEAKER_03]: Who?
[SPEAKER_06]: Pearl, I hate her.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's a little cat that looks like, oh, God, she looks like she has, like, burn scars all over her face.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, she's in my village.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wolfgang.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't believe we're having this discussion about a game made for 12-year-olds.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I got a bunny in my town.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want the lesbian to move back into my town.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was her name?
[SPEAKER_06]: Was that Barbara?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Barbara was a sheep.
[SPEAKER_03]: She was a duck, I think, and had gym equipment in her house.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we put rainbow signs outside of her house.
[SPEAKER_03]: and she was our we put all kinds of happy signs and sent her letters and the bitch moved out I mean if that is not you know you think you know somebody and you move in after a month I'm sorry that's you know she just got pissy and moved out
[SPEAKER_06]: She probably moved in with her girlfriend after the second date, like most lesbians.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_03]: She moved out of my village because I got boring and wouldn't send her any more letters or peaches.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she moved out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lesbians are so needy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Dan's been playing Need for Speed Undercover and I've been mocking him because it's fun and easy and then even though it's not a video game I've been watching a lot of Supernatural which is more fun because I got to watch Jensen Ackles naked not completely but it was a lot more exciting than playing Animal Crossing
[SPEAKER_06]: Remind me, this is a show geared towards 16-year-old girls?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hell no!
[SPEAKER_03]: It is geared towards me.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's on the CW.
[SPEAKER_03]: We forgive it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_07]: My gaming week was all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I watched my wife play a lot of Animal Crossing because I'm not allowed near it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: and there was like a bunch of stuff that she's done.
[SPEAKER_07]: She harasses her animals quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, do you know that now it censors things?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like you can't just have your animals say fuck.
[SPEAKER_06]: And like mine, I tried to get mine to say poop and it wouldn't say it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It said that word is not allowed.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to tell you though.
[SPEAKER_06]: So now he says poop.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the animals defaulted, their little catch word was the N word.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the way they got around it was they put N and then an I with an accent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, no, it was someone who, one of the programmers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or they probably copied something to test it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They copied Ranma, someone that had already played it and unlocked all the stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, they, I don't know, should maybe look at that first, you know, do a little testing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone's getting fired.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not sure but or 1400x900 not 1440 but it runs pretty good for me you know 40-50 frames per second and I have a lot of sliders put up all the way you know although I don't like the fact that this brand new game does not support SLI so that's kind of a waste and it's got to be patched in later on you know absolute laziness just to get it out
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, very, very hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll fall off a building a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think people are pissed off because it's, you know, short.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, sure, I guess it doesn't innovate much, but the way I look at it is, is it fun?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: So then what are you complaining about?
[SPEAKER_07]: But, yeah, I'll have to play some more of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hear it is really short.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, I believe, what was it, um,
[SPEAKER_07]: Yotzi had reviewed it this week and man said he beat it in a day so it'll be interesting to see how long it takes me to finish it then I've got a bunch of other games on my plate in fact I got another one this week which I haven't even touched yet Prince of Persia so that looks pretty fun too so well lots of stuff
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, my gaming week's been Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_06]: A couple weeks ago, I think I mentioned Animal Crossing, but didn't really get too far into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really spent some serious time with Animal Crossing on the Wii this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: As much as we're joking around and kind of talking about reliving the thrill of the GameCube version all over again, I have a real hard time recommending this game overall because it's just not enough new for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I kind of feel like there's Animal Crossing on the GameCube out there for much cheaper prices.
[SPEAKER_06]: and you almost get more in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there are some cool things in this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: The problem with this game is it feels like it's just a port of the DS version with a couple extra frills and it just kind of leaves an Animal Crossing fan really wanting more.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they should have taken more risks with this game than they did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I will say the internet functionality works pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have worked WeConnect24 into it a little bit so you don't really have to go to somebody's village to send letters and things of that nature which is an improvement over the DS version but
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, is that really worth the whole new upgrade?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not so much.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't really do a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: The city is for getting all of your special characters who only would randomly show up.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is so you can have the convenience of having them all the damn time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I think that's stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then that takes away the special part of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No way, you still get presents floating on balloons, and you still get, you know, Gulliver, you know, showing up, and I'm actually, you know, Wild World didn't really hold me all that well, but this one's, I'm really digging it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: I kind of feel the same way.
[SPEAKER_06]: The DS one, I got really fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: But for some reason, I have been actually going back to the Wii one to kind of see if there's new stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: I say all this, yet I can't in good conscience really recommend this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to really be hardcore about these types of games to get a thrill out of this.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to really be an Animal Crossing fan, of which I was.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm still left wanting more.
[SPEAKER_03]: For me, it's my sit down for an hour and relax.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got wowed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Addict?
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob What?
[SPEAKER_06]: and the consensus overall amongst at least my guild, which is a casual raiding guild.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were never very hardcore about the endgame.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all the people from Final Fantasy XI still.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of the same people that were there have moved over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even Glenn and some of these people from old school.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we haven't seen them in a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be the turkey coma.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, it's been a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're rating ill.
[SPEAKER_06]: The general consensus is this expansion is better than the last one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob, can you help me power level?
[SPEAKER_06]: I can try.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a level 20-something priest.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've also been playing Ragnarok, and you can play that with me.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got a lot of games to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can get you to level 100 in two hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not joking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sky, your voice like that, not sexy.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you actually see him.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did a much better job with this expansion.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they learned a lot from the last one.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, that's the one thing I would really like to see in an MMO is that they have it function like an actual RPG where you have to do point A to point B to, you know, where your quests are not just, oh, look, this person has question mark over his head and I want...
[SPEAKER_03]: Money!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It got really dull.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might also be on the wrong server.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should try a roleplay server on WoW.
[SPEAKER_03]: You might have fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was on a roleplay server, actually, and I didn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one stays in character.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's annoying.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just rather hang out with everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: When you finally get the battle and defeat the Lich King, he'll be all, I have one last thing to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't forget Guitar Hero 5 pre-orders and StarCraft 2 is right around the corner.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: You forgot Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Warcraft 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like how you tried to do your lazy bass echo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your Lich King sounds like a drunken asshole.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, how much have you really gotten to know the Lich King yet?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, DJ Tyrant hit the nail on the head.
[SPEAKER_06]: The last expansion had nothing like Wrathgate.
[SPEAKER_06]: He says Wrathgate is one of absolutely the best questlines of all time.
[SPEAKER_06]: In-game cutscenes for the win.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have cutscenes in the quest this time, and they're epic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Epic cutscenes are very epic.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Wrathgate was hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody in our guild, because we're all WoW nerds, was having a gigantic orgasm over the Wrathgate questline because it was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, that sounds like it would be more fun to me just having actual story to follow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to spoil what happens in Wrathgate, but it's pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty epic.
[SPEAKER_06]: You get to learn a little more about the phasing technology, and it's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobbie Blackwolf Show
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's actually going to be like they're going to do the interaction with the live crowd as well as the people in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to have some neat co-hosts and stuff too.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I don't know how much more I can say because I don't know what he said yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's going to be cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: So listen to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: FNGLive.net and that starts January 9th on All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, that's really all the housekeeping I have tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: So how about some gaming news, even though it's been kind of a slow news week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So a short show seems appropriate tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, what's up?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there is a certain Kingdom Hearts game that's scheduled to come out for the DS, and you may have heard about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kingdom Hearts 358 slash 2 days is going to be getting a North American release.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, did anyone have...
[SPEAKER_07]: KINGDOM HEARTS 3
[SPEAKER_07]: Never.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have to whore it enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kingdom Hearts 2 you have to understand is like Final Fantasy 7 or the upcoming Final Fantasy 13 where it's got to have 90 billion versions for it first before they move on to the next one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then they can whore that one out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Got to wear out the first prostitute first before they can move on to the next.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still want my Kingdom Hearts 3, though, on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be very nice, with my high-def graphics and hopefully a working camera.
[SPEAKER_06]: But although Kingdom Hearts 2 wasn't bad, as far as the camera goes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought Kingdom Hearts 2 was really solid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kingdom Hearts 2 is a very solid game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need to actually not glitch mine out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I miss games like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been a little while.
[SPEAKER_06]: When did Kingdom Hearts 2 come out?
05?
[SPEAKER_06]: 06, maybe?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe 06.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anyhow, let's get into some other news and some other games that are dated that are highly anticipated.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably another anticipated game by Jamie, Tekken 6.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's coming out on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 and it's been confirmed that it will be in the fall 2009 time frame.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the Xbox 360 is supposed to, I don't know if it's getting a slightly earlier launch or something, but they're going to hit generally at the same time, the Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: This official announcement was made by Atari
[SPEAKER_06]: who is publishing the game over in Europe.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's not going to be in the same time frame as like Street Fighter 4 and we know there's not going to be a new Mortal Kombat next year because they just had one this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: So
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, then, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were putting out those Mortal Kombat games a dime a dozen for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: They could still do another Mortal Kombat game because all they would really have to do is just port the engine over and add new characters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's face it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mortal Kombat and Tekken have very, very different fan bases, so I don't think there's going to be any overlap there anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tekken 6 coming soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: No mention about arcades, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: I weep for the arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really, where is the market going?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they do have the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_07]: It should be already out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not coming over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: WeWare
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_06]: The stuff I'm boycotting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, come on, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: True.
[SPEAKER_07]: True.
[SPEAKER_07]: They did promise that they'd have more storage, but where the fuck's the update?
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably March.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's just like Sony's Home.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where the fuck is Sony's Home?
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't play it, therefore it's not out yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: What can the more common folk, who are not stuck up enough to be boycotting the Nintendo Wii, what can they be playing?
[SPEAKER_03]: There are more games coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's actually going to be ArtStyle Roto Hex, that's a remake of the Bit Generations game Dial Hex, that was on the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's actually going to be 600 Wii points.
[SPEAKER_03]: Episode 4 of Strong Bad's cool game for attractive people on its way.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it will have the Danger-esque 3 theme.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's 1,000 Wii points.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will allow you to get the Strong Bad game because it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I do want to point out it's also available on PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't want to put up with the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to know when the hell they're doing an art-style version of DotStream, because that was the most kick-ass bit-generation game that they released.
[SPEAKER_07]: That and Sound Voyager, I guess, is supposed to be pretty good, but I never picked that one up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's also Bang, which is a shape-matching game, and Pit Crew Panic, which should make sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's mechanics for broken things.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the one where you fix toilets.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember, there's a giant toilet one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we talked about that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oblivion, Beatmania, and Kingdom Hearts 2 were all released the same week.
[SPEAKER_06]: BlackWolf wants to point out that Strong Bad is also cheaper on the PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_06]: And YYR in chat, I believe, is commenting on the Tekken 6 story.
[SPEAKER_06]: The arcade version will not be released in North America.
[SPEAKER_06]: They announced that a while back.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember when.
[SPEAKER_06]: Selected arcades in the USA do have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's like three in New York.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've played it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It rocks.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there will be an upgrade called Bloodline Rebellion.
[SPEAKER_06]: All of that from YYR.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to mention, since we're on the topic of WiiWare, Xbox Live Arcade will be getting Meteos Wars and Power Up Forever this week as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Meteos, but I can't imagine not playing it with a stylus.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know I love Tetsuya Mizuguchi through the good times, like Luminous, and the bad times, like 99 Nights.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love that man, and I will get Meteos just because it's Q Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really liked the DS one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was kind of underrated.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I can't imagine not playing that game without the stylus, that's all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, other things that you can expect this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a very short list, unfortunately, because it is this time of year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Most games have already been released for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there are a few late additions, including Prince of Persia on the PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's tardy to the party?
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's stumbling in hungover to the Christmas party?
[SPEAKER_07]: And Sonic Unleashed on PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Both of those versions coming out later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Neopets Puzzle Adventure Puzzle Quest
[SPEAKER_07]: Just with Neopets, does anyone still play Neopets?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just talking about playing Neopets the other day because I miss playing the little games on the site.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you weren't playing them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Talking and doing are two different things though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was talking about Neopets the other day in the mall when I was walking by Claire's.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do they have Claire's nationwide?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that a nationwide chain?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so then you all know, well, for the international audience, Claire's is like the pretty, pretty princess store.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the store for like 11-year-old girls who want to dress up like princesses.
[SPEAKER_06]: and you can stop with the comments right now about how much I love Claire's but I was looking in the window not in the store but in the window and they had all these Neopets things for sale and I was telling my friend I remember when I used to play Neopets damn I needed a life so that's all and you don't now
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, watch it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Core on DS, that'll be coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see, Hidden Expedition, Amazon, and The Tale of Despero, both on PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other titles for this week, Slingo Quest on DS, Left Brain, Right Brain 2 on DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Driver's Ed Portable, yes, you can practice your Driver's Ed tests on the DS now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Build the lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can practice your, is it like just the written test on?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I practice driving on Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Build a Lot, Ski and Shoot, Dungeon Maker 2, The Hidden War on PSP,
[SPEAKER_07]: Kate West, The Vanishing Files on DS, and of course the big one for the week, Shin Megami Tensei Persona 4 on PS2.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that is the special edition that comes with the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because Atlas is really hooking you up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Freaking rad?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I have to say that it's only going to get worse from here.
[SPEAKER_07]: The next few weeks are crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Banjo-Kazooie Nuts and Bolts is going to be released over in Japan on December 11th as is Mirror's Edge in Japan on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also being released December 11th on the PlayStation 3, Hakuna Matata!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's actually a general Asia release.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did that game ever get released here in the U.S.?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's going to be released here under, I think Namco's doing it, under National Geographic Africa.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that's a better name.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did that game get a facelift all of a sudden, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, they're changing it up for here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not coming over here for a while, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to see animals eating each other.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Hakuna Matata gets the general Asia release.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an English-Chinese version, so you could import it, technically, December 11th.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I want to see the monkeys throw poo and do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or you can import the UK version, which I believe is in English and I think is already out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mina No Golf 5 gets a price reduction this week, this Friday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mirror's Edge also comes to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Virtua Fighter also gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a localized version of WALL-E, the video game, on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be the Disney movie, WALL-E.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the Wii, Cooking Mama, Minato Isho ni Aoyoi Takai.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fancy name for Cooking Mama 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Donkey Kong Jungle Beat, the Wii edition, comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has this face breaker and major Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Samba de Amigo comes out as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Taiko no Tatsujin also gets a Wii release.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know we have some Taiko fans from the music game folks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, also, Dark Sakura, are you listening?
[SPEAKER_06]: December 11th, Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Tatsunoko vs. Capcom, Cross Generation of Heroes comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you might want to be looking into imports pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the PlayStation 2, Galaxy Angel 2 gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think most of our listeners are probably going to be looking for Shimogami Tensei Persona 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: Call it a hunch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh no!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, that's the US release.
[SPEAKER_06]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes some US states sneak into my list here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I have dates for our UK people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Return the ferret, I command thee.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will put it like on a bungee cord.
[SPEAKER_06]: You do need to put it on a bungee cord so every time you throw it, you can yank it back.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a bungee ferret.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not that I should be encouraging you to do this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for... You know, there was a totally random conversation that we had yesterday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: But did it involve ferrets?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it didn't involve ferrets.
[SPEAKER_07]: It involved small animals.
[SPEAKER_07]: We were talking about that they should... Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: We were talking about that they should breed like micro monkeys and call them like munkins.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know where that came from.
[SPEAKER_07]: We were at a really boring Christmas party at my dad's house.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're out of alcohol.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's eat sugar and brainstorm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, you know what they need to do?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, since we've been talking community games and all this stuff and all this good Xbox Live thing, shouldn't they have a game called Bungie Ferret Tossing?
[SPEAKER_06]: It could be like Orange Launch Radio presents Bungie Ferret Tossing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Add this to the list of Orange Launch Radio dream games.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, add this to the list of Orange Launch Radio reality games.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to tell Becky about the dream games.
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to learn how to program or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a series of games that we're mentally developing.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, you're in school.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take a class on programming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Learn it!
[SPEAKER_07]: Absorb via osmosis.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can learn it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're a towel.
[SPEAKER_06]: UK dates, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the 11th, Luminous Supernova on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: That makes me go squee and get happy in places.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the 12th, some stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Prince of Persia for PC, The Magic Roundabout.
[SPEAKER_03]: For people in America who don't know what a roundabout is, Traffic Circle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob is red.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: This show sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Laughter is warm, and we're not.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also coming out, your mom the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully your mom the game lasts longer than Mirror's Edge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Longer than the player.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, I...
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: They're trying to get guys to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: First they get them cooking and then they get them planting stuff in the garden.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait a minute, this is some type of secret plot, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: To get men to do the things that women are supposed to be doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's next?
[SPEAKER_06]: Laundry Mama?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, actually... I will not stand for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't worry, Mama will wash it.
[SPEAKER_07]: The next one was... What was it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not Pet City Mama.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's something to do with pets, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pet Shop Mama.
[SPEAKER_06]: PoopScoopMama
[SPEAKER_03]: But food is delicious, and some pets are tasty.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is a little strange that Cooking Mama will work in the pet shop part-time, and then she cooks things, and PETA has a problem with it the other half of the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, that PETA thing was bullshit.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You were gone when all that went down.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember I posted on my Twitter.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the week we were all off, was the PETA thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I posted on my Twitter about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think we talked about it briefly last week on the show, and I was like, if Jamie was here, she'd say it's bullshit.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's bullshit!
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck you, PETA.
[SPEAKER_03]: My preemptive F you goes to PETA.
[SPEAKER_03]: May you get fucked with a steak.
[SPEAKER_03]: A big, bloody, cow rib.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're really mature here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, Loki, did she really just said go fuck yourself with a steak?
[SPEAKER_06]: Am I not mistaking?
[SPEAKER_06]: I did hear that.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: With ribs.
[SPEAKER_06]: R.I.B.B.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: America's Army, obviously, you know, the game is free to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's a fairly popular game, you know, because it's, again... It's pretty old, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the last game that they put out sucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, get this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right here in Rancho Cordova, where we tape our show, a suburb of Sacramento, where the OLR Studios is, not even that far from where we tape, only like one exit up the freeway, there was a U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: Army video game tournament for the game America's Army that happened right here in our neck of the woods.
[SPEAKER_06]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft,
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyone under 17 had to have a parent or guardian there in order to compete in the tournament.
[SPEAKER_06]: And sign up for the milter.
[SPEAKER_06]: If we had known it was going on, we would have gone out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I would not have.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have played.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think people think of Orange Lounge Radio when they think of America's Army.
[SPEAKER_06]: They think of the O.L.
[SPEAKER_03]: Army.
[SPEAKER_06]: Usually not the type of game we cover, but I would have gone out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just to kind of check it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you see what SSJ100Matt said in the chat room?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: The winner of the tournament gets to go to Iraq.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's like a twisted version of, you know, what the hell was that?
[SPEAKER_07]: God, why am I drawing a blank now?
[SPEAKER_07]: 80s movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Last Starfighter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, The Last Starfighter was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it's like The Last Starfighter, just more death.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got
[SPEAKER_03]: A friend of mine in Iraq right now, and I would not want anyone to go over there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And to go back to what I was talking about when she was mentioning Runabout, or Roundabout or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Roundabout.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the game I was thinking was called Runabout, and it was, yeah, the US title was Felony 1179.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fun game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got a bus stuck in a subway tunnel in that game, and it spun out of control until it took off like a helicopter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not to say that the game was glitchy or anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good times, good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about some more gaming news?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do I gotta?
[SPEAKER_06]: You gotta.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, this is actually some pretty good news for all of our Suikoden fans.
[SPEAKER_03]: All 108 of you.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a joke there.
[SPEAKER_03]: See if you can spot it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't even played the damn game and I get the joke.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks to Shane, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for all of our friends in Europe, Suiko Den, I guess it's pronounced T-Christ, is coming out on the DS in March next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically the game is, you start off as this unnamed person who's in a security force who has to recruit 108 heroes to battle the One King.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_03]: and you have a four person party and it's Suikoden and you can go over the Wi-Fi to send characters into different games or other worlds so they can get new items, different quests, meet new people and this one actually just came out in Japan and we here in America are supposed to be getting it in February.
[SPEAKER_03]: But sorry people in Europe, you've got to wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or import!
[SPEAKER_06]: with tactics and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: of course you know their Q Entertainment is known for their games that kind of blend in you know pretty cool musical aspects to it so making I don't know a musical game it's not necessarily a bad thing and not really unexpected something else to look forward to I guess I guess we'll find out a little bit more about this later on I would be more worried if it was called LLQJ nice
[SPEAKER_03]: I've had sugar today, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: And how.
[SPEAKER_03]: And how.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, hey, I'm all over this.
[SPEAKER_06]: You talk music, you talk Mizuguchi, Q Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know I'm going to check it out because I'm a whore for everything that man puts out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you know I'm excited about this one if I didn't already have everything that this is going to be offering.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Atari is going to be bundling several of Mizuguchi's games together.
[SPEAKER_06]: Res HD, Luminous Live, and Every Extend to Extra Extreme are all going to be retailed together in one retail package.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be called Q3, which is supposed to be some type of term meaning cubed, I guess, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or you could do San Q3, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's a cute idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it was the same pun with QQQ.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: SonQ, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I get it, I get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you can also do, I mean, you know, the third power is Q being something, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: Either way, I didn't even think of the SonQ thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, you know, I'm sure a lot of our listeners probably already downloaded these games, but this is good news for those that are the more casual Xbox 360 people that don't take it online.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would get this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean... Because we haven't downloaded all this yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then here's your perfect opportunity, because...
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's going to save very much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't see a price point listed here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably worth all the download content for Loomis.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, with the download content included, I think this is actually a pretty good package deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: It saves you time and effort, really, if just that.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, that helps.
[SPEAKER_06]: Works out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I mean, there's no reason for me to get this because I always bottle this shit the first day it came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm glad to see that there's enough faith in the product that they're giving it a retail release.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, who would have thought years ago when Rez was on Dreamcast it was kind of a cult title?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, not everybody really knew about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knew that it would be kind of resurfacing in the mainstream again today?
[SPEAKER_06]: If that makes any sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I kind of wish they'd do a true sequel to Rez.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wouldn't that be hot?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: They are already, Gordon Chan is directing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's not too many details, but they're sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is basically what was put out saying about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like the King of Fighters movie will introduce a new science fiction spin into the setting.
[SPEAKER_03]: That right there is enough to make me vomit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fighters in Space
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like the crap they tried to do with the last Mortal Kombat movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, don't ruin my movie, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't ruin... King of Fighters was like classic staple in fighting games for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I grew as a gamer when King of Fighters came out and expanded my mental universe and made me realize that, yes, SNK can do a good fighting game other than Samurai Shodown.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what kind of cherished childhood memory would it be if they didn't come and rape it later on in a movie form?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, at least it's not being directed by Uwe Boll, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm glad I have something to be thankful for this holiday season.
[SPEAKER_03]: But stars in the movie are Maggie Q, Sean Ferris, William Lee, and Ray Park.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, Ray Park.
[SPEAKER_03]: Darth Maul!
[SPEAKER_06]: Darth Maul, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Seth Rogen.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what?
[SPEAKER_06]: And Toad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toad, eh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you know what happens when lightning strikes a toad?
[SPEAKER_06]: Same thing that happens to everything else.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was awesome when Storm said it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: It really, really wasn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, do not get this couch started on Halle Berry and how much ass she sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, but Jamie Catwoman.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've blocked that out of my memory.
[SPEAKER_03]: It does not exist as a part of my universe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, it could be worse, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: They could have had Tyra Banks play the part or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tyra Banks has more personality, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: She would have brought the much-needed sass to the part.
[SPEAKER_03]: She would have brought the sass and she would have brought...
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the gut to?
[SPEAKER_07]: Call of Duty Game
[SPEAKER_07]: And then finally, they're going to do something a little different with the next Tony Hawk game, which apparently is going to not be played with a controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: And will be a game that you're not going to be playing with a controller in your hands, according to them.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, what everybody's been speculating, the rumors have been around for a long time now, that it's going to be actually some sort of motion-controlled skateboard thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which, at that point, I have to ask...
[SPEAKER_07]: Why don't you just go skateboard then?
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're not actually going to be playing with a controller, just go skateboard.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you're almost there anyways, and it's a hell of a lot cheaper.
[SPEAKER_03]: But air conditioning.
[SPEAKER_03]: Carpet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But still.
[SPEAKER_07]: Skateboarding.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, once you get to the point where it's so much like the thing that you're doing that you're actually doing it, you might as well just go actually do the sport.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I'm sure I forgot to mention that they're probably going to be pumping out four more Guitar Hero games because they haven't buried that into the ground enough yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and Bizarre Creations.
[SPEAKER_07]: You may remember them from the Project Gotham racing series.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're actually working on another racing game as well that's going to be racing and driving focused.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, because that would be any other racing game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um,
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're also working on one that's going to be similar to Mario Kart meets Forza.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: Mario Kart meets Forza?
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe it's like a Mario Kart type of game, but you actually tune your cards and what weapons and stuff are on it and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about a cute Forza game?
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: They already got Coral Q. You know, if you want your cute racer, buy the Coral Q franchise.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you see that they're actually putting out, and I don't know why they've done this over here, apparently EA doesn't know how to make games for the Wii, but they've decided that the next best idea to bringing NASCAR to the Wii instead of actually, I don't know, bringing NASCAR to the Wii is NASCAR Karts?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's like Mario Kart with NASCAR drivers.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, while Loki was reading us that last little story there, I actually was working on my portal that lets us peer inside Dark Sakura's alternate universe.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: So I actually have a clip from Dark Sakura's alternate universe where Tyra Banks is Storm.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, I'm going to show you how fantastic my underwear make me feel.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really feel crazy standing up here in my underwear.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm used to doing this on, you know, a Victoria's Secret runway or in a catalog, but not on The Tyra Show.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I need a little help.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody, on the count of one, two, three, I want you to lose those under the canopy robes right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Free that underwear, everybody!
[SPEAKER_07]: This is too much tire for this show.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have the best parts coming up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lord.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because today, today is a panty party!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a panty party.
[SPEAKER_02]: Panty party.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, if it was possible for this show to get any more uber gay, it just jumped the pink shark.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would just like to point out that's one minute of your time you can never have back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Courtesy of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: And how is this part of the gamer lifestyle?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're doing really good because we have not discussed food.
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Hero DJ Tiesto
[SPEAKER_06]: Dance, trance, kind of scene.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, very excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dancey trancey.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also should be noted, Paul Oakenfold apparently has seen the game, and that was kind of news that came out previously, but no word on whether he's on the soundtrack, but that would be quite a list of... I'd probably have to buy it then.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm already thinking Testo's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Tigerclaw is quick to point out, because I know he loves this kind of music.
[SPEAKER_06]: This guy was number two on the DJ Mag Top 100 of 2008.
[SPEAKER_06]: He got beat out by Armin van Buren, who, by the way, if I remember right, if memory serves me right, was in Beatmania 2DX7 style.
[SPEAKER_06]: How's that for useless knowledge?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, go sign you up for Jeopardy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, I love Jeopardy.
[SPEAKER_03]: As long as you threaten Alex Trebek for us.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then when I lose, I'll sing, I lost on Jeopardy, baby.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you just respond to everything Alex Trebek says with, Well played, Trebek.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like your mother, Trebek.
[SPEAKER_06]: More news, then calls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, how about Lips?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, the mic that's coming out with Lips works for Rock Band 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or Will.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, is Will... That's a sexy microphone, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: That Lips microphone is very cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: It glows.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't believe I left this out of my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought SingStar ABBA!
[SPEAKER_06]: I only got to play it for like five minutes because singing by yourself is no fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: But SingStar ABBA... We need to do... After the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll show it.
[SPEAKER_06]: After the show, I'll show you SingStar ABBA.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's magnificent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Becky sings fantastic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here, let me tell you this though, listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: You already know how you would feel about SingStar ABBA.
[SPEAKER_06]: You already know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Abba, Abba, Abba, Abba
[SPEAKER_07]: I was actually at Best Buy a few times this weekend looking and just going through like their music section music game section and it's funny all the stuff that they have for Rock Band available they actually sell the ion drums there in store which is kind of crazy but you know what else I saw right underneath those ion drums that I was like for half a second going huh maybe I should the Rock Band stage kit
[SPEAKER_07]: with the fog machine, and the lights.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Fire drill, bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Question from the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Acidic Vampire wants to know about Sing Star Abba.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are there harmonized duets in Sing Star Abba?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I'd rather be Frida.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good question.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think three of the songs were duets, but again, I was playing it by myself because I was sad and lonely and playing Sing Star Abba by myself.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know it would take a chance on you?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hey, I got like...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Something that I've been saying, and I'm not really a big fan of it, but something that I'm saying that they should have done from the get-go with Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rock Band country music is going to be coming out, or at least some country download tracks will be coming out on December 16th.
[SPEAKER_07]: and they're going to have, it doesn't really say yet what songs they're going to be, but the report, apparently they're claiming that there's going to be five songs as part of the pack.
[SPEAKER_07]: Names include, let's look at it, Bentley, Brad Paisley, Brooks and Dunn, Miranda Lambert, and the Dixie Chicks as artists.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, I do think that they should have download content for country music in the game because...
[SPEAKER_07]: There are people that like country music and they want to play that kind of stuff in Rock Band, and the download content's optional, so why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: And I also think they should have more heavy metal in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, you know, I do think that it's a good idea, though, to do the country content like that, because, I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: Currently, country music is not all the boring crap it was when I was a little kid.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you've got some pretty difficult, I would say, difficult guitar out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yes, I do agree, we need a lot more metal.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I love the joystick posts that they were talking about, the different things.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to take a moment to read the man, Jolene.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're saying, who's going to mow your grass and the gambler?
[SPEAKER_07]: I am 26.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything Kenny Rogers is fine with me.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Gambler would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: What about Islands in the Stream?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, give me anything, Dolly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dolly Parton is the woman, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: But you know, I bet this is them feeling the waters for a future...
[SPEAKER_06]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: I would totally dig having some... I actually would pretty much dig the Brooks and Dunn content.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would love some Alan Jackson.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be freaking rad.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I would also, though, like to see them... This is my thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: If the country content does well, then maybe they should expand and do some jazz content.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do... Don't give me that look.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I was just thinking Karaoke Revolution did a country version, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember when Karaoke Revolution got so popular that they did a country spin-off of that?
[SPEAKER_03]: But I was thinking they should do other styles, because they're really sticking into that broad category of rock, as in the classic rock to hard rock.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I could do less punk and rock music.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there's plenty of it, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's plenty of rock music, plenty of punk music,
[SPEAKER_07]: They're really kind of starting to do that Scott stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what you'd call it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did give us Rush, and that made me happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am all over that No Doubt album next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, but I'm ready to party like it's 1995.
[SPEAKER_06]: With that whole OJ verdict and everything this week, it's like 1995 all over again.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that awesome?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to just get out my Beanie Babies and Pogs and just have a day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_06]: Listen to Jagged Little Pill, watch some Apollo 13.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's 1995 of them and her.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1995 was Radiohead for me, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: That works too.
[SPEAKER_03]: But seriously, we should do a list list one day of non-rock songs we want to hear in Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I could get a little crazy with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of the games have beat it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, that's awesome right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope it wasn't Rock Revolution because that would suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it was Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you rocked that Metallica edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: Got one more song for you guys before we start to get into the last segment of the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, they're going to have Guitar Hero Metallica, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_06]: This news is actually coming to us from LiveJournal, of which our eyes and ears are sometimes on LiveJournal, but apparently there's a whole Beatmania 2DX community out there on LiveJournal, and there was a post that highlights that some of the clips from Beatmania 2DX Empress, you know, which is the new one in arcades, it's what, 16th?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, darn.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how he'll ever manage to get more clips up on the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not like there's other services out there where they can do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, wait, there are.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do you think though that Konami would suddenly put the squelch on this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's not like 2DX is a huge thing here in America anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they have us stick up their ass, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they won't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of dumb because it doesn't really hurt anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't see, you know, if anything, it's driving hype for it because everyone wants to see how hard these songs are and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't see what the big deal is, but hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: They're in the right to be able to protect their property or whatever, but still, I think it's kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only thing that can come good of this, of Konami taking this down, is that then I won't see them and get angry at them for not really trying to support Beatmania over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that's the only good thing that can come of it, because then I won't see them and get frustrated, even if
[SPEAKER_06]: The quality of those games, in my opinion, has gone down ever since Red.
[SPEAKER_07]: Once you get to the 16th version of something, it can't really be that edgy anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's tough.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did have to go back to something from the previous story, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Suss says that they should have Rock Band Weird Al edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: It's sadly enough totally off topic with this.
[SPEAKER_07]: For some reason in my carb, I was switching up the music that I've been listening to, and it got me thinking there is actually a way I was thinking that they could bring back DDR and make it actually new and fresh and have the same appeal as it did before, but I know that they would never do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: It would take too long to explain, but it's basically taking a different direction than they have it right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, kind of going back to the way it was and just, you know, making sure, like, keeping things...
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can't dig enough into Loki's head.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot of stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got a spoon.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can try.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, anyhow, I don't know about you guys, but I get angsty when I think about all this news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just the fact that we don't really have Beatmania here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: The fact that the one way I got to watch it is taken down off YouTube.
[SPEAKER_06]: I get a little bit angsty and thus queues the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: My biggest ever FU right now, because I have big ones all the time, goes to my finger.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it also goes to not being able to find my splint earlier.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've had a bad flare-up, and I've talked about it on the show before, but I had a flare-up of flexor tendonitis, which more commonly is known as trigger finger, in my right hand ring finger.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I would like for people to look this up, because it's really kind of gross.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's basically, it started to hurt a lot, and I have art finals due.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it hurts to type.
[SPEAKER_03]: It hurts to draw.
[SPEAKER_03]: It hurts to write.
[SPEAKER_03]: It hurts to do almost anything that requires holding something.
[SPEAKER_03]: It hurts to hold a fork.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can hold chopsticks pretty damn well, though, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: That means I can go have sushi all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I should use that as my excuse, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, I can't hold a fork.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want sushi.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's been kind of a major pain in the finger.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, F you to my hand.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, I've got to go see the orthopedist.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want surgery.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because then that will put me behind on any of my physical drawing classes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Surgery sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and you know all about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't the end of the world, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have no gallbladder.
[SPEAKER_06]: Laparoscopic surgery is not so bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, look, you know, I've been starting to eat some of this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had Jack in the Box the other day, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was not getting that for like six months and getting to eat it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Great.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the other thing also having to do with medical woes is the fact that every time I eat anything, it makes me sick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of which, small accomplishments in gallbladder world.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had Mexican food yesterday.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't had Mexican food.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm not talking about like fucking Taco Bell.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm talking about like Aldo Berritos where you get like pretty decent Mexican food.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually ate that yesterday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Made with real lard?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's been like randomly every time I eat something I get kind of lonely.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like when I had the plague.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, we talked food after all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I had Indian food today and I didn't care how sick I got.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's one thing we've got to do soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are so going back to Star of India.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, Loki, do you have any FUs?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um,
[SPEAKER_07]: SmallFU2 fries because they sold me a defective set of RAM.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to upgrade my computer from 2 to 4 gigs and the second pair of RAM chips I got apparently no worky because my computer crashes after like 2 minutes every time I launch it up now.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I had to take those out, so that sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then FU to Kaiser for reasons I can't say.
[SPEAKER_07]: And FU to my work for giving me way more accounts than I can handle and not giving me any more money.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least I don't think they are.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that sucks because there's nothing I can do about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't FU'd your work for similar reasons.
[SPEAKER_07]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I told you I would be all over that if it paid more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, yeah, I'd be all over it too if it paid more.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll keep mine short.
[SPEAKER_06]: My F.U.
[SPEAKER_06]: is to the cold weather because it's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Beckers, you've been quiet tonight, but maybe you have a little angst in you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have anything you want to give a good F.U.
[SPEAKER_06]: to, a good hearty F.U.
[SPEAKER_06]: to?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, we got one more segment before we open up the Skype lines for you guys at our Skype line, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's a favorite here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: One that I stole last week when DarkSakura wasn't here.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: I stole it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are a whore.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was a good game, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got to give the Commodore 64 a little love last week, so it was good.
[SPEAKER_06]: But now we get to go back to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
Heart.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's tonight's classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Super Metroid!
[SPEAKER_06]: A very good choice it is tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is a good way for you to return to the program.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had to put the intro music up there first.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then my favorite music in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's my favorite music in the damn game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you want to turn it up a little bit?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the Brinstar music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, Super Metroid is basically a... I mean, it plays... We know what the fuck Metroid is.
[SPEAKER_03]: You run and you shoot shit and you're a girl in armor and you get weapons on the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, Samus returns back to the Metroid-y planet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Zebes, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically gets to explore around and kill things and find all of her old enemies and get some very new weapons.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, um, you get the moonwalk, which means you can slide backwards while firing.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have, um, the ability to combine beams.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, um, it has the save system that they put in Metroid 2, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: You also can go back into the gunship and save and recharge and do fun stuff there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And all kinds of little secret areas you can get to by combining your weapons in different ways.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really, really fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: But basically, you have to go back and find her baby Metroid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: In Metroid 2, she took home, there was a Metroid that hatched and believed Samus was its mommy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so she took it off to be studied to see if they can help people.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then someone stole the Metroid and she had to go back after her baby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Samus' jellyfish looking baby.
[SPEAKER_00]: The last Metroid is in captivity.
[SPEAKER_00]: The galaxy is at peace.
[SPEAKER_03]: Digitized voice for Super Nintendo, hi!
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did think it was funny that the Metroid producer was busy working on the Virtual Boy at the time and didn't have much involvement with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this is a game that I'll get Dan to play, and I'll just sit back on the couch going, go this way, go that way, go this way, go that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's really freaking cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're better at this than I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know my thoughts on this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love this game more than most other games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty much any other game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love this game so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've already been caught up in the controversy about how much I love this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I won't repeat it, but let's just say I love this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: This game is electronic nookie.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, um, what?
[SPEAKER_03]: It is!
[SPEAKER_06]: It is Sex and Pixels.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Without being dirty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, we all know that this game has been the big influence for the current series of Castlevania games, you know, with that same type of map system running all over the place shooting stuff, except using a whip.
[SPEAKER_03]: um it also is one of it's actually stated um in my resource that it was a contributor to the speedrun phenomenon because you did actually if for beating the the game in different ways you got different rewards different things you can speedrun through super metroid like a mofo if you know where you're going and what you're doing
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen this game beaten in person on a major speedrun.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was beautiful.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it's really awesometastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Super Metroid!
[SPEAKER_06]: Super Metroid Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to get it to the point where it plays the theme.
I think it's just going to start the first level.
Here we go.
All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do love this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to play this game right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: The music in this game was freaking fantastic.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really was.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what the Nintendo sound processor was eventually what was incorporated, if I'm right, it's what led to the one in the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Sony made Nintendo's sound processor.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really just want to say, because we do have some younger folks that listen to this show who weren't a teenager or junior high or whatever when this game first came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: You really owe it to yourself to check out this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is gaming at some of its greatest.
[SPEAKER_06]: And as much crap as I've given the whole Chrono Trigger versus Super Metroid thing that came up totally unnecessarily.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, seriously, no one's going to care if it's a 2D game.
[SPEAKER_07]: No one's not going to buy your game just because, oh, it's 2D, I don't want to play a 2D game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you know what, people will play a 2D game and they will like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at a game like Braid, you can still do awesome things in 2D.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at Castlevania games, they sell like hotcakes on the DS, and they would sell like hotcakes on the Wii if they put out a really cool looking 2D Castlevania game.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't have to go all 3D.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just make it fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make it exciting.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all you have to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we are going to go... Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: That Metroid Zero game, even though it was on the Game Boy Advance, was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a great successor, in a way, to Super Metroid, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they revisited the original Metroid, but changed just enough that it really felt all new again, which I thought was kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's open.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just now seeing, though, that our time might have run out on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whoops!
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm curious if the Skype line is going to work tonight or if I'm late.
[SPEAKER_06]: Today was the day it runs out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we may or may not be able to get calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR I'm going to try calling it myself real fast and see if it works.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Oh, we have a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that call is coming in on Skype though.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR
[SPEAKER_06]: O-L-R Let me see if it works.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm calling it myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, do you have any last minute stories while I do this live on air test that's very professional?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Real quick stuff, just confirming a lot of the rumors that we had from a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uncharted 2 Among Thieves was announced.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember that thing that supposedly leaked out from Sony saying that there was a new Uncharted game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, apparently it's true, so I wonder if the rest of it will be true as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another big game that we should have mentioned during this show, but Killzone 2 finally got a release date, February 27th.
[SPEAKER_07]: If there's ever going to be an epic first-person shooter game for the PS3, it definitely kills into their Gears of War, if you want to look at it that way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of interesting, someone's bringing Catan to the PS3 as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Game Republic is bringing out that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually going to be a different version that was on the 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of like this one better.
[SPEAKER_07]: No word on when that's going to be out, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: and it will create objects for you based on what you write in.
[SPEAKER_07]: So for example, you have to collect these stars throughout the game and you can write in ladder and a ladder will spawn.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can climb the ladder to get the star or you write in football and you can throw a football at the tree or beaver and the beaver will chew down the tree.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well apparently there's such an enormous dictionary of words in this game you can literally put whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean just...
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: And then finally, I'd like to mention that apparently, according to YYR in chat, he is having a contest.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I was going to read this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: You go ahead and read this.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: You stole my thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I will say this.
[SPEAKER_06]: The contest actually doesn't start until Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're giving you a sneak peek right here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Snake360 contest.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and you can win, there's $450 in prizes to be given away, and they have three different challenges, Race to Fanatic, Survivor Challenge, and Battle Video Exhibition, and of course, different prizes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Looks like the prizes for each category include either a 4,000 points card or one year of live.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots of stuff being given away, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And apparently the contest starts on Tuesday, ends on Sunday, January 11th.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we can really say, and truthfully say, you heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because Aaron, the author of the game, just put this up and sent us a message first.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we had him on our show a couple weeks ago and he hasn't forgotten about us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't know if we're automatically ineligible, but I'm thinking the battle video might actually be kind of fun to try.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, um, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: That sounds pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, of course, Gran Turismo 5 apparently is on track for holiday of the night.
[SPEAKER_07]: Funny, because I thought that was supposed to be out this year, but, you know, hey, I guess it's still on track to come out someday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Show us home.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, we got a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, Orange Lounge Radio land.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, I'm very special tonight, and...
[SPEAKER_08]: The One Voice of the Crowd, or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, when DJ Hero and all that stuff was kind of coming up, I was just kind of going around looking for information, and I pulled up a Kotaku post about it with the first notes on it, and the picture of it reminded me of a story that I don't believe I've told on here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Before I get into that, I was just going to kind of ask, there's been a screenshot that makes DJ Hero look like Guitar Hero with a DJ floating next to the chart, but we don't really know anything about the game itself or the controller, do we?
[SPEAKER_06]: There were some rumors about the controller a while back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wasn't the controller supposed to be like a giant turntable with kind of like buttons around it or something like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I seem to remember there was a story a couple... Yeah, something like, it's not going to look like Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's for sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a common misconception about it is that, oh, well, they're going to rip off Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nah, it doesn't look like they really want to go for that exact same game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be different, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guitars and drums can't exactly be made original when they're supposed to be guitars and drums, but DJ decks have a lot of liberty to play with.
[SPEAKER_05]: True.
[SPEAKER_08]: So the Kotaku entry that I was talking about, you know that Joystick and Kotaku and everybody else picks a featured picture that my Mario Kart code has been so greatly featured on three years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have this little actual DJ Pioneer deck that reminded me of something I saw at Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our Best Buy opened up a musical instruments corner of the building.
[SPEAKER_08]: and when we were there the last time, we kind of poked our heads in there and were killing some time.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had a bunch of drum kits, digital drum kits laid out.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had drawers of DJ kits with full-size digital turntable decks, I guess, and little miniature turntable decks with the crossfader and the, if there's a specific name for the centerpiece, far be it for me to know what it's called.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kind of looking forward to seeing more with what comes about with DJ Hero I think we are all on pins and needles about DJ Hero, Jason But the sad thing is I don't think we're going to see it until E3 I think this is going to be Activision's big thing at E3 next year Because with Guitar Hero, we know that shit They say new Guitar Hero game, we're like whoopty shit, we know what this is all about But DJ Hero is going to be real new, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah
[SPEAKER_08]: and you can draw the parallels to everything you want that's already come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Beatmania and Kraken DJ and I seem to remember there was something even more obscure that I can't think of.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kraken DJ was fun and all, but it just wasn't a real deck besides... Okay, it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Two turntables and a crossfader.
[SPEAKER_08]: But none of the effectors, none of the volumes, none of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, remember this, Jason, like 98% of gamers haven't played any of those games you just mentioned, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: But DJ Hero really has the potential, you know, to kind of
[SPEAKER_06]: The foot is already in the door, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to get shelf space right next to Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, sometimes women will come in here and want to know, where's that guitar game for my husband who's been away?
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm thinking, like, wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, like, that really just kind of put into perspective, like, it really has kind of crossed over now into, like, that guitar game that every family has to have, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's because they picked music that people actually know and care about to some extent.
[SPEAKER_06]: But DJ Hero is going to have a huge foot in the door because of the mainstream success of Guitar Hero and Rock Band, really.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: and the fact that they're actually going for names like Tiesto and anybody else that they're going to sign and announce later on down the line.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who would have thunk it when we started this show a few years ago that music games would become so huge, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially after we moved away from just music games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's what did it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember there was no new DDR for like years and years and literally two weeks after we said, we're going to move away from the music game things and talk about general gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Supernova is coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bastards.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Konami exists to spite you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Konami does exist to spite us sometimes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really truly believe that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think the most interesting part about all this is the Guitar Hero arcade cabinets that was talked about a few weeks back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: And just the fact that they can do, especially with the fact that Guitar Hero itself went world tour, and the fact that apparently Konami's working with Activision for the cabinets.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: If that didn't just signal Rock Revolution's death that we already knew was coming, what does?
[SPEAKER_08]: But just the fact that World Tour exists and DJ Hero was acquired by Activision.
[SPEAKER_08]: Should I say Freestyle Games was acquired by Activision, who was making DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_08]: The big linked performance games that we always wanted out of DDR, 2DX, Guitar Freaks, Drum Mania, and optionally Keyboard Mania, but that died pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: can actually come stateside, stateside music, and possibly too a lot for arcades for all we know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be freaking expensive, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I said this a long time ago on the show, and I truly believe it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Harmonix and these developers were willing to take the risk that Konami wasn't, and look where it got them.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Konami should be kicking their own ass right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if they didn't have the, if there weren't patent laws and all that stuff so that they could essentially ride the coattails now of someone else's success from their idea, which is odd, there wouldn't be a lot going for them right now in the music game world.
[SPEAKER_08]: As much as we can hate on them for filing those lawsuits, the fact that they're working together for an arcade machine is kind of redeeming.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to quickly say this comment, Jason, before we let you go, get your reaction to this.
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw in chat says,
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to play your own version of DJ Hero, you can download a DJ mixing program on your PC and mix your own MP3s.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's boring because that's not telling me how to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't play without arrows on the screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no arrows to step on or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jason, we've got to let you go to get a couple more calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's always good to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Giant Dorkfest.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's this show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Later, dude.
[SPEAKER_08]: Night, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio is our name on Skype.
[SPEAKER_06]: The 800 number is broke tonight because I don't know how to pay a bill on time, apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: For shame.
[SPEAKER_06]: I forgot it was expiring today.
[SPEAKER_06]: They sent their reminders.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got busy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really see any other calls coming through.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do we clear out our last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ring, ring.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're done?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you wanted to read mail.
[SPEAKER_06]: We never did mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is Jimmy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to do the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, first you told me there was no mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now you're telling me there's a mailbag.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't think we'd have time.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we'll do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Since no one else is calling on Skype, we'll close Skype.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's for you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to actually have theme music for the Skype thing, and we need to play Bananaphone.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the fortune cookie message last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you weren't here, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: How funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I thought Ranma was calling in to give a review on something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where is he?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, because he's on the phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: Love you.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we love the mailbag, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag, orangelaunchradio.com, which apparently we are doing this segment tonight, although I only saw one email in there when I went in earlier.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'll send an email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, OLR buddies and friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually titled Why Hello There, OLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: I finally joined the new millennium and got an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've survived solely on DS and PSP for the longest time, and I have to say that it's nice to have a non-portable gaming system again for the first time in nearly three years.
[SPEAKER_03]: So far, I only have Guitar Hero 3 and Guitar Hero Aerosmith.
[SPEAKER_03]: My band's names are Spock's Eyebrows and Doodly Ladies, respectively.
[SPEAKER_03]: but I hope to remedy this soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are some good Xbox 360 games that I should look into purchasing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Fable!
[SPEAKER_03]: Fable 2 is kind of evil but it is definitely entertaining.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can beat up chickens.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please go on Xbox Live Arcade and look at all the sex that's on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Symphony of the Night!
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't already have that on PlayStation 1, definitely Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go look at how much sex is available for cheap on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's where you need to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: and, um, oh shoot, there's also, um, there's of course the Rock Band series and, um, um, Brain Fart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Brain Fart the game!
[SPEAKER_06]: Guitar Hero?
[SPEAKER_03]: She already said she had them!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, moving forward.
[SPEAKER_03]: Since Jamie mentioned playing Order of Ecclesia, I figured I would quickly plug the review I did of that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's great!
[SPEAKER_03]: And can be found on my blog at www.AvengersTower.com
[SPEAKER_06]: The game is great, or the review is great?
[SPEAKER_03]: Both.
[SPEAKER_03]: Order of Ecclesia is definitely a very difficult game compared to earlier Castlevania games, but the difficulty of the game most certainly adds to the fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, OLR, take care of yourselves, and I'll quite possibly see you soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: As soon as next year, perhaps.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eyebrow waggle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sincerely, Marin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care of yourself and each other.
[SPEAKER_07]: Real quick, and this kind of goes back to something we were talking about way earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kunimatata, that was on your release dates for coming out in the Asia regions.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's already been out in the Asia regions, but this is the English slash Chinese version.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you could import this and play it in English.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thought about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's only $49.90.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't run over the animals, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is a downside.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dope.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's hear more.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of them tricked me!
[SPEAKER_03]: It said love, love, love, love, love, and I thought it was about me, but it was spam.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bastards.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate those spammers.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know who you should have F'ed?
[SPEAKER_03]: The one who stole your magnet off your car.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I forgot about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a rainbow all love is divine magnet on my car, and somebody stole it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's on the fridge right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's so messed up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn thieves!
[SPEAKER_03]: Bastards!
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't make a fist.
[SPEAKER_03]: This sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, this is your Friendly Neighborhood Mexican Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_03]: A few weeks ago I got Tales of Vesperia and it's a pretty good game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I recommend it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I point out where we live?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's lots of Friendly Neighborhood Mexicans.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, lots and lots.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: But he's an actual in-Mexico Mexican.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that makes him special.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: with the most recent global economy crisis the Mexican peso has lost its gain to the US dollar but for gaming it has meant a good thing rather than bad when I bought Tales of Vesperia I bought it for 755 pesos which is the MSRP price for it down here now a dollar is worth 1350 pesos approximately so doing the math I solved the game and cost the equivalent of $55 US total that's a savings of $5 US without added sales tax
[SPEAKER_03]: I marveled myself on how this crisis has caused at least one good thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Another example is Gears of War 2, which is a newer game.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the US, it costs $60, while in Mexico it costs around $6.50.
[SPEAKER_03]: Again, doing the math, the game's cost in Mexico is the equivalent of $47, approximately $13 in savings.
[SPEAKER_03]: and there are other games that would cost less here than crossing the border.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, there are other games that still do cost more here than in the U.S., but like I said, it's because of store making up prices rather than giving us the real retail price, especially on PlayStation and Nintendo games since they don't have a real representation in Mexico or Latin America, unlike Microsoft, which does have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh well, that's all for now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh well, that's all for now, OLR Crew.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind of happy news in all this crisis stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: See ya.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry to Jamie who reads this email if there are any grammatical or spelling errors in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: You have better...
[SPEAKER_03]: Grammar and spelling than most people in America do.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you consider the English is not this gentleman's first language, from what I understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe he said before Spanish is the native language.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're my freaking hero today.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: A very rare commendation from DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't get that very often in the mailbag, Saban.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wear that badge with honor, my friend.
[SPEAKER_03]: We also got an email forwarded to us.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: What might be your thoughts regarding you as the consumer using LittleBigPlanet as an advertising and self-promoting marketing tool?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, let me give you the gist of the email because it is kind of long for air, but I did read it off air.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, the emailer was wondering, he was listening to some other shows on All Games and this kind of crossed his mind and wanted to hear our take on it because I guess he's been pulling some different shows.
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm glad I didn't put it on the forum then.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, it's a good question.
[SPEAKER_06]: LittleBigPlanet has this potential to be a new medium for all this marketing.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's the potential for it, or where do you see people using it?
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think people could be using LittleBigPlanet for with all the marketing?
[SPEAKER_06]: And to me, I kind of think, in a way, it's a new...
[SPEAKER_06]: LittleBigPlanet, I kind of compare to a new website.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like a YouTube or iTunes or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess iTunes isn't really a website, but you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: If there's a way to sell your product on it, there will be people that want to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it is the quote-unquote American way after all.
[SPEAKER_06]: I-Tunes Podcasting
[SPEAKER_06]: When we signed up to do podcasting, it was people like us in their garages, in their basements with microphones talking about shit they liked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now it's hugely commercialized, and we're having a hard time staying afloat amongst all these... I mean, we'll be here doing our thing for a long, long time, but we have a hard time getting recognized because you have all these commercial people out trying to tie it into their website, their TV shows, their...
[SPEAKER_06]: TV networks that have very little to do with gaming but they have video game podcasts anyways and so on.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: True story.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was playing Warcraft the other night, and there was a shout in one of the villages.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not even kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you live in, like, I think it was Boston.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you live in Boston, come check out this show on Saturday night if you like this metal band.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm like, dude, how many people in this world of Warcraft might live in Boston?
[SPEAKER_03]: Boston's a pretty big place.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know it's a big place, but World of Warcraft is a really fucking big place.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like 100 Bostons.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you very much, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very true, very true.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't even think about that, but you're right.
[SPEAKER_06]: People have been using video games to promote their shit for a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we could actually have all of our villagers say OrangeSoundsRadio.com and then when they move to other people's villages, they'll spread.
[SPEAKER_06]: LittleBigPlanet
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, and granted, I don't think he put a lot of effort into the level.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he was more, it was his way of exploring the game and being able to give the game a good review.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think he ever kind of intended it to be like, you know, the one and only thing he ever does.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, he invested a fair amount of time into it, but he kind of did like a real easy-ish type of level that kind of slyly worked in a plug for his show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think as long as you're not crazy about it, I bet they wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were actually promoting a LittleBigPlanet fan community on there, and it got pulled.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that's so weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it is stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're getting a little stupid with that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are you laughing at over there?
[SPEAKER_03]: A picture that I got sent for the cover of Wolverine in Power Pack.
[SPEAKER_06]: To go back to the email, definitely where there's a way to do it, people are going to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just a matter of time, but it's kind of interesting to see the moderation and how that's going to play into it because it was very hard to moderate Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, look at the N-word snuck through on one of those cartridges.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, I guess that's it for our show then.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was that the last email too?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was indeed, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Last email tonight, and if you want to send us some emails, mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're ready to get out of here.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got the final thoughts tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never mind, because it comes after.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm looking at this actual P90 tactical load-bearing vest, which is kind of neat, because that would work with my airsoft gun, even though it's meant for actual real guns.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakra, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Deadpool's fucking funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is I'm fucking funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Beckers, shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Beckers, thanks for joining us tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you didn't get to talk a whole lot, but I'm glad you and Jamie got to sit there in the corner and giggle like girls.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have any final words for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's freaking cold here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is cold here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should see what it's like in the summertime, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Trust me, this is better than The Alternative.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to have Becky on when we have stupid parent stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we definitely need to hear from someone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, thank you for reminding me.
[SPEAKER_07]: We didn't even mention that story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh oh, what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is good, this is good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, it was another game that Grand Theft Auto was getting blamed, or another crime that Grand Theft Auto was getting blamed for, and it had nothing to do with Grand Theft Auto at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, it had to do with, uh,
[SPEAKER_07]: Children torturing animals.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, the newest crime to get blamed, or Grand Theft Auto can get blamed for, is hanging kittens with game controller cords after playing Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently...
[SPEAKER_07]: A pair of unsupervised boys, six and seven years old, stoned a kitten and then strung it up following a Grand Theft Auto session.
[SPEAKER_06]: They reportedly used the controller cable in lieu of a rope.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you're not talking about blowing the bong smoke in the kitty's face.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God, that's terrible.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently this happened in late October in Mesa, Arizona.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it says the investigation began when deputies went to the neighborhood of one of the two boys.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I'm thinking this goes a little bit beyond video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm thinking these kids are just really, really, really, really, really fucked up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on, but the county sheriff actually said... So one question...
[SPEAKER_07]: or Arpaio.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not sure if it's the boy's parents or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says, this game allows players to kill cops and rape women.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a little wonder why they perpetrated such violence against a little animal.
[SPEAKER_06]: YYR in our chat, it says, the parents are to blame.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should have bought wireless controllers.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_07]: They would have stoned it to death anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Beckers is dying to say something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Institutionalize your children.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to grow up to be serial killers.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has nothing to do with the video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is coming from a mom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Parents, this has nothing to do with video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: This has everything to do with you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your genes did this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop passing them on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your Hellspawn, Damian Light, did this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree with Becky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Padded room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or just give them a hammer and leave them in a room by themselves.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now can we end the show?
[SPEAKER_06]: Can we end the show now?
[SPEAKER_03]: No!
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for ending the show on dead kittens, you ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I gotta go home and hug my kitty.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have one thing that will make it all better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cookies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay, cookies.
[SPEAKER_06]: And on that note, we're going to go eat some cookies and end the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and by the way, if you enjoy Orange Lounge Radio, please tell two people you know about the program and help us spread the word, because as I mentioned earlier, it's really hard to stay afloat amongst all the commercialized and corporate shows out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Word of mouth, it rocks, and you rock when you leave us happy reviews, and join us for live shows on All Games Radio Sunday nights at 6 o'clock, but if you can't, hey, listen to our recorded shows too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send us an email sometime, because it is the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: www.allgames.com