Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts?
DarkSakura
Sky and Lowkey
Tonight, July 18th, 2010
3D YouTube is set for the PlayStation 3
Details come out on Mega Man Universe
And one retail chain puts user reviews on the shelves
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello everybody out there on the internet
And welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
We are that video game show dedicated to
Video games, gaming, gaming culture, the gamer lifestyle
You name it, you talk about it
Live in our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com
My name is Rob Roberts
I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my co-host
And only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
Hi!
How are you doing, Jamie?
Hi
You're high?
No, actually, um
Starting the Prop 19 celebration a little early?
No, no, no
I've got Vicodin in me
I see
Because I've got a slice in my hand
Yes, you had your surgery
As we've been talking about for a couple weeks on the show
Because it was scheduled last week
But it happened for real Tuesday, right?
It did, and it was really boring
But you're here, so obviously you're doing alright
Yeah, it hurts
I'm sorry, well Vicodin's supposed to help that
No, Vicodin's supposed to make you not care
Supposed to?
Supposed to
Oh, it's going to be a fun show, folks
Well, I was fun yesterday, though
I was really entertaining, I feel
I'm going to get into yesterday in just a minute
But it would not be a show if I didn't introduce the one and only
Techmaster, Loke
It would be a show, I just wouldn't be introduced
How are you doing, Loke?
I'm doing fine
Excellent
How's the baby room painting going?
Because I've seen pictures show up
And for the listeners who might be new to OLR
Who are just tuning in for the first time
Loke's wife is expecting really soon, right?
I think in the next couple weeks
August 19th, but she's 35 weeks and 3 days now
Wow
So, you know
She looks like she's ready to pop
She's basically ready to pop
That's right
What I'm surprised, to be honest, is our friends
Annie and Jim
I mean, you know, Annie
She's 39 and I don't even
She'll be 40 weeks next Wednesday
Or this coming Wednesday
Wow
So she's ready to go
That baby's well done
That baby is done
Well, it's her first, right?
Yes, possibly going to be extra crispy, but
Well, Becky was 10 days overdue with Julian
But yeah, so any day
Basically, they get to the point, though
The doctor will only let you go up to 42 weeks
And then they just say, okay, no, you're having the baby
We're inducing you and you're going
So, no, but Nellie
She's hoping to have the baby by the end of the month
Preferably at 37 weeks
Which would be a week from this coming Thursday
And we don't know what's going to happen to OLR
While you're gone
Knowing you, you'll be here
Even if she delivers Sunday morning
I will probably be gone at least a week or two
But it is so funny
Because, like, there's seriously
People like vultures clamoring for your spot
While you're gone
Even that one week
Drew's been showing up more and more lately
We got an email tonight
That Jamie's going to read later
That has another suggestion
So it's really funny
It's too bad he's not here this week
It really only takes three weeks
But unfortunately
He was shy one week
So that ain't going to work
Well, we'll figure it out
But the point I was actually trying to make
For those that didn't know
You are doing your baby room in a
What? New Super Mario Brothers theme, right?
Yes, New Super Mario Brothers theme
So we've got
We've been painting a lot
And actually I'm trying to get them uploaded
On the photo gallery thing
But it's being a little on the slow side
There's some pictures right now on there
That are really
It's a lot of work ago
I mean, there's a lot of stuff we've done
Since the stuff I posted
And I'd say it's about now
Maybe
I don't know, 60
60, 75% done
And this is all the base stuff
We still have to go back and actually shade it
So that it looks more 3D looking I guess
But I will probably be posting
Pictures in the chat room
I have uploaded them to Flickr
So I'll be posting a link to that
In the meantime while we're waiting for them to upload on the website
Yeah, I know there were some changes on our website this week
And I'm going to get into
It's mostly transparent
Except for this apparently
The picture thing is slowing down
Most of the changes that happened to the website this week
Are transparent
But I'll talk about those in a little bit
When we get to housekeeping
I actually have a lot of housekeeping tonight
But first I need to give a plug to
All Games
Because we do tape live every Sunday night at All Games Radio
www.allgames.com
6 o'clock Pacific
9 o'clock Eastern
Thereabouts right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
We were a little late tonight
And that was my bad
Because I got caught in traffic
Coming back from San Francisco
Which actually is going to tie into
Where we're going to start tonight
We usually do start off the show talking about our gaming weeks
But Dark Soccer and I kind of had a unique event yesterday in our gaming week
We did
And I know Jamie wants to talk all about this
I do
So Dark Soccer
California Xtreme
Tell the listeners who don't know
Because I find not a lot of people outside of California
Or NorCal even
Seem to know what this is
So tell our listeners what this is all about
Where it's at
Why we go
It was Xtreme
California Xtreme is a classic arcade and pinball type of expo thing
And they have speakers, do panels, typical convention stuff
But all the games are out there on free play
And they've got pins dating back from the 50's and up
They even had the Iron Man pinball there
Which by the way was not very exciting
Stern sorry you sucked at this one
I was way more interested in the Dark Knight table they had a picture of
But didn't actually have there
Yeah that's supposed to be pretty hardcore
Dude they had Big Bang Bar though
I'm glad the people that bring
And it was the real Big Bang Bar not the
Because they got the rights to redo Big Bang Bar
Okay I gotta rewind because you know how disjointed I'm gonna be tonight
Big Bang Bar was a table they were only like 16 prototypes of
That Capcom's pinball division did before they decided to not do that anymore
And they eventually did the rights did get out
And someone was doing reproductions of them
But this was one of the 16 prototypes
So it was pretty cool
Anyway they had like
They had the Star Wars pachinko machine
They had old pong
They had a game called Touch Me
It was very 70's
Cocktail tables, sit downs
A really nice Star Wars arcade
It was kind of like going into Microsoft's game room but for real
And journey
Like if it was a real place
They just take this ballroom and just lots of arcade
And more pinball than I was expecting
I didn't realize how much of it was dominated by pinball
They had ultra pin there too
The ultra-cade pinball
That was a cool machine I played pinbot on that it was cool
I've played one of those before like I played Black Knight for a while on there
But it's not the same for me
I've wanted to make one of those but it really
It's cost prohibitive
It's really expensive I have an extra TV that I could use for that
But it's just I don't play that much pinball
And considering how much I play my arcade machine
I don't need to build one of these
Let me go to our chat room at chat.orangelaungerator.com
Because we do get live chat comments as we tape the show
And I'm going to start with Salacious Pop tonight
He was there with us yesterday
Salacious Pop in our chat says
Hi
I played a few rounds of Lethal Weapon 3 pinball
But try as I might I could not unlock the hidden racist misogynist screen
Yes I was hoping they would update the pinball machine
So that like when the ball goes down the gutter it would yell at you
I deserve to be blown
But unfortunately no not going to happen
Anyhow sorry classic games good times
Free play
You pay one fee to get in it was 40 bucks to get in
I got in for nothing
I got in as press for Geek Life
Yours special
Which by the way there's going to be a big write up on this
Showing up tomorrow morning on both Orange Lounge Radio and on Geek Life
Look at it
I had a geeky time while I was there
Looking at all the classes like I was playing a real gyrus machine
And a real time pilot machine
You can't emulate that so well on the 360
The tempest kept having problems with the vector
The vector display
Crystal castles with a real trackball the way it was meant to be played
The lifeguard trackball forward on the 5200
And I played for the first
I know this is going to surprise people
I don't believe I had ever played the Empire Strikes Back game
Isn't it great
Star Wars
Yes and the Star Wars vector game
Man that game was epic
Oh man I love that game
The one that they had there the sit down one
Had like this really nice bright monitor
And the speakers were just so clear
It was fantastic it didn't sound muddy or anything at all
I thought I got a bad headache playing it and it hurt my hand a lot
Because yeah I didn't really play a whole bunch of stuff while I was there
Because um
And we'll probably go into the surgery thing later
I've got 8 stitches in my right hand
Good times
And while I'm healing really nicely
They hurt a lot
Because unlike my last surgery when I moved my hand
I've got more range of motion now
But it pulls the stitches
Ew
And yeah well it'll bleed a little bit
It's really
But you were able to play some stuff
I played since I played Baby Pac Man
I had to play Baby Pac Man
Me too
And that game for being notoriously hard
I always remembered being kind of good at it
I got to the third stage which is not bad for Baby Pac Man
They had a Junior Pac Man
Which is like one of the really epic Pac Mans of its day
Of course I played Big Bang Bar
And Iron Man Pinball
I didn't play Journey
I played Star Wars
I played Journey it was awesome
I played Timber twice
Because I love those old school
I played Mouse Trap
And then Mouse Trap though was the big mistake
Because Mouse Trap has a right hand joystick
And I was like
And I forgot about the stupid bird
Because keep in mind when I was playing a lot of Mouse Trap
I was playing it on the ColecoVision
And there's no bird in the ColecoVision
You know what else was there that was very random
That was cool was a 80s or I guess maybe mid 90s laser disc jukebox
So the whole time people are there playing games
There's these old school songs playing
Everything from like you know
Contemporary-ish songs by like Garbage of You Two
To like pour some sugar on me
On the little four cube TV
Yeah it's there every year
One of those TVs that's made up of little TVs
It was awesome
Yeah totally 80s style
But there's more Rob
There's more
What?
Coin Toss was there
I love the Coin Toss game
It's like one of the old 50s games
It was so fantastic
Like one of the pre-course precursors to our pong
But anyway
There was the Boxcar game
The Sega Boxcar game
Oh yeah the Minecar
Like you actually push up and down on the big lever
Like an old Minecar
And Top Skater
And DDR something or the other
Extreme
I took some video of Mel and Ali playing
I actually got up there and played DDR
I'm not allowed to
Man am I out of shape
I'm not allowed to play DDR until my stitches come out
No
I can't get my heart rate
I miss much
I'm not supposed to get my heart rate up y'all
So I can't get very excited tonight
Um
Looking at our chatroom at chat.orangesonsradio.com
Sure
I always say this name wrong
Surezo in our chatroom says
Sounds like a nice spot
Damn I need to plan to get out to California Extreme
Now I think he's kind of local here
I think he's our guy
It was in Santa Clara
That golfs or does the Roseville Golf Line and everything
But I
Would this be something worth traveling to
Like a long distance
Totally
Yeah we were people there from out of country
I think they could
I mean here's the weird thing
It's an arcade trade show
So I get that they don't want to like expand on
Probably that core part of it
But you know what would have made that expo even more awesome
Would have been like a classic gaming room
With like console stuff
That reminds me
And I know that might be outside the scope of what they're trying to do but
Classic Gaming Expo is coming back
Oh yeah
In Las Vegas
We need to make plans
This was different from Classic Gaming Expo though
I can't really explain
Classic Gaming Expo was its own kind of thing
Yeah
Classic Gaming Expo was more like booths and things set up to remember
But this was just straight up a room full of free play games
I love the story though about
Because Dan's little brother Mason came with us
And there was
They were at this panel and Mason's like who's that
What did that guy do, make Atari?
And Dan's like why yes he actually did
And it was the
Nice
But I got to meet Steve Ritchie
Who designed at least a couple of the tables that we have in this house
No Fear
He did the voices for No Fear
So when I was
When I gave him some of our plastics to sign
And he started doing the voices from No Fear
And I was just
So cool and I talked to his wife
She was a really sweet lady
And told her about a pinball table that I'm designing
Because I'm actually designing the art and everything
And the layout for a pinball table
I just need someone who can program it
Vidpower in our chat room says
California Extreme was in the Donkey Kong documentary King of Kong
I don't remember that
Was that the place they go
I thought that was a place on the East Coast
But they go, it's like an expositions going on
And Billy, not Billy, the other guy
Steve tries to top the score at this expo
But he just barely misses it
He doesn't do it
Well no he did this at conventions since I thought
Yeah I don't know
But anyway
No Steve Wiebe's been I think at these conventions
And all those types of guys you see in that documentary
Are here at this type of event
Good times
Anyway though
And then there were vendors for pinball parts
And you know
A stern marketer was there
The guy who brought the Iron Man table
And the guy that plays the 12 string guitar thing
Was there
Because he's there every year
And he's always really cool
I just had this
I googled myself and I walked
I was walking sort of
Catty corner around
And all of a sudden in the distance I hear
Bong, bong, bong, bong
The Space Invaders thing
And then there's also one of our listeners there
Really cool guy, Carlson
Really cool guy
And I purchased a game for my husband
Got Gunstar Heroes for the Game Gear
I was kind of surprised
Treasure
I was surprised to see him there
Because the last time I had seen him
Was out in Washington D.C.
And he's based in the East Coast
He's mostly the cons out there
But I guess he has a relative that lives out here
So he was at this con
Very random moment
Because I was actually looking at the shirts
At his booth
And he has this really funny
And I guess this is his own original design
It says like Shaq Fu
I loved that
And I almost
I was thinking about buying it
But then I got distracted
Because he's like
Hey Rob
And I was like
Oh wow
I remember you from like four years ago
So this is kind of funny
Like running into people
He recognized me
And I didn't know who he was
Or anything
Well it was funny
I was looking for you
To go introduce you to him
When you just found him on your own
I had Melody and I did
Oh good times
I had a quick bundle
You just cut out suddenly
Did your switch go down?
Uh no
I don't have a switch
Oh weird
I don't know what happened
Well meh
Tonight is going to be a night of technical fun
The soundboard's on Vicodin
Alright well before we get to
The rest of our gaming weeks
Outside of
Oh boy
Outside of just this convention
Is there anything else you want to say about California Extreme?
Maybe the thing you most want to see them do next year?
Do it exactly like they did it
And make it cheaper
And bigger
Oh yeah
Bring back the Kung Fu game
What game was it there at Kung Fu Master?
It wasn't there
And and and
Damn it
Somebody bring a theater of magic
Because Melody and I were annoyed
Alright
Well uh DarkSakura
I know you had the surgery
I don't know if you've been playing a lot of video games
But outside the expo
Did you play any video games this week?
How was your gaming week?
I'm playing Sims right now
Um
I was playing some Sims
I tried to play Star Trek Online
But it hurt too much
So I just went on to let my fleetmates know
That I wasn't dead of gangrene of the hand
Um
Damn beat Crackdown finally
It was anticlimactic
First one or the new one?
Second one
Oh wow
It was anticlimactic
Um
And I also really hate the guy in that game
He's like
Are you trying to piss me off?
Go back to the tactical location
I just wanted to tell him
Shut up and bite my butt
You sound like you've got
A wedgie
Um
And um
I know I played something else
I don't remember
You're too high to remember
No, no
Um
Are you playing the Sims right now?
I said I was playing the Sims
Oh um
I played a little bit of Portal
A little bit of Portal
Just a little bit?
Just a little bit
It's just like
Just enough to get taunted by GLaDOS?
Yeah
It was just like
I'm getting so bored
Not being able to do much of anything
That I'll sit and start to play something
Like with the Sims at least
You know I can do a little bit
And rest my hand
But if I get in the middle of a battle
On Star Trek Online
I'm there until it's done
Cause you can't actually pause it
Unless you're on a
Away mission
Yeah, MMOs don't usually have a pause button
Yeah
And the only ones of those you can pause
Are the ones you're on there by yourself
So
Alright
Yeah, and it's only 45 seconds, meh
Uh, let's try Loki
How was your gaming week, Loki?
I didn't play a whole lot cause I was paying
So really the only stuff I played was at work
Gloria Paint!
Literally!
That's true
That is true
Um
No, the only things that I played this week
Was, um, actually Grand Theft Auto
But, um, kind of funny
We didn't really play much of the
Battle of the Gay Tony this week
Apparently my co-workers are tired of me
Kicking the crap out of them at
The Battle of the Gay Tony
So they went back to Lost in Dam
So I had to keep the crap out of them
In Lost in Dam
Um, but it's fun
It's a nice little break
I just
I always forgot how slow the characters run
And oh my god they run so damn slow
In that game
It's ridiculous
And
I don't know if they've
You know, remembered it being
It's not quite as exciting as I remembered it
Just because when we played it last
It was
With all sorts of crazy explosions going off
On our mod games
Which will hopefully come back soon
Once I'm done painting the baby's room
Um
But yeah, we've been playing lots of that
And that's pretty fun
And then
Uh, Crackdown 2
Played a little bit of that
The only thing I don't like about Crackdown 2
Well
There's many things I don't like about Crackdown 2
One of the new things I don't like about Crackdown 2
Was
Um
Our internet at my work is not the greatest
Because we're sharing it with like
80 computers
I mean it's ridiculous
But
Usually it's enough to play
Online games
Not a problem
Um
Every now and then we have connection issues
With trying to get into like say a
Free mode game or something like that
And Grand Theft Auto
But
You know, minor stuff that we can usually get around
Crackdown 2 will not allow me to play a game
With anybody else
At my work
Like if my co-workers say I want to play a game with him
It's impossible
I can join another person's game
Away from our work
But it will not allow me to connect to a person that's
Literally next to me
Is that maybe because the game is seeing you guys
Like in the same room
No
It's not
The reason is
It's saying that our um
Connection is too strict or
It's basically layman's terms for
Um
Our internet connection is too slow
I do just want to point out though
Loki you do know most people
Don't get to play Xbox at their jobs
Right
Just throwing that out there
I understand that but you know
I'm just saying during our break
We wanted to play some co-op Crackdown 2
Which would have been really fun
But uh
We can't do that and say we have to play
Lost and Damned
Um
But I just wish that they
First off I wish they just had System Link
Back from the first game
That would solve all the problems right there
Well most of the problems
Cause
Even Red Dead Redemption
And
It was
You know it was a good testament to how
Take Two
And Rockstar Games
Still find ways to fuck up multiplayer
Um
Even in Red Dead Redemption
It sometimes can't find
The other people
Like we'll be
And that was funny
We're playing Free Mode in Red Dead Redemption
And we go to try to play like a little
Deathmatch in there cause in
In the online for Red Dead
You have to basically go these different points
On the map and then it'll send an invite
To the other players that are playing
You know the System Link game with you
Um
That you want to do a
Deathmatch
So we all
You know say okay yes
Let's enter this Deathmatch
And then it puts us in the three separate
Deathmatches
With just us
Our one single
You know each person is in their own
Deathmatch
How the fuck does that happen
I have never seen
A System Link game
Not figure out how to connect to another
System Link
Console
It doesn't make any sense
Only Rockstar could do that
But yeah
So um
That's about all I played this week
Hopefully gonna play more once we get the
Babies room done cause
You know we're under a deadline here
And uh
You know I have lots
I have
You know
A little bit of work left to do
But um
It's looking good
Alright well good luck
With the rest of that
And uh
Our well wishes to the
Misses as well
And uh
Through all that
My gaming week
Outside of California Extreme
I've been playing
Um
Mostly the same stuff
I didn't get into a lot of new stuff
I would say the newest thing I played
Was some of the extensions
That they have in game room now
You know some of the recent games
That they released
But of course that's just really
Old stuff
With new paint on it
Uh
And
I can't tell you how
Horrifically
Games like
Kaboom
And Crystal Castles
And things that ran on the Xbox
Or I mean things that ran on like
Trackballs and
And uh
Paddles
How horrifically they translate
Into the Xbox 360 controls
But there are some other cool
Stuff on there
That I was playing
Um
Like Hero
H-E-R-O
Was still one of my favorite games
Uh
They did some changes to game room
This week too
Where now you have like a
Live leaderboard
As you are playing the game
You watch yourself climb up
This live leaderboard
On the right hand side of the screen
That's actually really cool
So um
I kinda
Was a fan of that
That's only a ranked match
By the way
So you have to actually own the game
To be able to see that
But um
Yeah
Uh
Still more Puzzle Quest 2
Still more Warcraft of course
I revisited
Revisited
Uh
The pinball games
That are on
Xbox 360
And Playstation 3
Zen Pinball
And Pinball FX
Uh
Because I was trying to uh
Represent OLR
In the big battle
Cause
The response from the listenership
So far has been a little bit tepid
But I'll get into that in a little bit
Um
So I was trying to help represent
OLR in that
And I tried
I didn't get at the top of leaderboard
But at least I
I got on it
So I'm happy with that
And
I hadn't really played
Especially the one on the PS3
I don't think I appreciated enough
But that Earth Defense Force table
On PS3
Is actually a lot of fun
And uh
I actually kind of enjoyed
Um
Getting to spend a little time with it
This week
As much as I was not
As wonderful at it
I'd be more excited about it
If it was actually
Earth Defense Force 2017
It is not
But it's
It's still cool
It's a cool little board
As far as pinball goes
But uh
Yeah had a good time with that
So that was
That was really it
There wasn't um
A whole lot of other
Stuff
In my gaming week
And I pretty much
Echo a lot of what
Dark Sakura said
With uh
California Extreme
Uh
Played a lot of fun games there
So uh
Since I brought up
The Big Battle
Let's go into housekeeping here tonight
Before we get into tonight's gaming news
Uh
Big Battle is
Is all games
Um
Kind of competition
With these various video games
Uh
Throughout all the different shows
On all games
Well
Most of them
I don't think all of them
Signed up
Of quite a few
Are participating
In RPG Grinders
Electric Sisterhood
All these other shows
On the network
Sorry I didn't name them all
But they're all there
Uh
At thebigbattle.net
And um
It's really just for fun
It's not
Although I hear now
There's a prize
I got an email this week
That now there is a prize
So get this
The winning show
And this is not about the hosts
Of the show doing battle
With each other
Although I'm choosing to participate
This is about the listenerships
Representing the shows
In these battles
Well
The winning show now
As I understand it
Is going to get
A gold Atari 2600
So it's a
Like I think it's just
Spray painted gold
But it will be an
Atari trophy
So I know Dark Soccer's
Dying to have one of those
In the vault
Although
I do think
If we get a gold Atari 2600
We should maybe
I don't know
Give it to a listener
That helped us get it
Maybe?
I don't know
Go for it
We'll have to decide
Rob if I really wanted
A gold Atari 2600
I would go find one of ours
And get a can of
Rustoleum
And the meaning behind it
It doesn't mean it the same
When you do it that way
I know
But I'm just saying
We can give it to somebody
It will be just fine
Well I'll tell you right now
The way the leaderboards look
We ain't gonna get it
We are in second place
But we're gonna win
A gold 32X
But we are way behind
Dead Pixel Live
Dead Pixel Live has 164 points
We have 42
Which has us in second place
Now how many things
Have already completed already?
Uh
I think three
But there's still more
Going on right now
But let me
You know
It got off to a little
Bit of a slow start
The whole thing started
Right when E3 was going on
And then you know
My birthday and the 4th
Were all in there
You know
It took a little while
I think for us to
Kind of really get in there
But there's more games
Happening
And I think a lot of the
Early feedback we got was
You know
I don't have Solnarex
And I don't really have
The pinball game
So what's there for me to play?
Derek's been very open to
Putting stuff in there
So I can tell you
And it looks like
It's scheduled now
I didn't even know
It got a date
On August 1st
Super Street Fighter 4
Now I know tons of bitches
Have that game
I'll make Dan play
And can represent
Get Dan to sign up
At TheBigBattle.net
And represent the OLR
Because seriously
If we lose
Super Street Fighter 4
Or we don't have
Good representation
Super Street Fighter 4
We're just going to kiss
That gold Atari thing goodbye
Because it ain't happening
Like this is a game
That I know we can do
Well at
I'll blame everybody personally
So yes
I will be
Blaming certain individuals
That are very very good
At Super Street Fighter
If you don't participate in this
Unless you have a really good reason
I will blame you personally
But it's yeah
TheBigBattle.net
And it's August 1st
And sign up and participate
But there are other games
If you're not a Street Fighter person
Forza's going on right now
And I wonder if we have people
In Forza
Like I'll tell you this
So far
We can really thank
Arkadian42
Really made a good showing
For us in pinball
Like he got us 7 points
On Zen Pinball
And he got us
Another 7 points
On Pinball FX
I got us like 4 on one
And 3 on the other
And let's see
We actually have Monty Boggs
Participated
And got us 3 points
On Pinball FX
So thank you
Arkadian42
Monty Boggs
And me
The rest of you all
You need to go find a game
You can help us out with
I'm injured
Alright
Fine
You can sit on the bench
Due to injury
But depending on how long
This thing goes
Up B or a win done
Look at this
3 points
On Forza Motorsport 3
Right now
Way to go
Brrr
You rock
Keep up the good work
And there's also
Super Stardust HD
Is the other competition
Going on right now
And I
Oh
We
Holy crap
We are leading
The leaderboard right now
In Super Stardust HD
Who is Zui?
Who is a Z-O-O-I?
I don't recognize
That name from chat
I don't know who Zui is
But
That's from us to you
Cause you're currently
Kicking butt
Brrr
That's from us to HD
Good job
And Battlefield
Bad Company 2
Is also happening
So there it
Big Battle
In chat
DarkTetsuya
Says
I thought
I heard a rumor
There going to
It an upcoming
I heard
meaning
That
In the
There ya go
Other housekeeping I wanted to get to tonight.
I want to talk about the feed.
Most people shouldn't notice this, but the podcast feed actually moved
this past week and I want to take a minute to thank
Dekeman and Jason, VX JasonXV,
who do a lot of work on our website. And I'll tell you, like, Dekeman,
he kind of did this whole thing where he moved our podcast
and he's doing it so that way when we, usually when I post
a show, it takes like 24 hours for it to show up on the website
because someone has to go in there manually and do it, but that won't
happen anymore. Like, when I post a show, it will be instant.
So, most people are going to be able to get their shows faster and that's going to be
really good news. So,
yeah, I'm hoping nobody notices
the differences, but if you do,
just sit tight while we are under construction
a little bit. But I'm hoping if you're listening to this show
and you're on the podcast feed, then clearly your
feed player and all that updated and noticed the change
just fine. You don't need to do a darn thing. And for those
that did not move, Jason was kind enough to
record like a little special message that will show up over there
for those folks that know they have to resubscribe. So, I'm hoping
that is all better and all that good stuff now.
So, that's just some maintenance going on on the website. And also,
an excuse for me to thank the guys that make it happen, Dekeman
and VX JasonXV. Like, Dekeman put together this whole little, like, training manual.
Like, here's how you post to the website. Step one, dah dah dah.
It's like the type of thing I do at my day job. And we pay him
nothing because we have nothing. So,
it's very much appreciated by all of
us, as all of you listening should appreciate it too.
How about some actual bonafide gaming news now?
Are we ready? Thirty minutes into the show, we're going to touch on some gaming news.
Loki, what is going on in the world of PlayStation?
Absolutely nothing. No, just kidding.
Actually, in September, there will be some stuff going on,
including the 3D Blu-ray support,
which will basically turn your PS3 into not only
a Blu-ray player, but a 3D Blu-ray player.
And as of right now, I believe there is only one
3D Blu-ray movie out there. So, if you're looking
to see Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs in 3D,
you can do that now. Assuming, of course, that you have a 3D TV.
But why wouldn't you have a 3D TV if you have
that movie?
And then, of course, with that, there's also going to be some...
Wait, wait, isn't the regular Blu-ray just happen to be
regular and 3D? I don't think you buy a special
3D Blu-ray. So you could own the movie
and just not have a 3D TV because they're kind of pricey right now, right?
No, I do believe that it's actually a different movie.
It's a 3D Blu-ray. Wow. Wow, I didn't even know that existed.
The regular movie, you can watch with the
glasses, the magenta,
cyan, or the red-blue stuff.
But, no, this actually requires
a special... You have to buy your movies all over again, yes.
Just in case you thought, you know, Blu-ray
was enough. If you want them in 3D, you gotta buy them again.
Oh, great. Because it's, you know,
Mark Smith of that way. Also, there's gonna be
some additional support for, apparently,
Play TV in Europe is gonna
be in 3D as well. Different broadcasts through that,
as well as YouTube supporting 3D content
over the next 12 months as well. So there'll be
3D YouTube stuff. Which...
begs the question, and this is my
thing. Why?
That'd be the second question. Why? The first question is,
I understand, okay, YouTube, okay, great, we've got
3D YouTube, but...
as far as I'm aware, there's not really 3D film camera. Like,
I can't go out there and buy a camera that shoots
in 3D. Yet. Well, YouTube
isn't just underground stuff right now, you know?
Like, there's a lot of big studios who use YouTube to push
their stuff. I understand that, but, you know,
I'm not gonna be able to see, you know,
some viral video or something like that,
you know, in 3D normally. And...
why? Like you said,
why bother? It's because...
This 3D thing is happening too fast for me. But you know
why that they're pushing it? Why? It's because Sony is
selling 3D TVs. And Sony
has movies, Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs,
that happen to be in 3D Blu-ray. They figure,
hey, look! Look what we did for Blu-ray already!
We beat HD DVDs! Now we can convince
people to buy 3D Blu-ray! So they're kinda like riding on a high
right now, like they own everything? They're basically thinking, you know what,
yeah, we may have fucked up UMD,
but hey, we won in Blu-ray, and now we're gonna try our
hands at 3D Blu-ray. It'll print money!
But I have the... Here's my thing though, is people,
some people, not even all
people nowadays, are willing to make the jump to Blu-ray
because the picture quality is pretty good
compared to the DVD. But
those people probably just bought HDTVs.
Those same people are not gonna go, oh, well
I need to throw away my HDTV, I just bought and buy
a really expensive 3D HDTV with
really expensive 3D glasses to go with that. Because
I'm a consumer whore. Most people will not
do that. And so, yes, it is a bit
early. It's why you're not seeing, you know, Microsoft jumping
on the bandwagon with this stuff, because it's way too damn early.
You don't need to be putting out 3D games because
most people don't have the hardware to play them.
Going to chat.thatorangehonestready.com and some comments there, TigerClaw
says, if the studios have their way, they will release the regular
Blu-ray version, then a couple months later, the 3D version.
The 3D version of Avatar won't be out until 2011, and right now
they're planning on re-releasing the movie back in IMAX theaters
as a special edition with eight minutes of extra footage.
Because, you know, it is THE 3D movie.
But here's the funny part about that. The whole reason they are
doing a lot of 3D in theaters now is to get people back into
the movie theaters to watch these 3D movies. If you have the
technology at home, thank you, you know, Sony and
all these guys, you're basically just shooting the
theaters all over again, because now what are they going to do? Well,
I'm not going to the theater to watch an expensive Blu-ray, you know, 3D movie.
I can watch those 3D movies at home. And how many people remember this
particular parallel happening in the video gaming industry?
When, basically, you could get a Dreamcast, which
basically ran things like a NAOMI system back
in the day. It's just a matter of
consumer technology bypassing the mass
technology. What comes down to is, really,
Sony doesn't give a crap about movie theaters, because
they don't own movie theaters. They sell movies to these
movie theaters, and they could care less if their technology
is going to impede on their business.
Can I just say this real quick, because I think Dark
Soccer makes a good point, is that I think things like the
3DO and the CDI come to mind, those
things kind of, to me, feel like they were a little ahead of their time.
And the technology was really cool,
but the games were kind of crap and too much money.
You know what I mean?
I think a lot of that stuff was really ahead of
its time. I think all this stuff is a little too
soon as well. We've got other people in chat saying,
Katsune in our chat room, yeah, I just got my HDTV,
I'm not going to get a 3D TV anytime soon. Probably never.
And Miyamoto also thinks the 3D thing is happening too soon.
But see, the 3DS, I'm a lot cooler with
that, because, let me tell you the best thing about the 3DS.
There's a little lever on the right side, and when you get sick of 3D, you just
turn it down, it goes off. Ta-da!
The difference between the 3DS and the
PlayStation 3, the PlayStation 3 to see 3D,
it requires you to buy a bunch of additional hardware.
Glasses that are really expensive.
The TV that's really expensive.
The 3DS, you turn it on.
And you see 3D. And if you don't want to see 3D, you turn
the little slider down. And the great thing about that too
is if games, say for example, don't want to use 3D,
but they want to have a really high resolution, well
not really high resolution, but a pretty high resolution screen,
they could do that because now the amount of pixels
that are on the second screen are nearly doubled, and it's widescreen.
So you could do pseudo HD type stuff on there
if you want to.
And at the same time, I guess, Sony
on their games, they're also limiting the use of
1080p 3D in PlayStation 3 games.
Apparently, Sony's official guidelines
for 3D gaming on the PS3 limit
the displayed image to a resolution of 720p.
Even games that run natively at
1080p, like Super Stardust HD, are
downscaled to 3D mode to two 720p
images, one for each eye.
And I'm guessing this is because
the PS3 probably just can't handle that amount
of data going through there.
It says it will support 3D Blu-ray movies at that
resolution, 1080p,
later this year, but
upping the resolution
to
1080p also expenses the
60 frames per second. So for example,
Blu-ray movies run at
4 frames per second.
I don't know.
It's interesting. Honestly, with resolution
and stuff like that, I don't really think it matters. I mean, if you're looking at
high def in 3D, it's not gonna matter. It's gonna look cool.
Whether it's 1080p or 720p.
I mean, when you have the glasses on, you don't really give a shit. You're like,
oh damn, this is just horrible in this 720p.
What am I, like, a peasant here?
This is ridiculous.
It's not enough pay for me. I need my pay.
So,
one thing though,
kind of going back to this, that I had to laugh about,
and this isn't even really the 3D stuff, but it just
kind of stuck out to me in my mind during the Sony
press conference, because it made no sense to me as far as
as an actual feature that you would advertise to your
customers. One of the things that they said regarding the PlayStation
Move is like, because
you can only do this on the Sony PlayStation 3,
because we use Blu-ray technology, Blu-ray technology
will allow us to put both the
regular version of the game and the Move version of the game
on the same disc. And that was
a feature that they threw out there. And I'm like,
I've never seen people
not able to put, you know, two different control schemes
on one disc before because of disc space. Oh my god,
we can't fit. Why would you even put a separate
copy of the game on the disc? That's a little redundant if you ask me.
I'm trying to think. I think you could go back like
15 years to the Super Nintendo
and a game called King Arthur something
that had the mouse. It was one of the few third-party games that supported the mouse.
But you know what, you could also use a controller. Oh my god,
two different control schemes on one cartridge.
The only game, or only games
I guess that I would say that had two different control schemes,
and because they were, you know, released later on,
would be those new play control games because they had the Wii remote.
But that was added later and that does not count. I mean, that is not
something that they released. That was the equivalent of re-releasing
the same movie on Blu-ray 3D. Yeah, exactly.
And I'm sorry, but
nobody is making that argument, oh well, you know,
you're gonna have to buy a separate version of Halo 4,
the Kinect version, because we just can't fit it on those
pesky DVDs. We have to create a whole other game.
That's just stupid.
Going to another little side conversation in our chatroom,
SSJ100Matt is saying, do we really need 3D?
And some of the response is, no, no, no. It's a stupid gimmick.
Well, and then the other thing if you want to
know, 3D is obviously taking away some sort of processing
power from, you know, your games.
So, they're gonna have to make the games
slightly less, you know, elaborate
in order to, you know, allow you to do this 3D stuff.
Now granted, they're gonna have 3D in like Killzone 3 and I'm sure
that's gonna look amazing, but, I mean,
is that gonna really affect the performance of the game?
Is what I want to know because they're not adding any additional
hardware to, you know, run this 3D stuff. It's just basically
data going through them and if they're having to process twice as much data,
one for each eye, then you gotta
think that that's got a bottleneck somewhere.
I just don't think I've ever really experienced 3D
where it was like, oh my god, blow my hair back, amazing, like,
this is just, like when I went and saw Avatar in 3D,
I was like, okay, this is cool, but I probably would've
liked the movie just the same in 2D. I wasn't like,
oh my god, 3D was just everything,
I was moved to tears, it was better than having my dick sucked,
it was amazing, ah, you know, it just wasn't
that great, you know?
3D was not necessary. I thought it was, I thought it
actually added a very good dimension to the movie, but that was, you know,
It was neat, but it, wait, you wouldn't have felt the same way about the movie
in 2D? I probably would've liked it, but if I had seen them
both side by side, my preference would go to the 3D.
It's just, if it's gonna cost this much money to upgrade
right now too, like, it has to be, like, truly, truly amazing.
Well, it's not cost effective right now. I mean, it's
by no means cost effective. And just wait anyways, because
it's only a matter of, like, years before holograms, and then you're gonna have to buy
your hologram TV, and one step closer to the holodeck,
as we always say, that's gaming's ultimate goal, is the holodeck
from Star Trek The Next Generation. Everything
is just one step closer to the holodeck.
I have a holodeck in my backyard. Frisbee says, question,
all games suggest that you take a 15 minute break after one hour
of playing. How many people will hurt their eyes with this 3D stuff?
I'm kinda curious what the safety manual and
disclaimers are gonna look like on the 3DS. I'm very curious about that.
Don't play for more than 5 seconds. Well, here's
the best part about the 3DS. If it starts bugging your eyes,
there's a little slider to turn the 3D off.
Oh my god. And that's awesome. One
of the comments I wanted to read, S.J. 100 Matt in our chatroom said,
give it five years, maybe there will be enough support for it. Right now, there's
nothing worthwhile. It's all James Cameron's fault.
Maybe that stupid rant he had in E3 2009 actually meant
something. I don't remember that rant, but apparently he got up on stage
and talked kind of about, you know, the 3D stuff.
Just, we weren't ready for it. We're not ready to handle it.
Although it's kinda- You can't handle that extra D.
You can't handle the truth. But look at, okay, look at 3D
and what it's done so far to cinema. I mean,
we're getting a lot of gimmicky movies. And they-
We got a lot of gimmicky movies back when, you know,
the red-blue-glass 3D was really popular.
Just a lot of, like,
you know, Final Destination in 3D.
Oh, look at the head flew towards me. You know, Saw
in 3D. Oh, look at the head flying towards me.
You know, it's Jaws in 3D.
Oh, look at the head flying towards me. I mean, it's just, it's basically
the same stuff over and over. And a lot of these movies
that don't necessarily need 3D, like Clash of the Titans,
have the 3D tacked onto it and it looks like shit.
So, you know, take that, you know, and add that
to, like, say, games, and now you're gonna get 3D games that look like shit.
It just occurred to me, I thought of something
that was Blow My Hair Back Amazing
3D experience, that 3D was
intricate and necessary to the presentation that would not have been the same
without it. Captain EO.
I was thinking the same thing. Well, and remember that seventh
portal thing, the Marvel thing at Great America?
Those rides that are like that.
The Muppet Show. Captain EO, really.
Captain EO was first, and Captain EO was, what, 1985?
86? Yeah.
When Captain EO comes out
on these 3D TVs, wake me up.
Then maybe I'm ready for 3D TVs.
In the meantime, let's move on to something else that's
completely unnecessary. Yeah, I know they did a Captain EO game.
That's what the Michael Jackson game should be.
None of this, like, imitates his dance moves. I don't give a shit about that.
Yeah, just build that stuff in a dance. Captain EO and
Michael Jackson Moonwalker 2. Amazing.
Moonwalker HD.
SSJ-100 Matt says your other answer is Lawnmower Man.
Remember when Virtual Reality was like the big
Virtual Reality.
They tried. And stock footage of all the Mind's Eye stuff.
Ooh, that was really cool.
Yeah, I remember back in the day when Virtual Reality stuff was
really big. God, we were stupid back then.
Alright, speaking of things that are completely
useless and unnecessary, Real ID.
I had to do that. That's a fantastic tie-in, Rob.
I'm very proud of you. 3 weeks in a row I'm talking about this.
And look, again, I'm going to say this. I know a lot of you could give two shits
about World of Warcraft, but this is important because where Blizzard
goes, other companies will inevitably follow.
I'm going to keep it brief this week. There's two quick things that happen to Real ID
that are newsworthy and necessary to cover.
First off, this is kind of one of those, like,
part of it's really funny and the other part is
actually not funny at all. And that is that, you know,
a bunch of people when this Real ID, and going back to when they
Blizzard was saying, oh, we're going to post
your real name to the forum whenever you want to make a
post, right? Remember that whole thing they had to retract last week?
Well, a lot of people complained to the ESRB.
And a lot of people wrote them and said, this game is violating our privacy.
You should go back and re-rate this game.
Kind of like trying to get at them that way. Well, the ESRB sent
an apology letter. Well, not really an apology letter, but they sent out
a letter of resolution basically saying, thank you
for contacting us. Your concerns were legit.
It's our understanding that Blizzard provided an update announcing
they're not going to do it, so we're closing your request.
Just kind of one of those, like, you know, hey, we appreciate
your concern, but, you know, it's kind of done
with now, right? But we wanted to follow up with you anyway.
Well, here's the part about it that really
sucks. All of the people that wrote in
to complain, yeah, all of their names
and email addresses were in the to field.
Because somebody didn't think, oh, I should put those in the
BCC field. So all
of the people who complained had their
email addresses exposed.
Oh, they're going to sue.
And now granted, ESRB wrote
an apology, like, not even 24 hours later.
They sent out an apology that, and the nice thing was
they kind of addressed the irony. They didn't try to beat around the bush.
They did say in their apology, the fact that our message
addressed an individual's concerns with respect to their privacy
underscores how truly disappointing a mistake this was on our part.
We work with companies to ensure they are handling people's private
information with confidentiality, care, and respect. It is only
right that we set a good example and do no levs ourselves.
So at least they didn't try to give you a BS corporate answer.
Well, I mean, to some extent. It was a little washed out.
You know when they said they were like, aw, crap.
Well, first off, you know an intern did this.
And secondly, when he hit the send button, you know he went,
aw, fuck.
I'm going home. I gotta go home.
Please don't crap on interns. I'm planning on being an intern. I am an intern.
I'm just saying. It's not that I'm crapping on interns.
Rob, an intern designed the FedEx logo.
Okay. The Federal Express logo or the FedEx logo?
The FedEx logo.
It's clever. Regardless of whether it was an intern
or the CEO, you know after clicking the send button,
they went, aw, fuck.
The FedEx logo, all that is is just the Federal Express logo.
They just dropped it down the FedEx like Bevmo.
The E and the X make an arrow.
That's very clever.
Alright, look. Just drop it. It was a mistake on their part.
They apologized for it, but it's just one of those
moments where you just cover your face with your palm
and shake your head. Anyhow, there's more
in the Real ID saga. And this is important
because after all the ranting I've done in previous episodes,
if Blizzard's gonna come out and say, oops, we made a mistake.
I think it should be acknowledged. And to some extent,
that's what's happened this week. Nathera, who's one of the
community managers, did post on the official WoW forums
about some Real ID follow-ups. One,
my biggest complaint about the system as it was, the Friends of Friends
feature. She went on to say,
they've been evaluating how Real ID has been used since its release
to identify the new functionality that will help improve our players' experience, blah blah blah.
The in-game Real ID Friends of Friends list is designed
to give players a convenient way to populate the Real ID Friends list,
blah blah blah, corporate speak corporate speak. Oh, however,
we recognize that some players would prefer not to be displayed on Friends
lists in this fashion, so we plan to include an option
that will allow players to opt out of appearing on
their Real ID Friends, Friends of Friends list.
This should be ready by the first StarCraft 2 patch.
Yay!
Yay, someone knocked some sense into Blizzard.
But, I'm not totally over this yet.
Am I to the point now where my number one concern
with Real ID was addressed? Yes.
But, I still get a little nervous
because remember last week we had that story about the one
line of code that would show your real name out there?
Now, yes, it was hotfix, blah blah blah, but the fact that it existed
in the first place, that still kind of makes me nervous.
And I think I have a right to question,
just where the hell is Blizzard going with all this?
And an awesome point that was brought up to me today
was Blizzard hasn't said anything about their next MMO yet.
And we're anticipating that we're going to be hearing a lot about it
at Blizzcon this year.
And after all this mess of the past few months
and Real ID and this whole trying to get closer and closer
into bed with Facebook, I'm kind of really
concerned about what Blizzard has planned for their next MMO.
FaceCraft?
Blizzard goes on to say,
what are your plans for Facebook integration?
With regard to Facebook, our goal is to help Blizzard gamers on Battle.net
more easily connect to their real life friends and family.
For the launch of Starcraft 2, we are introducing an optional
Facebook friend finder feature to help achieve this goal.
The friend finder enables players who decide to use it
to easily populate their Battle.net friends list
by sending Real ID friend requests to the people on their
Facebook friends list who have Battle.net accounts.
We hope players will find this feature convenient, but it's completely optional,
blah blah blah blah blah. So in other words, you can
now, if you want to go onto
Facebook and pull all of your friends' Real IDs
from your Facebook, you can do that, I think is what they're saying?
This way people in China
that may have to leave their game
to visit friends and family
don't have to do that. They can sit there and play their games.
I do not like this direction that Blizzard
is going. They are a gaming company. Stop trying to be
a social network. Throughout all of this,
what they really should have learned,
they really need to sit down
in a meeting. They need to come into the office Monday morning,
sit down in a meeting, and I feel like I can speak
to this with some authority. And stop sniffing glue? Well, that's
the first place. But I've been a corporate trainer for the past
seven years. I sometimes have to facilitate
meetings like this. I think these guys
should come in, sit down, and really ask
themselves, why are we here?
What is the goal of our company? Why do people
pay us $15 a month? To make money.
That's all they're in for the money.
Do they pay us $15 a month so that they can
have their real life be reminded
of their real life and their Facebook friends and all this all the time?
No. People pay $15 a month to escape the real world
and slay internet dragons. That is why they pay the money.
Are people leaving the game in droves because of this? No.
I don't think they are.
Boy, when that announcement went out, yes they did. There was lots of people
that posted screenshots, said they were leaving,
etc.
Oh, I'm going to boycott Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2.
Oh, I'm going to boycott Left 4 Dead 2.
Just like all these people. What they're going to do is wait for them
to say the magic words,
and then they'll come right back and then they'll get screwed again.
Salacious Pop says this beautifully.
If they are already a real life friend, I know where they are
because I've met them. If I want to be on their Facebook,
call and ask. Perfect.
You know what? From here on out,
until Blizzard has decided that they are
not going to get into bed with Facebook so much anymore
and keep sucking their dick as they've been so much recently,
until Blizzard comes out and says,
we are games first, I'm going to be referring to
Blizzard as Blizzinga, because that is what they are.
They are Blizzard meets Zynga.
So, Blizzinga from here on out.
When I say that on the show, you know who I'm talking about.
But until they have decided, you know what, we are a gaming company first
and maybe we should not try to get so much into
the social network stuff or push it down everybody's throats
as hard as we've been, they are Blizzinga.
And Blizzinga needs to take a cue
from Xbox Live,
because I think it's one of the things that Microsoft has done very, very well
and the great thing about Xbox Live, it does have that
community feeling, you have achievements and messages
and you have that Facebook integration if you want it
and you can find Facebook friends if you want to.
It's done right on Xbox Live, I think.
I don't understand why they make it like you can't
like all of a sudden I have to find my friends out there.
I mean, there's so many social networking sites out there right now.
Twitter, Facebook, MySpace if you're still using it
and a whole bunch of other sites and games that do this.
Why do I need their help in connecting with my friends?
I've already connected with my friends probably a dozen times now.
And there is still the phone, there's still mail,
there's still email, there's still a bunch of other ways to talk to your friends.
I just don't understand, it's like, oh my god,
I'm cut off from the rest of the world unless
I use Blizzard to connect with my friends.
Let's see here, Tigerclaw in our chat room says,
Sky, maybe they should pull an apple and do a Q&A press conference lol.
Well that's why Blizzingacon 2010 this year is going to be awesome.
Because there are going to be some of those people that bought tickets
before all this shit happened that are going to the con.
Those developer Q&As are going to be awesome.
Like, I hate Blizzcon, like I kind of think it's kind of ridiculous
and I have zero interest in going and paying $150 to go to one company's E3 booth.
But look, this would be the year to go.
It's the point where I'm seriously considering getting the DirecTV feed
because those Q&A sessions are going to be awesome.
Angry nerds in the building with the developers who anger them.
They will not be angry.
Reality television show in the making.
They'll be drinking the Kool-Aid, they will be just...
Tables will be overturned.
They'll be taking it and they'll be like, hey look at this wheel we got for you.
And they'll be like, oh I forgive you for everything you've done.
That's so awesome.
Oh my God.
Unicycles now in World of Warcraft.
That's just the best thing ever.
People are sheep.
And you know what?
The people that follow Apple products, the people that follow Blizzard products
and countless other different brands out there that just eat up this shit
despite all the crap that they do.
They're going to still be playing the game.
They're still going to forgive them.
And you know what?
They leave for World of Warcraft, they'll come back for whatever the fuck
next MMO they've got because, oh Blizzard's fun.
I'll give them another try.
No one's going to...
No one really just up and just says, oh forget it.
I'm not dealing with them anymore until their next shiny thing comes out.
They're just going to be right back where they were before.
I will say that I have quit MMOs from principle.
So...
But...
Go ahead.
That's the person I am.
If I don't like something, I'm not going to put up with it.
But would you go back if your problem changed?
Probably not.
Really?
Well I mean...
It ended up getting a lot worse.
It was the whole crap with Ragnarok Online and just how stupid they were getting
and how...
What my problem was with them was them implementing the in-town raids.
And it got worse.
I had a list of grievances and they weren't doing anything so I quit.
I've got to read this comment from chat because I've been wanting to get it out there
and it has to do with the same topics.
So let's just pop in chat.
Chat.orangewormsready.com if you want to join us on this Sunday night.
It says, I don't think it's disingenuous for someone who boycotted something to come back
if the bad policy was lifted.
That just means you voted with your wallet and it worked so you came back.
I agree with him.
I agree.
This kind of reminds me though, SSJ100Matt says,
are you people still mad at Blizzard about no LAN support?
Blizzinga, please.
Blizzinga, whatever.
That's your thing, okay?
I'm not going to try to remember that because that's stupid.
Well, the name's stupid.
I'm just with the work on the name.
Well, because zinga are the people that make Farmville.
I understand that.
I get the reference.
We don't need to point more attention to them.
No, I was just saying that he brings out a perfect point
because they took out a feature that really pissed off everybody else
and they're like, oh, I'm boycotting the game.
How much you want to bet that Starcraft 2 sells millions of fucking copies
and it would be like as if that never happened,
as if those features were never removed,
that maybe the fans still bought it anyways
despite being pissed off at the company.
So you're basically saying never forget you were pissed about the LAN thing.
Never forget.
I've got more of those.
There was something else I saw earlier this week.
I guess we can talk about it real quick because it sort of ties in with Activision.
Real quick, because we've got to move on to more stories.
Real quick, I'm sorry.
There's another tangent I have to go on here.
Okay, real quick.
Remember how I brought up, and no one seemed to give a fucking shit about it,
remember I brought up that Activision is starting to price Wii games,
remember the Wii games usually are 50 bucks retail at the most,
for $60 retail for certain games
because they think that they should get some more money
because music licensing or whatever.
I forgot. Thank you for reminding me to never forget.
And I'm not saying that Activision is the only one to blame too
because Beel's Rock Band, same thing happened with that.
They were charging $60 for the Wii version of the game.
Well guess what?
It's been another year, no one's really complained, and it's happening again.
And guess what? It's not just happening now with music games,
but the new Tony Hawk game is also going to be $60 on the Wii.
Why? No one's going to buy it anyways,
and now you're giving them another reason not to buy it.
But also, Guitar Hero, Warriors of Rock, I'm sure DJ Hero 2,
those are all $60 price points.
You guys need to not forget this stuff
because they're going to start sneaking out more games like that.
And I know for me that's not a big deal
because I don't game that much on the Wii,
but for other people it might be a big deal.
And if you don't stop it here, they're just going to keep going.
What's going to stop them from saying,
oh, well now we're adding 3D into our 360 games?
They're going to be $70 retail.
Vote with your wallet.
Seriously, so...
I think we should make Loki's never forget a regular segment.
Ray Ayanami says he doesn't play any Blizzard game anyways.
You know, you may not play Starcraft 2 or Diablo 3 or this unannounced MMO,
but the reason why we spend so much time on it,
and I apologize, I know not everyone's into WoW,
but keep in mind, WoW is that behemoth of an RPG game right now anyway.
Where they go, a lot of the industry tends to follow.
Blizzard right now is the Rockefellers back in the day,
and you know what happened with them.
Go back and read a history book.
And this came up last week, and I think it's doubly true
after a lot of this Blizzard talk this week.
The WoW killer is WoW.
It's just a matter of when.
So anyhow, I will tell you what the WoW killer is not,
because I was reminded I didn't even mention this during my gaming week.
I played the Final Fantasy XIV beta this week.
I spent a little time with it.
This is my little tangent I wanted to get on,
because I forgot to mention this during my gaming week.
I played the Final Fantasy XIV beta on Tuesday.
I'm not sure if I'm actually supposed to be talking about it or not, but...
Who cares?
I'll tell you this, it's not my account, so I'm not under any NDA.
Ha ha ha.
So anyhow, I'm not going to tell you whose it is though.
I played the beta, and it's awful.
It is awful.
It is horrible, awful, laggy, not fun.
I'm not buying this game when it comes out if it's in this shape.
Granted, it's a beta, not a demo.
Betas are buggy, betas are slow.
But betas also are supposed to give me an impression, at least,
of what I'm to expect in the final product.
I got dumped into this world with no explanation
what I was supposed to do, where I'm supposed to go,
how you proceed, all these fancy big words of guild levs
and armethith crystals and these quests and all these things,
and I realized I could probably go online and figure it out,
but I thought the big thing about Final Fantasy XIV
was that it was supposed to be more accessible than Final Fantasy XI was.
It's not in its current shape.
This game is supposed to come out September 30th.
It is not ready. Not ready.
I'll try it again. I'll try the beta one more time
before the actual game is released to see if maybe they added some expositions.
I will say this. At first, I was like,
Ooh, this is pretty. Ooh, this cutscene is so pretty.
Ooh, my characters in this cutscene.
Oh, my gosh, this is a beautiful game.
This looks so amazing. This character customization is really thorough.
And then I was stuck in the city running around for an hour
because I had no idea where the hell I was supposed to be going
or what I was supposed to be doing.
I want to try it.
It's bad.
I still want to try it.
I want to try it though.
Just so I can see how bad.
S2100Matt says,
So wait, Rob, what you're describing is Final Fantasy XI.
Yeah, kinda.
Yeah.
At least with Final Fantasy XI, I don't know.
Maybe it was because I had friends that played,
but I still feel like I was able to figure it out somewhat,
but I went into combat. I was fighting a rat or something.
I don't even know, and I got frozen in combat,
and the rat wasn't targetable anymore,
and I had to abandon the quest,
and if I wanted to start the quest again,
I would have had to run 30 minutes back into town.
It was ridiculous.
Again, I know it's a beta.
I'm not supposed to be giving my final impressions on the game,
but if the beta was supposed to be raising my excitement
for somebody that spent three years of his life
playing Final Fantasy XI, didn't work.
I'll tell you that.
That's a shame.
Yeah, it is a shame. It's a real shame.
What's also a shame nowadays
is that it will still be released on the 30th,
and what'll happen then is just,
oh, well, we'll patch it later.
Well, I mean, they still have time to patch it, but not much.
All right, let's actually get to another story.
I'm sorry we've taken up so much time with real ID and stuff,
but, you know, this stuff's important.
Jamie, what do you got for us?
What about a story I never played?
Nice.
Okay, because a lot of people love games on Facebook,
and a lot of people love Zuma.
I think you said you liked Zuma, didn't you?
Zuma's pretty fun.
It's not my favorite PopCap game,
but I don't think there's any PopCap games
that are really bad, per se.
Like, they get the job done.
As far as casual games go, they're all crackerific.
I love Peggle.
I love Peggle, too.
At any rate, Zuma Blitz is gonna be coming out on Facebook.
It's supposed to have in about three weeks a beta,
and then we should start seeing tournaments and levels
and experience points and getting different features
and treasure chests and virtual currency and blah, blah, blah.
So it should be cool.
I mean, it's gonna go up there with Bejeweled Blitz,
and that's got a lot of people playing it.
I like me some Zuma, and it should be good,
and I know a lot of people eat that up,
especially on Facebook, so it's gonna be cool.
You know, the only thing that I play on Facebook right now
is that Hotel City thing.
You know who would like that?
Xtifer.
He used to play lots of Zuma.
That's right, he did.
Someone should tell him.
He should be listening.
Blazinga, take note.
PopCap knows how to do the Facebook integration thing,
just saying.
And, um, well...
No, never mind, we've beaten this horse.
It's already dead and bleeding from his pores.
Give it another whip.
You haven't said enough on this.
We haven't skinned the horse yet.
It's not over until we skin the horse.
Because my Vicodin's wearing off.
I really think that, well, I was just thinking about
what you said about them really needing to sit down
and go over their business model,
but what if this is actually a true integrated part
of their business model?
Abandon ship.
I'm gonna just go back and say one thing about it.
Everybody, if you really are displeased with it,
do it in numbers.
Hit them in the bank and do it with people.
Organize.
But then where will I fight my internet dragons?
There's other games, Rob.
Rob?
It's just not the same.
What did I say last time?
Principle versus entertainment.
What's more important?
I don't know. I really like entertainment, Jamie.
Entertainment, Rob?
Rarely got anything going in motion.
Well, this is interesting.
THQ apparently is impressed by the 3DS piracy protection.
Of course, you may remember the piracy has been
a really big problem for the Nintendo DS,
and tons and tons of games being hurt by the amount of piracy
that there is on that system,
and because it's so very easy to do.
Ian Curran, THQ's executive VP of global publishing,
is saying that what excites me even more about the 3DS
is that there's technology built into the device
to really combat piracy.
He added, they combated piracy on the DSI,
which they don't believe is cracked yet,
but they know they've been hurt across the world,
and they believe that the 3DS has got the technology to stop that.
I'm kind of curious what that is, but I guess they can't tell us,
or then the pirates would start getting to work.
Well, here's my observation about that.
Nintendo thinks that they've stopped piracy on the DSI.
Really?
I mean, because I've seen flash carts with the DSI.
I'm not going to go buy a DSI,
because I'm probably going to pick up a 3DS eventually,
but I mean, they haven't stopped piracy on the DSI,
and they're just going to get smarter.
I mean, since it's basically cartridges it's reading off of,
if you can mimic the data that's on there,
then I don't see how it can really stop it.
I mean, they have anti-piracy measures that they put into the games,
but it takes like a week or two to crack them at the most,
and a lot of them get cracked day one, if not early,
because they come out in other regions.
I guess we won't really truly have the second half to this story
until the 3DS is out.
We know what that anti-piracy measure is,
but it just seems like an echo of what we always hear.
It'll probably take a few months,
but considering the technology is still going to be somewhat backwards compatible
because it's going to be playing DS games,
it's going to probably be as easy to crack as the DSIs,
so it'll be a matter of time.
I don't think that they've finally solved the problem.
Well, here's something, and maybe this ties into it.
I don't know. This could be interesting,
but you know the 3DS has something that they talked about briefly called Tag Mode,
which I always thought was supposed to be a part of the regular DS,
but it kind of wasn't.
But anyway, what Tag Mode is supposed to be,
a passive communication feature that lets the DS systems talk to each other
and send the data back and forth,
which I always thought was some type of, it was in the DS, right,
because you could carry Animal Crossing around in your pocket,
but of course now you had to have the game on,
and you had to be in that mode that sent out the letter in the bottle
or whatever it was, that mode. Remember that?
You could send the letters in the bottle.
But anyhow, I'm assuming this Tag Mode doesn't require that.
Like maybe your DS can be off, and it still will tag.
Maybe it uses low battery power to still kind of do this when it's asleep.
Yeah.
I don't know.
But there is a little more information given by Hideki Kono,
who is the platform producer of the 3DS,
in an interview with Wired Magazine.
He says, in the hardware, we have the capability that when you first play a game
that supports Tag Mode, it will save to a Tag Mode data slot in the hardware system.
We're planning to support multiple games at the same time.
So that's the difference.
Mario Kart, Nintendogs, Animal Crossing, and so forth.
I see, because right now the game does have to be running.
So there will actually be a Tag Mode viewer where you can manage the data.
It will bring consumers a sense of wanting to play a game again
after they get new data from games that they'd already forgotten about.
What if the piracy is firmware updates delivered through Tag?
I'm sure that's one way they can do it.
That's what I'm thinking.
Like maybe that's one of the ways they're going to do it,
is that you don't have a choice.
These things are going to show up on your system
because you walked by someone else with the newer firmware.
Wouldn't that be amazing? I bet that's it.
I bet that's one of the antivirus images they have in it.
Well, one of the original ways that they used to have the flash carts kind of work
is they had some sort of thing with the Wi-Fi where you could do something with it.
I don't remember.
I probably sound like an idiot with this.
But I know there was something that involved Wi-Fi at one point
with the original DS flash carts and stuff
when they were first getting those to work with proprietary code and stuff like that.
It's possible.
I think it's kind of a neat feature.
Speaking of going back to play games that we haven't played in a while,
and I'm sure most people out there already know this is possible,
but since I don't check up everything on the internet,
I was unaware that they had these things.
Apparently there's a track editor for Mario Kart Wii, and that's awesome
because there's all sorts of cool tracks out there that people have made.
I'm like, ooh, that's exciting.
That would actually get me to go back and play Mario Kart.
Why didn't they include that as a feature in the goddamn game to begin with?
It would be so epic.
But then, of course, they couldn't sell Mario Kart 2.
Yeah, exactly. That would be in the sequel.
I mean, look at LittleBigPlanet, though.
I mean, they could easily.
Or ModNation Racers, which that's the whole thing, basically.
Exactly.
Such a missed opportunity.
Sj100Matt, in commenting on the possible tag mode is the anti-piracy,
Sj100Matt says, Nintendo isn't that smart.
Let's see.
Toygak says, wireless is a battery hog. It better not be on.
You can probably turn it off.
Well, yeah, and there's probably a thing where it uses really, really low battery
until it detects that DS, and then it uses it for a minute, and then shuts back off.
Like, I don't see why the technology isn't there to do that,
where it slowly drains your battery.
But the battery power, you know, it's been, what, five years since the last DS?
Or, sorry, not the last DS, but the first DS?
I would think they've probably made the batteries in those things a lot better.
And it's not like the games probably require that much more battery.
I mean, yeah, they're 3D, but I don't think it's going to be that much more.
And Sj100Matt says, yeah, it does sound like the Pokewalker type of technology.
Sj100Matt also says, maybe they can track me via my 20-digit friend code.
Didn't they say they're going to...
Oh, God, I hope they're not going to do friend codes this summer.
I think they kind of hinted they might be doing away with that.
Or changing it, I suppose.
10-digit friend codes, woohoo!
One-digit friend codes.
All right, let's move on to another story.
Dark Sakura's got something for us, and then release dates.
And the classic game of the week is not too far away.
Well, for fans of Josh Stone, she's going to be the next Bond girl, at least, in James Bond Bloodstone.
Josh Stone. Bloodstone.
She'll be playing Nicole Hunter, who is a socialite, works in diamonds, and said that she thinks it's crazy to be a Bond girl.
So, just talking about having a full-body scan and everything, but it's supposed to be a third-person cover-based shooter with vehicle stuff in there.
It's the bizarre creation tool.
Including cars and speedboats. So, should be fun.
Her name is Nicole Hunter.
Nicole Hunter.
In the game. That's kind of a shitty Bond girl name.
Like, whatever happened to Pussy Galore? That was awesome.
And you know, even what was her name? Denise Richards was like Christmas something, or it was something really ridiculous.
Nicole Hunter.
Nicole Hunter is kind of boring.
Well, she did, though, describe the character as a posh version of Paris Hilton.
I thought Paris Hilton was supposed to be kind of posh already.
No.
I mean, she's kind of trashy.
She's posher!
She's like, more posher. Oh, okay, that explains it.
I would probably say, I would exchange that word with classy.
Let's make the character like Paris Hilton.
She's not posh enough! I can't make her any more posher!
Of course, if you want to make the character more posher, you should have gotten posh spice.
I was saying classy.
At any rate, you know, if they wanted to make her real trailer trash, you know, they probably just could have called her Atmore Motel 6.
Salacious Pop, thank you. Christmas Jones. She was a nuclear physicist.
That was Denise Richards in, whatever, like, was it Tomorrow Never Dies?
She played a character named Christmas Jones. How ridiculous is that name?
Christmas Jones.
Nicole Hunter? That's, I don't, like, I don't know, but I probably knew a girl in high school named that.
Like, that's not that exciting.
Now we got all these random Bond, Bond girl type names being yelled out here. Honey Rider, Posher Spice, maybe that could be the name.
Toa Gax says Paris Hilton equals Pussy Here, Pussy There, Pussy Pussy Everywhere.
That's kind of how she got famous.
Bond girl names could be exchangeable with, you know, porn star names too.
Oh, yeah, Jinx. Wasn't Hal Berry called Jinx?
What was her name? I think it was Jinx, because they were going to do a spinoff movie.
By the way, you know what my favorite porn star name is?
What?
Alice in Chains. I just thought it was funny.
And lastly, before we move on to release dates, let's just pop in our chatroom.
Chat.overtonesloudandstrated.com says, how is Paris Hilton like Kansas?
Both are flat, white, and easy to enter.
Strawberry Fields. Really? That was a Bond girl? Strawberry Fields?
See, Strawberry Fields, Pussy Galore, Christmas Jones, Nicole Hunter.
It just doesn't work.
Alright, let's move on. Release dates. Travel around the world and talk about games coming out soon.
In a store near you. We'll start with the US, Loki.
You know, her name's sort of broken down. It could sound like Hole Hunter, so I mean, you know.
Sort of.
What about Mike Hunter?
Mike Hunter.
That would have been better.
I did know a guy named Benjamin Dover.
Poor guy.
So stuff coming out this week. Not a whole lot, because July is a pretty slow month.
But there's some generic DS games, of course, coming out.
Hidden Objects Mystery Stories. That's another Hidden Objects game.
Yeah, because there's not a lot of those on the DS.
Apparently Trackmania Turbo, but I somehow doubt that's actually coming out, because I think I got delayed to October.
Samantha Swift and the Hidden Roses of Athena, which also I believe was delayed forever.
And I definitely go Trackmania on the Wii, man.
You know, GameStop needs to update their fucking release list. It is terrible.
Mumbo Jumbo 6-Pack Seccident Edition. It's six games from Mumbo Jumbo that you can buy on PC.
Hooray!
Wow, is that it?
So there's, like, nothing coming out this week. That can't be right.
Maybe it's just a slow week.
Well, Hidden Objects Mystery Stories it is.
I gotta go back to chat. I know the Bond girl thing is getting old, but this comment is too good.
I'll look at a different list, because that's a pathetic listing.
Eric H. is in our chat tonight. He's actually the brains behind the big battle over at Dead Pixel Live, so welcome.
He says, Christmas Jones led to the worst end lines of any Bond film. I thought Christmas only came once a year.
Okay, there is other things this week. I forgot.
They had him on weird release dates, so it didn't really make sense to me.
Dark Star One Broken Alliance on Xbox 360, which that game actually reminds me of.
I don't know if anyone remembers this PlayStation 1 game, but Colony Wars, or even, like, Descent Free Space.
So that might be kind of cool on 360.
Ark Rise Fantasia on the Wii, really awesome role-playing game.
And Cats and Dogs Revenge of Kitty Galore on DS.
And I don't think it's on this list, but I remember it, and why the god hell did they make this game in the first place.
The Bachelor, featuring The Bachelorette, as well on Wii and DS.
Yes, the Bachelor video game. That is correct. And Zany Golf on Wii.
Really? Like, what game do you make out of- is that the closest thing we're gonna get in America to a dating sim?
Um... Maybe?
I wanna be the Bachelor that rejects them all. Like, didn't that happen on one of them?
Like, he or she, I don't remember, one of them just said,
You know what? You all suck. I don't want any of you.
Oh, fuck you all. I'm outta here.
Later. Oh, I played again.
Losers. I just wanna get laid. Done. I don't need you.
Christmas only came once a year. On the Xbox 360 in Japan this week.
Blur Razors comes out in Japan this week. You know, I'm kind of thinking that is actually Blur over there, and it is.
But they call it Blur- it's Blur Racers. On this website it's incredibly spelled.
Razors? I know, I thought that was a dumb name.
Blue Racers!
Blue Racers with a Z, by the way. That's important. Blur Racers with a Z is out in Japan this week.
Bruh. Bruh.
Stop it. 99 Nights 2 comes out in Japan this week.
I saw that on the shelf at the gaming store. I thought about buying it for five seconds, and I was like, what am I thinking?
That's pretty much it on the Xbox 360 this week in Japan, so unfortunately you guys had to wait for some of the games we've had here.
But on PlayStation 3 you get Blur Racers as well, or Ken Tomahou to Gakuno Mono is coming out as well.
I don't even know what this is. This is an upgraded version of the Cute Fantasy School Life RPGs.
This must be a remake of an old game that's now available.
It looks like it involves kind of like the card style battle in the game.
Kind of mixed with a Dragon Warrior-esque style battle system.
I like how in big letters it says Hito! On that screenshot.
So that's probably not something coming out over here, because that does not look familiar to me at all.
But on the Nintendo Wii this week, one new game, Kage no Tu is coming out this week on the Wii.
This is a Hudson game. You control a light source to solve puzzles and battle monsters.
This is not a game I'm familiar with over here.
No, that's Lost in Shadow that's coming out. It's that really cool, trippy puzzle platform game.
I did see that at PAX East I think they were showing that.
Okay, so it's that. It's Kage no Tu over there in Japan.
Yeah, it's coming out over here in September.
I like how on Play Asia they have a wonderful combo where I can buy blur razors for the PS3 and I can combo with blur razors for the PS3.
Oh, I'm sorry, that's blur on the PS3 in case I want both versions of the game.
You're gonna play American and Japanese. Why not?
It's the same game.
I'm not playing both. It's region free.
On the Nintendo DS, Katekyo Hitman Reborn DS Flame Rumble XX. Yes, that is really the game's name.
They have some crazy names over there.
They like their subtitles.
They love their subtitles. They really do.
Well, remember how long the one Street Fighter I have is like something, something, something for matching service.
Remember, the longer the subtitles, the better the game.
TV Anime Fairy Tale Gekitou Madoushi Kessen comes out as well. Is this like an interactive anime?
That sounds like a really good game.
It looks like an action game that's just based on an anime. Like the anime plays on the bottom screen and you're kind of controlling the top screen.
Looks a little silly.
And lastly, going to the PSP for Japanese release dates, Fate slash Extra is the big release this week on the PSP.
It's coming out in regular and limited editions because the only thing they love more in subtitles are limited editions in Japan.
Yeah, but my limited edition has a bowl and a plate and a knife and a clock.
Well, this is an RPG on the PSP. It actually looks kind of cool.
It's kind of got a very Phantasy Star look to it. The newer Phantasy Star games, that is.
Yeah.
Kind of in its like action-y type attack. I got to say, this looks kind of neat, actually.
Who's the spy? Marvelous. So it's not even by Sega, but it kind of looks inspired by the newer Phantasy Star games, at least to me, at first glance.
There it is, your Japanese release dates. How about the UK?
Well, in the UK we have some games. We have, um, on the 19th we have Alien Swarm and the 20th Need for Speed World. Those are both PC, by the way.
The 23rd is Dragon Quest IX Sentinels of the Starry Skies, and that's it until... Yeah, that's it.
Alright. Just a couple quick more stories for you guys, and then the classic game of the week while we transition into Part B tonight.
Loki, you got something else for us?
Guess what? If you've signed up for the PlayStation Plus service, you may be a wonderful contestant in checking out Hulu Plus as well.
Hey, it's another service with Plus in the name. It's got to be good, right?
Which will become available to select subscribers of the Sony's PlayStation Plus program starting now.
Apparently, eventually all subscribers may be able to check out the Hulu Plus service once it finally launches.
But as of right now, you can download the Hulu Plus software and request an invitation to an exclusive preview.
And if you're chosen, then you can preview the wonderful stuff that Hulu Plus will be allowing you to check out.
Am I hearing you correctly that you're telling me, if I pay Sony $50 a year, I might get the opportunity.
I might get selected, my name might get pulled out of that hat, and I would be given the opportunity with my $50 a year to pay Hulu $10 a year to watch old crap on TV.
Am I correct in what I'm hearing?
You are correct, and doesn't it sound awesome?
Sign me the fuck up! All this and core? Wow!
I don't know, I got nothing.
It was beyond my ability to comment on, Rob.
Wait, can I tune in Hulu Plus stuff on my TV in my Sony home apartment?
Probably not.
Can I possibly, I don't know, put out core magazines in my Sony apartment on home, like on my coffee table or anything like that?
I don't think you can do that, but in the mall they sometimes show clips from core.
Oh wow, clips! I'm gonna stay there in the mall forever until I see the whole month of core, just so I don't have to pay for it.
And eventually I'll see all the clips, so that's gonna be a worthwhile investment of my time.
You know, there's the OLR clubhouse right now, right? We have a clubhouse at home. Dumbest $5 I ever spent, but I had to do it.
OLR, we love to explore new ways to interact with our audience and all these social things.
Some of those ways may not be good.
Stupid dollars. Look, look, I took the hit for the team, okay? I spent $5 on this clubhouse at home.
Right now, we're limited to 25 members, and believe it or not, I don't know how this is possible, but I still get requests at least once a week to join the club, and I have to just file them away and ignore them.
Trust me, you're not missing out on anything.
Yeah, here's the thing. The clubhouse is a room, and I decorated it with the arcade machines that I won in the Namco demo, and I tried to put some stuff in there, but I can't put anything...
I can't put anything OLR-related in there. I can't put a clip from the show. There's a giant TV that sits at the top of the clubhouse. I can't do anything with it.
I can't put, like, video, you know, because we've shot video before. I can't put that there. I can't put... I can't even put, like, the OLR artwork on the wall. I can do nothing.
So what you're saying is you've transformed your OLR clubhouse into your game room.
Yes, I did.
Oh, Sony.
And I paid five bucks for that exclusive opportunity to beta test the clubhouses.
Feeling a little impotent now?
I'm just shocked. I'm hearing the words come out of my mouth, and I want to smack myself on the back of the head and call me an idiot. I paid five dollars to beta test the clubhouse.
Here's the funny part about it, though.
God, I'm an idiot.
They're still, like, gung-ho with home and saying, oh, it's such a wonderful platform. Oh my god, it's so successful. Doesn't that sound a little bit like, oh my god, sodium one will blow your fucking mind?
UMD is such a wonderful format. It will change the world in, like, portable media. Damn it! Digital content? On a memory stick? Ah! Why didn't we think of that first?
It's just so funny.
Okay, okay. We're going to make this just fucking kick-ass game in home, and we're going to give it away for free, alright? You ready?
You're going to be in a tank, and you go around in this 3D space, and you shoot other tanks. Oh my god, it's a print! Run with it. It's amazing.
And you can, like, post to your... You'll be able to post to your Twitter when you overtake other tanks, and you'll win stuff for your house. But not your real house, your fake house. And shirts.
Oh, but then you have to pay for additional levels once you get there. And for the record, I never got to the point where I had to buy additional levels because I got bored with the game that quick.
Look, I just... And for those that think we're being Xbox fanboys right now and giving Sony an unbelievable amount of hate, look, I'll just say this. Never forget Yaris.
So, it can happen to anyone, alright?
Hey! Speaking of the Xbox, actually, maybe this is a good thing to follow it up with. You know how they're making this awesome new channel called The Destination Arcade?
Actually, it's not really... It doesn't actually sound that awesome at all. Destination Arcade is, like, this store that you can download to see the store in a whole new way.
I mean, really, that's what it is. Destination Arcade, like, when we release this, you guys, you're gonna get to see the store in a whole new way. You're gonna have this all-new opportunity to buy things.
Man, that sounds awesome! And everybody's like, fuck yeah, sign me up! Destination Arcade's gonna be the shit!
Well, guess what? Major Nelson came out and said, okay, so Destination Arcade, you get to download it this week and it's gonna, like, blow your mind, and then August 18th, we're shutting it off!
So, it's a limited time only!
We fixed all the problems with, you know, Xbox Live Arcade. We made things easier to find for a limited time, and then you're gonna have to go back to finding things the old hard way. Why bother?
So, there you go. I don't even have to defer to yours. This is just as stupid. You know what this is just like? This is just like, hey, guess what, guys? We know that you've been bitching about the D-Pad forever, and we're gonna release these wonderful limited edition FIFA controllers that are green, that have the D-Pad fixed, but it's only for a limited time. We're going back to the crappy broken D-Pad.
Okay, apparently, I didn't even know this until just now. Here's the best part. Wait for it, guys. Okay, so Major Nelson had an interview with Shaq News, apparently, and said that, I didn't even know this, I'm hearing this for the first time, said to Shaq News, if you've downloaded it, it will continue to work, but you can only download it until August 18th, apparently.
So, if you wanna be part of this exclusive club, that's like, I don't even know, that's like going to a mall, and like, you could go to Macy's to buy clothes, or you could go to JCPenney, but you know what, you had to sign up for this, during this month-long promotion to go to JCPenney.
And if you didn't sign up during that time, there's gonna be a guard at the door who's just gonna bounce you. Like, did you download this between July and August? Come on in. Fuck you, go to Macy's. We don't want your business.
It's gonna be like this. It's gonna be like, okay, if you've downloaded this program, all the clothes will be on the shelf, but if you haven't downloaded this program, you're gonna have to go to the store where all the clothes are in a giant pile in the middle.
They're just on the floor. It'll be like that old Nick game show, Finders Keepers.
Just to let everybody know right now, at this point, Rob has doubled over and put his head between his knees.
I mean, how many news stories have we read tonight that just don't make any fucking sense? Like, what is wrong with all of you? Are you all high? Did they give out drugs in E3 this year?
Well, why didn't we get to go then? I want drugs.
You don't understand. Blasinga, Sony, Microsoft, you're all stupid. What is wrong? Rob is breathless with disbelief.
We just figured it out. Our eyes are open.
I just simply cannot. Rob's gonna cry.
That's the perfect thing to do when you've solved problems in making things easier to find. You cancel it. That's perfect. That makes sense to me.
Not much makes sense anymore in this world.
So, enjoy this very special store that you can only download for a limited time. And Salacious Pop's asking, so is it like a skin or what? You know, I don't know. I'm just told it's like this super special new way.
It's fairy dust, okay? It's fairy dust.
I got nothing.
We're gonna offer this free game for a limited time. It's featuring a car from Toyota called the Yaris. It's gonna blow your mind.
Alright, you guys. We're gonna put out this vision camera.
That was so bad it made me burp.
We're gonna put out this camera and it's gonna allow you to play these awesome fucking games like totem ball. Yeah, it's like pinball, but you like use your hands. Use your hands. You flail. You make the pinball thingy go.
By the way, this is the same company that's putting out a camera this year that you're gonna use your hands to.
Rob, yeah, let's not. It's too painful. What if it's too late for me to sell back my vision camera for, say, some store credit?
Salacious Pop in our chatroom says, Major Nelson announces new store, announces that Seattle has the best weed, and that this dude at Rare takes the biggest bong hits he's ever seen.
You know what? I think we need to take, we need to take a, what? Yes, Loki, final. I have a great idea. Yes.
We want to show off the Kinect to get people excited about it. What store can we back connect with?
God, Macy's. Where do all the people that play Kinect gather on Thursdays, Fridays, and Saturdays between noon and 8 p.m.?
Where are they all at? Where would I go? Would I go to the mini golf? No, fuck the mini golf place. Would I go, would I go to the movies? No, no. Kinect players don't go to the movies. I know. We'll go to Macy's, who doesn't even have an electronics department.
What the fuck? Oh, that's fun. You're all high.
So let's take a look at the way they did it in the past. Let's see how you used to get high in the 80s, huh? With the trip down memory lane and the classic game of the week.
That's right. We're going to take a moment to see the drug induced effects of video games back in the day. And boy, did Jamie pick a good one tonight for this topic, didn't you, Jamie?
I'm sure that did. I just want to point out, she picks these well before the show starts. It's just, it's just too good tonight.
And I really put this in an honor of classic gaming expo because it's there every year. You mean, um, the California extreme? Whatever that thing was. Yeah, California extreme. The event that let you in free with a media pass? Yeah.
I know they were great. Well, I'm, I'm covering it at media like and stuff. By the way, she just took another Vicodin folks. So you're in for a real treat in part B.
Well, my element was wearing off. I was in pain. Um, anyway, um, so yeah, Journey. Uh, Bally Midway put it out in the 80s. Um, and, uh, it was after, you know, Frontiers, which was their 1983 album by Journey, you know, got them really popular.
So, um, it was supposed to go along with the US band tour. Um, and then, um, it was actually, uh, brought in incredible technologies as a second team of developers to, uh, bring it out for Christmas around that time.
And so it's features the, who the band members were at the time, which was Steve Perry and Neil Sean, uh, Steve Smith, Jonathan Cain and Ross Valerie. Um, they have a sort of cartoon bodies, but their faces are really like these digital black and white photographs from while they were on tour.
Um, and it was supposed to use, um, this, uh, photo technology for another game, but it failed in location testing. So anyway, um, you have to, uh, go through the game to find the different, um, musical instruments or a microphone.
So you play each of the members of the band in these different levels to get their missing musical implement. And now turn this up.
That's in the last level. Um, there's actually a cassette player in the machine, um, that, um, when you get to the last level, it'll play a looped version of separate ways, which is what was playing on there.
And the last level is that you have to keep fans from, uh, storming the stage and stealing the instruments again. And then of course, when they finally get past you, then, um, you have to go find the things again.
Um, there, there was another game that Journey was in. It was called Journey Escape for the Atari 2600. This was listed as number nine on the top ten worst licensed game ideas ever for, uh, Game Informer 2007.
Who doesn't know Dick, apparently, because Journey is awesome. Just saying. I want to see what this Journey Escape thing is. Yeah, Journey Escape. Here's from Emmanuel. You're on a boat with Journey. One of the world's hottest rock groups.
A spectacular performance has just ended. Now it's up to you to guide each Journey band member past hordes of love-crazed groupies, sneaky photographers, and shifty-eyed promoters to the safety of the Journey Escape vehicle. And time to make it to the next concert. Your mighty manager and loyal roadies are there to help, but the escape is up to you.
Sounds like a ten to me. You have to make it to the Scarab Escape vehicle, the same one that's on the cover. I know, right? It was very different from the arcade game, so if you only played the 2600- The song Escape, though, ironically, is not in the game. But the intro is Don't Stop Believing. There you go. Alright. There it is, your classic game of the week journey. Oh, and by the way, the manager is the Kool-Aid man. What? Oh, the 2600 version?
The manager, inexplicably depicted as the Kool-Aid man. Hey, Kool-Aid man! Oh yeah! Oh no! Naughty, naughty Kool-Aid.
Alright, we're gonna take a quick break here. It's been kind of a fun Part A tonight. I don't know what's in the air tonight here at OLR Studios, but we're having fun. I hope you guys are, too. Join our chat if you're not already there. Chat.orangelaungeready.com. We got plenty more coming up in Part B tonight. We got our rapid-fire news, and Loki already blew it, but we are gonna talk about the Big Macy's tour. We've got to talk about some of that.
Also, 1 vs. 100 got canned this week, so you know we gotta talk about that, because it's kind of sad. And yeah, man, there's a lot of stories here tonight that are just, like, bad ideas. This is not Good News Week, everybody. I'm sorry, but hopefully there'll be some good gems tonight.
Go ahead. To be fair, we're actually not talking about the Macy's tour so much. It's actually a lot. Other places. Oh, there's the Roadshow, too. Alright, we'll mention them both, I'm sure.
And there is some good news, though, we're gonna talk about as well. Mega Man Universe we'll talk about a little bit when we come back, and we'll talk as well about a very, very classic Atari 2600 game getting updated for the new millennium. That should be kind of interesting.
So we'll talk about all that when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio. Don't go anywhere, we'll be right back.
Hello, everybody, and welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio on this July the 18th, 2010, where we are taping live at All Games Radio. We're moving into Part B of our show, and I gotta tell you, if you're just tuning in, we've had a pretty funny show so far. Lots of fun chatter in Part A. Just a lot of weird news. It's been a very weird week in gaming, and a lot of strange ideas going on out there.
And the fun is gonna continue here in Part B. If you are just joining us, come into our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com and have your say, because the big part of our show that makes our show unique is you.
And your chats and your tweets that we're gonna get to in a minute, and all that good stuff. And I also wanna call this out, your awesome iTunes reviews, when you say nice things about us on the internet that make us feel warm and fuzzy. I wanna read one here in a minute, but I gotta pull it up.
So in the meantime, let's get to some rapid fire news and things that happened throughout the week that we can mention in a few seconds.
The Expendables, a pretty awesome movie coming out this summer with a bunch of old action stars, is gonna be getting its own Facebook game, and it's very similar to Contra. And everybody loves Contra, and it kinda looks a little similar, I guess, because you can kill a bunch of people on a 2D platformer.
But what you need to do is you just have to like the Expendables fan page in order to get access to the game. I don't know, you should like the movie. Looks awesome.
Sonic Colors is a new game from Sega coming out this fall, and GameStop has a wonderful pre-order bonus with that. You can get a Sonic the Hedgehog hat.
Yes, putting it on will make you that much closer to Sonic. And it's kinda neat looking, actually. Not enough for me to say pre-order the game.
Does it have like a blue spiky thing on it? Oh, it does! That's adorable.
It's very adorable. So yes, you can check that out, and of course the game is gonna be on Wii and DS sometime this fall, probably around November.
And there is a new Oddworld game in the works being developed by the company Just Add Water. And they did a game called Gravity Crash.
And apparently it's got the, there are multiple projects across multiple platforms starring all your favorite Oddworld characters.
And they haven't said exactly when they're actually coming out, but you should just at least take solace that they are in the works at some point soon.
We'll see some Oddworld games come back.
Alright, I got some quick stories for you guys. One of them is about Kid Icarus. Kid Icarus? I like Kid Icarus. This is some other news coming out about Kid Icarus Uprising. Of course that's the 3DS game that finally brings back Kid Icarus after not being around ever since that Game Boy game.
Apparently, in a chat with Games Master, this is a magazine in the UK, Mashahiro Sakurai, who is the game designer at Super Smash Brothers Brawl, says that the online capabilities are currently being tested.
And by the way, yes, he made Brawl and he's making this game. He's saying the online capabilities are currently being tested.
There could be some versus play, but we can't go into any detail. There are a lot of capabilities that expand on what was in the DS that people are taking advantage of.
Hmm, so it sounds like the online and versus and all that is being toyed with, but we don't know anything for sure just yet, but it's kind of cool because I don't know about you guys, but I just assumed it was like a one player only thing.
Also, apparently some Capcom games are going to be making their way to the Wii Virtual Console Arcade. Sometimes you forget that the Virtual Console has an arcade, but they're going to be getting some Capcom games in an announcement this week.
Among some other Capcom announcements, we'll get into it in a little bit. So that's going to be kind of cool, some old school Capcom games.
A place where Capcom games would be welcomed would be Game Room, who saw the release of Fishing Derby, Barnstorming, and Quad Run all on the Atari 2600 this week, as well as the JIRUS for the arcade and Hover Force for the Intellivision.
Unfortunately, as awesome as it is to have JIRUS in Game Room, it was already on the Xbox Live Arcade, so it's probably the most awesome game that hit this week, but it already had a version released, so unfortunately Game Room didn't have a lot of win there.
However, I will say one place where Game Room wins, and I mentioned this in part A, but I wanted to say this as well, it did have a little upgrade this week that they patched into the game some new little features.
Like now, if you've been playing a game for a long time, the other avatars will come up behind you and start watching you and applaud you when you finally lose, although I don't know why they applaud you when you lose.
And then like fireworks when you get a medal, and most importantly, live leaderboards. When you're playing in ranked mode, you see your position in the leaderboard in real time, and you watch yourself conquer, like who's in 900th place, then 800th place, then 700th.
It's actually a really cool little addition, I thought that was neat. I was most excited as someone who's really tried to support Game Room and has sometimes been disappointed, but I'm really happy to see that they are doing updates, it makes me very hopeful for the future.
Now they just need some more licenses, like the Wii God with Capcom this week, that would be great. So we'll see. DarkSakura.
Well, something great coming out for iPhone will be Star Wars Battle for Hoth, especially good for fans of the Empire Strikes Back, right? Which people will arguably say is the best Star Trek movie, although I am personally a fan of Return of the Jedi, it's just me.
I think A New Hope was the best one. I know, I'm weird.
Rob hurt my brain. Anyway, it's gonna be out for $2.99, and it's meant to celebrate the 30 year anniversary of the Empire Strikes Back. Pretty cool, huh?
For Rock Band News, we have the Stooges and Bad Religion, the Stooges Pack 01, which total will be 440 Microsoft Points, or $5.49, includes $19.69, I Wanna Be Your Dog, and No Fun, each of those, well actually, $19.69 and No Fun will be 200 Wii Points a piece.
I was wondering why it's only saying that one of them has a Microsoft Points list. Forget I said that. They're $19.99 a piece.
Individual songs coming out are both by Bad Religion, New Dark Ages, and No Control, each 160 Microsoft Points, or 200 Wii Points.
And they will, of course, some of them being the Stooges Pack and No Control by Bad Religion will be in Lego Brock Band Store. I love Bad Religion. Gray band.
Alright, we're gonna get into this. Oh, I'm sorry. I thought you were done. My bad.
I have three!
Ah, my bad.
Rob is ignoring me. I am being marginalized!
I am multi-tasking, and I thought I heard three things.
I'm being marginalized! Cause I'm a woman!
Yes, because you're a woman.
I know. Anyway, um, now there is this really cool dude who has an even cooler, I would have to say, uh, I guess you're married by now, I don't know.
Um, but his name is Ray, is Ray Arafanto, who works for Xbox platform team, um, is getting married, or has gotten married, and his wedding ring is fantastic.
Um, it is a USB platinum wedding ring.
And, um, and on it, it says, um, for a lifetime of memories.
Isn't that pun-tastic?
Is it actually like you could plug it in a USB slot with the ring?
No, I don't need it. Actually, you know, I read though, um, Rob, I did read about another one, and I tried to find the pictures of it and I couldn't, about a couple that did have a USB wedding ring, a real USB wedding ring, and on it were, um, photos of their courtship.
Wow.
Yeah, that's why I would think, that's kind of what I thought of when you first talked about a USB wedding ring, like somebody's gonna plug one in.
Yeah, this one's just sort of cut into a USB-looking pattern.
But, um, but no, I did actually find one, um, about a couple that actually did have the, their, uh, ring, their rings each were, uh, photos of their lives together, built into the ring.
You know, this whole, like, USB, and to some extent mini-USB, and that whole technology is really interesting, like, you know, um, you know those, like, MedicAlert bracelets they used to have back in the day, and they still do, that, like, you know, they're like silver, and they have little snakes, the very identifiable medical thing on it, and it's usually for people, like, who are diabetic, or allergic, or have some type of medical condition, whereas they ever become unconscious, you know, and have to have an ambulance called on them, the ambulance knows something about them.
You know, they're putting that stuff on USB now.
I'm actually planning on making one for myself.
You see, like, these little, like, USB jewelry type things, and now it's, like, your whole medical records will be on there. Well, not, not your whole thing, but, you know, everything they need to know is there.
Well, see, that's actually a plan that I have, um, is getting one of those little, um, kind of rubber with the USB clasp, as it were.
Um, because, I mean, I had to repeat for the staff a couple of times that I'm allergic to penicillin, and amoxicillin, and the psyllins of the family, the mold, you know, and I was just thinking, what if I had fallen unconscious and had a bad infection, they tried to give me penicillin, you know.
So, I think that those are fantastic ideas. I'm actually looking into the cost of just making it myself.
Either with a micro-USB or doing, um, a micro-SD, to have it embedded in there.
Uh, bonesis6, 006, bondsis6, there's two Zs, which makes it very strange to pronounce, bonesis6 in our chatroom says a USB dildo.
You know, you could charge it, kind of like you do an iPhone. It's not outside the realm of possibility, I'm sure it's sadly been done.
They have USB AA batteries, that can charge in the...
Salacious Pop says RFID would seem more intuitive, that's what they use for pets. I didn't even think about that, of course, like if a pet gets lost, that's all you'd need. Crazy.
Um, alright, we're gonna get into Twitter topics here real quick, but first, I mentioned I was gonna read this.
We are so appreciative when people leave us nice reviews on iTunes, on our listing there, because it helps us spread the word about our show.
This one was especially nice, so I wanted to read this real quick, because it's awesome. It's from HungryMrDrunk, is the name of the user.
I know when I get drunk, I get hungry.
Uh, I have been a hardcore listener, lol, for years, and I can say that every Sunday I only think about running to my PSP to listen to this amazing podcast.
I think it should be syndicated on the radio. After all, they are official game analysts under President Cat.
They got me into music games like DDR and Guitar Hero, and because of them, I became a better gamer.
Thank you guys for the best eight years of my life.
Not to mention, we are the official podcast of the universe.
Actually, it's funny, he actually says in the title, why OLR is the best podcast in the galaxy.
Although technically it's the official video game podcast of the galaxy.
But I like being called best too.
It is nice, it's very nice.
That was a very sweet thank you person.
Thank you HungryMrDrunk.
HungryMrDrunk, you should come over and have a beer with me.
Yes, that's right, I hope you're next week.
When I'm not on Vicodin.
Lots of Guinness and Cheetos.
Alright, let's get into Twitter topics.
Shall we move into Twitter topics? We shall.
I guess.
You guess?
Get a fan.
I'm a god Rob, I'm a god.
When did you last take a Vicodin?
An hour ago.
So during the show.
Yes, it is during the show.
During the show.
Let's see.
Whatever.
Alright.
You know, I figured out why it's affecting me very strongly.
Why is that?
Because keep in mind, I did one of those major detoxes when I went raw.
I quit like almost every bit of medication.
I didn't even take any pain medication or anything.
And so it's hitting me harder than it really used to.
It is.
Can I get to the Twitter topic?
Kitty!
Sorry.
SSJ100Matt sent me this link. It has nothing to do with anything.
This is why I really don't like to click on YouTubes during the show.
But SSJ100Matt is kind of funny.
And he sent this link and it's adorable.
He says, this new game is coming to the Wii.
And so this box comes up with nine little holes in it.
And then little kitties come out of the holes.
Get bonked.
Oh my god, send that to me Rob.
It's so adorable.
It's in our chat.
Are you in chat?
I'm in chat.
SSJ100Matt just posted this.
It's adorable.
And so this makes for terrible radios.
This is awful, terrible, horrible radio.
I'll put it on Facebook.
Yeah, let's put it on Facebook.
Alright.
Can I get to Twitter topics already?
Twitter.com slash O-L-R.
Follow us, ask us questions, we answer, da da da.
DarkTattooia wants us to plug Retro Review.
Oh no, he says he's planning one.
I don't think I saw it posted yet.
But DarkTattooia does a lot of great work for the site, so thanks very much.
Let's see, Sturlok wants to give a shameless plug.
Is this turning into the shameless plug segment?
I think it is.
Actually, I really like this article though, so I am going to let him have his shameless plug.
He wrote an article for Geek-Life.com.
That's us.
Geek Life.
It's like all the O-L-R people are suddenly moving over there.
You're defecting.
No, that's okay.
He actually made this story and I just linked it there in chat.
It's GeekLife.com.
It's called The Blind Gamer Perspective.
Because Sturlok is actually a blind gamer and you might think, like, how is that even possible?
You can't see the sprites on the screen.
But he actually explains it and talks about audio cues and how helpful it is when you have a role-playing game
that tells you when you're running into walls.
Like, makes that bonk, bonk, bonk sound.
Like, you know, like some of the old Final Fantasy games do.
I thought it was a neat article, so I approve.
Two thumbs up.
Tigerclaw gives us some links and one of them is kind of, well, they're both kind of sad, actually.
Let me read this first one here.
Starcraft 2 cost a hundred million to make.
Wow.
That apparently is according to the Wall Street Journal.
Activision Blizzard spent a hundred million dollars on the three-part sequel.
Where did all that money go?
Oh, my God.
I guess this game's going to be epic beyond epic.
Purely development and that has nothing to do with marketing.
It exceeds Gran Turismo 5's 60 million development cost.
They'll make it all bad.
That's the sick part.
Let's see, also from Tigerclaw.
Killer gets two life sentences in an Xbox motivated murder.
I hate stories like these because usually they have nothing, I mean, no offense to Tigerclaw
because he's pulling it from a game blog.
But I just, I hate that this stuff gets tied to gaming at all because it's just that this guy's just sick.
Some sicko killed people and it somehow involved an Xbox.
His name is Kyle Sebastian Scott, 19 years old, and he killed a 22-year-old in January of last year.
He hit his body in a ravine near a hiking trail in Colorado Springs.
Apparently he wanted the guy's Xbox and killed the guy.
Oh, this is even better.
Jason Holly, the victim, 22 years old, developmentally disabled.
Terrible.
And the judge said he trusted you, he would have given you anything, and he did.
You could have taken the Xbox and he would have never told anybody.
He was trying to be normal, a buddy, or one of the guys.
Two life sentences.
Not enough. Not enough.
Spazinator's sending us an update.
Remember he called in last week to talk about his Sony woes?
Update, update.
Sony Computer Entertainment of America finally gave back my remaining 55 videos this past Monday.
Woo, that's a lot.
Still rather pissed that it took so damn long.
They actually called me as they were doing it so I could confirm if they had everything.
Well, that's kind of nice, I guess. At least they did that.
Jay Jugo on Twitter is listening to some old episodes of OLR. I guess this is a never forget kind of moment.
Hey guys, here's a funny flashback.
Procrastination is like masturbation.
It feels good until you realize you fucked yourself.
Irene said that quote on your sixth episode.
Just wanted to share that flashback moment with you guys.
Keep up the great work.
Nice.
Old school OLR. They do exist out there.
They're out there if you know where to look.
The pictures are now finally on the website.
Apparently, well, my initial email bounced because apparently there's too many pictures attached.
So now I'm sending them two at a time.
So remember folks, if you're going to upload pictures to the website, do so in small quantities.
Because the email may not be able to handle it.
But now you can see pictures of Baby Room and they're right there in the header of OrangetownsRudy.com.
Yes, they are up on top. In fact, I'm just waiting for the last two to refresh on here.
Take a look.
And they're awesome.
Actually, if you look at the gallery, you can see my progress of last week, which was not much progress.
Dark Tetsuya says, anyone be interested in an OLR game in the same style of the Journey coin-op?
I've been wanting to do that for quite some time.
That would be awesome if you could actually do it.
That is no small programming feat.
That would be cool.
Yes, of course. I'd love that.
The Journey arcade game is rad.
It's a classic game of the week now. It's official.
And lastly, Retertainment. What nerd thing makes you think of an old TV show?
Mine is the red-green show after the duct tape iPhone 4 fix.
That's a tough question.
What nerd thing makes you think of an old TV show?
I brought up Mr. Wizard yesterday.
Why did I bring up Mr. Wizard?
Because somebody then tried to say Mr. Wizard hated...
That was me.
What did I say in response to Mr. Wizard? I don't know.
You said you thought he was dead.
He is dead, isn't he?
I don't know.
I don't know. Forget it.
Mr. Wizard never really dies.
You see, he's figured out a way to become one with the Force.
He's just going to disappear into a robe.
Well, I just thought about Finders Keepers, thinking about the Xbox store earlier.
So I guess it does happen once in a while when I think of old TV shows.
Is there something nerdy that makes you think of an old TV show?
The status of the gaming industry and the show Bonkers.
I think that's pretty close there.
A coworker said this to me the other day, and I like this.
This really has nothing to do with gaming or nerd.
But she said, you know, sometimes my life here feels like the dinosaurs TV show and that little baby.
Not the mama. Not the mama.
I don't know. It's funny to me.
That is pretty funny, Rob.
Anything you want to add, Dark Soccer?
Well, I don't know. Usually I think about my job and all I can think about is...
What was that?
Running Man.
Blade Runner?
No, Running Man.
One where he's trapped in a game show and to get out he has to escape.
Richard Dawson was the villain. That was awesome.
Yes, now I know.
The best part about that movie.
Alright. Let's move on with some more news. Back to gaming news.
That's almost as cool as Mega Race with Don Knotts or something I think was the villain in that.
Don Knotts was not in that, was he?
There was somebody who was like Don Knotts in that game.
In that game?
It was weird. No, Don Knotts was not in the Running Man.
That would have been even more epic. Don Knotts should have been one of the killers in the Running Man.
That would have been cool.
Tigerclaw, by the way, says Mr. Wizard died in 2007. Don Herbert. Just so you know.
In case you weren't aware, Mr. Wizard...
And he hated kids.
He did not hate kids.
Yes, he did.
He loved kids as much as Mel Gibson loved his wife and daughter.
Alright, back to news stories.
Don't get me started. He's an ass-wife.
Don't even. Just pull back. Move along. Nothing to see here.
That name is banned from the show.
Move along. Nothing to see here.
Low-key, back to gaming.
Mega Man Universe is apparently a game that's coming out on the Playstation Network and Xbox Live Arcade.
They had a little teaser trailer that came out this week that featured absolutely no gameplay whatsoever.
But it kind of gave us an idea of what we may expect.
Apparently, the game will actually combine universes in different Capcom game universes.
The teaser trailer showed, at one point, a stop-motion animation of Ryu, Arthur, from the Ghosts and...
I'm saying it the Western way, okay? The improper way.
You're wrong!
Fine. Ryu and Arthur from the Ghosts and Ghouls and Ghosts and Goblins series.
And, of course, Mega Man.
Facing off against a bunch of Mega Man villains.
So either I'm guessing that Mega Man's going to get powers from these other players or the other game heroes.
Or he's going to be teaming up, I guess, with...
Kind of think of the Super Mario crossover, but the Super Capcom crossover with all these different characters from different series facing off against Mega Man characters.
Or, perhaps, facing off against Capcom universe characters.
Although, then you would wonder why it's called Mega Man universe and not Capcom universe.
Can I play this trailer? Because I haven't even seen this yet.
I've been waiting until tonight's show to watch this.
This is only about a minute or two, right?
It's short.
Okay, so I've got to go into the studio right now.
Capcom! Yay, Capcom!
Bored down. Here we go.
Ooh, I approve of the music.
Why is, like, some kid sleeping? That has nothing to do with Mega Man.
It's Toy Story Mega Man.
Bored down.
Oh, it's 20XX.
Man, there's something else I forgot at the very end that's kind of cool.
Cut man.
I'm turning this down a little bit so I can talk for it.
Well, it looks cool. Too bad this is all, like, a pre-rendered thing that the actual game's not going to look like.
It looks like stop-motion animation.
Sweet!
What?
That little kid's probably on drugs.
This is going to be, you know what this looks like to me?
Can I tell you what this honestly, like, I think right now?
No, it looks like the Mega Man fighting game.
But it's going to be like Capcom's own version of Capcom vs. Capcom.
If that makes any sense. That's the first impression I get of what this is.
Wait a minute.
He's also quite, like...
Watch this, this is awesome.
Okay.
So he's still in bed. Mega Man universe.
Your world. Mega-fide.
That's great.
That was the old Mega Man box art guy?
Yeah.
They're going to have the Mega Man box art Mega Man.
I don't get it!
Suck man.
I don't get it. I felt like that was a waste of two minutes of show.
Welcome to any two minutes of this show.
I don't know. Alpha-Can-Anagram, you asked me a question.
Why are they fighting only Mega Man bad guys, though?
I don't know. I have no idea.
It doesn't...
I seriously think it's like one of those, like the Nintendo, the Super Mario crossover.
It's going to be like that.
Why can't we just have Rockman power battles?
Just do a new one of those.
Because that wasn't very good.
I liked it.
It's like one of the few games...
The arcade version of it. That was so cool.
Alright.
You just need to do a game just storing bass.
What they need to do is they need to do a Mega Man game that's very similar to the upcoming Castlevania game.
You know, with like 16 players at the same time fighting Mega Man characters.
Alpha-Can-Anagram says,
Sky, imagine possibly Mega Man mixed with LittleBigPlanet with Mega Man powered up level editor.
Well, that sounds awesome, but I don't think that's what this is.
If it is though, hey, it might be fun.
Actually, it might be a lot of fun.
Is this only supposed to be download though?
Like it's a live arcade in PlayStation 3?
Live arcade in PlayStation Network, yeah.
Alright.
Let's move on with some more stories.
And this is something about something the Xbox is losing.
Microsoft cancelled 1 versus 100.
That's right.
There's not going to be a third season of 1 versus 100.
This is confirmed with Xbox...
Sorry, Microsoft Game Studios General Manager Dave McCarthy saying,
quote, we're very proud of the 1 versus 100 team and their accomplishments and are excited to apply what we've learned to future programming.
And yep, it's on the Xbox.com.
A fond farewell.
That's it.
Aw, that sucks.
They're going to have Mega Man foam Mega Busters or whatever at Comic Con they're giving away.
Do you not even care?
The 1 versus 100 is gone?
No, I don't care.
All you can think about is Mega Man?
Ugh.
Never forget, there is something funny, Xbox Live Prime Time, whatever the fuck happened to that.
Well, that's my point.
That stuff sounded so exciting.
Hey, we're going to have the service that's going to blow away all the competition.
And we're going to cancel it.
It's going to make your Xbox Live Gold Account more worthwhile than just paying to play against other people.
But it came down to where they couldn't get advertisers.
Yeah, that's the buzz I'm hearing too is that it was always a Sprint commercial.
In a while you might see another one, but that was mostly it.
So they just couldn't get the advertisers to give away the prizes.
But you know what, I think there would be...
Call me crazy.
But I think there would be a lot of people that would still play the game, not even for prizes.
I mean, when you went into the non-live rounds, which didn't give away anything but points really,
and supposedly more of a chance to play in the live rounds,
there would still be like 10-20,000 people on at any time.
I mean, you can't tell me that stuff is that expensive to run.
Really?
I mean, I guess they have a question writing staff.
And why can't you get advertisers? I see advertisers for stuff all the time.
Like, there's different movies that they're promoting on there.
There's different stuff.
Where's Axe Body Spray?
Just do a crossover. Get the Old Spice guy in there.
Mountain Dew.
Old Spice is very up on the new technology stuff. Get him in there.
That last marketing campaign was brilliant.
Brilliant. Who doesn't love that guy?
My favorite thing, I'm on a horse.
Did you see all the YouTube videos?
I didn't see the new ones, yeah.
Oh, you got to see the marriage proposal. That's the best one.
Monty Boggs in our chat room says,
Microsoft always promises cool stuff to live and then never does it
when they realize it requires work.
You know, it's just disappointing because they didn't really announce what is next.
I think that would soften the blow a little bit if they were like,
well, sadly we're losing 1 versus 100 because, you know, licensing,
they're going to make it a real show again, which by the way is also a rumor
that 1 versus 100 is actually coming back to TV
because of the success of Xbox.
Weird, right?
I know, right? I don't think it'll be the same thing.
It's not going to be Bob Saget and NBC.
I'm thinking like Game Show Network.
I actually, I read blogs about game shows. Leave me alone.
Hey, Rob, that's one of the reasons we love you.
I know.
I just, I don't know.
But if they'd come out and said, okay, we're canceling 1 versus 100,
but we are bringing you, I don't know, The Price is Right
or Family Feud or hell, Wheel of Fortune, Jeopardy, anything.
I can play The Price is Right.
People would be excited about that.
And I don't even think you have to give away prizes.
Give away E-peen and people will still line up.
Give away achievements. Give away shout-outs on websites, leaderboards.
People will play for E-peen.
Here's the opportunity now.
Make something very similar to, say, PlayStation Home
and you can have the prizes in your living room.
Hey, look at this virtual.
Oh, my God, why aren't you working for Microsoft?
That's brilliant.
Brilliant.
Win avatar items and themes and cool stuff.
You could do it.
You don't have to give away a free game or points.
I want a free game and points and a car.
Well, I mean, you know, that's nice.
Maybe give that away to, like, the season-long winner
and it won't cost as much out of the prize budget.
AJ Mix in our chat room. Double Dare featuring Natal.
Why aren't you people working for Microsoft?
These are brilliant ideas. Brilliant.
Won't happen.
I don't know. Here's a thought. Make up your own game show.
You know, get somebody out there who's got to be creating these game shows.
Hire him. Make your own damn game show.
Make a new Xbox Live game show.
Yeah, I'd love that idea.
You could maybe even, like, broadcast some stuff on MSNBC or something.
Or, you know, one of the companies that you own.
Fucking stream it on the internet. Have, like, uh...
Have something. I don't know.
I love this. Monty Boggs.
Are you smarter than a fifth grader?
Were all the little kids in Halo are the fifth graders?
You know, there is a fifth grader game on Xbox Live.
Are you smarter than a fifth grader?
It's on all the systems, I think.
But it's not, you know, interactive.
I was really excited about Xbox Prime Time.
And it's really disappointing that it's just like,
Eh, well, you know, it didn't work. Bye.
So I really hope they come out and say,
Yes, we've been working on another project and it's still part of Xbox Prime Time.
But it makes me nervous when they come out at E3 and don't say a damn thing about it.
That should have been the sign right there.
They didn't say a damn thing about it at E3.
It wasn't like, Oh, you hope you liked 1 vs. 100.
Or, you know, but now we're going to bring you Jeopardy! and Wheel of Fortune!
Or something like that.
Well, you know, Jeopardy! and Wheel of Fortune! games were being shown off on the Wii.
Somewhere else.
Yep, I know there's Jeopardy! and Wheel of Fortune! games coming up this year.
Actually, the Wii's been getting a lot of those game shows.
They have The Price is Right and Press Your Luck.
The Wii's the place for game shows right now.
It's not live and interactive.
Oh my god, think of the possibilities.
Rob, don't cry.
I'm just...
It's just...
What the fuck are they smoking?
I don't know.
You can buy PlayStation Plus and maybe you'll get to pay somebody else to watch Hulu.
What's it going to...
They don't make any sense.
They do not.
When are the good ideas going to stick?
They just couldn't make money off of 1 vs. 100.
They weren't making enough in advertising to just buy PlayStation Plus.
I bet they could have charged...
Well, they're making the money off Xbox Gold.
They're making the money off Xbox Gold, subscribers.
There's other ways they could do it.
I don't believe the subscribers were giving them that much money.
It's about selling.
I know people who bought it at Xbox just to play that game.
They've got to be pissed.
They make the money back in other ways.
It's dumb. Dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb.
Yeah, but that's a different reason to buy an Xbox, too, if you ask me.
So she just pops in chat and says,
Rob wants a Big Brother port for Wii with a throttle-that-bitch Wiimote mechanic.
I would totally play Survivor on Xbox Live if it was, like, somehow real.
What?
There's a Survivor game coming out on the Wii.
It's going to be stupid.
It's not going to be online or anything.
It's going to be like the horrible PC games that were out.
At least the PC games.
I think one of the PC games you could actually play on the internet.
Probably it's going to be a port of the PC game.
Dumb, dumb, dumb.
Well, the last PC game came out a long time ago.
Yeah, that'll probably be a port of the PC game.
Alright, let's move on.
That's frightening.
Moving on, DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
Well, there is some stuff.
As soon as my, you know, system decides to stop being crappy.
I was also, you know, completely enamored with the whack-a-kitty.
Thank you, SSJ100Matt, for completely derailing the show.
We appreciate you.
With your cute kittens.
No, because my thing-okay, there it is.
I'm sorry. Well, actually, what was going on was that my window decided to hide itself.
Yay.
And my brain is broken. Doesn't work.
Anyway, how about some news about poor, poor Nintendo?
Can we have some sad music, Rob?
Some sad music?
Well, you didn't request this in advance.
Well, how about just break out a kazoo?
Hold on, hold on.
It's because I feel for them.
Sad music, you got it. Here we go.
Some sad music for Jamie's story.
Sigh.
There's an announcement made by the Nintendo UK General Manager.
His name is David Yarnton.
That demand for the Wii and the DS has declined.
He blamed the falling demand for the Wii and DS on the, quote, cycle.
And the recession in saying everybody's in the same boat.
We are not recession proof, he says.
We've probably, as an industry, been better than other industries.
We thought we would be selling more, but we're not, pretty much.
Um, yeah, that's really not the case of worlds in the world so much.
But there's light, Rob, there's light at the end of the tunnel.
We're waiting on the 3DS.
That's what they're saying.
We had to let that go.
Yeah, they're waiting on the 3DS because you don't need glasses.
Um, and he also, though, denied that Nintendo has been forced to slash prices.
But, um, yeah.
Alas, Nintendo. Alas.
I can't help ending up here drinking ginger ale.
What?
Just your perfect cap to destroy, alas, Nintendo.
What is wrong with you?
Salacious pop in our chatroom says, now I'm imagining Reggie in tears floating on a wooden plank saying, never let go, Wii. Never let go.
And then one of his thumbs break off.
Uh, yeah.
Uh, the kinectix-
No, no, no, no, guys, I got, I got, um, I got some, uh, advice here for Nintendo.
Um, here you go, Nintendo, I have some advice for you, okay?
Keep holding on, cause you know I'll make it through, I'll make it through. Just stay strong, cause you know I'm here for you, I'm here for you. There's nothing you can say.
Sorry about that. You just took it too far there. Yeah, I did. You went too far.
Yep. Let the, let the-
Should've just let it. Yeah, should've just left it with that, I know, I know.
Sequels are never as good as the original, they're really not.
I hear that Titanic 2's gonna be awesome, though.
Um, kinectix-
Three more hours of the ship sinking.
The ship sinks again.
You think it sunk and everyone died. They really went to a magical town under the water.
We found it! It's Titanic Atlantis!
Atlantastic? Oh, I can do it.
Um, anyways, uh, the kinectix experience tour, coming to your town soon, um, they are traveling around the country, um, on the east coast and on the west coast, showing off a bunch of different kinect games including kinectimals, kinect sports, kinect joyride, kinect adventures,
and Dance Central, the only game without kinect in the title.
And, um, they will be doing this, um, very close until launch of the actual kinect on November 4th.
So, some notable east coast, uh, locations, let's see, um, actually starting earlier of this, or, well, uh, yesterday and today, they were at Macy's!
You probably didn't see them because they were at Macy's, so, but if you-
I like Macy's!
If you just happened to go there, then you might have seen it.
Um, some other notable places, uh, August 4th through the 6th, they're going to be in Canton, Ohio at the Football Hall of Fame Rib Burn-Off.
Okay, well that makes sense, Football Hall of Fame, okay, that seems to be a good place to go, alright.
Okay, um, let's see, October, was it, uh, October 1st and 2nd, Orlando, Florida, the Disney Wine and Dine Marathon.
Disney has a wine and dine marathon? Is that like the wine thing they do at California Adventure?
No, I think that's, like, remember how Disney in, um, Orlando has a lot of those fancy adult places where you can go taste wine in fancy restaurants and shit like that?
Okay.
Yeah, there. Um, and then October 4th, 14th and the 17th, or through the 17th, uh, you can check it out at the Texas State Fair.
Or, October 21st through the 24th at the Louisiana State Fair.
Uh, what other state fairs are they going to be hitting up as well?
Uh, Minnesota State Fair, Tennessee State Fair, uh, I know the California State Fair.
Oh, my, I was going to say, really, because I'm like, the California State Fair is going on right now here in lovely Sacramento.
Are they going to be there, really?
Yes, July 28th through August 1st at the California State Fair. Almost worth going.
Almost. Almost worth going and getting subjected to getting shot by a gang. Almost.
Uh, also.
There's two things you can count on at the California State Fair. The smell of animal poop and gang shootings. Every year.
You know, this is a surprise to me, but I never knew that Minnesota was on the west coast, but apparently they're going to be at the Mall of America from July 15th to August 22nd.
That's a pretty long-ass time there. So, Mall of America, that's your place to go.
You'd think they'd have the parking lot of America to go with the Mall of America.
Exactly. Um, what other state fair? Colorado State Fair, Utah State Fair, New Mexico State Fair. They're going to be at the Universal City Walk on September 24th through 26th.
And, uh, October 7th through the 11th, San Francisco Fleet Week.
And, uh, oh, the Arizona State Fair.
So, yes, a bunch of different dates. They have it, actually. Um, you can check it out on, um, Facebook. Facebook.com slash connect or the Gamerscore blog.
Uh, they've got the dates posted there as well, or a lot of the gaming sites, too, in case you're interested in checking it out.
I might be interested in checking out the state fair, but, my God, it's a state fair and I have to go there and it's hot outside.
It's hot.
It's so hot.
It is. It's hot.
And, seriously, the state fair sucks.
Slacious Pop in chat is asking me, can we go this weekend and get deep fried foods and ride on Spin-A-Hurl rides?
And I'm like, honestly, my first reaction is like, no.
No, we can't. I don't know. I, the state fair is okay.
It might be neat to check out, but, honestly, um, Dance Central will be the only game I might be kind of interested in checking out, but.
How, how would you go? There's no way in hell you're going to be able to take the wife to the state fair. It's way too hot out.
I'll just convince the coworkers to go.
Oh, okay.
That's where I'd go myself.
I'll go with you, I guess.
I'm not going, dude. Okay, let me put it this way.
Let's break this down here. July 28th through August 1st.
There is a good percentage chance that the baby will be here by then.
I will not be going anywhere.
You're going to be too busy changing poopy diapers.
Jamie, save a Vicodin and then take it and we'll go.
If you pay for me to get in, I'll go.
Maybe.
Okay.
Do we still have OLR funds? Maybe the show can pay for us.
Um, yeah, it's sitting right there on top of.
We're on assignment. Alright, fine.
Rob.
What? And apparently Alan wants to go, so we could maybe do it next weekend. I can't go this weekend.
Well, next weekend I've got plans on Sunday.
But Saturday, Saturday afternoon, I don't.
July 28th through the August 1st.
Is next weekend, right?
We need to go on August 1st. You know why?
Why?
Because that's the last day of the fair and it's weird Al.
Uh, that's, it's, it's a week from next week from this upcoming weekend.
So August 1st is what, a Sunday?
It would be.
We have a show that night.
Uh, yeah, Sunday.
Well, it's the 28th though, that's like.
A show live from the state fair, is it possible?
Maybe.
No.
I don't think it is.
We can just record, ring the, I found the little recorder.
It's like, it's state fair, it's hot.
Look, there's a lot of things that I would call off a show for.
I've called off a show to go to Disneyland.
I've called off a show to go to various expos.
I would not call off a show to go to the freaking state fair.
Like, I just, it's just.
It's just too tacky.
I've gone to, um, what was it?
It was a, I don't remember what the fair was.
It was some sort of like rib cook-off and like country music fair thing that was down
by a Rayleigh Field to see rock band two.
And I did that one time.
I saw rock band at the state fair actually a couple of years ago.
Yeah.
Was that, that was the same night that I broke up with that asshole.
That was the same night.
Oh my God.
Wow, this show took a tumble.
Where's sad trombone?
Hey, next story.
Something a lot happier than horrible experiences at the state fair.
I saw a guy land on his head.
Hopefully, hopefully this won't be the same experience.
A haunted house.
This is an old ass Atari 2600 game.
An old ass Atari 2600 game that was out many years ago.
It's actually out on game room now if you want to re-experience it.
They call it the original survival horror game.
Not really.
No.
Basically you like could hit a button and make things illuminate around you and sometimes
scary things would show up like spiders and stuff.
But you were trying to collect things.
Well, they are completely revamping this game and it's coming out for the Wii, Xbox Live
Arcade and PC.
It's being developed by Imagine Engine who's a kids game designer.
And it's actually about the original character's grandkids going back to the haunted house
and it's basically kind of a very similar plot.
And I got to admit, looking at the graphics it looks very kid-ish.
But I guess it's kind of cool that they're bringing out the old games and making new ones.
I hope there's some other old ass Atari games that they maybe do this to.
But I don't know.
Maybe this is one of those games you might fire up once and go,
Oh, that's cute.
And then probably never play again.
Uh, they're actually...
Are there other ones they're talking about?
There's supposed to be other ones.
I thought I had heard something about that there were other games they were thinking about.
Centipede.
Really?
Yeah, I saw a game for Centipede.
I'm like, really?
Hmm.
What the hell are they going to do with Centipede?
I think this is not Frogger.
Human Centipede?
No, it's not Human Centipede.
Um, there was another one too.
I don't remember what it was.
But Centipede was one of the games.
It was also leaked out on Gamefly.
They had it.
Because everyone trusts Gamefly over me.
Sad days.
Alright, I think we need to move on with our show and get into the mailbag.
Every week you guys send us emails and we read them here on the program to our much amusement.
Mailbag at Orangelaunchradio.com and we're going to answer your questions that you've emailed us.
Mailbag at Orangelaunchradio.com.
Sometimes you guys share funny stories and things of that sort.
So, let's get to it.
Dark Soccer is going to read some emails.
Um, we've got three to go through and I'm going to start with the shortest of them first.
Well, kind of the second shortest but the other one's got some stuff.
Hey, OLR!
Pliskin here to ask a few questions.
First, if you could be in any video game, which would it be and why?
Um, if I had to, I'd be in Sims 3 so that I could have an infinity code so that I'd never get hungry.
Um, I could never age.
Never.
And I could decide how hot the person I want to look like and everything.
I would be in Animal Crossing so I could get rewarded with refrigerators and dressers and radios for running people's mail to the post office.
Loki.
Um, I don't know.
I wouldn't really want to be in any game.
Mega Man Universe because that looks retarded.
I don't know. I don't have a good answer.
I'd also want to be-
I know, Totem Ball because it is such an awesome game.
But you were in Totem Ball!
Oh my god! Mind blown!
Second, I know you guys bash-
Wait, wait, wait. I'd also want to be in Pokemon.
Just saying.
Okay.
Score it all. Score it all.
Second, I know you guys bash on Facebook Gaming, but believe it or not, there are some fun games on Facebook like My Hero's Ability and thousands of poker games.
So my question is what gives?
As in, maybe you're into those games, but I don't think we are.
I don't hate all Facebook games. Jamie, you admitted to playing one.
I played Farmville for like a week, okay? A moment of weakness. It was dumb. I was young and naive.
I think I played Bejeweled Blitz once.
Yeah, Bejeweled Blitz is cool.
Um, I don't hate on Facebook games a lot. I mean, I think the whole social networking gaming thing is kind of retarded.
And that's kind of stupid. It sounds like an old man saying,
Oh, get your fancy electronic shit. Um, but no, it's really, I don't understand what the point is. Like, hey, look, you know, hey, I sent you unicorn. Send me something.
I hate it when people send me shit in Facebook. I delete it. I do not forward anything.
I think that's it. It's not Facebook games we hate. It's Facebook games spam that we hate.
I'm all for free games. I just don't like the spam.
Yeah, that's annoying. Um, it's like those seriously, those chain mails where it's like, oh, send it to five of your friends and lucky things will happen to you.
Um, so I don't hate that. Oh, God, I had a point, but I totally forgot it was in arguing about how Facebook games are.
Um, oh, what was it? Oh, my hero's ability. Um, or whatever. That reminds me of like that Stephen Lynch song, Superhero, where he starts like naming off, you know, superheroes.
It kind of sounds like Pokemon.
Um, Monty Boggs, by the way, is also answering that question about what video game would you want to be in in our chat room at chat.orangehonstray.com.
I would want to be in Deal or No Deal. Constant money. There's a Deal or No Deal Facebook game.
I think that's the most pointless freaking game in the entire world.
I think they're all relatively pointless.
Guess the number, but like Deal or No Deal, especially. Guess the number. That's what it is.
But Rob, it's Howie Mandel. How can you go wrong there?
Don't get me started.
It's Howie.
Is there more to the email?
Yes, there is.
Yes, all right.
Stupid, stupid Facebook.
I am looking forward very much to the Civilization game on Facebook.
Because you're a Sith whore.
I am.
And how.
And how, and I can't wait to Sith whore it up with my friends on Facebook. Yay!
More!
Third is for Loki.
You know, I'm trying really not to be so grammar crazy and eh.
But.
This sucks.
Third is for Loki.
I found a PSP 1000.
I've owned a PSP 1000 for almost a year.
And now all of a sudden the D-Pad is freaking out.
All I want to do is go right dot dot dot.
I used an ellipse okay.
All by itself.
Now this wouldn't bother me, but it gives me vertigo when playing Dissidia Final Fantasy.
Cause the D-Pad controls the camera.
My question is can this be fixed or do I have to shell out money to be a new one?
To be a new one.
You want to be a D-Pad when you grow up.
Well we know what video game he wants to be in.
Um.
Yeah it can be fixed.
Because the D-Pad is actually on what they call a ribbon bus cable.
Which you cannot solder to unfortunately.
I've tried.
And it breaks it.
Um.
But all you have to do is buy the replacement ribbon bus cable.
Assuming that that's what's wrong with it.
So probably there's like a kink or something where something broke and so now it's just being held down.
It could be dirty.
You never know.
Um.
Basically you just have to bust the system open.
And possibly replace that.
Which those aren't that expensive.
You can probably get a set of ribbon bus cables for.
I think I bought one for ten to twenty dollars.
Maybe.
It should be really cheap.
Probably under fifteen dollars.
Um.
So that's all you need to do and you just slide it in there and put it all back together.
And it should work.
No guarantees though because I don't know if that's exactly what's wrong.
It could also be.
Um.
There could be some sort of bridging going on somewhere else in there.
It's hard to say until you bust it open and see what actually is broken in there.
But.
If it's.
If it's the actual D-Pad sticking.
Like the controller button is actually sticking down.
It's probably dirty and you just need to clean it out.
I've seen some friends with PSP's that I've fixed for them that are fucking disgusting.
There's just the amount of dirt and grime that's on it.
I just like.
What do you do?
Do you like seriously sweat grease?
I mean or sweat like.
Axle grease or something.
It's ridiculous the amount of dirt that's on there.
But yeah.
Cleaning.
Cleaning your PSP.
Try that at first.
If that still doesn't work then you may need to replace that ribbon bus cable.
If that doesn't work you're probably going to need a PSP.
Um.
I kind of agree with Legend of Zaku in our chat room.
PSP's D-Pad in general is ass.
They're better than the.
Um.
You know.
They're better than the Xbox 360 D-Pad.
Exactly.
That's for sure.
Alright.
You guys are being mean to the poor Xbox.
What else is new tonight?
Alright.
Was that it for that email or is there more?
Um.
Final question is for Rob.
How would I go about coming out to my family?
Wow.
Uh.
That's a bit of a tangent.
Um.
I.
Okay.
I'm a big fan of skywriting.
I can offer a resource.
Yes.
Please.
Um.
The um.
Human rights.
Um.
What's the name of the.
Their equality thing.
The human.
They've got the store in San Francisco.
Human rights campaign.
Thank you.
The human rights campaign has actually brochures and free material up on their website if you
do want to actually have something in writing, you know, by a psychologist and stuff.
So they do have resources there.
Uh.
Okay.
How do I tackle this question without taking 30 minutes?
Um.
Okay.
First off, if you need additional advice, send me a personal email.
Rob at orangehonestrager.com.
I'll address this off the air.
Um.
Because I really don't know anything about this listener.
I don't know how old you are.
I don't know what you're like.
If you have a hostile family situation or what's going on.
Cause I think different situations necessitate different responses.
Um.
I know there's a lot of push out there that say like, you know, come out, come out wherever
you are and all this stuff.
But I, I completely understand that sometimes that is not necessarily the answer.
Um.
At the end of the day, who you have in your bedroom is your business.
And I understand your desire to tell your family that.
And I think, you know, if you have that type of family, you should tell them that that's
going to be supportive and loving.
Um.
But there are sometimes some, some sticky situations.
So I don't know your family background or what have you.
My advice would be tell your best friend because your best friend will always be there for
you no matter what.
And if they run away because you tell them this, then they're not really your friend
to begin with.
And again, I don't know how old this person is.
They could be 15, they could be 30.
If you are younger, if you're still in high school, I honestly don't think there's any
rush because I think a lot of people in high school and even somewhat college kind of go
through that phase where, you know, they're not sure what's going on.
And I don't think there's any rush to label yourself.
But if you are, you know, older, experienced, whatever, and you know this is, this is it,
and this is the way it's going to be, then, um, you know, tell your friend first.
It'll be much easier to tell friend, friends.
And that way, if your family does have a negative reaction, you have some, somebody else you
can turn to.
Um.
I, I hope that you are fortunate to have a family that is loving and supporting and all
that.
And in most cases it will, but it would be disingenuous of me to sit here and say, just
tell them everything will be fine because in some situations it's not, but you know
your family better than I do.
So I guess that's really all I can say on that for now.
If you need help, um, contact one of the resources Jamie mentioned or email me directly.
Yeah.
Good job.
I hope.
Yeah.
I don't.
That's, that's, that's a challenging question.
I haven't been asked that in the eight years of doing this.
I don't think I've been told by people, you know, which is always a wonderful compliment.
It's an astonishing feeling, you know, like thank you for being, you know, out on the
radio and just, you know, being a guy who likes games, who happens to be gay.
But I don't think I've had that question.
Yeah.
But, um, thank you for asking because I think it takes a lot of guts to even type that out.
So please email me if you need it.
Um, this one's from Rababa.
It says, this is particularly for Jamie and he sends me a link from doitmyself.org of
a TARDIS cake, but it lights up and it's got the inside of the TARDIS through the window,
but it's a cake.
That is awesome.
And he concludes his email with, it's probably too involved for most, but it is cool.
I'm going to share the link with our chatters real quick.
I like the TARDIS made of cake.
I would eat that.
Delicious.
I think I just make a cake in the shape of a TARDIS, but I can't bake for crap.
I can't even make pancakes, right Rob?
That, that's awful.
Okay, last email.
Greetings, OLR.
Rini here.
A few episodes ago, you mentioned having a contingency plan for when Loki needs to care
for his newborn bundle of joy.
Although there is always the amusing chance that he may never be gone, I still would like
to suggest a host, a guest host, Scott Rubin.
I'm just listening to the guy, and I think he'd be doing OLR and his All Games fans
a favor by chiming in once with his thoughts on games and gaming news today.
Also, he would make this show run seven hours long and prompt everyone to call in sick due
to copious, but responsible amounts of drinking, perverted discussions, and not giving a fuck
in general.
I think I approve of that.
And since Dark Sakura and Sky recently purchased Team Fortress 2, I'd like to make a few
suggestions on classes since Sky isn't so hot with the aiming.
One, learn the maps with Medic.
You can learn where items and paths are while helping your teammates.
Overall, over-heal everyone, but focus on assisting those taking fire, and especially
do not be afraid to turn around and see what's around you.
If you unlock the Uber Saw, feel free to knife Uyghur classes to gain power for your Uber
Charge.
Two, try Pyro.
Can I say, I was actually thinking of being a Medic, because I'm always the White Mage
in these games.
Always.
Okay.
Two, try Pyro.
Incredibly helpful with this flamethrower because it can airblast to push enemies in
rockets, grenades, or slash grenades while putting out fires on teammates.
Be sneaky and use hit-and-run tactics to let the afterburn make enemies retreat, or at
least hold off them a bit.
If they're alone or weak, finish them off.
Always check for spies and never use the backburner.
That's capitalized never.
And that's capitalized always, by the way.
Three, try Engineer.
Build teleporters and dispensers to help teammates and play sentries where they can cover an
important point while being shielded by some part of the level.
Unlock the Wrangler and the Gunslinger to deploy many sentries for offensive play.
Don't forget hitting buildings with your wrench doubles their construction speed, and all
but the many sentries can be upgraded to level three.
If your buildings get sapped by spies, always kill the spy first and then get rid of the
sappers.
Don't forget that your wrench has a higher chance to deal critical hits than most other
melee weapons.
I was actually going to try Engineer because I found that they have now where you can move
your sentries around.
Your turrets.
Apparently everyone's playing Engineer because of it.
Yeah.
That's what I hear.
For more information and strategies, okay, I have to do the voice.
Ready?
For more information and strategies, I direct you to the official TF2 Wiki here.
Http colon slash slash wiki dot Team Fortress dot com slash wiki slash main underscore page.
Good luck and don't fail, dammit.
Rini is very excited to have us playing Team Fortress 2.
I've seen it on the Twitter as well.
I actually need to revisit it.
I didn't really touch it at all this week.
Well, I really haven't been able to do much.
Well, yeah, you got the hand thing going on, though.
Well, we still have to have our game.
We shook on it.
So whenever your hand's better, we're going to get on that.
Do you like my announcer voice?
I do.
I could do my wacky morning DJ voice, though.
Wouldn't that be fun to do an entire episode?
I can do the annoying female co-host voice.
Maybe for the next April Fool's show.
Oh, the Scott thing, too.
I think a lot of the All Games folks miss hearing him on the radio.
He certainly had a fun show.
He's not on the radio anymore?
Well, he does the Appaday thing now.
They're doing the TV thing.
Him and Diane Mizona do a show, which is kind of fun, that's online.
Well, I don't know. I'll hear about these random takeover shows,
but I don't think they're podcasts or anything because I never hear them.
So I don't think he's really doing radio frequently.
He's not doing regular radio.
I'm comfortable in saying that.
It would be awesome to have him on the show, but here's the biggest problem.
Having a co-host via Skype anything is going to suck.
And I realize other shows do it, and they do it really well.
But you have to remember, we've been spoiled over eight years
of being in the same room doing the show,
and I think it's honestly what makes our show different at the end of the day.
And I will tell you, the most fun I've had doing radio with Scott
was when we were in the same room, like the E3 Outpost
and the random times we dropped into All Games Interactive
and some of those things.
When they had that frat house, practically, in Santa Monica.
That place was fantabulous.
That place was fantabulous. It was like a frat house.
Good times. Good memories are had by all.
And sadly, that place doesn't exist anymore.
If you wanted to drive up to NorCal, though, hell, we'd host him in a heartbeat,
but I think he's probably busy with all his other stuff.
So, again, we don't want to be so quick like,
Gosh, Loki!
All we can do is sit here and talk about who's going to replace you for one week.
I don't even care.
I know, I know.
It's kind of one of those, we're just going to see who's available that week.
We'll burn that bridge when we get to it.
If we have to pick someone up off Skype, we will,
but we have got lots of great people.
I'm sure Alan could come back for a show.
Drew, you know, wants to do it.
It'll be done through an elaborate ceremony featuring roses.
Dan could do it. He's here.
That's because he lives here, Rob.
I think the chatters would love it if Extifer would come back for a night.
Maybe Irene. We'll figure something out.
You know what?
I really, I really, really, really would like for,
and Dan was actually excited about wanting to be on the show tonight,
but the family's leaving town.
But I think that we need to have Dan be a co-host for a night.
Well, maybe that'll happen.
I live with the man. He wouldn't let me live it down.
All right.
I mean, I love my husband.
Let's move on to the next email.
That was the email.
Oh, that was it? That was it? All right.
Mailbag. OrangeLoungeRadio.com if you want to send us your email in the future.
In the meantime, angst, hatred, boo, hiss, the FUs of the week.
FU to the absolute and utter pain that my hand is in.
Yeah, while I'm healing faster and I've got more range of motion,
it actually hurts worse, if that makes sense,
and the little tight stitches.
And I know it's all for a good thing and I'm very happy,
but FU to just being in pain and being tired all the time from it, too.
I'm really tired all the time and wanting meat,
and I'm not supposed to be eating meat.
So, FU to all that and FU to work stuff I've heard about.
FU to Apple for reasons I think I explained either on Bobby's show
or at the beginning of this show.
I can't even remember now. It was all blur.
FU to stress.
I bought a car this week, which is actually awesome and I'm happy,
but now I've got to get rid of the old car and that takes a lot of work.
So, yeah.
That's it.
FU to one particular person I saw driving on my way to the show today,
completely swerving all around the road,
and of course she was texting on cell phones.
Thank you, wonderful, reckless person.
Oops. Sorry.
FU to the fact I just started playing the credits music on accident.
And that's it.
Can I punctuate that? Can I punctuate that with something?
Sure.
Nobody's text message or phone conversation is as important as Elijah's
on the road around you.
Even my mother?
Even.
I think she'd disagree.
Rob, I have told my mother to get off the phone with me
if I found out that she was talking to me while she was driving
without hands-freezing.
I'm just saying. Is it okay if I'm stuck in traffic
because I totally texted you and Bobby today,
but I was sitting in stopped traffic and I was watching.
I think that's a little bit different.
Okay.
But there's people who do this crap while they're moving on the road,
and that's just not right.
Yeah. I'm not perfect, but safety first.
But you want everyone to think you are.
I know. Well, you know.
Well, no, I take that back. I am perfect, actually.
Rob.
All right.
Couple more stories for you guys, and then the Skype line.
Brace yourselves, 877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
Couple new stories real quick before we get there, though.
Loki.
I guess Kmart wants me to put reviews up for games.
Honestly, wouldn't have known that because I have not been in a Kmart in...
Yes, think about it.
Oh, God, at like ten years now.
So, yes.
You should go. It's fun.
And remember Kmart's one of the... on our Wiki.
It's a cultural experience.
It's like stepping back into the 80s.
It is. It is.
Hey, remember the 80s?
Remember back in the day when they used to have, like, those touchpad sensors for opening the doors?
It wasn't this fancy infrared.
It was, you know, you step on a sensor and...
Actually, I think you guys, Kmart has modernized a little bit.
I think they are right now somewhere around 93.
Eh.
Just so you know.
Rob, you're adorable.
I just want to let you know.
I know.
Um, apparently they are looking for reader reviews or I guess shopper reviews on different titles.
Um, they said, uh, one thing, uh, we'd like to feature your reviews on our shelves.
Um, it says, but at this time we will not be sending out free games for you to review.
Which is kind of funny.
Wait, what? So, like, on the shelf they'll have, like, papers with reviews printed out or something?
I guess.
What?
They're, um, they're basically looking for reviews, um, to help sell games, I guess.
So, we're supposed to help them market games.
But they're not going to publish the negative things then.
So, in other words, they will extract one or two sentences that are glowing about the game.
Like, you fucking kill zombies and it's rad.
Like, you know, or whatever.
They'll put that on a little tag next to the game.
Yeah, um, so you can go, like, uh, I guess re-register at MyKMart, um, I don't know, that's MyKMart.com.
People are gonna make shit up just to get their stuff in the store.
Dude, all you gotta do, Kmart, seriously, is do a little work, um, I don't know, go to Metacritic
and there's, like, a list of all these fucking reviews with little synopsises of each review
and little, like, blurbs and stuff that you can print out and put on your shelves.
I guess, or maybe that would be copyright.
Yeah, it might be a copyright thing.
Whatever, so.
Then put the Metacritic score.
That's what they do on Steam.
You can see the Metacritic score right there.
Unless it's, like, under a certain amount, then it's not, it's just not there.
Love it.
I don't, I don't understand.
Or have it on your website.
Have people review the, you know, stuff like Amazon or GameStop or whomever.
I think it's an interesting idea.
It's just a weird one.
You know what I mean?
Like, it's, it's interesting that they want to put people's reviews up there
and it's, I guess, to encourage a community type thing on the site
to get people, like, thinking about Kmart, because otherwise you don't.
Whoa.
Here's, my mind's blown here.
Apparently Kmart has blogs.
What?
Yes.
Get out.
MyKmart.com.
Do they blog about the coffee shops at Kmart?
No, apparently.
This Week in the Icy Machine, Blue Raspberry, yum.
Well, let's see, here's some wonderful, whoa, that's weird.
Here's some wonderful blog posts that we have going on here.
Some of these may even be slightly relevant.
Which way do you weed?
And this is talking about either using, I guess, a rake or weed spray.
Kevin Butler versus Old Spice, Old Spice Man.
Who wins for being, I guess, most infamous.
Gamer Chat number one was a success.
Thanks to all-
Wait, is this, like, only gaming stuff on the blog?
No, this is just blogs.myKmart.com.
They have Blue Light Special stuff.
They post Blue Light Specials on the blog?
Yes.
Attention, Twitter.
Blue Light Special on Pepperidge Farm cookies.
50% off.
Gamer Chat number one was a success.
I gotta read this.
Thanks to all who joined yesterday's, you know, pound, Gamer Chat Twitter event.
We had a spirited discussion about gaming,
including the best year for video games, people's first games,
and some of this year's surprises, both good and bad.
Oh, but if you weren't able to catch it yesterday,
you can download a, or you can check out a full transcript.
What are some of the topics that you'd like to discuss in the next Gamer Chat?
Oh, oh, wait, what's this?
I, they have a gaming blog, too.
Kmartgamer.com.
Are you a Kmart gamer?
Or, I guess it's blogs.myKmart.com slash games.
It's just, it's the same fucking blog with video game tags pulled out.
I see what you're doing.
They talk about, what's your backlog of games?
Oh my God, Kmart, you're so current with your blogs and fun stuff like that.
I have to shop at you now.
Kmart is awesome because most every Kmart I've been to totally ignores street dates.
Totally ignores them.
I bet if you went into Kmart and go,
yeah, I saw it on your blog and be like, huh, what's a blog, huh?
On the internet? What the hell's the internet?
That's witchcraft.
Did I tell you about the time that like Target was closed for like six months
and Walmart, I just, I wasn't going to go to Walmart.
So I actually went to Kmart to get like razor blades and it was the most like challenging.
First of all, they have them locked because, you know,
I guess there's rampant thievery of razor blades across the nation.
I had to track someone down to get a key and they give it to just like the old cragly lady.
Here's another wonderful topic.
What kind of razor blade did you want?
Did you want the Gillette Mach five or did you want?
I mean, just like, Oh my God, I want to die from June 23rd, 2010 fat guy in a little coat.
Biggest loser special.
You're talking about the biggest loser game.
Wow. My life is now complete.
Now that I have discovered Kmart has a blog, I will read it every day.
You know why? For sure.
Kmart updates their blog more regularly than any of us post on orangehoundsradio.com.
I don't care. Do you want me to post nonsense like this?
I will be happy to post nonsense like this.
I played that game. It was wonderful.
Go buy it at Kmart.
Look at me making a reference to it.
Would you please sign up for a Kmart account and start reviewing games?
I think we should all sign up for Kmart accounts and start reviewing games on there
with just like complete nonsensical reviews of things.
Like, you know, like, you know, I was sitting here on the couch and I was playing Naughty Bear
and it was fun, but I was sitting there naked and the dog came up and licked my balls.
So I think this game should be called Naughty Dog.
Like just these complete nonsensical things that have nothing to do with anything.
I would love that very much.
I'm sorry, Rob. My brain started to shut down when you started talking about that.
What you're describing sounds like a lot of effort.
I'm going to do it. I'm going to start a forum thread for awesome Kmart reviews.
And I want all the OL Army to post their awesome Kmart reviews and link them.
You mean like butt-tarded?
And just that they have to be like complete. But don't get yourself banned.
Don't say stupid shit. You have to say like really awkward things.
Basically you have to go on tangents a lot.
Just like us.
You'll be talking about your Red Dead Redemption review and then somehow talk about how you like horses.
And this one time you rode a horse and then it gave you like, you know, car crash or something like that.
Now that was terrible. But at least the horse's name was like, you know, Biscuit or something.
I was riding my horse Clyde and I skinned a horse in Red Dead Redemption that reminded me of Clyde.
And one time Clyde kicked me in the shin.
And it made me pee.
How about that?
Monty Boggs here. This is great. Now people are posting their reviews. This is great.
Alan Wake makes me want to buy Energizer batteries at Kmart. Buy Alan Wake at Kmart.
Alan Wake from Gamestop wasn't as good. That's pretty good.
Ray Ayanami says, great rail shooter. Now has anyone been far as decided to use even Go1 to do look more like?
I get it.
Let me try to read it again. That's awesome. That's an awesome review.
Great rail shooter. Now has anyone really been far as decided to use even Go1 to do look more like?
I love you guys.
That should be on the tag right there.
That about sums up what I think of Kmart in the reviewing.
You've been far as decided to use even Go1 to do more look like?
That's about right.
That's the point. Dark Dead Studio is like, I don't get it. That's the point.
Like he just he just threw a bunch of words together that make no sense at all.
And it's funny. And I'm laughing so hard. I'm crying. I can't stop.
Yet Dark Soccer is not like throwing up over there like the bad grammars.
She must be. No, because this is appropriately bad grammar.
OK. Like there is like little cats.
I didn't go around correcting the little cats. I pet them on the head and feed them fish.
All right. One more story for you guys and then we'll get to the calls.
1877 Game OLR username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
The Brick Theater in Brooklyn, New York is putting on some shows and they are video game inspired plays.
Yes, that's right. There's Grand Theft Ovid, which takes the Roman poets Ovid's songs and talks like integrates it with Grand Theft Auto.
Modal Combat uses guitar controllers. And I don't even understand this.
This is just like what? Let me let me look at the official website here.
Let me look here. Go into the Brick Theater website here.
Gameplay at the Brick is art playable.
Our video game cinematic is Mashima theatrical. Our smartphones a stage.
Is there an architecture that connects these diverse media forums?
What boundaries can be broken within and without the walls of an off off Broadway theater to change your reviews?
They're having. Rock band karaoke night.
Well, that's not a play. Baby Castles, Chiptunes Dance Party, Kool Aid Man and Second Life.
Theater of the Arcade, five classic video games adapted for the stage in this collection of short plays.
The creators of Brick hit suspicious package and this is stupid. Like what?
This makes no sense. It gets a Dan quote, Rob.
What? Really? That's Dan line.
You know what? I'm going to write a review of these plays and it's going to say great rail shooter.
Now, has anyone really been far as decided to use even go what to do look more like?
Because that's pretty much my reaction when reading this story.
One, eight, seven, seven. Game. O. L. R.
Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio. If you want to give us a call, we'll talk.
username is Skype is Orange Laundry.
The Skype line is now open.
Frisbee is asking what game should I review? You should review blur.
Frisbee, I'd like you to review the game blur. Let's go to the phones.
Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio. Who's this?
Hi, it's Ray Iannami. Hi, Ray. Good to see you yesterday at the show.
Yeah, it was really good to see you. Yeah.
So what's on your mind?
So for California Extreme, the games I'm looking for,
The Don't Bunch Diode 2, Blue Space Harrier, Red, among other things.
Wait, there was a space harrier there? There was a space harrier in the back.
Oh, I missed it. Fortunately, the person who said the machine forgot to put in an add a credit button.
So for instance, you had to put in a coin and take the coin out of the coin door just to start a game.
And the second day they closed the coin door. So you had to put it in a corner, which is kind of dumb.
Yeah, it was kind of bothersome when some of those games would run out of credits.
But you know, I can't hate because they're just arcade collectors and they're actually doing a favor,
putting their machines out there. They don't have to do it, so I try not to bitch.
But it was really frustrating when I wanted to play Tapper and it was out of credits.
It's like, wham.
So in other news, I've gone around to playing Deathmatch and Sin and Punishment 2.
Now, what was your real review of Sin and Punishment 2?
Because by the way, that was you I noticed in chat that has now spawned the new OLR quote.
Has anyone really been far as decided to use even Go What To Do Look More Like?
Well, it's actually an already existing Internet meme. I just thought I'd throw in some random meme to go with my review.
Did you bring 4chan to this show?
Maybe.
Oh, god damn you.
Well, I brought games back to the show.
Oh, okay. Whatever. No, I'm just fucking around.
Kids on the Internet are funny.
I've been playing Sin and Punishment 2 for the past two days.
It's pretty fun. It's a great improvement over the last game.
But I'm going to warrant anyone who wants to get that game even though it's not played the original.
It's fucking hard.
I see. Aren't most of those shooter games pretty hard?
Yeah, I mean, if people aren't too bad by real shooter standards, it's a bosses that get to me mainly.
I have to do a few tries if we get the patterns down so I don't end up bullshitting through a pattern.
And I've been playing Death Moth as well for the past two weeks.
And how's that?
So Death Moth, for those who haven't heard of it, is a side-scrolling shooter by Kave with gothic loli elements.
Awesome.
And that aside, I especially like this game. I love the fact that you can fire in both directions, which is a luxury that most side-scrollers tend to lack.
Like, you're stuck firing to the right, which is usually the direction you scroll.
And it's also much easier to play than other Bloodhog games.
Even with the in-game difficulty at the highest, I can get to the final stage easily.
But on other shooters, I usually end up only halfway through the game on my first credit.
Hmm. Interesting. You can get that far?
I thought that would be the harder game, because usually those, like, SHMUP games are impossibly difficult.
Death Moth, no, not that... it's not that hard, really. It's been one of the easier cases.
I play as opposed to the Donpax, which I play as much harder.
Alright.
They do call him Bullet Hell for a reason, though.
I fire bombs on the first spot of the Donpax Dial Joe, and that's not something I do in both shooters.
Like, I can easily get through the stage one boss of a vertical shooter just fine without using any bombs.
Okay. Okay.
Well, are there any other games coming up in the near future that you're going to be reviewing in the future on the show?
That you're looking forward to playing?
Um, I'm not sure, because I've spent a whole lot of buying new games until this mess up begins next month, because Death Moth and Standard Placement took a toll on my money.
I hear ya. Now I have a car payment, so I have to watch my gaming funding as well, so I think a lot of us are in that pinch.
Like, including tax, both of those games cost me $110, so I've already been waiting until this mess up begins, so I'll probably, I don't know, I'll probably pick up a person that's pretty portable.
Alright. Well, we gotta let you go so we can get some more calls, but thank you very much for your call, and we'll see you at the next big Bay Area expo, okay?
Okay, then. Alright.
Later.
Alright, 1877 Game OLR. Let's go to another call that's coming in right now. Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio. Who's this?
Uh, this is Recon Elite.
Recon Elite! Welcome to the show. Have you called in before?
Uh, no. I'm a long-time listener, but first-time caller.
I've always wanted someone to say that on this program. Long-time listener, first-time caller. Well, welcome! How you doin'? What's on your mind?
I'm doing good.
How can we help you? What's on your mind?
Yeah, I just wanted to know, um, I have a quick question. I don't know if you guys ever played it before, but Borderlands, what do you think about that?
Borderlands is awesome!
I have not played Borderlands, but I've watched someone else play it, and it kinda looks like, it has a really neat art style. It's kinda like Oblivion meets this very, like, post-apocalyptic kind of, uh, world. I don't know. Have you played this?
Okay.
With guns! And it's fun!
It's awesome.
It's hilarious.
I've heard a lot of great things about this game.
Totally get the Isle of Dr. Ned.
At least, though, you totally missed your opportunity to get it on Steam for, like, super cheap, because I almost bought it because it was down to, like, 20 bucks, but, unfortunately, the Uber sale's over. But, let me guess, you're probably gonna get it on console, huh?
Well, it was either one. It didn't bother me too much.
Oh, okay.
Well, the community was big, you know, as in playing it, because the last thing I wanted was to go online on it, and then nobody ain't there, you know. That was my fear.
You definitely would have people to play with there. And, you know, they've released several expansions for it. I've really heard nothing but good things about it. I just haven't had the time to play it myself, thanks to certain MMOs that I spend a lot of time playing.
That's wild.
Addict!
I say wow too all the time.
Okay, phew. Okay, then you understand what I go through.
Yeah.
But, yeah, no, I've honestly heard nothing but good things about the game. Here's a thought. If you want to try it out, here's what some people I know are doing. OnLive is this new thing that's out there, and you can sign, they're still doing sign-ups, and I just read something, like, it's extended through Labor Day.
You can try to get into the beta by signing up. Are you on OnLive?
Yes.
Okay, you can play demos of games. You can play the first, like, 30 or 45 minutes of a game without buying it, and Borderlands is one of them.
Oh, okay. Oh, that's a nice good suggestion.
There you go. Go on to OnLive. You know, I gotta say, as weird as I think the OnLive pricing, but here's my suggestion, don't buy it on OnLive, because the whole thing is that, yeah, it's cool that you're playing through another computer that has all the graphics and everything, but you're paying the same price you'd pay at retail for the game.
And it really is only guaranteed to last three years. If OnLive fails, you're going to lose that game. You're basically paying for a three-year rental. So, if you like the game, go get it on Steam.
Okay. Thank you.
That's my suggestion.
I just got one more quick question, and I'll hang up.
Of course.
Do you think Project Natal, what do you think about Project Natal? Do you think it's going to fail, or do you think it's going to succeed?
Well, keep in mind, we're all supposed to call it Kinect now, but I think it's a huge risk on Microsoft's part. A lot of it has to do with how they market it.
The Macy's thing, as much as we give them a hard time about who the hell at Macy's plays Kinect, we know exactly who they're going for. And, you know, all laughing and jokes aside, they're trying to appeal to Mom, or AKA Santa Claus, because they're going kind of directly to make their case there and show the games there.
That's a huge risk on Microsoft's part. I think the price point is everything. I think if they release this for $150, that's really $210 if you want a game.
And I think there's a lot of people that are going to run away from that, but if they can hit that magic number, $99, I think it'll sell twice as much, and it could be a success for them.
Got you. Okay. I just want to end it with that. Love the show. Keep it up. The good work, man. You guys are awesome. I love it.
We love the call. Thank you so much for your enthusiasm. You're awesome.
And thank you for saying the phrase that we've been waiting to hear.
I know. I've been waiting eight years to hear that. Longtime listener, first time caller.
All right. I got you.
All right. Take care, buddy.
All right. You have a good night.
Uh-huh. You too.
All right. Bye-bye.
Bye. That's how you know we're like legitimate radio now, because, you know, whenever you listen to a radio talk show, there's always that guy that calls in,
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Dr. Laura. Longtime listener, first time caller.
Love it.
I don't know why I named Dr. Laura, because she actually really sucks.
It means we've arrived.
It is. We made it. We made it. That decree meant something.
Now the Laverne and Shirley theme is going through my head for some reason?
We're gonna do it.
By the way, Gold Anthro in our chatroom at chat.orangelandradiocom is kind of offering the counterpoint to what I was just saying about Borderlands.
Meh, Borderlands just isn't the game for me. I played it and was like, this isn't as fun as it sounded.
So, you know, not everybody's a fan, so take that. But I think OnLive is going to be great for demos.
Like, even I have to pat myself on the back. I think that's a good idea to just go play the first 30 minutes of the game for yourself and make a determination if you want to play, you know, more.
All right. 1877 Game OLR, or our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio.
Loki, do you have any last minute stories for us?
Uh, sure do. Let's see, let's talk about this really funny hack that they have for Sonic the Hedgehog.
Sonic 2 XL, it changes the gold rings to onion rings and Sonic gets fat to the point if you eat too many rings without running around enough, you will just sit there and kind of die.
But he gets a big ol' potbelly. That's kind of funny.
And that's actually a real ROM hack. You can actually download the ROM that's available on the Sonic Retro forums, forums.sonicretro.org.
So check it out there.
Can I say this real quick? Because bonds006 in chat just spoke up and it reminded me of something he said earlier that I forgot to mention, but apparently he ran into like a New York Times reporter who was doing a story on DDR and BeatMania and stuff.
He totally pimped our show. Now that's a fan. Now that's a fan.
Thank you! We love you now.
I saw that in the chat.
Yeah, I forgot to mention it earlier. I was going to mention it after the iTunes review, but you know, I'm easily distracted by shiny things. So I apologize.
You may remember there's a company called Blick that puts out different gamer decals or vinyl decals you can put up on the wall. I'm using them in our nursery. But if you're not interested in New Super Mario Brothers or 8-Bit Mario or Donkey Kong, you can now get your hands on some Atari ones.
They have Centipede and Asteroids. And they're available for $45 for a full set. They are kind of expensive, but they're kind of neat if that's what you want to put on your wall.
Could have just done that for the baby room. Although I don't know, the Centipede one's a little creepy.
It's kind of dumb. Asteroids isn't bad. Centipede...
I think it's... actually are those up on ThinkGeek?
They've got 8-Bit Mega Man ones coming at some point. That's going to be awesome.
If I married a gamer nerd someday, you know, like, I think that would be an awesome addition for our house. Like, honestly, I think Dark Soccer should have that up in the vault. I think that looks kind of cool. Although, actually, the way the vault's designed, that wouldn't really work.
Dan and I actually did have a talk, because I'm sure I've mentioned it on the show before, before we were going to, you know, when we were talking about a kid, we were going to do a Mario theme. And Dan said, uh-uh, Sonic.
That'll be great, too, because at Loki's house, it'll be Mario, and then you'll have Sonic. What do I get, Crash Bandicoot?
Yes.
Crash Bandicoot? Crash Bandicoot was fun for, like, three games, and then they just totally, like, beat him into the ground. I'll get Kevin Butler.
Kevin Butler-themed nursery? That would be creepy.
Why is the baby crying all the time?
I don't know what's going on!
Anything else? Yes. Cave has announced two more SHMUP games coming out. They are going to be releasing, I guess, Gwanji on Xbox Live Arcade.
Or, I should say, yeah, they're going to be releasing that. What else are they releasing here?
Oh, here we go. Kai Katana, or Red Katana, is going to be a new Bullet Hell shooter coming out. I believe that's going to be on, I think, the download services, like Xbox Live Arcade.
And then for the iPhone, they're going to do Dondopachi Daifukkatsu.
Yay! I totally want Dondopachi on my phone.
And that'll be coming out of the iPhone this summer. So, that's kind of cool. Let's see. Screenshots here of, uh, that's a private video. Well, fuck you, I don't want to read it then. Or watch it, whatever.
Apparently, Amazon Germany has listed a Xbox 360 4GB arcade system bundle. Of course, they've already announced that they're going to be doing some sort of arcade system this fall in the US and other territories.
But now we kind of have an idea of what it's going to be. It's going to be probably that slim down system without a hard drive, but a 4GB memory stick, or not memory stick, USB thumb drive that you're going to be able to use with it.
And that's fine, since, remember, you can actually put in your own laptop drives into the Xbox 360 S, or whatever the hell you're going to call it, just like you can on a Playstation 3.
That's kind of neat, I guess. But that'll be available this fall. It looks like it's going to be, well, right now it's listing at 148.99 euros.
So, um... I believe that's it.
I think Apple needs to work on, I don't know, making the iOSes work on their phones first.
I'm raging because I have a 3G, and the iOS 4 upgrade just borked it, and it kind of was pointed out to me, and I think it was a very good observation that they do this to make me upgrade, and it stinks.
That's all I'm saying.
And I know, then I shouldn't get an Apple, I shouldn't buy an iPhone, I shouldn't support them. Maybe I won't! I don't know.
No, we all know I'm going to get that shiny, white, new iPhone, because I want it.
Alright.
ST100Matt is currently working on a Kmart review, I'm so excited.
Okay, that's it, though, for the show now.
Thank you guys so much for tuning into our show, and listening to us, and downloading us, and supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
We can't do it without your support, you know, we don't have massive advertising or anything like that, it's really word of mouth, and the awesome reviews you guys do, and telling reporters and shit about us, that is word of mouth at its finest.
Thank you guys so much, we so appreciate it, and you guys are the reason we come back week after week, and don't let the State Fair distract us from doing a show.
Alright, but Disneyland might, I'm just putting it out there.
Alright, anyhow, for now, though, we're going to go around and give everybody's final thoughts. Uh, Loki, why don't you start us off tonight with your final thought?
I want to make some of these custom Mario Kart tracks for the Wii. They look fun.
And I can make some pretty killer tracks, probably.
My final thought is, my server on WoW is scheduled for 24 hour maintenance this week.
Nooooooo! Just kidding, I'm going to play lots of Team Fortress 2, and Left 4 Dead 1, and these other games I've been meaning to play forever.
Dark Soccer, your final thought?
My Sim's house is freaking gorgeous.
You've put a lot of flowers in it, it's a very girly house because you have flowers everywhere.
Well, it's not very girly, it's this one part of it that's set up as a wild flower garden.
And those are totally Sakura trees, aren't they?
Yeah, they are. But the rest of the house is very sort of neo-modern, and my house floats. We all float here.
Alright, that's it. We're tuning out and signing off. Thank you guys so much again for your support. We'll be back to do it all again next week.
We'll see you next week with more of Orange, unless Loki's wife has the baby, then he won't be here.
Because that could happen at any time, so stay tuned.
I hope she doesn't have anything.
Yeah, well that's true. She's still got what, another month, right?
Preferably at least two weeks.
At least two weeks, alright then. So hopefully two more weeks of Loki at least.
Alright, but that's it. Have a wonderful night everybody. We'll see you soon next time here on Orange Lounge Radio. Good night.
See you next time.