[SPEAKER_06]: Tonight, December 27th, 2009, Pac-Man might soon fight at Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_06]: Could your portable games soon be banned on airplanes?
[SPEAKER_06]: Can we take a look back
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are live with our 350th episode on this lovely Sunday evening, December the 27th of 2009.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, we're here for the holidays.
[SPEAKER_02]: Broadcasting live every Sunday night, www.allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're an All Games Radio affiliate and we are very thankful that they let us steal their bandwidth every Sunday night to do our little program.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joining you over the next few hours, myself, Rob Roberts, and of course the one and only...
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie Summers, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why we're not hearing you at all tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the wonders of live radio, is that sometimes you get technical difficulties, things happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes people play with my volume, apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what's up with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think what's going on is that behind our backs, DarkSakura has been secretly taping another show.
[SPEAKER_02]: No!
[SPEAKER_02]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he's just screwing with some of the audio settings.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't touch Loki's.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I don't know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Try again, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we'll hear you now.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, now we hear you too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's really loud.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we're good now.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you have a good holiday?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did Santa bring you lots of good stuff for the holidays?
[SPEAKER_03]: Pots and stuff to do yard work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, Santa brought you pot?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, like pots and pans.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's in time for New Year's, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I also pre-ordered... I hate the word pre-order.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I just ordered my copy in advance of Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_09]: And apparently if you do the order through Amazon or through I guess any of the others, you'll get like a thing to do the beta.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm going to be in the beta.
[SPEAKER_09]: When's the beta start?
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's so many like... January something, something-teenth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Closed beta and open beta and retweet to get in the OMG right now betas.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's so many betas going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel like I'm in the 80s all over again and VHS is just around the corner.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's January something-teenth.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's so helpful.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I also got... Dan picked up for me...
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, by the way, it has to be the collector's edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, for you to get the beta?
[SPEAKER_09]: To get the beta.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which is what I got.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is what I imagine a lot of people are getting anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Dan picked up for me the Silent Hill game on Wii, so I need people to come over and hold my hand while I play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I watched a friend play that game a couple days ago, and it was very strange.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw the nightmare sequence happen, and it's weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't get all rusty, it's just snowy in that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was just running through doors, over and over, running through doors, running through doors, running through doors, trying to avoid zombies.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, this is...
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't really run.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you do run in Silent Hill, but this felt like an action game or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was strange.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't play it, I watched.
[SPEAKER_09]: It shatters your memories of Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_03]: You have a bug about to crawl into your hair behind you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gross!
[SPEAKER_03]: Our studio's infested!
[SPEAKER_09]: It is not infested.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's a tissue, you big baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's bugs in our studio!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, is that what you plan to end the decade with?
[SPEAKER_02]: Killer bugs?
[SPEAKER_02]: Destroy the host?
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob, it probably snuck in through the window.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, kill it, you big baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, I'm going to take a picture of it to show the listeners how big this scary bug is.
Fuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make sure to zoom in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else for your gaming week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_09]: I played the game where I laugh about Rob being a big baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up, it's a big scary bug.
[SPEAKER_09]: We also played some Marvel Ultimate Alliance 2, which was really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I upload this to the feed, it's going to look like a big poop on your curtain.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just kill it already, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it a pincher?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to kill it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It better not.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it pinches, I'm going to scream.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Give me the napkin.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hold my mic.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura saves the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: I should just let it do its thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a scary bug!
[SPEAKER_02]: But pinchers pinch, that's why they're called pinchers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now that our show has been sufficiently derailed for the decade, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't play a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played more Grand Theft Auto this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, what little I could.
[SPEAKER_03]: It went crunch.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I brought my 360 home hoping to play more stuff, but I just didn't because I ended up messing around with other things.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I played a little bit of Little Big Planet, the new Pirates of the Caribbean water stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not as exciting as, you know, the Paintnator, but, you know, how can you top guns?
[SPEAKER_03]: You just can't.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's pretty...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess I did at some point so that's kind of neat but I was going to play also Mod Nation Racers and granted I did all this like an hour before the show so I meant to play Mod Nation Racers as well because I'm in the beta for that however since I haven't played LittleBigPlanet in forever I had to download the updates which took 15 minutes oh jeez yeah I can imagine so I was just you know what hey props to them because that means they have just been putting update after update after update on that game you know tons of updates yeah
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I think the last time I downloaded the update was update 1.05, and they're up to 1.23 now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a bummer, though, it's not smart enough to just go, okay, I'm going to download the patch that takes you from 1.05 all the way up to, without having to download five patches in between.
[SPEAKER_03]: Something like that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes PC games do that, especially MMOs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sonic!
[SPEAKER_03]: Sonic, yes, perfect example.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the Pirates of the Caribbean stuff's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: The characters, obviously, they don't really have anything that looks too much like the stuff in the movie, but the same typical plot.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have the two royal guards or whatever, the
[SPEAKER_03]: Imperial Guards or whoever they are from the movie are in there and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I only got to play the first level though before I wanted to move on to other things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then I actually played a little bit on the arcade cabinet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had a friend over and we were testing out my...
[SPEAKER_03]: Newly souped up joysticks because I added octagonal restrictors in them now and also tighter springs.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did everything except for take apart the actual push buttons to put the little paper in there and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, I just don't want to mess with that because I have a feeling it's going to fall apart after a while and it's enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: so uh played Marvel vs. Capcom 1 and uh I'm not very good at it I like Marvel vs. Capcom 2 but I you know I couldn't figure out why I didn't have it yet and it's because I don't have any Naomi games yet and so that's what I basically spent most of the holiday doing was downloading Naomi games and downloading um you know Sega Model A games and you know Zinc Emulation games and all sorts of crap um
[SPEAKER_03]: to put on the cabinet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and CPS3 stuff, so I have Street Fighter 3 and JoJo's Bizarre Adventure and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyways, actual game, though, I did play.
[SPEAKER_03]: We played all the way through Simpsons, the arcade game on MAME, so that was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love playing through that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know there's a Simpsons arcade on iPhone now, but it's not even the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just the same name, and I think it's definitely inspired by the old arcade game, but it's not...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love playing the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had a lot of fun playing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to think of other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were just trying a bunch of random games on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: MissWorldNude96 didn't play that but the problem is, see right now I'm going through my list of games I have on there because there's a ton of games, first off clones that I have on there that I need to get rid of and I got rid of them on one list but I need to get rid of them on the list that's for my front end so that they don't display on there and then also a whole bunch of Mahjong games and crap I'm not going to play so I have to go through and delete all that stuff or stuff that just doesn't work um
[SPEAKER_03]: You sound like me trying to organize my iTunes library.
[SPEAKER_02]: a friend of mine inspired me to organize my iTunes a little better and I've been trying to do that and it is a mess like I have all these misspelled artists and albums and trying to get the right album art and things from compilations and it's a pain in the ass it sounds very similar just what you're describing is going through that whole process
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so it'll be nice when it's done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially, I'm really excited to try some of these new Naomi games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because a lot of them don't necessarily work.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you have one emulator for Naomi disc-based games and Dreamcast games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you have another emulator for Naomi cartridge games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And some of those work and some of them don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of the ones that will work, though, like Ikaruga, Marvel vs. Capcom 2...
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some I haven't even heard of before.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like a lot of these really crazy shooter games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, you know, just some of the normal ones like Senkei no Ronde or Rondo, I believe, in...
[SPEAKER_03]: Radio Allergy or Radigy or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of the cave shooters and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that would be kind of cool to put in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially now that I have the heavy springs on the joysticks for really twitchy movements and stuff that will really come in handy for shooters and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, just lots of downloading stuff for the cabinet.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's mainly what I've been doing during the break and a little bit
[SPEAKER_03]: I still haven't played Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, I'm gonna play Borderlands this break!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm gonna do it!
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't done it yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I even brought home, like, Bayonetta.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, oh, I'm gonna play Bayonetta.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I have, um... What was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oto... Was it Otomedius?
[SPEAKER_03]: Gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Konami shooter that has, like, chicks flying around.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was gonna play that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, uh...
[SPEAKER_02]: Just didn't get around to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_09]: One of my friends actually did some testing for a while.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, I'm so sick of playing soccer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Testing or reviewing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, sometimes, you know, that, God, that's a discussion for a whole other show.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was even trying to get into strategy guides.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, like, they'll have you review, like, they'll just play through some of the most meh games, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still want to do that, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else you wanted to say about your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, that's basically it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just lots of downloading stuff, and I'm sure none of that's legal because, you know, they're ROMs and, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not going to go buy multi-thousand dollar worth of arcade boards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going to our chat room, the always present fourth guest on the show, and if you are listening live to us on All Games Radio on this lovely Sunday evening, head on over to our chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com is the easiest way to get there, or if you know your IRC, you just want to join the Game Surge Network on IRCGameSurge.net, and we are in Channel Pound Orange Lounge is the name of our chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, reading some comments from chat, it went all the way back up here, talking about...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Tigerclaw had said that it's appropriate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a way to start the last show of the new year or decade with a bug.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going back to the bug.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you know how sometimes music will sometimes play when it's not supposed to here on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's, whoops, live radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the joys of live radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also reading some comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ray Iannami in our chatroom says, PS, get your asses to SVGL, Sunnyvale Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a Simpsons machine here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's interesting?
[SPEAKER_02]: There is Simpsons machines kind of still out there all over.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw one randomly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was at this hotel near Disneyland staying.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a game room in the hotel.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't seen a game room in a hotel that wasn't a casino since I was a teenager.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been a very long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the first times we went to Disneyland, there was a hotel that we stayed in that had a game room and I'd go down there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wonder if it was the same hotel.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might have been.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was near the convention center.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember?
[SPEAKER_02]: You probably don't even remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the convention center wasn't built when I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the Simpsons arcade game, obviously, a lot of people really remember this.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's still in arcades and probably still freaking makes money.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, this machine at this particular hotel, their game room was in pretty sad shape.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like half the machines weren't working.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the Simpsons one was, but it was where the monitor was like...
[SPEAKER_02]: So bright you could not like it's just faded over time, but it hasn't faded dark.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's faded light.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure what causes that maybe sun fading or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: They probably in the dark room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it probably what happened was it burned in and they just turned the brightness up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see to try and avoid that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: My gaming week, some of the things I played this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did play a couple new games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously Steam is having an obscene sale right now as DarkSakura mentioned earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: She picked up Braid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I picked up Luminous because the basic and advanced pack were on sale a couple days ago for $3.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was like, what the hell, I own Luminous on just about every other platform.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll get it on PC as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the same game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It certainly plays better than the iPhone one, although I still think...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Other stuff I played this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Saw a demo for a game called Crayon Physics, which was also on Steam.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a very DS-inspired game because you would basically have this little ball on your screen that you had to get the ball to the star.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you did that by drawing ramps.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or it was kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might have a little...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: But certainly, you know, not everybody owns a DS, but a lot of people own a PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is a way for you to get into those kinds of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I felt the game was a little basic.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the music was kind of crack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, it was really, like, trippy, scary almost, how happy trippy it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a little bit frightening.
[SPEAKER_09]: Best description ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Happy trippy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Happy trippy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's actually going to be 2DX 19th style or whatever they're up to now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Happy trippy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura holds up the thumb hat as she's talking there so happy trippy thumb hat 2DX19 style let's see what other games did I play this week Tekken 6 I checked out for a little bit I have to admit my reaction to Tekken 6 after having spent a little time with it is lol what like that was honestly pretty much the reaction I had every few minutes we were playing Tekken 6 lol what
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude is wearing pink pants and shoots electricity out of his hands while he's standing in water.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lol what?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a giant transformer guy who shoots laser beams into the floor that makes me fall through and I instantly lose.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Last Boss Looks Like Zombie, Big Bird, 8, like Raw from Stargate, and is glowing blue.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lol what is this game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Did we have any Voldo?
[SPEAKER_09]: Mr. Bondage Crotch?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's 40 fucking characters in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know, Tekken has obviously been lol what for a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's had the panda bears and the kangaroos.
[SPEAKER_09]: Voldo was so caliber, but I know that they brought in...
[SPEAKER_09]: Like some of the really weird ones.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, of course, anything with Yoshimitsu in it's going to be... The training dummy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you play as Panda?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't play as Panda.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played with my favorite tranny bitch, Anna Williams.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I'm telling you, in Tekken 6, she is one fierce transsexual.
[SPEAKER_02]: No dis... Obviously, I mean no disrespect.
[SPEAKER_02]: She just looks like your stereotypical, like, wearing all the leopard stuff and the boots and all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she just... Like, literally, one of her moves... You know how everybody has a throw?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: Angel, Angel, Angel
[SPEAKER_02]: from like 1981 where she's a prostitute by night and an FBI agent by day.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the best way I could describe Anna Williams.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lol what?
[SPEAKER_02]: So that was pretty much my review of Tekken 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I thought it was interesting that in certain parts of the game if you're playing offline mode it kind of simulates an online mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'll be playing against people with these fake gamer tags that you're playing for promotions and
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: The game is actually a lot more deep than I'm giving it credit for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep in mind I only looked at a couple modes on this particular outing with the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't really get too in-depth with the game, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lol, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, AlphaCanadagram in chat says, Sky, it's ghost data of players.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of strange to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, are they actual real people?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I saw, like, at signs and other signs I didn't think you could have in your gamer tag as part of the...
[SPEAKER_02]: What if I don't want my...
[SPEAKER_02]: Ghost to be online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hitstun says, pretty cool, but they really only copy the user's combos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which really is what Tekken's all about.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's not, you know, Tekken is not the fighting game with fireballs and, you know, all these insane moves.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really, there's only low punch, high punch, low kick, high kick.
[SPEAKER_02]: And those are pretty much all the buttons you use to do everything in Tekken.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you just string all these combos and juggle, etc., etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: Alphacanatagram also adds in Tekken 6 has been in arcades for years, so they get data from arcade machines.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess having that kind of come to light, obviously the game doesn't explain that to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I find that feature to be very interesting, but it doesn't really change my little what reaction to the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, other games I played this week A lot of World of Warcraft still I already have a level 80 character I've had one for a couple years But now my new character I'm trying to get to 80 My paladin, my dwarf paladin She is level 78 Two bubbles away from 79 Very, very close to level 80 And I'm excited because I'll actually be able to use the new dungeon finder with that Hold on, I've got something for you guys Oh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, fill time
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I was going to actually mention something about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of Warcraft and all this stuff, I don't usually listen to other podcasts, and I've kind of talked about why on the show before.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean obviously I listen to Bobby Blackwolf because he's live before we are, and I listen to most of his show because of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't want to inadvertently take ideas from other shows or what have you and all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my gosh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura's handing out presents.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, I'll open that in a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: But on Christmas Day, Scott Rubin, who's the ringleader of AllGames.com, if you weren't already aware, was doing like a marathon live show.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was live for like five or six hours that day.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I actually called him and talked to him for a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty sure it'll be archived on AllGamesRadio's site.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: We talked a long time about digital distribution.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he's very pro-digital distribution.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had a little lively debate about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: but I tuned in later on the iPhone app in my car because I was driving to San Francisco Christmas night and I wanted to listen to more like talk radio I thought would be good for the drive but he wasn't on anymore instead this other program was on uh talking about nothing but World of Warcraft and uh it's called the Warcraft Outsiders which I think is a spin-off of Video Game Outsiders another um all games radio program on the network I have to say you know I
[SPEAKER_02]: As much as I don't often listen to other podcasts, I thought they did a pretty good job.
[SPEAKER_02]: They knew their stuff talking about Warcraft, and I thought it was interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Since I play the game all the time, I wasn't hearing a lot of news that I didn't already know, but I kind of liked hearing about their experiences.
[SPEAKER_02]: The gal they have on that show, I think her name is Michelle, was kind of like the ringleader of that show, at least the particular episode I was listening to.
[SPEAKER_02]: She knows her shit on Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was...
[SPEAKER_02]: Very impressed.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's a pretty hardcore raider and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a good show, so I wanted to give them a shout out because we don't often give the other all games radio shows enough shout outs here, but we are all about supporting other independent radio and independent podcasts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because I say I personally don't listen to a lot of other podcasts doesn't mean you shouldn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should go out there and support all the other podcasts out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially if you decide Orange Lounge Radio is not your cup of tea, I bet there is another show on the network.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is their cup of tea, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Open present?
[SPEAKER_02]: Me first or Loki first?
[SPEAKER_09]: You've got your card, so go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: La la la card.
Crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a card and on the tree it says, wow, those are some really big balls.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the guy says, thanks.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it says, have a great big Merry Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_02]: The tree had big balls on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just fucked up my little hat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I'm going to open up this box.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to ruin it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a box, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: It costs a dollar.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is terrible radio, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm opening a box, folks.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's not a dick in a box.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a... Oh, cool!
[SPEAKER_02]: World of Warcraft Year of Here.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a...
[SPEAKER_02]: A 365 day calendar, I'm assuming Like a desk calendar That shows little locales in the world of Warcraft I will totally take this to work and they'll really think I'm a freak It'll be awesome
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why I bought it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Great, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: For people to think you're a freak.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like on Tuesday, the 26th of January, there's a little picture of the Violet Hold.
[SPEAKER_02]: On Thursday, the 8th of July, there's a picture of Icecrown Citadel.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just have all these little pictures from around Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I saw it and I thought you'd appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a vast world in Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's one of the reasons to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Open your box, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: My card says bacon.
[SPEAKER_03]: How'd you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's a dog jumping up and down because he got a box full of bacon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hope you get just what you're looking for this Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that what you got?
[SPEAKER_02]: A box full of bacon?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Open your box!
[SPEAKER_09]: What's in the box?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do it!
[SPEAKER_09]: What's in the fucking box?
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell me what's in the box!
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki's opening his box very slowly.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, Rob, did you see the thing that I posted on Facebook earlier?
[SPEAKER_09]: The 30 seconds of...
[SPEAKER_09]: of Lich King.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got the Worst Case Scenario Daily Survival Calendar 2010.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Day-to-day guide to surviving a year's worth of peril.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't this what inspired your old advice column you used to do?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I used to have this calendar a few years ago and I remember just cracking up on a daily basis and I figured that, look, you would appreciate some advice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, how to deliver a baby in a mall.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: How to control a runaway camel.
[SPEAKER_09]: How to navigate a minefield successfully.
[SPEAKER_09]: and How to Drive Santa's Sleigh.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you can find some old ass episodes of our To Go show, which I think was around 2005, 2006, when we first were getting into podcasting, we would do like a three to four hour live show, then record another hour that was separately podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: We merged the shows finally, got smart and merged them together finally a couple years later.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you can find some old episodes of the To Go show, it was really funny because DarkSakura had these little advice columns that were like,
[SPEAKER_03]: They have some pretty appropriate stuff, like for example, New Year's Day.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's essential survivor knowledge, appropriate attire for winter weather.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really, this should be the date before.
[SPEAKER_03]: How to carry someone who is passed out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Very useful.
[SPEAKER_09]: I freaking love worst case scenario, so I thought that maybe Loki would too.
[SPEAKER_03]: How to deflect encounter or sword blow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it was either that or I was trying to decide who I was going to give the bitch a day calendar to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does it actually have 365 bitches on it or is it like complaints?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like those magnets that you have the one that says remember when fat butts were in style or the I'm having screaming PMS with a really happy looking 40s chick on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was all stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: How to land a runway hire balloon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just in case.
[SPEAKER_02]: You never know, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Might need it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ranma in chat is bragging he has all of the OLR2GO podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought there was an archive online somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know there's like – and DarkTetsuya is talking about the descriptions on the wiki.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I haven't talked about this a lot on the show, but on wikia.com, there's actually a whole Orange Lounge Radio wiki that you can look up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it actually has like descriptions of –
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's the baby on your screen right now on Facebook?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's our friend Megumi's baby, Luke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aww, that's cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's cute, and it was great radio, but... Although that reaction is somewhat like, did you ever see Batboy on the World News cover?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: With the face?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's just a cute little baby yawn.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, let's get into some housekeeping real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, we're on Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: We also have a Facebook now, facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should definitely follow us on those sites.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we will still be here live next Sunday and the Sunday after.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do not know yet what the plan is for the show on January the – I'm looking at my calendar here – January the 17th.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hear there's a best of in the works, so maybe that'll finally be ready by that week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, start us off tonight with some news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Capcom has decided to pull a few games from their Quarter 1 2010 lineup, including Super Street Fighter 4, Lost Planet 2, and Monster Hunter Tri.
[SPEAKER_03]: And from what I've seen, they haven't really announced yet when they're going to...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and they said they're planning on spreading them across all four quarters which makes sense if you think about it because Capcom usually front loads the first part of the year with their games and I'm sure that a lot of the stuff that they put out ends up competing with itself so it kind of makes sense that you would want to spread that out and they still do have some stuff coming out in the first quarter they have Tatsunoko vs. Capcom Ultimate All-Stars and of course Dark Void coming out as well and that's not even including the
[SPEAKER_03]: Other things that they're planning on releasing digital distribution-wise, including Mega Man 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of stuff coming out still.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still a little bit disappointing, though, because when I read the article, what you say makes a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't want to load the year too front-heavy, I guess, for lack of a better term.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there were some big, like Super Street Fighter 4, I had the feeling we were going to be playing it come February or March.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still think we may.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still think it may come out in April or May, not
[SPEAKER_03]: Dead Rising 2 is still at some point, but they have a pretty big slate of games coming up this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Not putting them all out at the same time Lots of games got delayed
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, a lot of it's because of Modern Warfare 2, and a lot of people were afraid to kind of take on Modern Warfare 2, and so they've delayed their games to other parts of the year, which is fine, because I think that's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Normally, we get these really dead months where there's nothing coming out, and I'm like, you know, hey, it'd be the perfect time to put this game out, because there's really nothing competing with it right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, April, I mean, most of April's gonna be pretty dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you're gonna have Red Dead Redemption on the 27th, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: As far as I'm aware, there's normally not much coming out in April.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't that kind of traditional, though, that not much comes out around that time?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that's when you're starting to get into finals and college, which is your big gaming base.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't care about that kind of stuff, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't think that kind of stuff cuts into sales?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't think it really matters.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's just development cycles.
[SPEAKER_03]: And really, a lot of the stuff, they try to push it out before the end of March.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't Final Fantasy XIII April?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or is that March?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's March.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, my bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Final Fantasy XIII is the beginning of March, but that may be another reason too why some of these delays are happening, because if they're coming out around the same time as Final Fantasy XIII, maybe that's another... It's not as big as Modern Warfare 2, but it's going to be pretty big.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's a completely different audience, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, the kind of people that play Final Fantasy XIII aren't going to play these other types of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, well, you know, there's always somebody that plays both.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Monster Hunter, I think, kind of, you know, it's a little similar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I could see that kind of having some similar crossover.
[SPEAKER_03]: Street Fighter, yeah, not much of a crossover there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But still, though, it's, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a very similar strategy to how they do movies, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Yet, or it has been announced, I'm kind of surprised there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would have thought maybe Crackdown 2 might be coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or hey, even, you know, maybe, what was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't remember the name of the game now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's all right, because I'm not buying it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other Microsoft, Alan Wake, that's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: The one that's been delayed forever, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It probably won't be that great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it looks all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess it's good that they're delaying stuff just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: It kind of sucks because they have to lower their projections for how they're going to finish up their 2010 financial year, but
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: and um you know I don't think this year is going to be different obviously we're going to have another Call of Duty game and some more Guitar Hero games and some more DJ Hero and who knows what hmm
[SPEAKER_02]: It's definitely going to be a busy year next year, but then I wonder how much we're going to hear next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Delayed again, delayed again, lololol.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's going to be a lot of stuff that's delayed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Natal delayed, Sony Motion delayed, hahaha.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the other thing too, there's a lot of that stuff coming out, you know, kind of in the, I want to say it was supposed to be the second quarter, and maybe some of these games are going to use some of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe they're delaying it because of that, or maybe they're going to delay them to add that kind of stuff, or maybe...
[SPEAKER_02]: Pac-Man Battle Royale
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't know what the heck that could be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could that be a fighting game involving Pac-Man?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: We had a bunch of copies of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember how, maybe a chatter remembers this better.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had a stack of them and we're giving them out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but you had to get a copy of it somehow.
[SPEAKER_02]: You probably had that because of Game Store connections, but there was a way you were supposed to get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if it was like a pre-order bonus or what.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, who knows what this game could be all about, but of course when I hear Pac-Man Battle Royale, I don't know about you guys, but I think about the old Japanese movie where they might strand Pac-Man on a desert island with his peers and give him only a fan to survive.
[SPEAKER_09]: Paper plate.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be pretty amazing if that was actually the case, but I somehow doubt that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, I've won Paper Plate Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just can't see an M-rated Pac-Man game for the life of me.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although it would be funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, how about something that is a little bit more on the mature level, even if it's not M-rated?
[SPEAKER_09]: My single favorite Castlevania game ever, Dracula X Rondo of Blood, is coming to Virtual Console!
[SPEAKER_09]: It's about damn time!
[SPEAKER_09]: But, um, guess where?
[SPEAKER_09]: Australia.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hence my comment before the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: which only they heard if you're live tonight but that's alright which is very interesting because Australia has been getting a lot of bad news lately as far as video games go so this is kind of interesting the OLFC actually has a rating up for as it's titled Castlevania Rondo of Blood for virtual console release I hope that we get it over here but I don't know
[SPEAKER_09]: It's such a fun game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I hate having to break out the PC Engine every time I want to play it or try to find the PSP version.
[SPEAKER_09]: Honestly, I still prefer the PC Engine version over the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: If this game were to come out on Virtual Console, wouldn't it be the first PC Engine CD game to do so?
[SPEAKER_09]: Didn't we get Ys?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, I've got Ys Book 1 and 2 on CD.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_09]: Valus...
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's so many games on Virtual Console now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd have to look at the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Ys has been revived on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I know there's been some newer games there, or PSP, but I don't think the originals ever came to Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody in chat might correct us.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll have to check.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think the originals ever did.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, chatters, do our dirty work for us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go check.
[SPEAKER_02]: If Konami still loves us Why Australia first?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it could just be that maybe that's where the news is leaked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's really planned for everywhere, but the news has just happened to leak for Australia.
[SPEAKER_09]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe they had to put in their request for rating some earlier date.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right, and these ratings requests are how game announcements leak all the freaking time.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've tried to take measures to stop that here with the ESRB and the States, but that doesn't change Australia, Europe, and some of the other countries where we get our titles spoiled from.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know, I'll have that in an instant.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I will actually check that out too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Be finally a way I can actually play this game because I didn't collect all these systems that DarkSakura did.
[SPEAKER_01]: I told you to come over and play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, but it would be nice to have it in my own house.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, not that I don't enjoy spending time with DarkSakura, but it would be nice to fire it up whenever I want.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I want to play at 2 a.m., I don't have to call you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might actually have that day off work, so I'll let you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Super.
[SPEAKER_08]: The end.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Namco, they've got a lot of great games out there and some of those you may have missed.
[SPEAKER_02]: And some crappy ones too, just for the record.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some crappy ones you may have missed and may not want to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Would you really miss them if they're crappy?
[SPEAKER_02]: You may just want to collect the achievements and or trophies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Beautiful Katamari, sometime in the first quarter of 2010.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then on the PlayStation Portable, me and my Katamari on December 22nd.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's already out there if you want to snag that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, you know, that being said, they're also planning on putting out other PlayStation 1 and PSP catalog titles as well on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: And...
[SPEAKER_03]: There also may be other titles coming to the Xbox 360 as well, but they haven't really named names yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of neat, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: More Katamari.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but that was the worst Katamari game in the series.
[SPEAKER_02]: Both of those ones you named were the low points of the series.
[SPEAKER_02]: Personally, I did not enjoy Beautiful Katamari.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have friends that say I'm totally not being fair to that game and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: and maybe they think there's a grudge because of the history our show has with that particular title but no, I think really you put that side by side with Katamari Forever on the PS3 and it is staying no contest.
[SPEAKER_02]: The PS3 one's better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though the PS3 one is a rehash of some of the old stuff, I still say the PS3 one's better.
[SPEAKER_03]: And just wait for the PS3 one to drop down in price because it will pretty quick because it'll kind of fade off pretty fast and you probably will be able to pick up the new Katamari game um
[SPEAKER_03]: for $20 or something, and that's about what you're going to pay for these re-releases, so just be patient.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting how digital distribution is kind of best known for this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Breathing new life into games that had slipped off the radar, which is exactly what Namco is doing here.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I compare this to, you know how Steam is doing their epic sale right now, where, I swear, they undercut this shit down to cost just to get people in the door.
[SPEAKER_02]: They might even be taking losses on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what they're doing, but they're just trying to get as many Steam subscribers as they can.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, some of the games they're selling...
[SPEAKER_02]: would have fallen off the radar a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: For example, I think they were selling the LucasArts pack for like three bucks, which was the Indiana Jones games and Loom and all that was on sale for three bucks the other day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, yeah, that might be a steal, but at the same time for the publisher and all the salespeople involved, that's three bucks they probably weren't going to get because these games are so freaking old.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who buys them anymore?
[SPEAKER_02]: But digital distribution kind of opens it all up.
[SPEAKER_02]: XBOX Live Marketplace
[SPEAKER_02]: Guitar Hero World Tour, Band Hero, Lips, Lips No.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1 Hits, Lego Rock Band, Beatles Rock Band, whatever rock band there is.
[SPEAKER_02]: They all have these special front-end stores where you can actually sample music tracks and download the songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might be thinking, well, I can already do that in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you can, but now you can also do it through the Xbox 360 interface, which is kind of cool that you don't have to go find the disc to put it in the drive to sample the latest releases.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: If you remember from E3, though, a couple years ago, they said that that was one of the things that they wanted to do to begin with was offer the multimedia interaction with the games.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so I have not checked out that storefront myself, but I'm looking at some of the screenshots, and it definitely seems... It's nice that every game kind of gets its own little look and logo and so forth, but where's Rock Revolution?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where's the dedicated store?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, in the clearance bin.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's where it is.
$4.99.
[SPEAKER_12]: Xbox Live should have its own little clearance bin of sorts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's our dumpster.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, clearance bin.
[SPEAKER_02]: It kind of looks like Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like just this wasteland.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got a great idea for Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can do something similar to that with Project Natal, where you actually dig through the clearance bin with your hands, making different gestures using the Natal camera.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can find the Rock Revolution in there for $4.99.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, no one would ever get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So how about some news about a game no one cares about?
[SPEAKER_02]: Champions Online!
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, there is going to be a new update and an iPhone app and a recruitment initiative.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please play our game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: There is Champion's Companion for the iPhone, which you can use to review your character and see your online status, check your friends list, your mail, read news.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: So I guess that's kind of okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then they did an Attack of the Misfit Toys event over the weekend with new costume pieces, action figures, perks, that type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Please come play our game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: We need people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we had a story just like this a couple weeks ago, but it was Age of Conan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very similar type of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're practically giving the game away to get people to play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They already know where it's going to come in, and that's going to be with Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I'm holding out for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ironically enough, isn't that what got a lot of people to sign up for Champions Online in the first place?
[SPEAKER_02]: Was guaranteed access to Star Trek Online's beta or something like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember if you got an Uber subscription to Champions, you could play Star Trek Online early or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what, that wins the whatever award.
[SPEAKER_02]: That should have been a warning sign right there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I'm already getting a beta, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Our chatroom's actually lighting up with comments on the last story because we're a little bit behind.
[SPEAKER_02]: It takes time for what we say to encode and you guys to hear it through the All Games feed and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're still talking about Rock Revolution a little bit because I was giving a little shit in chat earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ranma in chat says, Sorry, Rock Revolution was well worth the $5 I paid for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brad from PodCulture asks, What sucked more, Rock Revolution or Yaris?
[SPEAKER_02]: To be fair, Yaris probably sucked more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yaris, but for your suck-to-money value...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yaris is free.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not that difficult to make a successful music game, Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you've done it in the past.
[SPEAKER_03]: You just kind of have to copy what you did.
[SPEAKER_03]: But somehow you just fuck it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't know how you do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, ah, they won't get it over in America.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's make it all ghetto looking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Way to shit on your fans.
[SPEAKER_03]: And trust me, we're not into that over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's other countries.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, we're going to travel around the world and look at some release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully some good things coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, then again, it's that time of year where probably there ain't shit coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that the story here?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm pretty sure that's correct.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is nothing coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And at least last I checked, there was nothing coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if there is anything coming out this week, it's probably crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I mean, I guess if you count Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles, the Crystal Bears came out today.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's something, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: And supposedly this week, Divinity 2 Ego Draconis is supposed to be coming out on PC and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought that was supposed to be next week, but hey.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dreamer, Zookeeper, World Party Games
[SPEAKER_02]: Really, it's the same story in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Literally not a damn thing coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very quiet over there right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: A price reduction on Tactics A2 on the DS is about all you got going for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, there's really not a lot to look forward to until January 9th when Kingdom Hearts Birth by Sleep hits the Sony PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's probably the next big, big release over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I didn't find a damn thing for Europe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just that time of year, folks, but we talk about them every week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is a good week to go back and play the games you missed this year in 2009, yes?
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, so back to some news then.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So soon, and I'm not sure if this is actually going to happen because I could think a lot of other people would be pissed off for other reasons, but pretty soon you may not be able to play your PSP or DS on airplanes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently somebody is trying to...
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, there is a guy, Omar... I'm not even going to try to pronounce his name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, the guy was arrested after failing to ignite an explosive device on Christmas Day on a plane.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God, I heard about that on CNN.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that had to do with electronic devices?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently... Let's see...
[SPEAKER_02]: One motherfucker always ruins it for everybody else.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how you can't take in water over a certain size, and your shampoo has to be in a clear bottle and in a plastic bag?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not mad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand that they're doing it for our safety and what have you, but it's because some asshole threatened to use it as a bomb and said that you could use water as a... It's just frustrating.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, yeah, he...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Full-bag searches were instigated at the boarding gates, and the ban on electronic devices is said to be a reaction to his ability to smuggle an explosive onto the plane.
[SPEAKER_03]: This would, of course, mean any DS or PSP would be banned, as well as anything from...
[SPEAKER_03]: Electronic Books, iPods, cell phones, other gaming devices, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to make flight so incredibly boring.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not going to fly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pun intended.
[SPEAKER_03]: I, you know, honestly, I'm surprised he was able to do that, because, I mean, they scan all that stuff through, you know... Well, he was on an international flight.
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't get screened at a U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: airport.
[SPEAKER_02]: He got screened at a Dutch airport.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not to... I don't know what they do over there that's different than what they do over here, but he didn't get in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have a bomb.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, you may go.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know...
[SPEAKER_02]: I really don't see them banning all electronics on planes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's a bit much.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's going to suck because I know a lot of airlines are looking into, like, I think Virgin Air, one of them, if they're not already doing it, was looking into, like, free Wi-Fi on flights now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, that's what the technology's gotten, is you can get on the internet on flights, which is pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it would really suck to kind of rip that all away.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the end of the day, if there is a true...
[SPEAKER_02]: Threat, I suppose, for lack of a better term, to, you know, electronic devices on planes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something that they can't screen for at the airport for God knows whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Safety first.
[SPEAKER_02]: People didn't have laptops 20 years ago, 30 years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Flights will still work, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, what if some dude was to create an EMP bomb using electronic devices?
[SPEAKER_03]: Can't detect that because it's not an explosive.
[SPEAKER_03]: The plane would go down.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's the point.
[SPEAKER_03]: They wanted to explode or, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone's probably thought of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have something.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't advertise all their countermeasures.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, for obvious reasons.
[SPEAKER_09]: First of all, if anyone was going to actually be able to project an EMP that would make a plane go down, it'd be a bigger device.
[SPEAKER_09]: It wouldn't be something that could be hidden that easily.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just playing devil's advocate.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just... Although that really would be about the only thing I could think of.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100 Matt wants to add, Rob, he hid firecrackers in his crotch.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Dutch screeners scanned him, but they wouldn't have found them unless they patted him down.
[SPEAKER_09]: That seems so odd to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: How many did he have in his crotch?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it was one of those things where it only takes a spark to ignite...
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have something flammable I don't know Obviously they're not telling you the details On what he was planning to do for obvious reasons But I still find it shocking That he was able to hide firecrackers Undetected You know It sucks
[SPEAKER_02]: Electronic Gaming Monthly is coming back!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be coming back with an April issue that's released in March because, you know, they come out a month before the actual date on the magazine.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's when it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a press release that came out that announced that it will be coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's also going to be an EGMI, the digital magazine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess there's a special code that will be in the issue that allows you to access the digital components for exclusive article extensions and original content.
[SPEAKER_02]: So trying to get you to buy the, you know, trying to tie it into the Internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: A little silly, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Features and things, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyone that doesn't have a subscription to Gameformer, and pretty much if you shop at GameStop and you have one of their cards, you have a subscription because you get it for free when you get their stupid card.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, the online portion of it is kind of useless.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have some additional screenshots, usually, or some...
[SPEAKER_03]: I miss the old magazines with demo discs.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, occasionally, though, they did have some free download content in there, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a few Oblivion expansions and stuff like that were free.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a little bit of a value.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, I'm kind of missing the days, like, well, you know, I used to buy PC Gamer, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: They used to have a whole bunch of shareware and free shit on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, wouldn't it now just be type in the code and get a demo on PSN or Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they could do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, why bother with the cost of discs now?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all digital.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you want to pick up your bathroom reader of Electronic Gaming Monthly, it will feature stuff by Dan, Shu, Sue, Sean Baby is part of the crew as well, and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of names you probably recognize from previous years.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, he did the comic, the Sue and Sean comic.
[SPEAKER_09]: I used to read those like all the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they had a webcomic I think for a little while too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if you want to check that out, it will be coming out soon, so check out the newsstands.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's some other stuff you can spend your money on.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sackboy plushies.
[SPEAKER_09]: They are now on Amazon.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can get a Sackboy and a Sackgirl for $20.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they won't have any until December 30th.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't like the look of the Sackgirl on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, the Sackgirl looks stupid, but the Sackboy's pretty cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sackboy is adorable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Team Fortress 2, if you don't have enough friends to play the game with you, Valve has the answer for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: They are beta testing right now AI opponents.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you will be able to use some pretty intelligent bots as your opponents to fill in gaps that you may have on your team.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, I believe this is available now.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do have some...
[SPEAKER_03]: stuff you use in the console, including ways to add people to there or remove AI players and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_03]: But apparently they're pretty cool, and they actually, I don't know, are good replacements for people that may not be there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think they've done this in Counter-Strike and stuff like that, so I wouldn't see why they wouldn't do it here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been playing ranked games, you know, now, almost every day.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Feel free to join our game because... You want to give out your gamer tag?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, LokiOLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: All one word.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's... Just feel free.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't really be invited into the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You just have to kind of join a ranked game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And trust me, there's hardly anyone playing right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really easy to join the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can just see if I'm online, most likely playing Grand Theft Auto, join the game, and prepare to get your ass kicked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice, it's so modest
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, by the way, they've come out and said, of course, deny, deny, deny.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's come out apparently that the Sony PSP-4000 mention was a mistake on their part.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is no new model of the PSP under construction.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh, sure, whatever you say, dude.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, just like they...
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't have an icon or whatever like that that was also available on Sony's website as well that someone found by changing the file name or whatever of like the PSP 3000 icon on there to the 4000.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, look, it shows up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, you know, Sony came out and said, oh, yeah, this is not true.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the company that put out the ad said, oh, yeah, this is not true.
[SPEAKER_03]: But come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they were really going to put it out and this company leaked it out, wouldn't they be telling the company, deny everything?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: The response coming here is, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Crazy people.
$4,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whether they do or not, let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not going to be significant either way.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, Sony.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're not coming out with a $4,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will pretend to be surprised when you announce the $4,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just like with the Go.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're not doing a UMD List PSP with a sliding screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's preposterous.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, by the way, the PSP Go is coming out now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here comes E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: LOL, gotcha.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, 4,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: You didn't see that one coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they should name it the 4001 just to spite everybody Sony, if you're listening, seriously that is how you could get the last laugh because we all know you're doing it now just suck it up name it the PSP 4001 and lol alright, we're going to take some time here on the show to respect the classics it is time for the very last classic game of the week of the decade
[SPEAKER_02]: No, this segment will be back in 2010, of course it will.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this is a chance for DarkSakura to dig through the gaming archives and pick a game from Gaming's Yesteryear that she says, Damn it, you ungrateful kids these days and your newfangled 360s and PS3s.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to go play the games we used to play back in my day.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then she'll run over you with her walker, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: I went, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: I went for Epic Old School Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so what is the Epic Old School Awesome video game of the week?
[SPEAKER_09]: The video game of the week is Salamander.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm pretty sure I haven't done Salamander yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think you have either.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is a shame.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, then here is a little clip of Salamander.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's listen to the intro.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now what is this Dark Sakura?
[SPEAKER_13]: This is just Life Force, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Life Force is the name it came out with in North America.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, it's a spin-off from the Gradius series.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it actually switches between horizontal and vertically scrolling areas.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you've got kind of a little bit of both.
[SPEAKER_09]: It also has a more simplified power-up system, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: and you can play two player co-op which is great.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's in all of the stages by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, player one is the Vic Viper, and player two is the Lord British.
[SPEAKER_09]: And actually, did you know there's a Salamander anime?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, they really called one of the ships the Lord British?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, the same guy who did Ultima Lord British?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because when I hear Lord British, I think of the dude who did Ultima back in the day.
[SPEAKER_09]: At any rate, well, you've got the Vic Viper and Lord British.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you play through six stages, and like I said, it alternates between horizontal and vertical.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can actually continue from where you left off upon death, instead of the checkpoint version that Gradius has.
[SPEAKER_09]: You do not have any continues in salamander mode when you play single, but you have two continues in two-player mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, whoever's doing this playthrough here off this YouTube, it's user Succula, S-U-C-C-U-L-L-A is the YouTube we're looking at here in studio right now where the music's coming from.
[SPEAKER_02]: Epic.
[SPEAKER_02]: This person knows what the fuck they're doing with this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They know where it's at.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, on top of that, just like any of the Gradius games, especially with the bosses, there are little hidey places that you can go to and ways to lure the boss or whatever to where you need it to be.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if I'm right, I think this is a one playthrough beating of this game, which is really freaking difficult.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love the laser.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was my favorite weapon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just freaking love Lifeforce on the NES.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I realize, you know, it has its roots different places, but I remember it as Lifeforce on the NES.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I got it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob, if you want to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember seeing it in the vault.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I just kind of, you know, I like the voice in this one, but I miss the double, you know,
[SPEAKER_09]: Option!
[SPEAKER_09]: And all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or Speed Up.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, so you've got different backgrounds.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have Starfields.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, you've got, uh...
[SPEAKER_09]: All kinds of different stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's actually some big differences between the Japanese version and the European version and Lifeforce.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Japanese and European versions are pretty much the same except the American version changes the plot to the game by having some opening text where you're actually going inside a giant alien lifeform to fight off bacteria.
[SPEAKER_09]: and so the star fields from Salamander were actually changed to kind of a web background so that it looks more organic.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure you remember that, Rob, don't you?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: The power-ups have different names.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have Speed Up becoming Hyper Speed, Missile becoming Destruct Missile, the Ripple Laser becoming Pulse Laser, and Force Field becoming Shield.
[SPEAKER_02]: OMG, I love the fire level.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, they're in Stage 3 right now on their epic playthrough.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the fire.
[SPEAKER_09]: There should be a link to Level 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: And actually, Level 4, Rob, I wish you would place at the beginning of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It should be the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, you want to skip ahead a little bit here?
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll get to the fourth one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but this music you'll recognize from B-Mania.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: That music right there was the beginning of the Accelerator B crush mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: And actually, stage 4 has my favorite music in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some other differences, your power-ups were modified a little bit to where for a
[SPEAKER_09]: You have the same for Life Force, the Japanese Life Force.
[SPEAKER_09]: You actually had the same power-up as Gradius.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some music was changed.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can, however, get the original Japanese version and the Enhanced Life Force with the Salamander Deluxe Pack that came out for PlayStation and Saturn, and Salamander Portable on PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, we have the NES version, which actually came out in 87...
[SPEAKER_09]: It actually, though, just took bits from Salamander and Life Force to kind of make it a bit of a new concept in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It actually, we got the port for the NES, and it's exactly the same, except it doesn't have multiple endings like the Japanese one does, and it's just called Life Force.
[SPEAKER_09]: All of these use the Konami code, and the NES version is out on the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_09]: 500 Wii Points.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's an MSX version that's pretty different.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have different pilots for each of the ships, which if I do remember correctly, I think that it was from the MSX version that the anime was based off of.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's been a long time since I've watched the anime.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got it on DVD somewhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's also a PC Engine version.
[SPEAKER_09]: You actually have checkpoints in this one, faster enemy animations.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, they improved some of the music from the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's Ocean Software brought it out for the Spectrum Commodore and Amstrad in 1988.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the Commodore 64 version, Rob, you may be particularly happy to find out, was pretty much...
[SPEAKER_09]: considered one of the best of the PC ports.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, like I said, it came out on the PlayStation and Saturn.
[SPEAKER_09]: We got the Salamander Deluxe Pack, and also included with that was Salamander 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that was Salamander Life Force and Salamander 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: PSP, we got Salamander Portable, which had actually a few other kind of rare games in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It had...
[SPEAKER_09]: Salamander, Life Force, Salamander 2, Zexix, I think that's what it's called, Zexix, X-E-X-E-X, that's a game I haven't played in a long time, and the MSX version of Gradius 2, which came out, I think, as Nemesis 2, which has nothing to do with the arcade Gradius 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: and for the record, Gradius 2 on PC Engine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah, here's actually the thing about the anime in here.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was an OAV and it had to do with...
[SPEAKER_09]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there's also a couple good soundtracks too.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's the Salamander Arcade soundtrack, there is the original Sound of Salamander, and Salamander again, Konami Kukeiha Club, which, you know, they did a few games from that series.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, a few soundtracks from that series.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yummy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lots of Salamander-y things.
[SPEAKER_09]: And also, I freaking love the cover of the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, look at that and tell me that's not awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm gonna link it in chatroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it's like a big demon face thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of scary, actually, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like an evil snake.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which really has nothing to do with the salamander, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Other than being, you know, reptiles, I guess, maybe?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, there it is, your classic game of the week, Salamander, which is available on a variety of different systems, but if you want to play the original, go play the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can find it if you know where to look.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, we're going to take a quick break, but we'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not done yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, we're going to be back.
[SPEAKER_02]: We still have some rapid-fire news, your Twitter topics, and then we're going to take a break from the news tonight and talk a little bit about what's happened this year, talk about our picks for Game of the Year.
[SPEAKER_08]: And donuts.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you want to talk about donuts?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want a donut too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also want a pony.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a pony, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did I tell you that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I have to share this.
[SPEAKER_09]: For our team, Builder, we did our annual present exchange and we were given these little pieces of paper that says write down what you want so that whoever gets our name doesn't buy us crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I was like, okay, I want an Amazon gift card or this gift card or that gift card or a pony.
[SPEAKER_09]: So someone, the person who got me, got me a toy pony.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then a gift card to Barnes & Noble.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I finally got my pony.
[SPEAKER_09]: That means I have to stop asking for one at restaurants.
[SPEAKER_02]: When they say, what can I get you tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: I need a pony.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you need anything else?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'd like a pony, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to have to stick with either the llama or the pygmy goat.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to take a quick break, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio in the year and the decade in review in just a few minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio on this Sunday night, December the 27th of 2009, where we're taping the 350th episode of our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yes, it's the very last Orange Lounge Radio of the decade, but we'll be back next week as always to do it all again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Since it is the last OLR of the decade and it's been a little bit of a slow news week, we're going to take some time to reflect on our favorite games of the year and of the decade.
[SPEAKER_02]: But meanwhile, we do have a few other news stories we want to get to real quick in a segment we call the Rapid Fire News.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, we'll get to your Twitter topics, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you haven't sent us your tweets yet, hurry up and do that because we're going to get to those very soon, as soon as we get out our Rapid Fire News.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, well, if you're looking for something to do shortly after the new year, you can perhaps join the MAG Beta, which was previously not available to everybody, but starting January 4th will be, and...
[SPEAKER_03]: You will be able to download it on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: Existing beta members will be able to update their files to prepare for the upcoming trial, which means that you shouldn't delete any of your magdata if you are already in the beta.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently the beta is pretty short, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is only lasting a week until, well, slightly under a week, until January 10th.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you will be able to play 64 player sabotage matches and also 256 player domination matches.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then of course the end of the game will be coming out shortly after that.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the 26th?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, also on the PlayStation Network will be coming Holy Invasion of Privacy Badman 2 Um, and what's kind of cool about it as well is that you will not only be able to get the sequel But the first game will be included with it for free Um, and that is of course if you get it via the PlayStation Network No word though if, um, when they decide to put this out as an actual UMD If the original game will appear on there as well
[SPEAKER_03]: But at least right now, it's kind of a nice bonus for people who may own the PSP Go and that's their only option.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then finally, in un-Sony PlayStation news, Crackdown 2 is scheduled to be coming out the first half of 2010, which makes me all sorts of happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And no word exactly yet when it's going to be coming, but apparently it was revealed on Major Nelson's weekly podcast that Xbox's head Aaron Greenberg apparently is saying that Mass Effect 2, Splinter Cell Conviction, and Alan Wake,
[SPEAKER_03]: and apparently also CrackedN2 who are scheduled for the first part of the year.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I guess Alan Wake isn't coming out later in the year like I thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably second quarter if I guessed correctly.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, some other games coming out before too long.
[SPEAKER_02]: Resonance of Fate, some folks might be interested in this, is by TriAce.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is already available as a demo on the Japanese PlayStation Network or the Japanese Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you have a Japanese PSN account or you have a way of getting onto the – I guess the Xbox is a little better now blocking the non-Japanese stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eh, not very good at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever you can do to get in there, you can do that to download that demo.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you haven't already heard about this game, it's coming out from Sega's publishing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of like a gunplay style RPG.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Resonance of Fate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now available in Japan or for those of you crafty folks over in other countries who know how to get in anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: LOL Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it's coming out on the PSP, but no camera, no cards, and apparently...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure the UMD is really going to be there either Legends is just going to be on the PlayStation Store It's going to be there in the spring of 2010 It'll have 300 digital cards 30 that are unique on the PSP No UMD release expected at this time It's only going to be a digital download That doesn't mean it's only playable on the go Because remember, if you have a big enough memory card on the 3000 That's all you need Is that included in the bet?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, good question.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, and the reason why is because it's not as ridiculous as The Eye of Judgment, whereas this, you know, is an actual game that can play like a traditional game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not something that's, you know, a card game with this extra camera crap that's added on top of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will give Loki that, I mean, let's face it, part of what made the first game so preposterous was the fact that, you know, you're playing this card game with a camera, and I think that's why he took the bet in the first place.
[SPEAKER_02]: PSP's deleting all that weird shit out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's actually a game, it'd be like almost like a translation of a Magic the Gathering game, whereas, you know, I judgment, I can imagine being played without the camera and all the extra crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fair enough, guys, let's just face it, Loki's never going to lose that bet, at least not in this decade.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: So don't expect any new weapons or any significant changes to gameplay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like, you know, la la la, Winter Wonderland, etc, etc, candy canes and so forth for you to blow your friends away to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have fun with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_09]: Some stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stuff like and such as?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Sega's having a big sale in their Wii Shop channel.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should have some of the games like Sonic 1, 2, 3, Gunstar Heroes, Streets of Rage 2, Pio Pio 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically, they're going to be $5 until January 6th.
[SPEAKER_09]: So each of them are $3 less than usual.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think they just want to make some money.
[SPEAKER_09]: So go buy them.
[SPEAKER_09]: and as far as other stuff going on, there is a New Year's theme for free on Xbox Live, which it's pretty colorful.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dan was using it for a little while.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has a big ball on top of the building.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also,
[SPEAKER_09]: They have some other things to go with the new year that you have to pay for them, like the 2010 Avatar glasses.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there's also the deal of the day stuff, like I believe it was the other day was Worms 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: and then last but not least, and actually this is I think the best news of all, is there is a country pack for Rock Band, but who cares about the country crap because there's also a Paul McCartney set in there as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's actually...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's actually December 29th is the Country Pack, which Alan Jackson's Good Time, Cross Canadian Ragweed, Cry Lonely, Jason Aldean, She's Country, Keith Urban, I Told You So.
[SPEAKER_09]: That seems to be the only good thing in the whole packet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kenny Rogers, A Gambler.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, maybe Kenny Rogers is a classic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Martina McBride, This One's for the Girls, Shania Twain, Any Man of Mine, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the Paul McCartney Pack is going to be out on January 5th or January 7th for PS3 owners.
[SPEAKER_09]: Haha, we'll get it first.
[SPEAKER_09]: Xbox, Xbox.
[SPEAKER_09]: For that set you get Band on the Run, the live, actually all these are live versions.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is from the Paul McCartney New York City concert.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there's Band on the Run, Jet, and Sing the Changes.
[SPEAKER_09]: All of those are going to be 160 Xbox points or 200 Wii points each.
[SPEAKER_09]: And these are actually, there's no telling if they're going to be available for Lego Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't wait until January 5th.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll start off the year with a bang.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or a few guitar strums, whatever the case may be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get into some Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've been taking some of your submissions over Twitter at twitter.com slash OLR for some things we might have missed so far in the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And some random-ass questions, such as this first one from Blue Swim, who tweets us, If you could bring only one celebrity who died during the Oz decade back to life, who would it be and why?
[SPEAKER_02]: He continues on to tweet, I'd bring Heath Ledger back to life so he could reprise his role as the Joker in the new Batman movies again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gosh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: To think all the way back throughout the entire decade of the O's, that's a long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people die.
[SPEAKER_02]: Death just kind of happens.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you could bring back only one celebrity, he specifically said a celebrity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anybody that comes to mind for any of you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I honestly, I'm like drawing a blank.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's kind of a weird thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean... What if one of those celebrities, if they were suddenly back, if their very presence, alive, disrupted the entire space continuum... Or if they got brought back as a zombie.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then we'd have to shoot them in the head, and we couldn't remember them in a nice way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to see...
[SPEAKER_02]: God, the name escapes me right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: A totally famous guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: The guy that was with the NRA.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not for my cold, dead hands.
[SPEAKER_02]: Charlton Heston, was that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Charlton Heston, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to see him reanimated as a zombie.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's the celebrity from the... I want to see Brittany What's-Her-Fuck come back as a zombie so we can shoot her.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rude, rude, rude.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, this is my whole thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I understand mourning the loss of, like, someone's contribution, but you didn't know the person, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Very good suggestion from chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have a couple people yelling out Phil Hartman.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a very tragic thing that happened.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is my whole thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: When people die, it's typically when they're supposed to.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even if it might seem stupid, it happens when it happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't see any point in wishing for something that's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really don't want to see anyone reanimated.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just the whole zombie thing totally makes me want to puke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, was there something smartass you wanted to add?
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, no, I just had to see when someone died.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, uh... Yes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just checking real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn it!
[SPEAKER_03]: That was in 94.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: No John Candy, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, I guess I'm gonna have to go with my original thought, which was Michael Jackson, because I'd like to see him do his actual comeback.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, uh, you know, all sorts of fun that would be involved with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100 Matt sent us this on Twitter, which is a link to a story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Police followed an Xbox trailer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I take that back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I renege that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would like to see... Oh, God, what's his name?
[SPEAKER_02]: The chatroom is correcting themselves, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Phil Hartman died in 98.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, not Phil Hartman.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other guy, the other pitchman Billy Mays Hi, Billy Mays here As a zombie No, not as a zombie
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you see that episode of South Park?
[SPEAKER_02]: Brilliant, that show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, back to SSJ100.
[SPEAKER_02]: Matt's tweet, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sent us to a story from LOHUD.com talking about police following an Xbox trail.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess because this guy in the Bronx was playing with a stolen Xbox 360 game system, it led them to a stash of stolen property, 200 car break-ins, and a couple of burglaries.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were very excited to recover all this.
[SPEAKER_02]: They went to, oh I love when they give the address in the story, it was 4064 Laconia Avenue in the Bronx is where all this stuff was hiding Apparently, they got a search warrant, they traced through Microsoft and the ISP where this stolen Xbox was being played from And it led them to a GPS system, laptop computers and all this stuff
[SPEAKER_02]: So, uh, looks like all this stuff was retrieved from 22-year-old Jeremiah, Jeremiah Gilliam's bedroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: To Jeremiah Gilliam, we say, uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next time, don't be stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stealing things is pretty stupid in the first place, but then, like, when you go and, like, play with the stolen goods on the internet, that just makes you stupid or stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: But let's face it, you're pretty stupid to be stealing shit in the first place.
[SPEAKER_09]: That makes someone extra stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, he probably wouldn't think that they would be tracking the system, and it's almost likely that they wouldn't know what the system's serial number and that kind of stuff was, but apparently they were able to track that via history and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dedication to them for trying to get it back to the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we got a link from DJ Ranma S on Twitter is linking us to another kind of local New York thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is coming from Gizmodo, which is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has to do with the iPhone, which some would argue is pretty much a gaming device in this day and age.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, the iPhone is not purchasable on AT&T's website if you use a New York City zip code.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because according to a rep at...
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess online.
[SPEAKER_02]: New York is not ready for the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've heard about all these types of complaints where in New York City, like, they can't handle the iPhone bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Calls are getting dropped left and right and all this crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yikes.
[SPEAKER_03]: But their 3G's better!
[SPEAKER_03]: Their commercials say so!
[SPEAKER_03]: Am I to believe that Luke Wilson is lying to me?
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't handle that!
[SPEAKER_03]: That's shocking!
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's probably just some type of weird, creepy bug.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think AT&T is going to acknowledge that this has any weight to it whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_02]: But apparently also Tigerclaw wants to add in our chatroom, you can still go into a phone and get a, or sorry, still go into a phone, still go into a store and get the phone that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little strange.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, also going to some other news stories that were submitted.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ray Ayanami sends us this link to Kitsui was announced for the Japanese Xbox 360s at what's called the Cave Festival.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is a shooting game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kitsui Kizuna
[SPEAKER_02]: Jigoku Tachi Extra is coming out on the 360 that'll cost you about $50 and it's another shmup that's coming to the Xbox 360 which has been getting a lot of those but you can see some screenshots online at this shmups.system11.org web forum where they actually show people playing at Akihabara at the Cave Festival this new game and there's even some footage on the internets but there's a lot of background noise I don't want to play that for you right now
[SPEAKER_02]: A couple stories coming to us from TigerClaw305 who is sending us some stories about, let's see, TimeGate has sued South Peak for royalties and breach of contract.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently this is the folks who developed Section 8, TimeGate Studios.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have sued South Peak because of a breach of contract.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently the publisher is withholding royalty payments and violates the deal with a PS3 porting deal with a Russian company.
[SPEAKER_02]: TimeGate What's Compensatory Damages According to the report, South Peak says that because they got in 2008 Gamecock, it exempts it from some of the specifics of the original agreement.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yet more legal troubles.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be settled out of court.
[SPEAKER_02]: They always are.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how those things go, yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what'll happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, also, what's also very interesting, the CEO of 3D Realms has teased a Duke Nukem resurgence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh god, here we go again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently numerous Duke Nukem games are in various stages of development.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gosh, does that include Duke Nukem Forever?
[SPEAKER_02]: funny that you should mention Duke Nukem because remember there was supposed to be the PSP and DS versions that were coming out in September oh but those have been delayed just like Duke Nukem now I want to point out the CEO of 3D Realms did go out of his way to point out Duke Nukem Forever was not technically cancelled yes we released the initial team but that doesn't correlate to the demise of the project great so this will be now what our third decade of Duke Nukem Forever rumors we're going to get into goody goody
[SPEAKER_02]: Our good friend Maren Marvel has tweeted us and said, What do you guys think about the Blizzard Authenticator?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's a really good idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate to say it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had my account hacked, and I will never undo the authenticator because of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially if you're an iPhone or iTouch user, it's free.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you get a free pet out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And even if you don't have an iPhone or an iTouch, it's like $6.50 for the keychain.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, considering they're also charging $10 for a pet, it's not a bad deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it does keep your account relatively safe.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's unfortunate that Blizzard won't do more.
[SPEAKER_02]: against these gold spammers and things.
[SPEAKER_02]: But unfortunately, what they're doing, they're hacking a lot of American accounts and going into the games and rolling level one characters and doing all the shouts and so forth.
[SPEAKER_09]: How well does the app work?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Never had a problem with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty much all you do, you boot it up and it brings you up the code right away.
[SPEAKER_09]: But is that one that you have to pay for?
No.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a free app.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, then I'll just download it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: I just I wish Blizzard would sue people I wish they would just start blocking IPs from maybe regions that are in America I mean I hate to say it but you know what there is WoW localized for other regions so maybe it's time to start locking players out from certain regions I hate to say it but if that's the way we're going to prevent but you know you can always IP spoof and all this other crazy stuff but I just wish the burden wasn't on us but hey it's free
[SPEAKER_02]: Lastly, one more question from JazayJazz on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where do you think games are headed in the new year?
[SPEAKER_02]: Digital distribution is going to be huge in the next decade.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think a lot of these game stores are going to have to change their business model or there's a lot to lose in the coming decade.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think digital distribution is going to be huge in the upcoming next few years.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's where games are headed online.
[SPEAKER_09]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_09]: Honestly, we've been seeing it happen more and more, especially since Sony's been really adopting it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, probably more digital distribution, but I don't really think things are going to change too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to probably try to push 3D, because that's the next big thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now with the two...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really see, I guess truly next-gen consoles, because Wii's kind of recycled hardware if you ask me, but now they're coming out with their 3D controllers, so that's really going to be the pushes for 3D, and you're going to see almost like a new console generation kind of being formed from this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I honestly would not expect to see all new consoles until, like, 2013, 14.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's gonna be a ways out, I think, especially with these motion and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless... I think Nintendo will have something very soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless it just flops and dies, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think from Nintendo, I don't think we're gonna see anything really new.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's probably just gonna be an upgrade.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to point out some comments from our chat room on some of those tweets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Misty wants to point out in our chat room, chat.orangelandrita.com Fuck that, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: I keep my eye touch with me all the damn time and in my pocket at work because due to some shit that happened around work last year, I'm paranoid about my eye touch getting jacked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to those stupid people that cause you to be paranoid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I get some people, yes, they do have their eye touch with them all the time, but I also know some people that, you know, they only have it at home or at work.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they don't really carry it with them everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: So just...
[SPEAKER_02]: you know what your habits are if you do have your eye touch with you all the time then maybe the blizzard thing is a good idea
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100 Matt kind of jokes, I don't know if this is a joke or real, but Blizzard banning IPs in Korea is an act of war, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not saying ban Korea or whatever country you want to name from the games, but if you have a game that has US servers that's meant to be played by the US that's localized for the US, Korea gets their own version of the games.
[SPEAKER_02]: WoW's been localized for China.
[SPEAKER_02]: WoW's out in other countries.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: I, I, unfortunately if all the gold farming is coming from China, maybe it's time to put some restrictions down.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they also need to place some restrictions on who can do these shouts and chat and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blizzard's done a really good job over the years though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, let's face it, every time they involve the gold hackers and the gold farmers have to get a little smarter.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to make it sound like Blizzard's done nothing because they really have done a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've gotten smart about how they do trial accounts and a lot of the various aspects of WoW.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just sucks that they just won't play hardball and start suing the pants off of some of these people that exploit their game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to see heads roll over my account getting hacked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that's going to do it for the Twitter topics for tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about some of the year-end news.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we'll start off talking about some of our favorite games of the year and games you might call your game of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: In chatroom, we're taking your submissions as well and I'll try to keep an eye on the Twitter too for those of you that can't be in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: What were some of your picks for the game of the year and why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Usually I find these Game of the Year picks to be a little silly, because it's just one person's opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: So keep that in mind as we talk about our favorite games of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're just gamers, we like what we like, and this is our opinion for the game that you think was the most important game of 2009.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll start with Loki tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think were, and if you have a couple, go ahead, but what do you think overall was probably the biggest game of 2009?
[SPEAKER_03]: of 2009, well, probably Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2 was, but I didn't play that game, so, the game I liked, or at least, just, if I was gonna vote based on how much I played it, I'd say Grand Theft Auto, mainly the two expansions, because that's what I was ending up playing, and, um,
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's kind of neat because whereas before we wouldn't really see expansions for Grand Theft Auto we'd just see a couple other games kind of using the same engine and still we may see that relatively soon but it was kind of neat to kind of expand upon the story and kind of bring different perspectives to it and what not and it was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: They kind of brought back some of the old stuff that I thought should have been in there in the first place a lot of the over the top stuff because they wanted to keep it grounded in reality whatever
[SPEAKER_03]: So that was kind of, you know, my favorite of the year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other important games, I think DJ Hero was pretty big.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, kind of a different take on the whole music game genre, and I kind of like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought DJ Hero was horrifically underrated, and it's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know, a lot of people were writing it off as a failure.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, in looking at my Twitter and my Facebook, it seems like DJ Hero was a big-time Christmas present that was showing up for a lot of people, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it'll find a second life of sorts as we get in past the holidays.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also some of the other underrated Wii games, you know, more of the mature stuff like Mad World.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I love that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's just, you know, unfortunately a lot of the mature stuff doesn't do well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially when they don't put a lot of press behind it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, there is, you know, some commercials and stuff, but I don't think...
[SPEAKER_03]: The mature audience is really that big right now on the Wii, which is too bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because a lot of people have kind of given up on it and just went elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'd have to vote that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And really, unfortunately, I didn't play a lot of other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure Borderlands would be on my list if I had actually played that this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's still time, but it's unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that was probably a good one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure a little bit of, I'm sure, Infamous...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Just, we gotta joke and say it, uh, President Cat, very strange and absolutely, uh, weird game to come out, but, uh, I think it could do well over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, there's, seriously, there's so much crap that comes out in the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't understand why anybody couldn't take a chance.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there are companies like this, Graffiti Entertainment, uh, Axis Game Localization, I mean, fuck, they're bringing over Choniki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on, man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take the gamble.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Loki's named about 20 different games for his game of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is your list as long?
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably not, given that I... I mean, Sims 3 came out, and that was big for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I actually really enjoy Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't gotten World Adventures, but that was... Especially now they've got out the Build a World thing for Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the fact that, of course, it didn't take too long for all of the modders to start putting out their own hacks to the game and their own items and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, of course, I love building houses.
[SPEAKER_09]: Other stuff... Yeah, I've really been enjoying Dan play Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't play it because I get motion sick.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got my Silent Hill that I haven't played yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to say, though, Street Fighter 4 was really big for me, especially getting Sakura in the home release made me happy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because then I could kick Dan's butt and be happy about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, though, we got it right around the time my hand was really in bad shape.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to also second Tatsunoko vs. Capcom because...
[SPEAKER_09]: Again, big Tatsunoko fan for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Big Capcom fan.
[SPEAKER_09]: So the two together was just like a squeagasm in the process.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I remember sitting on the couch and being in absolute pain and still insisting on trying to beat the stupid bouncing ball in Tatsunoko vs. Capcom.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, look, they're playing the Gachapon music!
[SPEAKER_09]: Look, they're playing the Gachapon music!
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm so happy!
[SPEAKER_09]: You know...
[SPEAKER_09]: Big, big squeegasm for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you looking forward to the localization next year?
[SPEAKER_02]: Heck yeah!
[SPEAKER_09]: As long as they leave most of it in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, they've got the voice actors.
[SPEAKER_09]: How can you go wrong with that?
[SPEAKER_02]: um let's see my I would say there's probably three games I would bestow the game of the year honor upon one of them you'll say okay yeah I see that because it's something everybody else named uh one of them you'll say damn it Rob why'd you have to say that and then the other one you're gonna go lol what the fuck
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Loki,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, I would say new Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wii is definitely worthy of the praise of Game of the Year for some of the same reasons.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it pains me when Nintendo does this because, damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, Nintendo...
[SPEAKER_02]: They really did get it right in...
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people don't want to touch Mario Galaxy, as great of a game as that is, because it's like, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: 3D Mario?
[SPEAKER_02]: Can't control?
[SPEAKER_02]: A little weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: But New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wii kind of takes Mario back to its roots.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's like, oh, jump on Goomba.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's absolute chaos getting a bunch of people together.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is hell in four-player mode, but I still kind of applaud Nintendo for making it work, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It brought a lot of gamers back to gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes you want to hate Nintendo for this, but like I said, it's a diamond in the rough of the Wii software that's out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's my LOL what the fuck pick for game of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I honestly think it's deserving.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a lot of people are forgetting that this game is from this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it is absolutely one of the best things to happen to gaming this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1 versus 100 on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think absolutely deserves the accolade of one of the games of the years.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of neat that you're actually playing for real money.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's such a different type of game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I give it such props for being new, different, and fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Best of all, if you happen to be an Xbox Live Gold subscriber, it's free.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or even the Silver folks got it free for a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, it's fair to say that this game was free.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, how can you go wrong?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think 1 versus 100, in some ways, is the game of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: and for whoever was asking earlier where are games going in the future I'll bet you see some more stuff like this the interactive stuff I think it's going to be very cool to see how that plays out in the next decade so check that out so those were our games of the year what about you guys in our chat room some of you guys were naming some of your things here
[SPEAKER_02]: GameGuru says, what's wrong with Street Fighter 3?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, okay, it's pandering to the base, but still, I don't want to buy Street Fighter 4 when Super Street Fighter 4 is coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that was unfortunate that Super Street Fighter 4 was announced kind of soon because, you know, it devalued the original.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, we had Street Fighter 2 and Super Street Fighter 2, so I guess it's nothing too unheard of there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: TigerClaw says Game of the Year for me is Batman Arkham Asylum.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, that did get a lot of props.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very good storytelling in that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And certainly panders to fans of Batman in the comic form.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did a really good job with that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They really did.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I really, really liked Harley in that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, that's actually a game that convinced one of my friends to get an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really good storytelling.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was.
[SPEAKER_02]: SJ100Matt says, from the sports side here, NHL 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not only was it great, but it beat out Madden 10 for the best sports game at the VGAs.
[SPEAKER_02]: A hockey game beating out a football game?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we've also got a contribution from Marin, Beatles Rock Band, which actually I'm going to have to go with as well, but he knows she'd say that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_09]: Heart, heart, heart.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beatles Rock Band was an excellent implementation.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm still opting for DJ Hero as my music game of the year, but I...
[SPEAKER_02]: I do respect greatly Beatles rock band and I think it was badly needed.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think getting it out was a big achievement.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think so too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to get everybody on stage at E3 to announce it, that was epic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, having Yoko Ono, George Harrison's wife, McCartney, Ringo Starr, all on stage at once, pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty, pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of some of the things that happened this year, just kind of like trekking back, and it's kind of funny to look back sometimes on what happened in previous months, kind of see where that put us this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just quickly going through some of the big things that happened this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you look at January and some of the things that happened there, a lot of restructuring and layoff news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony did some restructuring and announced a $2.9 billion loss.
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and interesting because maybe that indie development is going to lead to more digital distribution as we talked about before.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on to February.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the things that happened there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, more losses.
[SPEAKER_02]: EA cut back 11% of their workforce.
[SPEAKER_02]: Activision, Blizzard, I don't know how the hell they lost money, but they sure did.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they did not do any huge layoffs, though, at that time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, though, what I thought was interesting, Wii Fit sold 777,000 copies in January.
[SPEAKER_02]: That news would then roll over to February.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: WeFit was obviously a big piece of gaming in 2009 that none of us named in our game of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Has WeFit been good or bad for gaming?
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_09]: I wouldn't say in terms of gaming, but it's definitely been good in terms of making exercise enjoyable.
[SPEAKER_09]: WeFit is not something that I really consider to be a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I consider it to be a tool.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a fun tech demo.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Game Game Game Game
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to see a party-free 2010?
[SPEAKER_03]: I would like to see them actually go back to what worked before.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't necessarily need the change.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make some good side-scrolling games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make some good games that utilize the technology.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everything doesn't have to be a party game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everything doesn't have to be a waggle-fest.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do it what worked!
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I don't understand it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had, you know, a lot of games selling back in the day of, like, the Super Nintendo and stuff, and even the NES and whatnot, and they didn't really rely on a lot of gimmicks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Made Mode 7, but I mean, come on, it wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and soon TVs later in the year, although of course that never happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think about OnLive in the future of that?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that if it works like they say it is, then it's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it'll be pretty popular because everybody's really digging the streaming stuff nowadays, especially with Netflix and other video services out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Steam as a digital distribution platform has done pretty well, so kind of combining the two...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the news as we moved into April.
[SPEAKER_02]: Will Wright left EA.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of forgot that that happened, but that's when an epic designer leaves a big company like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You always kind of wonder what the heck is going on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, the disappointing sales of Chinatown Wars.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember how in 2008, Nintendo got up there at E3 and said, hey, we've got a Grand Theft Auto game coming to the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be awesome, and it's going to, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, so you can do it, but you just didn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: You didn't really put the effort into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead, you made these little mini games that involved the DS stylus.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess that's neat and all, but it just really didn't hook me in like the other ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess my standards have gone up since 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, not a lot happened in May, but then we got into June, and June was, of course, the big E3 Expo.
[SPEAKER_02]: And at E3 was when we got a hell of a lot of news, including the unveiling of Project Natal from Microsoft, Sony showing their ice cream cone controller, whatever that thing is supposed to be for their motion sensing, and then Nintendo showing the Wii Vitality Sensor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looking back on E3 this year, any kind of thoughts about how the show went or kind of where we are now six months later?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think everyone was still pooping themselves over Natal.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that Nintendo disappointed once again, you know, not as bad as the year prior, but this year was kind of pathetic.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, I'm sorry, the Wii Vitality Sensor... Okay, remember with the Wii Fit Balance Board, it's like, oh, it's going to revolutionize how you do these exercise games and stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: And great, now we have a bunch of these games that have the Balance Board sensors in there, and we use it, and okay, that's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a real huge step, I guess, but it's neat nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Vitality Sensor, I'm sorry, I don't see what the point is of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just don't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know they're gonna have that stupid game, We Relax, come out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Great, you'll sell some copies of that, but I think it's crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: What happened to that Metroid game that Team Ninja was doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, we saw a neat little preview at E3 and, like, literally not a damn thing since then.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's promises of stuff that'll come later on, like, next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I'll be surprised if that game comes out this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will be surprised.
[SPEAKER_02]: 2010, you mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, 2010.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll be surprised if it makes it out in 2010, but... I don't know, it's just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: They're coming!
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't worry, just be patient.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta play devil's advocate here, though, because of what I just said.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the other things Nintendo revealed at E3 this year, which was not expected by any means, was new Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wii, which, I'm sorry, is one of the best games that came out this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: It really was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's pretty sad that that's the best game that came out this year from Nintendo, a company that, you know, had really innovative games in the past.
[SPEAKER_03]: All have been, you know, really great titles, except recently some of their games that they released are kind of, eh,
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, seriously, what did they release this year?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me think here.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we had Wii Fit Plus, which was basically just a port of Wii Fit now with some added crap on there, and we're going to throw it in for a discount just to capitalize on Wii Fit again because people may have forgotten about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had Wii Sports Resort, which comes with an extra sensor.
[SPEAKER_03]: That really should have been in the Wii Remote to begin with.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of what they really promised with the Wii from the get-go, but, oh, we just couldn't do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was great!
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a great game that came out this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that, okay, and then Metroid Prime Trilogy, which was just a rehash of some old stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then they added the new Play Control series, which is basically ported GameCube games that they've added some Wii controls to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Great!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm glad you have the ability to port GameCube games and add Waggle to them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Way to be innovative.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, it's just, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: I kid you not, the descriptions are almost identical, except they changed the name of the game, because some people might get fooled by that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what did they have other than the Zelda game for the DS, which was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, they had some style simulation game, because God forbid there's not enough of those on the DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Between Ubisoft and Dreamcatcher, there's so many damn games for girls.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it just got lost in the fray right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And a lot of things that they released, I think Nintendo thinks that their name's going to sell these titles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's not been the case.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fossil Fighters, hello, there's been other games that have been put out exactly the same as that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just they just don't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm sure they're going to promise some more stuff, maybe Pikmin 3, and then everyone will shit their pants because it's Pikmin 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's going to come out, it's going to be exactly the same as Pikmin 2, just with some extra shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And people are going to buy into it because they're fucking cheap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Galaxy 2 is on the way too
[SPEAKER_03]: New power-ups?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, oh, I take everything back that I said about Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they have new power-ups in there, then, god forbid, game of the year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Super Mario Galaxy 2, yeah, I'm sure that'll be very different than Galaxy 1.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, we added some different levels now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Praise us.
[SPEAKER_03]: All the work's been done on the engine before, but now we have new levels and new gimmicks, and you're gonna think, oh my god, it's so awesome!
[SPEAKER_09]: and Yellen, that same little girly voice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe we'll get Twilight Princess 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be exactly the same as Twilight Princess 1, but it'll have some slightly new levels in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe they'll fuse them and do Majora's Princess.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know there's going to be the Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be the big thing they're going to unveil at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mark my words, 2010 predictions.
[SPEAKER_02]: New Zelda will be the thing that Nintendo tries to redeem themselves with this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what's great about Nintendo, though?
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, anything that you want them to do correctly, they're never going to do anymore because, you know what, you'll buy their shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, I still stand by it.
[SPEAKER_02]: As much as you're calling it recycled garbage and all this stuff, if it's still a good game, like, I think Mario Galaxy 2 has the potential to be really awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Galaxy 1 was great, and if they just improve on that, it's going to get even better.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you can't say that they don't have sequels and rehash shit on the 360 and the PS3 as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, they do, and I call them out for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a game that comes out every year that's a rehash of the last year's game.
[SPEAKER_03]: We call it Madden.
[SPEAKER_03]: And NBA Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: And NBA 2K.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: And God forbid, you know, Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, um... There's a lot of companies that are guilty of that, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: The fact that Nintendo has the balls To go, hey look
[SPEAKER_03]: We're taking these GameCube games and we're putting them on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're new.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they're now on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they have... We didn't really do anything to them other than change the controls.
[SPEAKER_02]: If that's the case, where the fuck is my F-Zero?
[SPEAKER_02]: That is the one GameCube game I have yet to see come over to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: And might I point out, not only is it just a GameCube game, it was the best fucking GameCube game that ever came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm sorry, they have to do Donkey Kong's Jungle Beat first because apparently people like that
[SPEAKER_03]: Game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It didn't sell very well with the bongos, but hey, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: We can also do a Donkey Kong racing game that used to be with the bongos, but uh, no, now we're just gonna add some sort of rival controls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Three words.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_02]: Donkey Kong is best left to the memory of the Super Nintendo, awesomely 3D rendered games, Donkey Kong countries that were there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm over it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where's my F-Zero game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, where's my good updated Star Fox?
[SPEAKER_03]: And they always manage to take their sequels and fuck them over in some way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Perfect example, Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_03]: The best racing game on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sequel, set to come out, ExciteBots Trick Racing.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the fuck did you do there?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, people like Transformers.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the fuck does throwing a pie at a clown have anything to do with racing?
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't have anything to do with racing.
[SPEAKER_03]: and God forbid they just shit on that sequel.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I was an idiot and bought it because, you know, I had hope that it was going to be as good as the original, but no, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fool me once, you will not fool me twice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see some chat, and the chat's kind of flying right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't really keep up with it, but I do see GameGuru saying something about the God of War collection.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's God of War 1 and 2 in HD.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rawr!
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, does that fall into... At least it's in HD.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they improve the graphics on the Wii games, on those new play control games, hey, that's different, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that's, you know... What, would they have widescreen now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I take it all back.
[SPEAKER_02]: F-Zero on the GameCube had widescreen support.
[SPEAKER_02]: It had, if I remember right, progressive scan support and all that fancy stuff on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_03]: Same with God of War 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: That also had 720p support through a code.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can we move on past the Nintendo hatred?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes we can.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the thousands of subscribers we just lost.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the Nintendo fanboys crying in the corner.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still stand by, you know what, again, the thing that pisses me off about Nintendo is that it's not that I don't disagree with Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Most of what he's saying I pretend to agree with.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then they release that one fucking game that's so fucking great I have to have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it justifies the purchase of a Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you have all this shit
[SPEAKER_02]: Out there flooding the market in that one game on the goddamn Wii that you just aren't going to get anywhere else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like new Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just like, okay, like Mario Kart, you know, Super Mario Kart and Mario Kart 64.
[SPEAKER_03]: The best fucking deathmatch, you know, battle mode ever was in those games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the GameCube and the Wii version, they just like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's just fucking ruin it.
[SPEAKER_12]: We don't know what plays that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll just fuck it over.
[SPEAKER_12]: You think that's how the boardroom meetings go?
[SPEAKER_03]: let's fuck this game up just for fun today we're in a recession let's have fun with it all they had to do was leave it exactly the same and just make new levels that's it, no improvement needed it was perfect the way it was but somehow they just go throwing it together and they just ruined the whole thing because they wanted to improve upon it way to go have you ever heard the phrase if it ain't broke don't fix it
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: What happened to Midway?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Loki's ranting just got the temperature up in here about 10 degrees, so I needed to cool off a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that it was just, it was bound to happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, they've been losing money.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know, especially given, I think, weren't they still the ones who solely owned the Mortal Kombat franchise for a while?
[SPEAKER_09]: Those games certainly weren't doing much of anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, sadly, I mean, they had the DC Universe game, but it was... That was crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it was just inevitable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because apparently Blitz League did not pay the bills.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then their next genius idea, which thankfully never came out, This is Vegas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, the game that simulates going to Vegas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Partying, driving cars, having sex with women, and gambling.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, some of the news that came out of August Apparently Wii Sports Resort was the best-selling game of August There you go, Loki, I thought I'd mention that just for you And the PlayStation 3 Slim was unveiled So let's get away from Nintendo for a minute here And talk about maybe the PlayStation 3 Because I think this was probably the smartest thing Sony did all year It was something they should have done a year ago Was drop the price down to $2.99 Yes, they were retarded from the get-go Saying, oh yeah, our system's gonna be $5.99
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't you remember that YouTube?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I know we played it on this show like a million times.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the press conference in under a minute that would go $599 US dollars, $599 US dollars, and just like over and over again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that really was the moment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like everybody was like so jazzed about the PlayStation 3 and then they're like, it's going to be $599.
[SPEAKER_02]: And everybody's like, I remember us watching that on TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were like, are you fucking kidding me?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Africa.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome Kaz Harai Ridge Racer
[SPEAKER_04]: The essence of the PlayStation DNA is real change and the consumers are ready.
[SPEAKER_05]: Genji 2 is an action game which is based on Japanese history.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ridge Racer!
[SPEAKER_05]: Being based on history, the stages of the game will also be based on famous battles which actually took place in ancient Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: So here's this giant enemy crab.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ridge Racer!
[SPEAKER_05]: and Mew attack its weak point for massive damage.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 3 will retail for 599 US dollars, 599 US dollars, 599 US dollars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Giant enemy crab.
[SPEAKER_04]: 599, 599, 599 US dollars.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ridge Racer!
[SPEAKER_02]: That is the best thing to come out of the decade by the way in gaming was that little one minute clip from YouTube user Macaw45.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why didn't they do it sooner, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why didn't Sony figure out, maybe we should have dropped the price a long time ago?
[SPEAKER_02]: Were they just stubborn with the whole blue rate thing?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just a matter of if they would have dropped the price sooner, they would have sold more units, but they would have also lost their ass from the cost of the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the problem was just building a system with that much in components in the first place.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, it's tough to justify, you know, so they end up having to cut some corners and stuff, and once the, you know, prices of the components came down, they could actually justify dropping the price of the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a little late, so they have some catching up to do, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: September, some other companies followed along with some price drops.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Wii dropped to $200.
[SPEAKER_02]: That happened in September.
[SPEAKER_02]: And some of the information came out about the PSP Go that there would be no conversion that happens.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like if you own a UMD and you want to upgrade to the PSP Go, you can rebuy your game because of licensing issues.
[SPEAKER_02]: licensing issues.
[SPEAKER_03]: But wait, the PSP Go wasn't confirmed yet, was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think by September it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: They showed it at E3, dummy.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it wasn't at E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was in that back room, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: You were wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could have sworn it was there.
[SPEAKER_02]: PSP Go was shown at Gamescom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: So by September, Gamescom would happen anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, and then moving on into kind of more recent things that happened to kind of sum up 2009.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, when the PSP Go finally did launch in October, that added 100 PSP games to the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was really some of the biggest stuff that came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Otherwise, some of the stuff about...
[SPEAKER_02]: Modern Warfare 2 was coming out pretty soon and some news about the DSi XL although that hasn't come out yet the news the early news that came out in October DSi XL what do you think it's just it's unnecessary I'm really at the point of all of this that I'm like whatever people are gonna buy it whatever I'm not getting one not yet anyway
[SPEAKER_03]: It's unnecessary, it really is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's keep shrinking down the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh wait, let's make it bigger.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, put the Game Boy Advance slot back in it then.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're going to make it bigger.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh no, we can't do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the point of making the screens bigger?
[SPEAKER_03]: For old people!
[SPEAKER_03]: Because bigger's better!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's for old people.
[SPEAKER_02]: But remember with the Game Boy Advance, smaller was better, hence the micro.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then that didn't sell very well, so they must have said, oh never mind, bigger's better!
[SPEAKER_02]: Right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's a spectator system now, remember?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because people want to watch you play DSi games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then I suggest you put a video out on the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a thought!
[SPEAKER_03]: Play it on your TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yes, I understand that that wouldn't really make sense, you know, playing a DSi on a TV since it's dual screen, but hey, you could maybe put, you know, split the video signal or something, or you could just put the top screen on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bottom screen, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just jamming through the last couple months here because they did just happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: In November, of course, EA cut 1,500 jobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was 17% of their games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Canceled a dozen games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a good year for EA in that department because that was the second big layoff story we got out of EA in the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was also the month where we had a funny story about how World of Warcraft was closed in China for three months, and we kind of joked about what would happen if you couldn't log into World of Warcraft for three months.
[SPEAKER_02]: There would be some people that just wouldn't know what to do with themselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: People would go outdoors.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they would take all my oxygen.
[SPEAKER_02]: What can we do about that?
[SPEAKER_02]: And then one of my favorite rumors that came out in December, that Logitech apparently is making a UMD add-on for the PSP Go.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, how ridiculous is that idea?
[SPEAKER_02]: A, why would that be coming from Logitech?
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless I guess they're doing it on behalf of Sony or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: But still, just what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's dumb.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't that the point?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would you... First off...
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would you buy that?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't understand why you would even pay the money to buy a UMD add-on for a system that was more expensive than the PSP-3000 in the first place.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the PSP-3000 has everything that the Go has, with the exception of the Bluetooth, which is fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I just don't understand why you would do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'd have to be pretty dumb.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just pull the PSP, go off shells already and cut your losses and make a PSP 2 or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that does it for kind of like our year little wrap up there, kind of walking down memory lane and some of the stories there.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to get to the decade in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to kind of just open up the Skype line to kind of talk about the decade and we'll get to that in a minute, but of course we do have some segments we like to do here every week on Orange Lounge Radio and one of them is very important.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's our...
[SPEAKER_02]: moments of angst because there were a lot of stupid people this year and stupid people that robbed things and you know like that guy who stole the Xbox and then played it so they were able to find who they were just a lot of stupidity out there he who shall not be named the lawyer that was disbarred one of my personal highlights of the year 2000 to 2010 and so forth anyhow we're going to call this our FUs of the week but in some regards maybe this is the FUs of the decade I don't know here they are the FUs of the week
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually do have an FU of the week, and that just goes to the TSA for putting in stricter ticket rules, I guess, where your name has to fully match.
[SPEAKER_09]: And my credit card information, you know, when I buy my ticket, it's going to come up under my name as I have it listed for my billing information, which is not exactly how my name shows on my license.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, annoying.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then as far as the year, or the decade, I should say,
[SPEAKER_09]: Um... The... The biggest FU has actually already happened, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's-his-fuck-got-disbarred?
[SPEAKER_09]: If that's not a ginormous FU, I don't know what is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, what are your FUs of the week and the decade?
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh... I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um... Guess... FU to... I don't really have anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess I feeded myself for not being able to play a lot of games during the holiday break.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think a lot of time I wasted trying to get games for my MAME cabinet, which I should just really play on the MAME cabinet, because I have, what, thousands of games on there already, and I haven't touched most of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, uh, why do I need more games?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, because I need more of everything, that's why.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, and then the FU of the decade goes to, uh...
[SPEAKER_03]: God, I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's tough to just nail down one thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess... To Nintendo for disappointing us on a consistent basis.
[SPEAKER_03]: And goddamn it, Embrace Online!
[SPEAKER_02]: My FU of the week... I don't know, I'm not super angsty.
[SPEAKER_02]: My FU of the week goes to... Selfishness.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think there's some selfish people out there I'm learning about and I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: My FU of the decade goes to people that steal things that aren't theirs.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might remember this decade my car was broken into a multitude of times.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had these people talking about, you know, stealing Xboxes and so forth that stupidly sign on to them online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stealing passwords and using them to hack people's account.
[SPEAKER_02]: FU to people that don't have the common decency to not touch shit that isn't theirs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and FU to Proposition 8.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was pretty fucked up too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, back to the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about the segment of the show where we open up ye olde mailbag and see what our listeners have to say?
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be at our mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com address.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have two emails.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_09]: First one, hey, OLR, I was in Spanish class a few days ago and thinking about the new year.
[SPEAKER_09]: We should have been focusing on Spanish.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then I started thinking about really crappy games with peripherals that no one will buy like Band Hero and Tony Hawk Ride.
[SPEAKER_09]: So my question to you is, what are your peripheral predictions for the new year?
[SPEAKER_09]: Personally, mine will be Knife and Fork and stuff like that for a new Cooking Mama game.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've already done that, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know, there's actually a burger flipping ticket game that came out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that we're going to get Bunga Bunga for the home, and it comes with a real finger-to-butt peripheral.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever happened to the table flipping game that was out in Japan?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to see that out here.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: What about here?
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder if Bunga Bunga is actually, or Bunga Bunga or whatever, is emulated in MAME yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go get it, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because if it is, that would be one hell of a fun game to make a peripheral for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as the rest of the email, what I think next year, as far as peripherals go, you already know, it's the motion sensor stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Natal and the ice cream cones from Sony.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those are going to be the huge things, game changers, that come out next year.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're also going to come out with the...
[SPEAKER_09]: I think not just necessarily something that reads your motion, but also I would actually like to see something that doesn't necessarily view your motion as much as checks your coordination.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like it gives you something like a full motion sensing DDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where it gives you your commands and then you have to mimic exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or even charades online.
[SPEAKER_09]: Could you imagine that?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I don't want to see?
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that charades online idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what I don't want to see is this whole brain scanning thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you heard about the brain devices?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like the game that you control with your brain and all this stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like that idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like that at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope that isn't where peripherals go next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like the whole thought reading thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of a little freaky to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Call me a warrior or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a little weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else in the mail rag?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there's still more to that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I have to give you a hard time.
[SPEAKER_09]: As soon as I can find where the crap my thing went to.
[SPEAKER_09]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, I wondered where you guys get your news from.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you have a set or are you all over the place?
[SPEAKER_09]: My favorite right now is GamesWithAZTraffic.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look it up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks, Mike.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you should give somebody a free plug.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I go to Eurogamer for a lot of my stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, another one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, everyone.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is from Spasmator, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seeing as this is topics and questions may possibly run a little long, I opted to send them via email rather than Twitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seeing as it's the end of the year and traditionally everyone seemingly does a top ten list of some sort, why not have OLR and the OLR Army do one?
[SPEAKER_09]: But do one with a twist.
[SPEAKER_09]: What I had in mind was a list of top games that came out this year that you
[SPEAKER_09]: You'd love to have the Hillary Clintons and the Voldemorts of the world be forced to play non-stop for days on end just to drive them all crazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, even crazier than they already happen to be.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, seeing as the year is virtually over, I have two questions.
[SPEAKER_09]: Compared to 2008, how do you feel about 2009 fared in regards to game releases, sales of both consoles and games, as well as improvements to consoles and or their online services, both in terms of actual hardware revisions or...
[SPEAKER_09]: as well as firmware updates.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have no opinion.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's about the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't pay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta say, I think 09's been a lot more disappointing than 08.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we've had a lot of disappointments this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Games getting pushed back, quality of games, you know, don't seem to be up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, there's lots of exceptions to this rule, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, there's been some real gems that have been released this year, but I think layoffs, etc., it's been a lot of disappointment this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think there's a lot of good that came out of this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except for, um, yeah, I got nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: President Cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a good thing that came out this year, that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, two, and as far as 2010 is concerned, is there anything in particular that's been announced that you three are eagerly awaiting?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you have any possible predictions for 2010, or at least something you hope to see happen?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, I hope that, um, we get President Cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, to kind of piggyback on what Loki was ranting about earlier, I would really like to see Nintendo come out at E3 and do the system they should have done last time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand that, you know, Wii was, you know, their gamble.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay for them, they won.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to see them kind of take that up to the next level and catch up finally to where their competitors are at as far as the hardcore gamers are concerned, you know, with the HD and the online and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not going to happen, but I'd like, you asked what I want to see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um,
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm always a big fan of more retro goodness.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I would like to see more retro games coming back.
[SPEAKER_02]: This whole achievements and trophies and cooperative online play.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a big fan of all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish the Virtual Console had achievements within it or ways that I could experience all these old games again with friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: As neat as Virtual Console is for some of the great retro games, it feels very lazy to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just an emulator you're paying for.
[SPEAKER_02]: and, to be fair, Xbox 360 has a lot of these games in their arcade, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not just picking on Nintendo here.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of arcade releases on 360, and Microsoft finally put their foot down on this, was just retro stuff that would throw in some achievements and, you know, I just, I don't know, I just would like to see retro games respected.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has been a decent year for retro gaming.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it has been a decent year, though, for retro gaming already.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, because we've gotten certainly a lot of nods.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, Bionic Commando and...
[SPEAKER_09]: I really, though, want to see something really innovative.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to see something really original.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to see a game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to see working designs come back and bring out all the cool stuff from Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I want.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm holding my breath.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that it for that email?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or is there more?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadar.com is the place to send your emails.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now we'll get into the decade a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't want to linger too long on this, but it's interesting that we're getting to the close of another decade here, the O's or whatever we're going to end up calling these in the past.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Games have kind of evolved with many of you.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, not all of our listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: Heck, the hosts don't fit into that age bracket.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm considerably older than that, you know, as we all are.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, I realize that that's where a lot of the listener base is.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just how much games have changed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to kind of rewind 10 years and show you how far we've come.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here are some of the big things that happened in the year 2000.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 2 was launched.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo finally sold its 100 millionth Game Boy handheld console.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sega launched SegaNet into the year 2000, and that's when the Dreamcast Championships took off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the games that came out in the year 2000.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Sims came out January 31st of the year 2000.
[SPEAKER_02]: That it did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was almost 10 years old.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thief 2 came out in the year 2000.
[SPEAKER_02]: Vagrant Story, EverQuest came out in the year 2000, Deuce X, Diablo 2 was from the year 2000, that game feels even older, Final Fantasy 9 had a release in Japan in the year 2000, Chrono Cross came out in 2000, Dragon Quest 7, American McGee's Alice,
[SPEAKER_02]: The Legend of Zelda Majora's Mask was in the year 2000.
[SPEAKER_09]: What else we also had that year?
[SPEAKER_09]: Seaman.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that, really?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not on this list, but probably.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seaman, did they have a lot of Dreamcast stuff on there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they account for Dreamcast on this list.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that, no, Seaman might have either been 2000 or 2001.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, the Dreamcast stuff was all early.
[SPEAKER_02]: Escape from Monkey Island, Tekken Tag Tournament, Final Fantasy 9 got its release over here too, Skies of Arcadia, Banjo-Tooie, here's some Dreamcasts, Grandia 2 came out towards the end of the year 2000.
[SPEAKER_09]: Grandia 2, Power Stone
[SPEAKER_02]: and a completely different generation of video games because the launch of the new generation, if you will, of games didn't really happen until, what about 2005, 2006?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think E3 is when we started hearing about this new round of consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you go back, I mean, heck, the GameCube just came out in what, like 01?
[SPEAKER_02]: Now we have the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, we've gone through many, many different game systems in this generation.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we would have had that all touched this last 10 years we had the Dreamcast,
[SPEAKER_02]: The PlayStation 2, the PlayStation 3, the GameCube, the Wii, the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft got into gaming in these past few years, or not even 10 years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course, I'm not even counting handhelds and the countless amounts of those and other one-off systems that came out as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's going to be interesting in the next 10 years, in the next generation, just how far games...
[SPEAKER_02]: Go will probably be another generation.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be talking about the PlayStation 4 and other Xboxes and maybe other companies that decide to get into gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or maybe one of these companies will buy another.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be very interesting to see what happens.
[SPEAKER_02]: Before we open up the phone calls, and yes, some folks in chat want to point out, OLR started in 2002.
[SPEAKER_02]: So while we didn't exist 10 years ago, we're getting into our 8th year of broadcasting.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's quite some time.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty impressive.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know this is a very difficult question.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a very difficult question.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what do you guys think were some of the best games to come out of the decade?
[SPEAKER_02]: The best games to come out of all freaking decade, knowing that you have all of those systems available to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not just maybe what was important to you, but what you think was important to gaming in general.
[SPEAKER_02]: The decade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, want to start?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you have anything?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR Max 2 in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It got people back in the arcade because you had stuff that you were working to unlock.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Fifth Mix too.
[SPEAKER_02]: That came out around the same time.
[SPEAKER_02]: These were also games that brought us together.
[SPEAKER_02]: We wouldn't have OL Army.
[SPEAKER_02]: As much shit as we give Konami and their music division now, ten years ago was a different story.
[SPEAKER_02]: We praise them.
[SPEAKER_02]: We love them.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they made a lot of mistakes, sadly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Grand Theft Auto 3
[SPEAKER_03]: Marvel vs. Capcom 2 Final Fantasy X Final Fantasy X
[SPEAKER_03]: Only MMO.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I played a little Matrix Online, but that sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gosh, yeah, it's tough.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, anything you want to throw out there as far as your games of the decade?
[SPEAKER_09]: Portal.
[SPEAKER_09]: Definitely Portal.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seaman.
[SPEAKER_09]: DDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, keep in mind, I got DDR for home in 2000 on Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rod Calibur, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rod Calibur is important.
[SPEAKER_09]: You remember Rod Calibur, don't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's when you play Soul Calibur with the Rod.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rod Calibur.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, I'd have to say, probably as far as shooters go, I'd say Ikaruga, getting Gradius V. There was a lot of good games that came out, though, in the decade.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah, but I'd really say, well, if I say Portal, I should say Narbacular Drop, because that's really the game that gave us Portal.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of people thinking in interesting directions, especially with having the Dreamcast come out, the Naomi system, the Hikaru after that, although I still want Planet Harrier, where is it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't work, I tried it during the beginning of the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Damn!
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, it still doesn't work in MAME.
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as my answer to the question, I've answered this on another show, but to kind of repeat it here on Orange Lounge Radio, I think I would split it up into a few categories.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you left yourself on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie's trying to have a sidebar conversation with me while I'm trying to talk on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, what was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yes, the game of the decade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some things that came up.
[SPEAKER_02]: My personal favorite game of the decade I think was probably Animal Crossing was one I really remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I loved how you, you know, as much slack as that game got for running around doing nothing, if you really went far with it where you could like go into somebody else's village, you know, you brought your friend over with a memory card.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I remember we used to do this shit all the time is that somebody would come over and we'd visit the town and try to get their townspeople to say dirty words and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also the fact that it had all the retro Nintendo games in it before Nintendo started gouging the prices for all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just loved that game when it first came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it kind of sucks that the game's franchise has been milked through the DS and the Wii versions.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just not really as fun anymore as it used to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that very first Animal Crossing that was on the GameCube in America... Yes, I realize it's based off a Nintendo 64 game, but I'm not counting that because that didn't have an impact on our culture here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: That first Animal Crossing on the GameCube I think was probably...
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the best gaming experiences I had all decade.
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as on a technical level, I know Loki's going to hate me for this, but I think Wii Sports, you have to recognize, is one of the best games of the decade because it got people to play games who don't play games.
[SPEAKER_02]: You see Wii Sports in nursing homes, for Christ's sake.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we didn't want those people playing games!
[SPEAKER_02]: You still have to recognize, though, that's still money in the gaming industry that can someday make a game you might want to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it won't, because they'll be catering to these people that don't really care about games, but they like Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: But without Wii Sports, and basically the Wii in general, would we have Project Natal and the Sony Ice Cream Cones, which may bring us the games you want to play, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm still skeptical on what they're going to bring us.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm skeptical too, but there is a possibility it could be pretty fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: World of Warcraft
[SPEAKER_02]: Haters gonna hate.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know there's a lot of people that are anti-MMOs out there, but I think World of Warcraft did amazing stuff for online games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the way Blizzard kind of caters to the different audiences, Blizzard is like the best PC game maker.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Name a bad Blizzard game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chirp!
[SPEAKER_09]: Super Mario Galaxy
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just saying Super Mario Galaxy 2 is not going to be that great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number 9, Half-Life 2 Definitely I think sometimes a forgotten about game from all of us console hoarding folks but the Orange Box did bring this back to the forefront Half-Life 2 was a hugely important PC game just for the way it integrated story into the shooter game and the graphical level and just the fact that the game you didn't really go from level to level, you were immersed
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I like this entry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this is often overlooked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number 7, Bejeweled from the year 2001.
[SPEAKER_02]: The original Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can totally see that too.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think a lot of folks forget what PopCap and casual gaming has done for gaming in this decade.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's a very important game to note.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number 6, they put Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think I need to say anything else with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number 5, they put Halo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think the Xbox would have survived if it wasn't for Halo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we'd be looking at the Xbox kind of like we look at the Atari Jaguar, honestly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Xbox kind of pushed, and especially Halo 2, kind of pushed the Xbox to what ended up happening on the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Halo was huge.
[SPEAKER_02]: And certainly Yahoo and their video game related site does too.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, Rob, it's all about Pet Society and Farmville.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number four was Guitar Hero, they put on the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's very interesting, having done this as a music game based show, when it was a very niche thing, it's very interesting that we have kind of watched music games explode into the mainstream, and a lot of this is because of Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they finally did what...
[SPEAKER_02]: Konami should have thought to do a long fucking time ago or excuse me well Konami of Japan should have taken a risk on a long time ago and stopped being so bullheaded when it comes to releasing stuff in the US and that is put in the songs that people in the US want to play
[SPEAKER_02]: and granted, I know those of us here in studio and a lot of our long time listeners were fans of stuff that Konami was putting in those music games a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we were a niche audience and those games were never going to break through.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guitar Hero finally broke it through and I think that's important to note.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it debuted in our living room.
[SPEAKER_09]: In my living room.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys had like a sneak peek.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wasn't here that day but you and Loki were on the news doing some sneak peek thing with Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just because I happen to have a big TV that wouldn't you know
[SPEAKER_09]: had a better refresh rate.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to point out a lot of our chatters, because I'm kind of keeping one eye on chat.orangelongerator.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some interesting comments.
[SPEAKER_02]: GameGuru, Half-Life 2 also introduced Steam onto the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the first one that had Steam in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then quite a few folks yelling out, Pagle, better than Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Peggle.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do love Peggle too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially on iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think without Bejeweled, you wouldn't have Peggle.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I can see why they opted to put Peggle on the list.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I mean, shoot, without Tetris or Puzzle Bobble, without Plinko, we wouldn't have Peggle.
[SPEAKER_02]: The number three game on Yahoo's list, The Sims, was the most important game of the decade.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think The Sims was pretty fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the best PC-selling game for a long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Modern Warfare 2 I got nothing
[SPEAKER_02]: Grand Theft Auto 3 was really the first sandbox-y type of game like that, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: And just opened up this whole new type of video game, practically.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to admit, usually I look at those lists and roll my eyes, but maybe with the exception of Wii Fit, that was a pretty good list, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, see what you guys think about there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of our folks in chat disagree.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know though, I realize Grand Theft Auto 3 might not be the type of game you play, but think about that whole sandbox type of game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, Grand Theft Auto was really kind of the pioneer in that, and I think without Grand Theft Auto 3, you wouldn't have that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, we're going to go ahead and open up our Skype line and see what you guys have to say about the year in gaming and the decade in gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: And honestly, it's just an open forum tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever you guys want to talk about, it's our last show of the decade, so please give us a call.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR is the number to call, or you can always reach us on Skype at username OrangeLoungeRadio is the place to call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Meanwhile, while we wait for some calls to come in, do we have any last minute stories, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't been looking at last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'm sure we do have some.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh good, you're saved because we have a call coming in right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's go ahead and take this call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, this is Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we're talking about, of course, the year in games, the decade in games, or really whatever you want to talk about tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, first of all, I want to wish you a Merry Christmas, a late Merry Christmas, and a Happy New Year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Same to you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I want to talk about my game of the year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which is?
[SPEAKER_01]: Forza Motorsport 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: That hasn't been mentioned yet on the show, but I can see that as somebody's choice.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is it about this game that makes it the game of the year for you?
[SPEAKER_01]: I can explain in only one phrase.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's racing simulation for dummies.
[SPEAKER_02]: And why does that make it game of the year?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, Mario Kart Wii is kind of racing simulation for dummies, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, Mario Kart Wii is more like an arcade style of racing, while Forza is more of a simulation like Gran Turismo, where if you make a bad turn, you will crash.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you go too fast, you'll crash, and if you do everything wrong, you'll crash.
[SPEAKER_01]: And not like in Gran Turismo or any other racing game,
[SPEAKER_01]: Your car has damages and possibly, well, not possibly, and it will affect your racing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it just the realism in that regard that makes this the game of the year for you or is it like a graphical achievement or what is it that just makes this game so awesome?
[SPEAKER_01]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_01]: in tuning, you can paint it, you can make the stickers or the calls, and make your own car.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like the teddy bear workshop, but in car form.
[SPEAKER_01]: And like I said, it's a pretty easy game to pick up, because the options let you begin to play, you have a lot of things that help you
[SPEAKER_01]: to race along and complete the challenges and all the tournaments and races you have to compete in.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if you're truly a racing expert, it also has all that other stuff that makes you like the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It makes a real simulation.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, the only criteria that you really have to use is the type of game that you enjoy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just your criteria and no one else's.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if that's your game of the year, then so be it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we appreciate the call and you chiming in on your game of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are there any other quick thoughts you have for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, other than that, I think that also Street Fighter IV is also a candidate for game of the year.
[SPEAKER_01]: A game that offers a studio name, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: How do you say it?
[SPEAKER_01]: The rebirth of fighting games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It definitely did energize fighting games in kind of a new way this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's interesting, having played Tekken 6 this week, I feel like Street Fighter 4 did inspire some things in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, thank you so much, Actdeft, for the call.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have a great new year, and be safe, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks, you too.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, later.
[SPEAKER_02]: again if you want to give us a call 1-877-GAME-OLR our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio we are open and taking some calls and I know the call the phones have been ringing so we're going to wait here and try to get a call when it comes through of course now that I say that nobody's calling in it's like everybody's waiting because they still hear Actdeft on the line oh we got another call coming in hi you're on Orange Lounge Radio who's this
[SPEAKER_07]: This is that one across the ocean, Akiripper.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, Akiripper!
[SPEAKER_02]: So good to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are things in your neck of the woods?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's quite fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have, like, mostly fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's, like, what is it?
[SPEAKER_07]: We have, like, a few feet of snow.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we have, like, well, what is it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, 20 minus degrees Celsius for a night, like, around minus something to something degrees.
[SPEAKER_07]: and, well, yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Game of the year is Sims 3, judging by the amounts that I've played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What makes Sims 3 your game of the year?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure DarkSakura wouldn't argue with that, but what was it for you that made that game for you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm new to this whole Sims game, so to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sims 3 was the first Sims game that I really got addicted to.
[SPEAKER_07]: Add to the following fact that I haven't played WoW in almost a year now.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, well, there is that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then there is the following fact that my computers tend to explode every new MMO release.
[SPEAKER_07]: It happened with Warhammer last year, and it happened with Aeon.
[SPEAKER_07]: and, well, once I get to fix my computers, I have no desire to play any of those MMOs, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think it is?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, we heard a lot this year about ION possibly being the first game that's finally going to really challenge WoW, and then all of a sudden it kind of landed with this big, you know, like it just landed with a thud.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, why is it that no MMO can take on WoW, you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: In my case, I don't know, since, well, as I said, my computer tends to just die a few weeks after it's been released, or the first week it is released.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, well, there seems to be this unlucky... I have this sudden streak of unluck, and it's quite annoying.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other mentions, well, on Game of the Year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shadow Complex and Dragon Age Origins.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even though, Dragon Age Origins, as been said before, because of the only games I play is mostly like The Sims 3,
[SPEAKER_07]: So I can't play, haven't played since Dragon Age Origins that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's a game that wasn't really mentioned before as a possible Game of the Year contender, and I think definitely a lot of big, big fans of that game, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, other than that, well, other than that, well, on the personal playing, well, this year I actually got a 360, so, well, yay on me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Supposedly so.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people joined in the Xbox 360 Club and the PS3 Club this year, too, with the Slim.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, Akira Ripper, we've got to let you go so we can get some more calls, but thank you so much for the call and getting in tonight, all right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a good new year.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Game of the Year Game of the Decade
[SPEAKER_00]: My game of the year definitely was Beatles Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_00]: As DarkSakura knows, because she was at my house visiting in the summer, I am a very, very, very big Beatles fan.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it was nice to get a rock band game that had a lot of songs that I know, as opposed to most of them where I don't know a lot of the songs because I'm an old fart and I only listen to oldies music.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: It was put together beautifully, too, I think is one of the great things about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just visually, it's a cool game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, that bass was awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it's really great, and I still like every time that I play through the game and I play the end, there's like one part where Paul starts to sing end in the end, and I'm like, I love you, Paul!
[SPEAKER_00]: It's so great!
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_00]: Game of the Decade Game of the Decade Game of the Decade Game of the Decade Game of the Decade
[SPEAKER_00]: Game of the Decade was kind of more difficult.
[SPEAKER_00]: I decided to go with something that came out actually at the beginning of the decade, and that was Diablo 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: We mentioned that in our 2000 list, yeah?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, and I think Diablo 2 definitely paved the way for a lot of the kind of games that we enjoy now, like World of Warcraft, Warcraft 3, things like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was just overall a really good game, and
[SPEAKER_00]: I still play that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's still a lot of people playing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's still no Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's still a lot of people playing Diablo 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's funny you kind of say that Diablo 2 paved the way for games like WoW because I really do agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, I used to kind of joke in World of Warcraft that it really should have just been called World of Diablo because that's kind of how it plays.
[SPEAKER_02]: It plays a little more like Diablo than it is Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_00]: but yeah so I mean that was you know like there's so many great games that came out this decade but I think Diablo 2 really paved the way for a lot of other games and it was just overall really you know a good game like I said I still play it so you know if it's a game that you can play 10 years later then that's something worthwhile.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's a darn good pick, so I'm not going to argue with you there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe even though I picked something different, I can certainly see where Diablo 2, without that, we would not have had WoW.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's a very good pick.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Battle.net and this whole infrastructure they had to build for that, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's something that's continuing to evolve for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, anything else on your mind tonight before we get to some more calls?
[SPEAKER_00]: I know that's it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know you guys are ringing off the hook because I've tried calling in a few times before I got through.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I'll go ahead and let you go.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it was nice chatting with you guys again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was very good to chat with you too.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think though that we should take this opportunity though for a plug.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: So something's going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm joking, obviously.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what's going on, you guys?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, we've had our long-running segment of my blog, which is Monday's Comic Mania, and it's just where DarkSakura and I kind of blog about upcoming comics in the week.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so we decided, like last week when I was there, to just kind of play around with the idea of doing a podcast of it, and we got a lot of positive feedback.
[SPEAKER_00]: So we are starting to do that on a regular basis, and we actually did record our second episode today.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was pretty fun too.
[SPEAKER_02]: So where can they download the podcast if they want to check that out?
[SPEAKER_00]: If they want to check that out, they can go to AvengersTower.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: An Affiliate Program
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah, you want me to do it after the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll be happy to do that for you tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, thank you, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, ToaGak in our chatroom, chat.orange.radio.com, wants us to fight over Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we will have to settle this in a battle of strip poker, clearly, is the only possible answer.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right, well, we'll make it a date next time that I'm up in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be one hot date, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: And no, it will not be broadcast on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Maren, thank you so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_02]: You take care and have a great new year, okay?
[SPEAKER_00]: You too.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bochikawa on chat says they're just trying to bribe me with the introduction speech.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's get to another call.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this is going to be our last call of the night.
[SPEAKER_02]: And from what I understand, the 1-877 number is not working, and I apologize for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what the hell is going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be one of those things I don't find out about until the show starts, so I apologize.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, Rama, you're on the phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, you couldn't have an end-of-year show without me, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: You do seem like a fitting personality to have here at the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_11]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just wanted to give what I thought was my game of the year.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, please.
[SPEAKER_11]: What was your game of the year?
[SPEAKER_11]: Ghostbusters, the video game.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was it about this game?
[SPEAKER_02]: What made it so goddamn awesome?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know how whenever they do a movie to video game, the video game generally sucks donkey balls.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ghostbusters the video game is one of those shining gems where it came out really good granted it's not really based off the movie on the same token it's like a sequel to the first two movies but you still kind of go through elements of the first two movies as you play the game which I thought was fun
[SPEAKER_02]: Game of the Year Game of the Year
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: Game of the Decade.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, this is so much.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think I can really pinpoint a Game of the Decade.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think I really could.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'd actually have to sit there and think about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I don't think a lot of people can truly, even though we read this list off of Yahoo and so forth and said, you know, they did a pretty good job, at least of where to start.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think you will truly be able to know what the biggest games of the decade were until about five years from now.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you're really able to accurately look back and say, okay, what games really shaped where we're at now?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can kind of do that a little bit with the earlier games in the decade.
[SPEAKER_02]: For instance, we were having a chat earlier about how Diablo 2 ultimately shaped World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I think...
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be interesting to see.
[SPEAKER_02]: If some of these things like Natal and the Sony ice cream cone fail, then you can say that maybe Wii Sports wasn't as big as we thought it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it really was just a flash in the pan.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if these two things blow up, then it kind of adds value to Wii Sports in a way.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I can't really say on the PC side of things with Diablo because I grew up mostly doing console gaming.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I had a PC, but nothing worthy of playing half these games that are out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: And when I saw some of these games in the store, I was always drawn towards the console games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and that's a lot of people in that same boat.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of people also the exact opposite.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just can't get into the consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have to play on the PC with the keyboard and the mouse or it just doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's one of the reasons why I don't play Halo.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Ranma, you're going to be the last call of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you have anything else you want to share with our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, a couple of things.
[SPEAKER_11]: Number one, a few episodes back, you had mentioned whatever happened to TradeWest.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think a couple of years after they did Double Dragon, they were acquired by Midway.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: So they're pretty much no more, is my assumption.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that makes sense, because I want to say Midway did some Double Dragon games later on, so that makes total sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: And last thing I'll leave this note on to you, Jamie, Matt, thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, really.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I tune in every Sunday to listen to you guys talk about gaming.
[SPEAKER_11]: And from time to time, you guys move off of gaming, talk about stuff in your personal lives, which do affect all of us.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I like the fact that we can come together as a family and discuss some of these things like Proposition 8 and so forth.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was something I really appreciate.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was like that one time, you know,
[SPEAKER_11]: deviate from the gaming talk about something that's more important more of an impact in our lives that we need to discuss and see how we all feel about that so that's something I appreciate and you know what thank you
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_02]: It makes us feel very good about what we do, certainly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that sometimes I'm kind of joking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes my role on the show is to try and make sure we get back to the games at some point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, I've certainly, with some of the things you mentioned, kind of gone astray myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm really thankful that the audience...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: is astounding and it's been something that's kind of grown through this whole decade and it's going to continue on over the next few... We are the LL Army.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like, you know, at first I felt like I should be kind of offended that you're bringing in personal stuff but then I realized if you guys don't talk about it and bring it up, who is?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, we all listen to you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're like the voice of gaming to us.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, we're like one giant happy mafia family.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh God, don't put that responsibility on us or we might get scared.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've already got a whole back full of tattoos now.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: We want you to come back and see us too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fanime was a blast I'm planning on it and working on bringing Jodea, Misty I'm working on it one way or another even if that means I gotta pack them in boxes and ship them Metal Gear Solid Snake style we'll be there for the 4th of July I'm actually wanting to get to New York I would love to find my way up there sometime
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, it's been since I was 17 years old was the last time.
[SPEAKER_09]: The one and only time, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I went once when I was an infant, so therefore I don't remember it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that was the last time I went to New York.
[SPEAKER_11]: Look at it this way, Amy.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you come out here, Patty's has a room just for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: The bed is ready and everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: It says DarkSakura's guest room right there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just looking for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: So who's got 400 bucks I can borrow, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sister Act's supposed to be on Broadway this next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm coming out there to see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Ranma, this is also going on the longest call of the decade.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I have to say thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it was all worth it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a wonderful night.
[SPEAKER_02]: And thank you for being a longtime supporter of the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And really a lot of people that called in tonight were in that same boat.
[SPEAKER_02]: So thank you, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_11]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, apologies to those that didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apologies that the 877 number apparently was borked and I was unaware.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't do that on purpose.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apologize to you guys who weren't able to get through because of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we are going to leave it at that note.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course we'll be back here next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: We always are.
[SPEAKER_02]: To do it all again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take more calls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do more emails.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Until...
[SPEAKER_02]: Our lives change and we're just not able to do it anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't know when that's going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to focus on that right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's just focus on what a great decade it's been for video games and it's just going to continue to grow and who knows what the future holds.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's that part of the show where we go around to get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, quickly, are there any last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot to have Loki clear those out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just really quickly, stupid things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like I mentioned before, Dark Void coming out from Capcom.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is also going to be a DSi game coming out as well for Dark Void that's being done in the 8-bit retro style.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's going to be kind of a side-scroller game, so that's going to be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll be out in January for $5.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does look neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aliens vs Predators
[SPEAKER_03]: Prinny is getting a sequel on the PSP, Prinny 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's about, apparently, you have to reclaim Etna's stolen underwear.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, the game is actually called Prinny 2, Dawn of the Great Pantsu War.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'll be out in Japan on March 25th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pantsu?
Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all I had.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and apparently, and I read this and just said...
[SPEAKER_03]: That's stupid, but hey, I'll add it to the show roll.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, John Gosselin's Wii was stolen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who gives a shit about that douchebag?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let him go to the cemetery of news people we just don't care about anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: He is no longer relevant.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bam.
[SPEAKER_02]: Done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who cares that he had a Wii that got stolen?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, there's also a free New Year's theme for Xbox Live, so you can download that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yippee skippee.
[SPEAKER_02]: But look, who cares about some a-hole in his Wii?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I don't think people should steal things even if the guy is a douchebag.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now when you steal it, people just report on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now you've done a double bad thing by stealing his Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, I don't mean to end this on a negative note.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: My final thought is I need to install more games on my main cabinet.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought is I hope I get enough sleep because I gotta go back to work tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tanaro.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: I only have three words, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_02]: A very lovely thought to end on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guys, don't forget about Orange Lounge Revolution's second mix, the awesome tribute project that's out there that our fans put together.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the information is available on OrangeLoungeRadio.com as well as information on the OLR Madness, what used to be the March Madness.
[SPEAKER_02]: That event is going on right now, taking your top 25 picks of all time, and we'll get into that more in future weeks when we're not so focused on the weeks and the decades and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check out all that on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, if you like
[SPEAKER_02]: the show All We Ask tell a couple friends about the show thank you guys so much here we are 350 episodes later and we're looking forward to doing episode 351 next week so we'll be here same time next week to do it all over again right after Bobby Blackwolf until then have a great and safe new year and we will see you next decade have a wonderful night everybody
[SPEAKER_06]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!