[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight, December 13th, 2009, a retrotastic Mega Man 10 is announced, LittleBigPlanet is about to give Captain Sackboy what famous video game has been adapted for the stage.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are that program dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course we tape live every Sunday night at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com, right after the Bobby Blackwolf Show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Except...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
[SPEAKER_08]: and I think she said something about a pinball party that she's going to.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Dan's turn to host the pinball party.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I will be probably running away from it tomorrow night to go probably watch Star Trek with Becky.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to have a special guest next week though.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it just seems to work out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: We have a special guest next week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who dat?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm wondering if I should spoil the surprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are going to have Tiara.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: She's going to be here next week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm very excited.
[SPEAKER_08]: So am I. Awesome, awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also joining us tonight, say hello to the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: Doing fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dingo Digital A320
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, but you can actually run, uh, you know, different emulators including, uh, CPS 1 and 2, which are the Capcom Arcade games, uh, MVS, which is the Neo Geo Arcade games, uh, NES, I wanna say Mega Drive, um, I think Game Boy Advance, those are all the default emulators that are, um, actually in the, uh, system itself, but you can load more stuff on later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was gonna say it doesn't look like an Australian canine.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't look like it ate a baby either.
[SPEAKER_06]: It did not eat a baby.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can also tune in radio on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you listen to Orange Lounge radio?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can listen to podcasts because it plays MP3s.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it has Linux.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's based off Linux.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not positive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, no, it's not based off Linux.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can install Linux on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure someone's put Linux on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: If they can install Linux on a freaking toaster oven, they can install Linux on that thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can install Linux on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It actually is not based on Linux.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it may have been because I know that GP2X, it's another homebrew device.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it also outputs to TV, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, how much did one of those suckers cost you?
$80.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: And where'd you get it from?
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: and you can put themes on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, I have a Legend of Zelda theme on mine.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's hard to see, Rob, but you'll have to take a look at it.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is great radio, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: It kind of has a crossbar thing going on like a PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Jamie is super gluing her fingers together apparently.
[SPEAKER_08]: What the hell is she doing over there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is she doing arts and crafts during the show?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like I know last week she was crocheting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now she's gluing.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's trying to fix something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and I forgot.
[SPEAKER_06]: The other thing you can do, it has a built-in microphone so you can actually do dictation or whatever, record yourself.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, guys, if you are listening to us live on this Saturday, you can join us in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chat dot Orange Lounge Radio dot com is the place to be.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or if you're on the Game Surge Network on IRC, you just want to join Channel Pound Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: All one word.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that is our chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: We do use a different room than the all games chatters.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_08]: We just always have.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a history thing at this point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of tradition, I guess you could say.
[SPEAKER_08]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, anyhow, now that we're taking care of business live on air, let's get into our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if DarkSakura's unglued her fingers, I'm going to ask her how her gaming week was.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got glue all over my fingers still.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was fixing, my cell phone case broke, and the little thing that clips it to my belt snapped off, so I just super glued it back on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because rubber cement clearly isn't working.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now I've just super glued my fingers, so I'm going to have to go run you some nail polish remover on them.
[SPEAKER_08]: What about gaming?
[SPEAKER_04]: I glued soap to my fingers.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's too busy gluing her fingers together.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently she's too busy gluing her fingers together to play games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I played some World of Warcraft yesterday for like an hour.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've got to like level 10 now, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a second character at 10 now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a character at 15.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on up.
[SPEAKER_04]: My goat girl.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fire, Frost, Arcane
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm playing Dark Elf Druid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Elf?
[SPEAKER_04]: What am I saying?
[SPEAKER_04]: Blood Elf.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not fucking D&D.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or Night Elf.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Night Elf.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, gotcha.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, D&D!
[SPEAKER_08]: It's okay, WoW ripped a lot off from D&D, so it works.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I'm gonna go pour acetone on my fingers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, have fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, Loki, how was your gaming week, besides the dingo?
[SPEAKER_06]: Besides the dingo.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually played on my arcade cabinet a little bit, because I finally got... It's almost done.
[SPEAKER_06]: The front end's working now.
[SPEAKER_06]: The problem is I have too many games listed on there because I have every single game that's been pretty much ever put on MAME on that cabinet.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes it really hard to find stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I have to go back now and remove stuff off the list that I don't really want to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's going to be a process in itself.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah, fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I did play a little bit of...
[SPEAKER_06]: What did I play on there?
[SPEAKER_06]: I was testing it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, just some random Neo Geo games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: It works really well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I've been playing Bayonetta.
[SPEAKER_06]: I finally broke out my Japanese 360 and that game is all sorts of awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love it because it's...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not quality, it's quantity, and he starts throwing tons of pistols at her, and it's just absolutely ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, is it dubbed in English?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all in English.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: The entire game is in English.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you didn't play, I just played the demo, which was a selected stage from the game apparently, but you actually have the full Japanese one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I have the full game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's absolutely all in English.
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: I love the Joe Pesci type character.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Joe Pesci, but not Joe Pesci.
[SPEAKER_06]: My favorite character in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just everything about the game is so over the top, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, it gives her new red pistols or whatever that are in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's this sequence where the guy's mixing a drink and she's putting on the pistols in the most...
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate Devil May Cry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this game is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_08]: This is totally one of those games I never thought I would like.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just kind of looking at screenshots where you don't really see the game in motion, you're kind of like, oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I have a proposal for you then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometime in the next weeks or so, you should totally just bring it over and the three of us should just play through it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe tape it or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have it in my car.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I have it in my car.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, I got to order pizza, or not pizza, but Pizza Hut pasta after the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: And since we're going to be wrapped up, you know,
[SPEAKER_08]: We have to be done before 5 Pacific because I think the next All Games program is at 5.
[SPEAKER_06]: So since we're going to be done before then, what I thought, we might have a chance to play it for a few minutes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Might be something we do after the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Too bad I don't have my video camera.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to think what else I played this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Still no Borderlands yet, but I'm hoping to break into that tomorrow night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately I got distracted by Bayonetta.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then of course more Grand Theft Auto because that's what we play every day.
[SPEAKER_06]: So
[SPEAKER_06]: it's really sad though there's not a lot of people online playing Grand Theft Auto at least not the Ballad of Gay Tony multiplayer man there's like times where we'll be playing ranked matches where we can't get more than four people in and those four people are us it's so slow that we can get into the same ranked game easy now but I don't know talk to Dan at some point while he's off work I'm sure he'll play with you guys
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: Umlaut happened this Wednesday, and I actually trekked out over to the Bay Area to check it out, and it was cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a fun little event.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't super crowded, but it definitely wasn't a bad turnout.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was tolerable, the amount of people in what is a much smaller club than you'd probably think if you're looking at some of those videos online of some of the bands.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, the whole catch was that people would pay money to get up on stage and play rock band in a
[SPEAKER_08]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Great charity.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's kind of hard to say no to something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, I wanted to do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just didn't have – with Jamie and Loki not being able to go, I just didn't have enough people to do the band.
[SPEAKER_06]: I completely forgot about it until I saw the tweet on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn you.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was today, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We still wouldn't have had enough people.
[SPEAKER_08]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it was his sister or niece and like her friends or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think his niece used to do freestyle with him too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it was cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, they didn't have a lot set up as far as games because you just had the stage, which you had to pay to be on, or in the back, they had Beatles Rock Band, which actually had the new content.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they had a lot of support from Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, they had tons and tons of just loot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you know, you pay $10 to get in the door, which technically you don't have to do because it's a $10 suggested donation.
[SPEAKER_08]: But since the whole thing's charity, if you don't pay $10...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: And they had all sorts of just random shit on these loot tables.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like PlayStation 1 games, Super Nintendo games I saw on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like a calendar for Bayonetta I was looking at.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like a lot of those promo type things you would see at E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like the types of E3 swag all like dumped out on the table.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I walked out of there with a...
[SPEAKER_08]: Plug and Play Intellivision Part 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: The second one they've released, apparently, with 10 Intellivision games, I guarantee you've never heard of.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, except Jamie, because she's crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, I walked out of there with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: My friend, who I went with, Alan, he walked out of there with a copy of Advance Force 2 for Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_08]: So just all this, like, cool stuff on the loot table, it was kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I mean, it was all donated to a great cause.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then they had a silent auction going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: which I know they gave away a very limited edition signed like
[SPEAKER_08]: Space Invaders thing of which I think only 180 exist.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that thing went for like several thousand dollars.
[SPEAKER_08]: They gave away like a stuffed thing from Lost Planet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I won one of the silent auctions.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't want to talk about it on the show because part of it's going to be a Christmas present for someone and even though I don't think they listen I just don't want to talk about it on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you figure it out please don't spread word out because it's somebody's Christmas present.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I did win one of the auctions and you know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: This guy named SHDragon left a comment.
[SPEAKER_08]: Other fun things.
[SPEAKER_08]: I lost the blank auction because the guy I was bid warring against was camping the clipboard.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't believe that went for only $100.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh well, I didn't really have the money to spend anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: First off, I wasn't camping the clipboard.
[SPEAKER_08]: We just happened to be sitting in that back corner right by where the silent auction was, me and Alan and a couple guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I did think, I will admit, yeah, I was going to go up there at $10.29 and make sure I was the highest bidder come $10.30, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: A.B.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tactics A.B.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tactics
[SPEAKER_08]: and it worked out and actually I got it for $90 not $100 so and it really it was a steal it was it was absolutely a steal and it should have gone for much more especially for such a good cause however $100 was about the most I was going to spend on this because I just you know even though it's for a good cause look I got to live too and got money and everything so you know that was probably about the most I was going to bid on it and I'm in turn giving half of it to somebody else so and I'll explain more about what that is after it gets given to the individual so
[SPEAKER_08]: That was my experience at Umlaut.
[SPEAKER_08]: Overall, very good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish I could have stayed for more of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish I could have got up on stage.
[SPEAKER_08]: But maybe next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have heard it is confirmed again for next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not sure if it's the same venue or what have you.
[SPEAKER_08]: But honestly, if you guys haven't already...
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't played that yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I downloaded it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sexy Bitch, or no, it's Sexy Chick, I think they renamed it, and When Love Takes Over, which is weird because that's download pack.
[SPEAKER_08]: The songs aren't mixed.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just the one song, but they're like remixes of the song, I'm sure, that are available on a CD, remix CD somewhere, I'm sure, or vinyl.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it was cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of them has a crap ton of crossfading in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I have to admit, I actually kind of like the songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: So even though one of them had dudes from the Black Eyed Peas, which usually is one of those bands you're like, ugh.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're so played out.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I hear that goddamn song at the club one more time, I got a feeling.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, oh my god, if I hear that at the club one more time, I'm going to poke my eye out.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I got to admit, that one song was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do it on camera so we can put it on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, anyhow, let's get into some housekeeping real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, we're pre-taping.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're just joining us on All Games Radio on Saturday, that's because we're pre-taping or pre-recording, whatever you want to call it,
[SPEAKER_08]: We're doing a pre-thing for our Sunday, the 13th.
[SPEAKER_08]: This will rebroadcast again on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're listening live on Sunday, sorry we are not live, but we do hope you'll send us an email or a tweet or something to tell us what you thought about tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course, the podcasters, well, you're used to getting this on the feed anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, join our Facebook at facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio or our Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: We always post little updates, especially if there is going to be weird things like
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Believe it or not, even though we're only a couple weeks out before Christmas, there's been quite a little bit of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, oh, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki wants to do this during housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Real quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki has brought Christmas presents or Hanukkah presents, I suppose, if you will, at an appropriate time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had to bring him over because the cat was starting to eye him up because she likes ribbons and paper and stuff and she'll start ripping into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And don't I feel like a douchebag because, like, you know, Loki's brought this so early and I don't have his present here.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't do my shopping until Christmas Eve.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did my shopping all this week pretty much.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do my shopping afterwards so I get it all on sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, ladies first.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, you can open your gift.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, DarkSakura, this is great radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're wrapped in gold.
[SPEAKER_08]: Surely the wife must have done this.
[SPEAKER_06]: The wife was wrapped in gold.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, there's no way.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's no way Loki did this wrapping himself.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did no wrapping of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Going to our chat room at chat.orangelongeradio.com Toagak says, If you ever lose an episode of OLR, I'm archiving the live editions for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, manga!
[SPEAKER_08]: What'd you get?
[SPEAKER_08]: Return to Labyrinth manga.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, that's super cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm gonna read the hell out of this.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: And dude, it's like... You gotta open the big one first.
[SPEAKER_08]: I gotta open the big one first before the little one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, you got it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm gonna open the big one first.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is a big...
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Fuck yeah!
[SPEAKER_00]: Guardian Legend, motherfucker!
[SPEAKER_00]: There he goes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Batteries.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is great radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you're the best.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take the Guardian Legends wherever you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so DarkSakura's gonna put these on the website or on the Twitter?
[SPEAKER_04]: On the website.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the website.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, whoa.
[SPEAKER_08]: Batteries fell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the batteries.
[SPEAKER_08]: But here you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Taking a picture live there.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's my FC Mobile and copy of Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you get that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know how I found those.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even remember what I was looking for, but I somehow came across them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, hey...
[SPEAKER_08]: No, yeah, DarkSakura would... Oh my god, if I'd found those, I would have bought them for her too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember what the movie's called?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's, you know, Labyrinth guest star David Bowie's package.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm sorry, this is prettier than David Bowie has ever been, and David Bowie is pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well now that I'm in a super duper happy mood, part of me wants to turn this on during the break or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to get this up and going.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dude, FC Mobile, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to go out and buy NES games like crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, now I can support portable gaming with this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you really?
[SPEAKER_08]: I can support portable games with this.
[SPEAKER_08]: The hell with the DS and the PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got an FC Mobile, y'all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, getting into some gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, start us off.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you may remember that a little bit ago, no doubt, and I believe Courtney Love tried suing Activision for the likenesses of Kurt Cobain and, of course, no doubt, in Band Hero more recently.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, Activision has responded to No Doubt's claim by countersuing them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, their main response is that the band's request that their likenesses be limited to performing only the band's own songs in-game was made.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, it was requested only after the band hero programming was finalized.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is a gigantic bitch slap to one of the biggest bans in the last few years.
[SPEAKER_06]: This...
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, for me, I think it's just kind of retarded that Activision's doing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I understand that, you know, they had an agreement in place and apparently, you know, somebody didn't read the contract close enough or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so, you know, they want their money back or they want, you know, the patch to this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they can't, at least they can't on, you know, Wii and PlayStation 2 and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: And at the same time, now I'm wondering if this is going to prevent them from having other bands in the game going forward.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a theory about this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that the logic behind this would be, okay, well, we countersue you to where, you know, if we've got to make all this content change, then we want our money back, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's actually going to end up in some kind of closed-doors deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure it will, but they can't make the content change.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you can't just... And I've seen this going around on Twitter, is that why don't they just patch it in?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you can't patch to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have no system of patching on the Wii, and you can't patch to the PS2.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you would have games... The damage is done, period.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can't go back and fix it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you would have people complaining, hey, you're removing content from the game, you know, what the hell...
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I want, no doubt, to sing some stupid song because it's funny and I enjoy that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you're removing that ability for a game that I paid for.
[SPEAKER_08]: To me, the countersuit just seems like a we fucking mean it kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you guys are wrong and we fucking mean it.
[SPEAKER_08]: To me, this seems like they want to recoup their legal fees.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think they honestly would expect to win the whole thing, but I would think it's just legal fees.
[SPEAKER_08]: That they see this as a quote-unquote frivolous lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I do see them winning this, actually, because the reason why is if they have them signed to a contract that agrees that their likenesses can be used in this fashion, there's not really much they can do.
[SPEAKER_06]: They can bitch and moan about it, saying, well, I didn't realize it was going to be this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, maybe you should have fucking read the contract closer then.
[SPEAKER_06]: Same with the whole Kurt Cobain thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's tragic, but maybe you shouldn't have, I don't know, first off, licensed his likeness to be in the game, and maybe you should have read your contract.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I kind of said this then, and that is that when they showed this to Courtney Love or when they showed this to No Doubt, they probably didn't show them all this other stuff because of course they're not going to like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: They wanted to show people having a good time, No Doubt singing No Doubt songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're not going to win No Doubt over by showing them in the band playing Taylor Swift songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not going to be how you get them to sign on the dotted line.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's not like the band is going to take the time to sit down for four hours and play this game extensively.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: The only thing it's going to do is hurt their chances now to have these people in their games next time.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the thing is, though, the majority of the artists in the game, they're not the only ones that were in the game, aren't really bitching about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they really care.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: So does Courtney Love, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_08]: She got friends, and bands are going to think twice.
[SPEAKER_06]: And maybe they'll think twice, and they'll also realize that, hey, this is what's going to happen if you get involved with Activision.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll see, based on this, if that's something they don't want, then they won't get involved.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or they'll just, for the next one, they'll just lock it so that these characters can only sing their songs or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: regardless of how this all goes down I would really like to see it settled on Judge Judy personally I would like to see Judge Judy settle this whole thing because I'll tell you what if you ever watch that show awesome and I'd like to just see her yell at the people from Activision don't talk when I'm not talking to you
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on to completely different news and quickly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mega Man 10 has been announced.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mega Man 10, I think a lot of us kind of saw this coming.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mega Man 9 was obviously very well received.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Mega Man 10 is coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not to be confused with Mega Man X.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Because Capcom likes to multi-platform their stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Nintendo Power is getting the first announcement on this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course they're not going to tell you it's available on 360 and PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't it come out on WiiWare first before with 9?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or was there a slight delay or something like that?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's probably going to be on all the platforms.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's probably like a week delay or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be on all the platforms.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Mega Man 10 has been announced.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's retrotastic again, the whole NES style.
[SPEAKER_08]: And one of the new bosses has been announced, Sheep Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I'm not joking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sheep Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's even some artwork out there that just looks kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, also there's supposed to be Proto Man as a playable character again, and there will be a third mystery character.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, it better be Forte.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dr. Wily is always the villain at the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you notice in that little screenshot there that they have the dragon shooting guns out of its nipples, which is kind of...
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, that is a little strange.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's just the awkward artwork that Capcom has learned to embrace.
[SPEAKER_08]: Their terrible, terrible box art for Mega Man 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: There will be dragons with nipple guns.
[SPEAKER_06]: I see it now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nipple Man!
[SPEAKER_04]: It should be Nipple Woman.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sadly, I don't see that happening.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think this is supposed to be a friendly family game going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Sheep Man, that's... If we have Sheep Man, we should have Cock Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: What would be Sheep Man's weapon?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like...
[SPEAKER_08]: A woolly gun?
[SPEAKER_08]: A sleep gun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Allergies!
[SPEAKER_08]: The allergy blaster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like he shoots at Mega Man and Mega Man gets a rash.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also supposed to be in the game in easy mode, which for those folks that were struggling a little bit in Mega Man 9, I'm sure in easy mode will be welcomed for the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Including me, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mega Man 9, I think I got past like three bosses and that's as far as I could get, so yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, what do you got for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's a particular, actually, it's a bit of fine culture, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: A bit of fine culture.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a stage production, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So culture.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going up and singing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it like the fabulous news I found out last night that Sister Act, the movie, is being adapted for Broadway next year?
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it had already been done.
[SPEAKER_08]: It had been done.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's in London.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did Xanadu.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's in London right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's going to be on Broadway next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did Xanadu.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Xanadu.
[SPEAKER_08]: It did pretty well, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it finally closed, but it did very well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, this is about another fine stage production, but actually it's being done in Sweden.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a Silent Hill stage production.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I mean, imagine you step out onto the, you know, the curtain pulls back and you see a man wandering around wearing a car suit, swerving off the road, and then getting out of the car suit to go chase a
[SPEAKER_04]: A 30-year-old dressed as a 5-year-old girl.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the production takes like 50 fog machines.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, 50 fog machines.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're going to be posting the whole play on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: So keep an eye out for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's done by a bunch of fans.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would say that this play would get shut down immediately for copyright infringement issues.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's based on Silent Hill 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: but seeing as this is in another country I don't know if that's as easy to do plus I mean I don't know if I were Konami I'd be kind of flattered like I wouldn't want to shut it down I think if I were Konami I'd be like oh shit how are they gonna pull this off one of my friends on LiveJournal they did like a Star Wars play they did a play out of Star Wars the movie and I think they were afraid they were gonna get shut down but it turned out like Lucas embraced it and it was ended up being like officially endorsed by them
[SPEAKER_04]: Josh Whedon is my lord and master now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, Silent Hill the play, yes or no?
[SPEAKER_08]: I would love to watch it, except the whole thing's going to be in Swedish, which you know what this means.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need Ake Ripper to go out and observe the play for us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ake Ripper, you are now our theater reviewer?
[SPEAKER_08]: Congratulations, you've just been promoted to OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's not even listening right now, I'm sure, because we're on at a completely different time.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, if you're listening on Sunday, Aki Ripper, you are now our official Broadway correspondent.
[SPEAKER_08]: This counts for Swedish Broadway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: MXT, by the way, going back to the Mega Man story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Sheet Man's weapon, according to Wikipedia, is thunder wool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you, chatters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chat.orangelandry.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thunder wool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it just using static?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you just rub the wool against your body a whole lot and generate the static?
[SPEAKER_04]: Aki Ripper is in chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is he?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_04]: You are now our theater correspondent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Aki Ripper's here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Congratulations, Aki Ripper.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've been promoted.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now go see the Silent Hill play.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thunderwool.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's probably playing on the complete other side of Sweden.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like hours and hours away from where Aki Ripper's at.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, how long does it take to get across Sweden?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: By foot or by car or by plane?
[SPEAKER_03]: It depends, I guess, which direction you're going to.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to be the...
[SPEAKER_06]: The ignorant Americans say, Sweden's not that big, come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, keep in mind... I think it's about the size of California.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's much bigger than California.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep in mind, our states are technically little small countries.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just happen to be under one big federation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sort of like, I guess, the European Union without having to... Or like Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone linked me to a Star Trek menorah, by the way, that someone made out of action figures and LED lights.
[SPEAKER_08]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Aki Ripper says it's 14 hours away from where he is.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not that far.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not that far.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get on a plane.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll send you gas money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get on a plane.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: Before you get there, then fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: If Aki Ripper is going to boo-hoo about 14 hours away, even though he's closer than any of the rest of us, then we need a Swede who's listening to the show who can go, who lives next door to this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that was answering if it was...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, 14 hours to get from one end of the country to the other.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I give up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or by sheep.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll just wait for the damn thing to get on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkTetsuya said, no, by sheep.
[SPEAKER_08]: By ThunderWool Airlines.
[SPEAKER_08]: ThunderWool.
[SPEAKER_08]: That sounds like... This Sunday, Sunday, Sunday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Live at the Monster Truck Rally.
[SPEAKER_08]: See the big trucks take on ThunderWool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Under 18, not admitted.
[SPEAKER_08]: Without parental consent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Candy Cane Jojo's
[SPEAKER_08]: You thought we forgot Orange Lounge Foodio tonight, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, remember that story that we talked about the PSP minis being playable on the PS3?
[SPEAKER_06]: How was the rumor and everything?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this week, update 3.15 came out, allowing you to play PSP minis on your PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: So hooray!
[SPEAKER_06]: If you were very envious of your PSP minis and you possibly didn't own a PSP, well now you can play them on your PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the best part about that is too, that one purchase of the PSP mini obviously will allow you to play it both on the PS3 and on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you'll also be able to connect the two systems via LAN to transfer data from one system to the next.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not all the games will work right away.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're able to play these PSP minis on your PS3, is that going to lead way to playing PSP games on your PS3?
[SPEAKER_06]: And then we won't need the PSP anymore?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can just buy your game and play the systems?
[SPEAKER_08]: I would like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if that's something they would do.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But...
[SPEAKER_06]: It'd be a good idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the next step to getting to the PlayStation 2 on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, chatters.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_08]: Chat.OrangeLinesRadio.com Do you think that having PSP games playable on the PS3 is a good idea for Sony?
[SPEAKER_08]: If it was technically possible.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's assume that it's technically possible.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you remember the early, early rumors of the PlayStation 3 and some of the trademarks actually showed a UMD drive on the PS3?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you remember that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember that vaguely, years and years ago, before this thing came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some of the early trademarks, I think we reported on this show, had a UMD drive in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So maybe this is something they were thinking of at one time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, well, one game that isn't on the PSP, well, it is on the PSP, but the PS3 game is amazing, is LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, this game has kind of gotten coverage a lot in the past few weeks on our show, which is amazing for a game that's been out a year, again, continuing to be supported.
[SPEAKER_08]: And one way that is continuing is through an alliance with Disney for Pirates of the Caribbean content to be added to LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, you'll soon get to play Captain Sack.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Water is going to be the next big thing they add in LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, you know, the last big mechanic they added was a year ago in the Metal Gear Solid content.
[SPEAKER_08]: They added the gun, the paint gun, and that changed the way you build levels.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, now they're going to have water.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Sackboys can swim in water.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to be huge for developmental levels, and whole new ideas will be there.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, of course, this is a great tie-in to have water-based content, because, obviously, Pirates of the Caribbean, they sail on water.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: This is all supposed to come out, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: The rumor is all of this is hitting before Christmas, which would mean probably next week, if this is true.
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep in mind, LittleBigPlanet has not had any major expansion like this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, granted, they've kept the game fresh with the levels, the costumes, and some of those things, the stickers and somewhat.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this is the first major game-changing thing they've done since the Metal Gear Solid.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's awesome I will probably buy it And I haven't played LittleBigPlanet in quite some time So this is something that I guess you could say could get me back I don't know
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, going into our chatroom, chat.orangeloungeradio.com Some of the comments from my earlier question about Do you think PSP games should be on the PS3?
[SPEAKER_08]: Toagak says, only if they give us our fucking UMD drive back Well, technically they never took it away The PSP 3000 is still being made, still being sold, yes And much better than the PSP Go
[SPEAKER_08]: Alpha Cananagram says, sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: PS1 games are allowed on PS3 and they look shitty, so why not PSP games?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, now, hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: The PS1 games only look shitty because you're spoiled.
[SPEAKER_08]: And those games were made for a different time when we didn't have HD TVs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even though I'm only talking like 10 years ago, technology was different back then.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're all spoiled now.
[SPEAKER_08]: They look shitty because we have better TVs.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: may be coming soon due to a leak in update trophies
[SPEAKER_08]: And one other thing from chat, TigerClaw says, who knows, perhaps Sony is secretly working on a PSP 4000, which would probably be a hybrid of the Go or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: You never know what Sony might be doing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know so much about another PSP revision.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think, honestly, the next thing we're going to get is like a PSP 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I've been wrong before.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, DarkSakura, what's up next for us?
[SPEAKER_08]: Stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And such.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there's actually been an announcement by SNK for some Xbox Live Arcade games.
[SPEAKER_04]: We actually have Metal Slug 7 isn't coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Metal Slug XX or maybe XX is the PSP remixed version of the DS one is going to be coming out in 2010 instead.
[SPEAKER_04]: and as far as Xbox Live Arcade fighting games, there's going to be King of Fighters 2002 Ultimate Match and Neo Geo Battle Coliseum.
[SPEAKER_04]: There also will be the King of Fighters Sky Stage.
[SPEAKER_06]: That looks stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks incredibly stupid, but I think I want to play it just for lols.
[SPEAKER_04]: So hey, more Metal Slug for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's never quite a bad thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or more Flying Iori shooting things in the sky with his big Orochi self.
[SPEAKER_06]: And how.
[SPEAKER_06]: Twin Sector on PC
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember Reader Rabbit on the Apple IIe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then also more stuff for little kids Playmobil Pirates and Playmobil Circus Pirates for the DS and Circus for the Wii and that's it that still sounds like a lot considering where we're at that's sad there's actually some better stuff well next week's even lighter but it's really like two games but they're decent games well I wish excuse me I wish I could say it's a slow week in Japan but it's really not it's actually still a pretty big week over there
[SPEAKER_08]: Gundam Musou 2
[SPEAKER_08]: I believe so.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks very much like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: The whole combo meter in the corner and everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably the re-release of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and the graphics are very, very pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, of course, this week is epic week in Japan and actually for a lot of people here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know a lot of people are going to be importing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy XIII does come out on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seeing as the PlayStation 3 is region free, if you want to pay $100, yes, that's right, that's what some importers are charging for this, $100, you can import this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Death Connection Not the Love Connection
[SPEAKER_08]: Amelia was entrusted to the priest when she was a baby.
[SPEAKER_08]: Growing up in the small town church, the girl became a gentle beauty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Along with the priest and Joshua, a boy she sees as a brother, she lived a peaceful life.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, everything changed the night mafia members charged into the church seeking to end Amelia's life.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's got everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's got the mafia, church, religion things.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all in the Death Connection coming out on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: And on the Nintendo DS, Dear Girl Stories, Hibiki, Tokokun Daisakusen comes out in regular and limited edition.
[SPEAKER_08]: Deka Sports DS also making its way to the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Loki, I know, has already probably pre-ordered Jewel Pet 2 comes out on the DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: As well as a game I first read as PP Girl.
[SPEAKER_08]: P-O-U-P-E-E
[SPEAKER_08]: and a total of 8 people can play Poopy Girl all at once.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't it like Poupée or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like French or something?
[SPEAKER_08]: The chatroom is yelling at me.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like Po-Pay, just the way it's pronounced.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm sorry, when I read it in my honky American way, P-O-U-P-E-E, Poopy Girl.
[SPEAKER_08]: To which all the Japanese purists are screaming at me in chatroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: on the PSP Dice Dice Fantasia.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dice Dice Baby.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you even care?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you even care when Poopy Girl's out this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: That, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, what's coming out in the UK?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not a busy week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have, for our buddies overseas, we have on the 15th, EverQuest Underfoot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does anyone still play EverQuest?
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of people, they wouldn't be doing these expansions.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the 16th, we have Alien Breed Evolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: 17th, we have Blue Toad Murder Files, whatever the fuck that is.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the 18th, we have Buzz Quiz World.
[SPEAKER_04]: And 19th, we have Nicky Rock and Ball.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm laughing over here from this comment in chat about Poopie Girl.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, Po-Pay Girl.
[SPEAKER_08]: Salacious Pop says, She spends the entire game walking funny and looking upset.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is excellent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alpha Cananigram says, Sky, y'all are trying to kill me by making me laugh to death.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we try to be funny once in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, moving on to some more news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our classic game of the week just a few minutes away.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, apparently, I didn't even realize there was a whole lawsuit against Divino, but there was, apparently, by Nintendo, trying to prevent the company from selling DS flashcards.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, they won, I believe, their injunction in Hong Kong, but in France, and why they're trying to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Winning in France as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, they lost.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, Divino won that suit.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now, of course, Nintendo is appealing the ruling.
[SPEAKER_06]: And finally, I guess another lawsuit against them to try to prevent them from selling DS flashcards.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it enables people to... Apparently, they call it a game copying device.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly though, that's a little...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: The device doesn't allow you to copy games, but it allows you to play copied games, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody's got to break this down for me, because I seem to remember talking about this when the whole appeal was won in Hong Kong.
[SPEAKER_08]: So now they're going to France.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there a production of this going on there, too?
[SPEAKER_06]: They didn't win in Hong Kong.
[SPEAKER_06]: They actually lost in Hong Kong.
[SPEAKER_06]: It shows you how much I was paying attention that night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Nintendo made a statement that Divino still owes the company damages from a ruling made in Nintendo's favor in Hong Kong last year.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it says... So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't you own this device?
[SPEAKER_06]: The R4?
[SPEAKER_06]: I own two in my life.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a Ninja Pass, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have an R4.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, have you ever used the R4 to pirate a game?
[SPEAKER_06]: To pirate a game?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've used it to play pirated games, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tricky, tricky.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see what you did there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I can't order from Divino because my bank doesn't like me ordering from countries across the sea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Malaysia, I think, is where they're out of.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I think if it's being used for bad things, Nintendo has a right to some extent, but at the same time...
[SPEAKER_08]: There are legitimate purposes for these, I suppose, and you can't go after the people that are doing this for legitimate reasons.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to go after the people that are dumping the games and putting them on the web.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's who they need to go after is the people dumping the games.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like with BitTorrent and stuff like that, a lot of times they're going after the release groups that are dumping the titles because the downloading of the titles isn't really...
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not really stealing anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of tough with digital media and stuff because you're not technically stealing something.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're just making a copy of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're kind of going after more like real piracy, like people actually making bootlegs and selling them on the street type stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, moving on to one more story before we get to the classic game of the week tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were actually linked to this story on our Twitter and it was suggested that we talk about this.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Kotaku ran a feature this week about who they're calling – well, it says – I guess the name of the story is Achievement Chore.
[SPEAKER_08]: She plays for Gamerscore whether it's fun or not.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkDeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Toshiba, anyway, nobody cares.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyhow, they ran this little story on her.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's a 24-year-old stay-at-home mom in northwest Indiana.
[SPEAKER_08]: She got started on this whole thing when I guess it became like a friendly race between her and her friend about gamerscore.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it was a race to see who could get 20,000 first.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now I guess it's just become an obsession.
[SPEAKER_08]: The girl has, I guess...
[SPEAKER_08]: a Japanese Xbox 360 and a regular Xbox 360 she has mad respect in the community for I guess being nice she says quote once I found sites that had guides on which were the easy games I beat 20,000 in like a month and a half it got me hooked and it was like a drug a bad drug a bad habit
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, we joke a lot about achievement whores here on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I know we've called Loki an achievement whore many times.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's kind of like... I just don't care anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, now you stop caring.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I did too to some extent.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's kind of interesting to see what makes them tick.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I thought this story was...
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: And she does have a six-year-old girl that she's raising, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, I'm playing with poopies.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you go onto the website?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was Tiger Claw linked us to the... I love these things.
[SPEAKER_08]: ...Pope Girl website?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or is it renamed Poopy Girl?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing... Well, keep in mind, I used to play with the candy bar doll maker thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, this is actually... And I've got my big dolls.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, this is actually kind of fun for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though, like, you know... So, you like Poopy Girls?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the top ten reasons, you know, to play Sims, according to them.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're all, your friends can throw a rockin' party, and then burn the house down.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so they show that, and then there's like another one, it's like, you know, these two women, oh, because learning a new language is sexy, is number nine.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have like the teacher wearing just lingerie and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's like all the really wrong things people do with the Sims.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your sister can flirt with death, which is awesome, instead of your boyfriend.
[SPEAKER_06]: or her boyfriend I guess um and then they also had like uh your kids can finally learn to get along and they show the girl like laughing maniacally and her brother's on fire and it's awesome your grandma can still spy on the neighbors and not get arrested and they have like her peeping on like some naked guy which is kind of funny um
[SPEAKER_06]: Your brother and sister, oh, your brother can finally get lucky.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they have, like, some chick staring him down.
[SPEAKER_06]: Killing your boss.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then they have, like, what are some of the other ones?
[SPEAKER_06]: Experimenting.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have, like, two chicks.
[SPEAKER_06]: One dressed up like a cheerleader.
[SPEAKER_06]: One dressed up like, oh, God, I don't remember what else the other one was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Making out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just all sex, violence, all the stuff he got.
[SPEAKER_08]: All the great things about The Sims.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: and pick a game from yesteryear that she says, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: You bitches should be checking this game out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I closed the link to whatever she sent me earlier for the game, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you don't have it again, that's okay, I'll find it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I can get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the game is Einhander.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay, Einhander!
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is a pretty cool shooting game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty rare.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, not as in it was made by Rare, but it's pretty rare of a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, it's a side-scrolling shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was done by Square, and it came out on PlayStation in 1997.
[SPEAKER_04]: It did get a re-release for PSN on June 25th.
[SPEAKER_04]: It means single-handed, because the ship that you use has a single manipulator arm.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the one that I thought sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, it's just the first one I found.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's one on there for like stage 7 or stage 5.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I'll find it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll try and help Rob find the right thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, it's about a war between the Earth and the Moon.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has a really cool soundtrack done by Fukui Kenichiro.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, you play through the game, and it's sort of a 2.5D, so it's got shifting camera angles, and everything in the game is 3D, but you mostly play...
[SPEAKER_04]: in a two-dimensional method.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got different multiples.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got different difficulty settings, multiples of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do have a free mode that gives you unlimited continues, but you cannot have a score.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can get different speeds, and you have...
[SPEAKER_04]: You start off with a machine gun and you can collect gun pods that will give you different enemy missions or cannons or guided missile launchers or even a lightsaber type of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's also... You have to throw away your gun pods when you run out of ammo.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, you have a multiplier bar and a hit gauge counter, so as you destroy the cores of the enemies, your hit counter increases, and you get multiplied points by that, but when you stop shooting things, your counter decreases.
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically, this is helping you for your score.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a pretty neat game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually the first 3D shooter that Square did.
[SPEAKER_04]: They actually said that Square used some of what they learned from making Final Fantasy VII into Einhander.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, uh... It actually... One cool thing about it is that, um... There was another game that came out in Japan that was, um... Chocobo no Fushigi na Dungeon, which is, you know, Chocobo's Mystery Dungeon.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it had a bonus Mystery Data Disk, which actually was memory card data for a lot of games, including Einhander.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um... Working Designs wanted to bring it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um... But, um... Square just actually did it anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Really cool game, really cool, really fun game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you have to understand, really fucking hot for this era on the PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_08]: The graphics were just outstanding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, and it's a pretty difficult game too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'd have to say that the play in it is really tight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, the music that goes with the stages, I always thought was spot on.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing that actually has a problem with it, I think, is that you can't play two-player.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's a bummer.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can't be, I guess, Zweihander.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they did a sequel, I think they should do Zweihander.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, like, have two different gun arms.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Einhander.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, there you go kids, your classic game of the week this week is Einhander, available on the PlayStation numero uno.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, that's going to do it for part A tonight, we're going to take a quick break though, we'll be right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio, our little special Saturday edition that we'll also play again on Sunday, and also play again on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: So stay tuned, we'll be right back with plenty more.
[SPEAKER_08]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio on this Saturday afternoon, December the 12th of 2009.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are taping a little bit early for tomorrow night's show.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you'll hear this again on Sunday, December 13th, of course, at our usual time.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, of course, on our podcast feed available at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, during the break there, I had to get my new toy all out of the box and unpacked.
[SPEAKER_08]: Check this out.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, there is a game that's out there on Microsoft's community game service that will help you talk to girls.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: In case you don't know how.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an indie game called Don't Be Nervous Talking to Girls, and it allows you to, I guess, practice by talking to a picture of a woman with some interactive dialogue that allows you to choose from a few different...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: I would like to see DarkSakura play this game on how to talk to girls and see how it goes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am a girl!
[SPEAKER_04]: And I like being told I am from outer space.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's only a dollar.
[SPEAKER_06]: A whole dollar?
[SPEAKER_06]: A whole dollar.
[SPEAKER_06]: I may pick this up just for shits and giggles.
[SPEAKER_08]: Leo Shen in our chatroom, chat.orangelandre.com says, will they have a choice to put it in?
Stick it in!
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe in the sequel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Yakuza 3 is making its way over to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be heading over here March 2010, and will feature the wonderful gameplay that the Japanese have already been able to check out for a while now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's also actually coming to Europe and Australia around that same time frame as well, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, 505 Games announced a brand new series that they're going to be putting out called Naughty Bear.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I have to admit, their bear rendering ability is quite amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've been a very naughty bear.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, in gay culture, naughty bear means a whole other thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, the game is actually a violent action game starring an animated stuffed bear.
[SPEAKER_06]: Specifically, a stuffed bear who swears revenge on other jerk bears for failing to invite him to a party.
[SPEAKER_06]: and so your goal is to scare and irritate and of course hurt other bears racking up naughty points as you do using weapons during about the game's 30 stages.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, so you play a bear encouraged to rape other bears?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they never said rape.
[SPEAKER_06]: They said hurt.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the face.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're calling it Manhunt for Teddy Bears.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's really what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is about violence.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is just teddy bears.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can tear Teddy Ruxpin limb from limb.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's just a bear.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's coming from the developer, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the same developer that put out Wet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Looking in our chatroom, of course, they are still hung up on the talking to girl game.
[SPEAKER_08]: TigerClaw says they probably have a version for the girls on how to talk to guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think they need one.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just with your tits.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's basically how they do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just two buttons, giggle, flash, tits.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just two buttons, giggle and tits.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bauer CTU in our chatroom says, are one of the choices, are you poopy girl?
[SPEAKER_08]: Lol.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, I like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Taking it back to a previous topic in the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, going on to some other stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brutal Legend, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: How has Brutal Legend sales been?
[SPEAKER_08]: They've been like okay, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: They've been alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, hopefully this will invigorate sales a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: A new download content piece called The Hammer of Infinite Fate is coming out this week on December 17th.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is a chance for you getting to, I guess, carve a giant disembodied head into Mount Rockmore.
[SPEAKER_08]: of Tim Schafer, the developer of Brutal Legend.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess that's what you get.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: You also get an upgrade that shows every collectible that's on the map and some new outfits for Eddie and what's probably a highlight for a lot of people, four new multiplayer maps.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to cost you $4.99 on PS3, yet $6 on the Xbox 360, but that might be an error because usually those things are the same.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, if you still haven't picked up DJ Hero, a place you could probably grab it is the Guitar Hero store.
[SPEAKER_08]: It got knocked down to $79.
[SPEAKER_08]: From what I understand, though, this thing got sold out very soon, so I don't think you can actually get this anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it is still telling and worthy of reporting on that the price is already coming down, meaning that maybe it's just a matter of time before this ends up in the bargain bins.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And as I tweeted earlier this week, the MPD numbers came out and it's sold 303,000 units total.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, now that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: In two months?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not bad at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or actually, technically one month, about.
[SPEAKER_06]: One month and a week or so.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll probably still sell a little more before Christmas.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think it's worthy enough of getting a sequel then?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Guitar Hero rocks the 80s?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or spins the 80s?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I forget.
[SPEAKER_08]: Joke gone wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would be all over that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no, my problem with DJ Hero, and it's the same problem that I have with the Guitar Hero series, is there's not enough download content.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've had two so far.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, come on, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: Both have been pretty good for what it's worth.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if this was a Harmonix game, I'd be getting download content every fucking week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rock Band 2, The Best Buy Demo
[SPEAKER_08]: Street Fighter Alpha
[SPEAKER_08]: as well as the arcade version of Shinobi and Rayman for the DSi which I thought was kind of interesting is now out so that's a big title on DSi lots of other stuff available on DSi including Ball Fighter, Pop Island, Army Defender and My Notebook not a lot of exciting stuff on WiiWare but of course the Virtual Console got the arcade version of Shinobi and Street Fighter Alpha for the Super Nintendo so if you were a fan of Alpha back in the day you might want to go grab that
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, in other news, we have something that actually I'm pretty considering trying out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a Voltron game on the iPhone and apparently has the best unpause feature.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually being put out for the 25th anniversary of the series.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you've got 30 levels, 6 acts total, where you go, you play as the lions going through the galaxy to stop Zarkon and everybody and, you know, all the weapons and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: and um it's actually uh supposed to be i think pretty neat but um there's a video up here actually that i can um i haven't watched it yet but apparently the the unpause sound effect is supposed to be amazing are they i imagine they're like rips from voltron or something probably i'm gonna check this out all right because i'm i oh there's stupid ads
[SPEAKER_08]: So now let's go back to Voltron.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, someone talking about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, there we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, no one can hear any of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to find the unpause.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it's the sound effects.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like the music in the game is actually from... Dude, you have Sven when you start off.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving forward, how about some rock band stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock band.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rubber Soul!
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally!
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally, finally, finally.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very happy, because that's my favorite Beatles album.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, we are going to be getting Rubber Soul next week for a Beatles rock band.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we already got Sgt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band and Abbey Road.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then...
[SPEAKER_04]: We are also going to be for the other Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be getting All-American Rejects, 30 Seconds to Mars, and more Green Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Rock Band unplugged download content is... I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: It actually isn't going to be getting any more download content from what it seems.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, some late-breaking news, I believe, speaking of the whole Rock Band thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, there's this teaser going on on MTV.com about this whole, I guess, Green Day Rock Band game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there possibly a Rock Band game going on with Green Day in it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's going to be as big as, like, Beatles Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_06]: It may be, like, an add-on content thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we've speculated this before, like the ACDC game was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: This might be something that actually shows up during the VGAs, which I guess are happening later tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Green Day is okay, but do you really think they're popular enough to warrant their own game?
[SPEAKER_06]: You've got to live up to the Beatles.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's...
[SPEAKER_08]: VGA's are on tonight
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: I find it odd that I host this show and I know really very little about what's going on here.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm very curious to see it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some people talking about listening to the show or not listening to the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Going to Leo Shen on Twitter says, Any songs from a recent game that you can't get out of your head?
[SPEAKER_08]: For me it's Bayonetta's Fly Me to the Moon Climax Mix.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought that was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: My friend's like, hey, isn't this from Neo Genesis?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and a bunch of other stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if I have a song stuck in my head, especially not one from a video game.
[SPEAKER_08]: For the longest time, though, I had that mix of Radio Gaga and Mary J. Blige from the download of DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would get stuck in my head so easily.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of the stuff from DJ Hero is stuck in my head because I played in my car on repeat, basically.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of bus moves around the world, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a game I haven't played in forever that I really need to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Old school, bust a move, groove, whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, SSJ100Matt on Twitter is saying, Target is having some nice game deals starting this Sunday, including DJ Hero $88 and Zelda Spirit Tracks $25.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was another game I forgot to mention that I was playing this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's alright, but my thing is...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not the same as the other games where the method of travel by boat was kind of a necessity.
[SPEAKER_06]: The fact that they're like, oh no, we can't go to these parts of the land because the tracks have disappeared.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just to me saying, I'm lazy and I don't want to walk there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like fucking walking was all you did in Zelda, Zelda 2, Zelda 3 even.
[SPEAKER_01]: But now I'm too good for walking, I need to take a train everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want another Wind Waker
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they keep putting out these DS games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's do another GameCube-style game or whatever, because Wind Waker is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to go back and actually play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of people disagree with you, but... Well... They can suck it, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: They can suck it, because guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: How many games have we seen that have been emulating the Wind Waker style being released?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, at least two of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: How many games have we seen emulating the style of the Marie Lissig Zelda?
[SPEAKER_06]: One.
[SPEAKER_06]: So tough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, that's it for Twitter topics tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Twitter.com slash OLR if you want to give us a follow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Meanwhile, back to some more gaming news and then our mailbag before too long.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, there's a new patent that's been put out for the Sony motion controller and it's showing a new feature including swappable buttons or like some sort of connector.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, at the top of the controller or possibly even the bottom, I don't know, they show this kind of like upside down with the cosmic ice cream cone facing down.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, there is a little spot that you could possibly put in either a D-pad, they have like the...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: But honestly, I don't see what the point is in adding face buttons to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, when you just have some generic buttons and if you want to use them... I don't know, it gives some more diversity for the developers.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would just worry about losing that shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those things look small.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would think losing them would be the problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: These little convertible things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not only that, but I would think, though, that the directional pad or whatever could be easily done with just four buttons like the face buttons, so there's no need to double up on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the jog dial...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really see why they would need that.
[SPEAKER_08]: To spin the wheel in a Wheel of Fortune game, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they make the movement with the whole motion controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is about, like, I don't know if you saw the article about Ubisoft with their crappy camera that they put out with that Your Self Fitness thing or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your Shape, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they have a new racquetball game coming out to kind of compete with Wii Sports, Tennis, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it uses, as an option, it uses the camera.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, all the previews I've seen using this camera have been crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: Toagak in chat says, Have you ever dealt with a DS game card before?
[SPEAKER_08]: Those are easy to lose.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like saying that, you know, well, these things aren't much bigger than a DS card, probably.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you can keep track of a DS game card, you can probably keep track of these little things.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe, but like, there's got to be an easier way to do this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, and it doesn't necessarily mean it's going to be true.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, it's just generally patents so that no patent whores try to get in there and, you know, patent it first.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will just sue them 10 years down the road.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, they always seem to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Star Trek Online is coming out next year, and of course there's quite a few people excited about that, including our very own DarkSakura, and I gotta admit, I am pretty excited about it too, even though I'm a big WoW whore, and I gotta say, lovin' the new patch 3.3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't say this during my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I like it too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I've noticed that it flashes red now when you're being attacked, and it's sort of like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm being attacked!
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of just random roar...
[SPEAKER_08]: And the quest tracking thing, if you didn't have a mod for that before, is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I used a quest helper mod, so I already had that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I gotta say, this whole dungeon finder is awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_08]: All the looking for group stuff is gone now.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I gotta be honest, all the groups I've gotten through the system have been really good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I have yet to get a group full of douchebags like I used to get before.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not like they have a filter on what kind of players get to use the group system, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: I've just gotten a lot of really good players.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that it requires a little bit more intelligence to use it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very, very exciting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, but we want to get back to Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_08]: Star Trek Online, of course, is coming out soon and a whole shitload of pre-order bonuses.
[SPEAKER_08]: But of course, it depends on where you pre-order it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: And depending on where you pre-order, Star Trek Online will change the bonus that you get.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, for example, if you pre-order the game at GameStop, you can have the classic USS Enterprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can only get the classic Enterprise at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there's going to be everybody riding around the USS Enterprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: At the Best Buy, you can get a Pet Tribble or a Targ, depending on what your faction is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, totally want a Targ.
[SPEAKER_08]: and everybody knows when you get one pet tribble it's actually hundreds of pet tribbles if you pre-order on Amazon you get a liberated Borg bridge officer with unique nanotechnology augmentation so in other words you can have sex of nine as your bridge officer there whose name is Poopy I actually totally think that I'm going to get mine on Amazon now because I've actually got a gift card for Amazon do you really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Direct2Drive, a multi-spatial personal shield.
[SPEAKER_08]: It regenerates itself and the player health.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Those are all game-changing items.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a little weird to me that depending on where you buy the game can kind of change up the game for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I imagine even these little items they talk about aren't like the best things in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It seems to me, I gotta be honest, it sounds, the Walmart one sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you get extra skill points that you can't get any other way, that seems like the best deal right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it seems to me, though, that, well, are they completely unique?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, does it say specific?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, I mean, if you can get skill points as you keep going, you know, as you level, then what's the point?
[SPEAKER_06]: What kind of skills can you get from Walmart anyways?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: Out of Dress.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which one had the, what was it, the transphasic shield?
[SPEAKER_08]: Direct to Drive has the shield that regenerates itself in your health.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I can imagine a Walmart bonus being like,
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, you get to command the Enterprise, except the Enterprise has a new paint job with a Confederate flag on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, I think I wouldn't really want the classic Enterprise anyway, because given when the game is set, it's like driving...
[SPEAKER_08]: A hooptie.
[SPEAKER_08]: I gotta be honest, the GameStop pre-order sounds the least interesting to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've gotta be honest.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is Star Trek Online, not remake Star Trek The Next Generation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it'd be the equivalent of everyone driving around in a brand new Bugatti, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're driving a 1983 Ford Escort.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: A Geo Metro.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm a pet whore though, and wow, so I'm almost down for this Best Buy pet Tribble.
[SPEAKER_08]: That sounds kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that the only way you're going to be able to get this pet Tribble?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, is there going to be a Tribble wearing a Best Buy shirt or something like that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't get a... And besides that, the whole... You can... Although I'm sure the Tribbles are actually 90% reproductive organs.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can just feed them very little and they won't have enough energy to breed.
[SPEAKER_08]: A few comments from our chatroom at chat.orange.com on this story.
[SPEAKER_08]: Vanis Lux says, Exclusive Walmart greeter class.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe that's what you get at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_08]: SalaciousPop says, you're not going to know how or what to min to max if you're just starting, and 99% of the MMOs nerf a lot of stuff within the first 90 days.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100Matt says, you can probably buy those devices and armor bonuses in some sort of store in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And BauerCTU says, I want the Classic Enterprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, screw what I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, obviously there will be a lot of people that want it, and there'll probably be a lot of them in-game, because GameStop is obviously still a very, very big retailer where a lot of people are going to get this.
[SPEAKER_08]: But just so you know, there's choices, so if Star Trek Online is really important to you, you might want to think around about where you pre-order the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll probably end up getting it on Steam, so I don't have to go outside the house, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: well in other stuff yay other stuff thanks Rob PS3 actually won Metacritic's console of the year they did a big survey on it and actually the higher rated games came out higher rated games were on Xbox 360 than PS3 but the winner overall though was still the PS3
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then again, Uncharted 2, you know, meh.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the Wii did okay on the thing too.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I mean, and also to keep going further into the list though, the best rated Xbox game was Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Metroid Prime Trilogy was on Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Street Fighter 4 scored the best for PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grand Theft Auto Chinatown Wars was number one on PSP and DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: So.
[SPEAKER_08]: This seems like one of those stories that's just there to start a controversy, to get the Sony fanboys and the Microsoft fanboys all riled up.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's been a good year for Sony.
[SPEAKER_08]: The price drop was what they needed to do three years ago, and it's finally bringing a lot of people on board.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I've heard a lot of people talk about...
[SPEAKER_08]: How they're probably going to take the plunge and get the PS3 now, you know, with Blu-ray and so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they're going to have a really good Christmas season.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, we'll see when the numbers come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Certainly Microsoft's not out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've already sold millions of consoles.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think this is going to be, I think there's going to be a lot of people that just simply have more than one console in this day and age.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know?
[SPEAKER_08]: So.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll move on to some more news stories and then we'll get to the mailbag in just a minute here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had a game that just came out, Avatar, that supported 3D with, you know, actually stereoscopic 3D with TVs that supported, you know, 3D gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of the 120 megahertz TVs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that because movies are supposed to be in 3D too?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of neat, though, because Avatar, actually, it was... It's dependent on which TV it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had a bunch of different options that you could do, including Real D was one of those, which you find in a lot of the cinemas nowadays, which is the polarized glasses.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well...
[SPEAKER_06]: Soul Calibur V
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, but it's neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, and I think this is the way games are going to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but how many TVs are fitted for this?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean... Not many.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the thing is, not only do you have to have these TVs, you have to have those glasses, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, the Real D wouldn't be bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you could do the Real D stuff, like, on your TV, I mean, because that's just a... It's polarized glasses.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, those glasses cost, like, five bucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that would be, I think, the way to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you get the more expensive, like, shutter glasses, you know, they're actual...
[SPEAKER_06]: Hardware that have timing and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: That might be a little bit difficult, but I think it's almost like pushing the technology too quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, we just got people sort of adopted to HDTVs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not everybody's kind of on board with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't believe this Avatar game's already supporting it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It seems so early.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hear it's good, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hear that Avatar's whole thing is really pushing what they do with cinema now, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: And by the way, Tigerclaws, Lincoln and Chad, apparently, even though I was bagging on the movie a little bit last week about how I kind of don't look interested in it, Avatar the movie apparently has an 89% on Rotten Tomatoes right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I guess some people are being pretty wowed by it.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the game?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, the movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: The movie?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not out yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it had its premiere in London, so some critics were probably there.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's probably had its critics screening.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to go see it, and in 3D, because that's the way it's meant to be seen, but if it's crap, then I'll call it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you going to see it by Sunday?
[SPEAKER_08]: Review it on next week's show?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to go see it with my dad, because the wife does not want to see that movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: I see.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think he's gone, so I may not be able to see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: She may go see it, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure some of our chatters will let us know next week, if nothing else.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're definitely going to see it next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will give you a review of Princess and the Frog next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to see that tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to see that too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe you'll see that tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_08]: That you could probably get the wife to see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do remember now she does want to see Avatar because she said it looked neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's see, moving on to another story here about something probably the wife wouldn't be interested in at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, Loki, maybe she would be.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bible Adventures is a new game that's coming out from Left Behind Games, which I want to say I remember reporting on the fact that the studio was developed quite some time ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do the Left Behind Game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: So now they're doing Bible Adventures as their new game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to educate young children by teaching them academic lessons vital to early childhood development through Bible stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: So in other words, it's gonna be throwing the Bible at them at an early age.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I could see this maybe being more of like a downloadable game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that would be a little bit more popular, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it's coming out as an actual game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to sell this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not that I don't like selling, you know, not to have anything against the Bible or anything, but I don't want to sell that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, just like, you need this because people love the Bible.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, it's based on the Charlie Churchmouse stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to span both of the Old and the New Testament, and it will teach mathematics, spelling, and I love this, reasoning skills.
[SPEAKER_08]: WWJD.
[SPEAKER_04]: I prefer WWTF.
[SPEAKER_08]: IDGAF.
[SPEAKER_08]: WWGD.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, the CEO of Left Behind has said that they expect their financial projections to grow exponentially as they transition from a PC game developer to a Wii and Xbox developer.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bible Adventures apparently is coming out for the Wii and the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I love this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Joystick, who ran this story, one of the many sites who ran the story this week, said, but what about PS3 owners?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they can go to hell.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the link, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: The link is for Dante's Inferno.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: I lulled.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like it or not, there's a market for this stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: They'll sell these in those Christian bookstores.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just want to know when we're getting dance praise or whatever the guitar hero equivalent was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guitar praise?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guitar praise or...
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Praise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where's DJ Praise?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Praise.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Praise?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe you should make that game, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I shouldn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, forget it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's move on to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_08]: Every week you guys send us emails at mailbag at orangelawnradio.com and DarkSakura jumps into the mailbag head first.
[SPEAKER_04]: And deletes them.
[SPEAKER_08]: And instantly deletes them.
[SPEAKER_08]: But not before she picks out a few of her favorites to read here on the air in a segment we call The Mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: Starting with an awful joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's from AZHP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi OLR crew, AZHP here celebrating the release of the new Silent Hill Wii game with a crude joke for everyone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you call what happens to your boobs after Pyramid Head rapes you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Silent Hill Shattered Memories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that we've got that out of the way, have you guys heard about the Silent Hill stage play planned for Sweden?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we already did that.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it's as good as the last Konami spinoff play I wrote into the show about DDR the musical, then I'm sure we can all say that we're extremely excited to see what comes out of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: There aren't any details besides the flyer, which has been making the rounds on gaming blogs, but it's Silent Hill, so it's plenty enough to get excited about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Am I right?
[SPEAKER_04]: TTFN, ta-ta for now, is EHP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we covered that.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, AZHP, I got this for you for your joke.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sound cue fail.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now this is for me and AZHP.
[SPEAKER_06]: We just need to get one of those fancy mixing boards with the buttons.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need a fancy mixing board with buttons.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will get on that because you already told me what to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next up comes from Gray Fox.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dear...
[SPEAKER_04]: OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need your help.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Give me a dollar.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not cheating enough then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now with so much of my time being taken up by other interests, I find myself having less time for games and I'm finding myself remembering my relentless quests across Hyrule or summoning some ridiculously large beast in Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I've asked myself if other people have encountered the same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have patience anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: I also have life.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have gamer ADD.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have told this on the show many, many times.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have the worst case of gamer ADD and it's not helping my wallet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will buy $60 games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I swear to God I play them once and then never play them again.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a disgusting, filthy habit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need to stop.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a game right over here that I haven't played yet, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should stay and play it with me sometime.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sometime, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have Marvel Ultimate Alliance 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: You still haven't played that?
[SPEAKER_08]: You've had that for like two months.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: To be honest, I've taken a liking to independent games like Bit.Trip Beat and World of Goo because I can usually beat the games within a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which makes me wonder if I'm no different from when I first started playing games like Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: or Duck Hunt.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this brings me back to my original question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Am I crazy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Am I thinking too much?
[SPEAKER_04]: Help me out, Gray Fox.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, just play whatever's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it's not fun, don't play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't force yourself into a mold you don't fit in.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think tastes change with time.
[SPEAKER_08]: And maybe it does have something to do with age.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, because I had much more patience when I was little.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I play some of those 8-bit games now, and I don't have the patience to collect everything like I used to when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's also a lot of peer pressure out there to be playing certain games, like the popular ones, like you'd be in the crowd.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like Smoking Crack, the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yet, yet, I spend hours upon hours upon hours on World of Warcrack.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, some of those are just good, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think part of it with an MMO is that because it is something that you can just pick up, play for a little bit, and put away, it has that casual aspect on it unless you're, like, I guess one of those freaks that goes raiding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't go like I used to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Raiding kind of ruined WoW for a little while for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: But keep in mind, for that, that's also a social aspect.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_04]: For me, when I play, I play with, like...
[SPEAKER_08]: I've described World of Warcraft to friends that I have that don't get the Warcraft obsession or just are curious about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will say it's like a chat room with fireballs is World of Warcraft for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's kind of neat because friends I have who might live across the country, it gives us a chance.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know this is going to sound so dorky and nerdy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It gives us a chance to hang out and do something, even though, yes, I understand it's not real life.
[SPEAKER_08]: But keep in mind, I'm talking about friends that live states and states and thousands of miles away.
[SPEAKER_08]: We get to kind of do something together, even if it's not, you know, going outside.
[SPEAKER_08]: So take that as you will.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I completely agree with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have the same logic about it, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we've got one more email from Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_04]: DeadPixelLive.com
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, that last week was, uh, we got a lot of compliments on last week's show, which is weird because I didn't think we did anything special, but talk about more porn than usual.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I guess the chatters like porn.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, as far as I remember what we did, um, I don't know the latest update from last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: My thought is they are, they had a epilogue, but they're still on the schedule.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they might, they're still doing something.
[SPEAKER_08]: So keep an eye on all games.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they have their own website at dead pixel live.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: and you can check out what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have not heard that they have left the network or anything like that so I don't know if they're just going through some changes over there or what's going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: But usually when shows change and stuff I'm like the last to hear about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: On Sunday night people are kind of self-sufficient I suppose.
[SPEAKER_08]: They don't keep us in the loop on what's going on the rest of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still have glue on my fingers.
[SPEAKER_08]: F.U.s of the week
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to the situation with my mother.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not to my mother, just with the situation.
[SPEAKER_06]: F you to having a cold.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob, I'm just going to take this moment to say, there's a...
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a couple arcade cabinets in Rancho Cordova for $25 each.
[SPEAKER_06]: Missing a monitor, but they'll sell you a monitor for $50.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can get a Street Fighter 2 cabinet working for $75.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, that's tempting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Arrgh!
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're in ranches, so maybe they'll deliver to you, huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, I don't really have a lot of FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually had, like, a really good week, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, um, I don't really have a lot of angsty stuff, except maybe FU to being exhausted after work on Friday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I just wanted to go home and die.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I did, I slept for an hour.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: And FU to the rain causing people to drive like crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: It took twice as long to get here as it usually does.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rawr.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, that's going to do it for the FU's of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: No story to inspire it tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everybody's been fairly well behaved out in the world.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just a couple more stories and then we'll get to your calls at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: But first, some more stories, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, they had an interesting, or there's going to be an interesting update coming to Team Fortress 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what's more interesting than the update itself is how they're deciding who will get the update.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I guess during the week, you will be able to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Get the update for the Soldier by becoming the Soldier and killing the Demoman.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you want the Demoman to get the update, you need to go kill the Soldier as the Demoman.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's apparently the, of course, the update's called The War.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, Team Fortress 2 is one of those games that they've done a very good job supporting for quite some time since its release.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, it says the update will award three new weapons to both the Soldier and Demoman classes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Weapons will be revealed piecemeal over the course of next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, two classes will be fighting during the week to unlock a secret fourth weapon for their profession.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mad Moxie's Underdome Riot Mad Max
[SPEAKER_08]: What the game will do there is it's actually adding some new Riot Mode arenas for single player and co-op.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's going to be a bank where you can store your weapons and the whole thing's going to cost you 800 Microsoft points or that would be 10 real dollars and that's how much they're charging on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're saying also it's an entirely new game mode.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're comparing it to Smash TV in co-op first person shooter in the Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_08]: That does sound kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: SalaciousPop in our chatroom at chat.orangehauntsradio.com calls it a first-person looter.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, so we're going to go ahead and open up the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR where we will take your calls right now if you want to go ahead and give us a call.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, I just want to say I followed up in chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: to one of the emails because I noticed that Derek from Dead Pixel Live was in the All Games chat while we were getting asked that question on the mailbag and he said that it is coming back at 7.30 on Monday after a brief cancellation so there you go so stay tuned to All Games Radio and check that out and I'm assuming 7.30 is Eastern because I know that show used to come on at like 3.30 Pacific it was kind of early for us over here so I think it's just going to be on at a slightly different time so check that out
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, and of course, for all the ladies, you can always check allgames.com for the latest goings on at All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, we are getting some calls, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go to the phones and take them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I just want to comment on the little story that you guys said a little while ago about firmware update 3.15 for PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, the latest update on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you checked it out?
[SPEAKER_08]: You used it?
[SPEAKER_08]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a slight hitch with the update.
[SPEAKER_00]: Even though the update on the PlayStation 3 is in place...
[SPEAKER_00]: You can't exactly take full use of playing the minis on your PlayStation 3 just yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we did note earlier when we were covering it that not all the games are playable.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I guess some of the newer ones and a sprinkling of the old ones you can do, but not all of the new ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I guess they're going to, like, patch that in later or something, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, in fact, you know, I talked to you guys, a few other sites made note of this, and
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess that I don't have all the details in place just yet, so I don't want to give out any bad information, but I'm guessing that they're going to arrange stuff in such a way on the PSN store that will make it easier to figure out.
[SPEAKER_00]: which ones you can play on your PlayStation 3 as opposed to which ones that still haven't been updated.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I'm hoping that they get them all playable before too long.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess that's the idea, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, yeah, really.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, the one thing I definitely want to get in the play is Tetris.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I know it's available on virtually every console known to man.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, you know, Tetris is pretty much a classic game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's imagine that technically it's possible.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's just throw the technical aspect out of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Technically it's possible.
[SPEAKER_08]: Should Sony do it?
[SPEAKER_00]: From a consumer standpoint, I'd say hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: However, from a strictly business standpoint...
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think it would make sense, because I would imagine from Sony's standpoint they would probably lose money, so it's all a matter of how you want to look at it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm all for playing your games, the PSD games on the PS3, but unless things really come to a push, come to a shove, I really don't see it happening, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't see it happening either, but it's too bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I can also see the business standpoint of the fact that where it might not then motivate the sale of systems, what it will motivate the sale of is the games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you know, and all the games that are available right there on the store for digital download.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's some stuff I would freaking love to play on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like the Final Fantasy remakes, even though I don't think those are in the store yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: But maybe like the Castlevania game that came out by Konami.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, there's a lot of games I would love to play on the TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although, I know, I could use a video out cable if I want to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe I want the convenience of not having to do all that.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, on a somewhat related note, you know, one thing that I think virtually every time you can hear a replacement of Damage would like to see is, you know, somehow they really bring back PlayStation 2 backwards compatibility.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, I know the early models, you know, PlayStation 3 had it, and they kind of weeded it out.
[SPEAKER_00]: and, you know, they're trying to tinker with the look and with the God of War collection and Call of Duty Classic, but, you know, I would love to be able to
[SPEAKER_00]: Play all my old PlayStation 2 games all over again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing to think of, but thanks for taking my call, Will.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll just have to create Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'll kick anybody who doesn't show up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll just have to create Loki's porn hut.
[SPEAKER_08]: You do.
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to make Loki's porn hut.
[SPEAKER_08]: But for now, we've got another call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: A couple of things.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll be on my merry little way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Number one, I just had my 360 replaced yet again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again?
[SPEAKER_05]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I got the dreaded disk read error, and because Best Buy screwed up the first time around when exchanging my console, I got it replaced yet again.
[SPEAKER_08]: I seem to remember something like this coming up a couple weeks ago about the whole Best Buy shenanigans, so they didn't put up too much of a fight in replacing it for you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: so the guy says he had some Geek Squad blow it out with compressed air which is something I already did he says take it home if it works it works if not bring it back and exchange it so I now have an Elite sitting on my counter how does blowing out a console fix a DVD drive well it works on Nintendo I don't know you tell me wow alright well I guess there you go they finally got you one though right
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I had to swap out the hard drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sitting there like, well, I could take the 120 gig hard drive, come home with it, and my roommate would kill me because of all the saves.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or I could just take the 60 gig, which I did.
[SPEAKER_08]: What else is going on in your gaming world, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I started back into playing Legend of Zelda Phantom Hourglass because I forgot where I left off at, so I'm starting from scratch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, sometimes that's what you got to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: You got to start all over.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't just hate that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You pick up an RPG after you haven't played it for a long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're like, where the hell was I?
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn it, I have to start all over.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I did that with Lost Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was on the second disc or something, and then I went back and played it again.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got all the way to the third disc, and now it's been a few months since I played.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I wanted to go back, I'd probably have to start from the beginning again.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will say, though, what little I've played of Dragon Age Origins, I do like, though, that whenever on the loading screen of Dragon Age Origins, it gives you a one-paragraph summary of where you are in the story.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought that was a really smart feature, kind of remind you what's going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Ranma, if there's nothing else on your mind, then I'll let you go so we can get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_08]: But thanks so much for your call, okay, buddy?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have one thing, and I'll be on my way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I talked about Avatar earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to let everyone know that a friend of mine, Kyle Hebert, who's a voice actor, he's doing the playable character, Ryuk, for Avatar the Game for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: maybe we'll have to get him on the show I know there's another voice actor we're trying to get on the show hopefully in the next couple weeks I will let him know and let's see what happens with it awesome take care buddy
[SPEAKER_08]: 877-GAME-OLR if you want to get through or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, that's 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Toll-free in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Canada, but if you're in another country besides those two, I would really urge you to use Skype because it's free, whereas you get charged for using toll-free numbers in non-North America countries.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do we have any last minute stories tonight, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Real quick, a few things on the Xbox 360 hacking scene.
[SPEAKER_06]: The two newer light-on drives that were unhackable before are now able to be dumped through a new method that they've figured out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also they found out a way to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Hack, Xbox Live Arcade Games, and now they can register any game that they have a demo for.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks to Yaris!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yaris made it possible.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there was some good for that game after all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Yaris had some good come out of it after all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, it does require that you have a modded homebrew-enabled system, which requires a certain mod chip and a firmware prior to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Beat Raiders coming to the iPhone, that's kind of neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's the Timbaland game, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you hear he collaborated with Miley Cyrus on the new album?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's an odd pairing, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Timbaland and Miley Cyrus?
[SPEAKER_08]: For real?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, she's trying to become more edgy, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if I can believe that, but all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all you got?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's all I got.
[SPEAKER_08]: When all is said and done, it wasn't a super busy news week.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, I'm going to ask you if you have anything last minute, but usually you speak up if you do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not feeling well, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope you feel better.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm feeling lightheaded.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, maybe you need to go lie down and take a nap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the good news is, then I suppose for you, is that the show is just about done here.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't look like we're getting any more calls, which there's a lot of shy chatters tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got some people going, should I call in?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm like, well, call in if you have something to say, but the phone's not going off.
[SPEAKER_06]: The good news is... What?
[SPEAKER_06]: I ordered my pasta for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that for you and the wife?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's for us and our guests.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a friend that just had their baby.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll back in.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't hate Utada's first US album.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's like OMG greatest thing ever, but it's not bad as a piece of pop music.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it was underrated, I think, by a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, if you're a fan of Timbaland, Utada's first US album, I'm looking forward to seeing her live.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to be a rare opportunity in January.
[SPEAKER_08]: So woohoo!
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, we're going to go around and wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know it's a little bit of a short show tonight, but it's been kind of a weird week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, right before Christmas, not a lot going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: People are just getting ready for the holidays and all that stuff, which actually already started with Hanukkah.
[SPEAKER_08]: It kind of kicks off the holiday season.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, you have all the other stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It really goes on through New Year's
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm tired.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't wait to eat the pasta
[SPEAKER_08]: That's my final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hail Godga, because it's the whole reason the show's getting screwed up tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you guys so much for tuning into and supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, we do the show for free, and all we ask, if you enjoy what you've heard, tell a friend or two about the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_08]: Word of mouth's all we got.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't have a big, big magazine or anything that backs us up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just us.
[SPEAKER_08]: We do accept donations.
[SPEAKER_08]: We will be back, though, next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Donations of money and food.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cookies are good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Macroons.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just gave Rob the last of my macaroons.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were delicious, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, that's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you guys so much.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll do it all again next week on the 19th.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, until then, I'm Rob, she's Jamie, he's Loki, and we're gone!
[SPEAKER_02]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_02]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_02]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but were probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: See you next week!