This week on the heels of the shakeup of gaming companies as we know them, the Legend of Android Gaming Machines returns. Let's just hope it doesn't follow the same path as Uya did. This is just one new alphabet initiative. Join us for more of the week's gaming news starting right now on the show where every gamer has a voice.
Orange Lounge Radio
I got a gamer hat on too, look!
It's a Klonoa hat.
Oh it's a Klonoa hat.
It's an official Klonoa hat.
I thought it was just Pac-Man because I can only see the one side. Awesome.
Very cool.
Because he has Pac-Man on his hat.
And Techmaster Loki of course is here as always.
Nothing video game themed on.
What's your shirt?
I couldn't see on the side.
I'm getting a whole bunch of new shirts this week.
Nothing green. Pinch. Pinch.
You see this?
Do you see this world?
I have green on my Apple Watch.
Happy St. Patrick's Day
to those of you that are in the mood for this season.
Or some of my friends call it
Straight Pride.
Oh it's an oatmeal shirt.
I'll explain this in a minute.
You know whenever gay pride gets brought up
there's always that troll that says
here you go, today's your day.
Celebrate. Enjoy your moment.
Every day.
Is white people straight pride?
All those characteristics are really
on display today. Have you been down to downtown today?
Have you been down K Street?
I avoided it like the plague you.
Anyhow.
So the shirt I'm wearing for the sake of the podcasters.
We are a podcast but we do tape
live at Twitch TV every Sunday night
at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 Eastern
at the Voice of Geeks Network.
VoGnetwork.com or VoGnetwork.com
right after the Bobby Black Wolf show.
So the shirt I'm actually wearing
is a Beat the Blurch shirt
from when they did those marathons a couple years ago.
Okay here's the funny thing behind this.
So I actually didn't run the marathon.
I was all signed up, ready to go.
I got super sick the night before.
And it wasn't one of those like
ugh I'm sick
and I don't think I can go.
No I was like
sick. So it wasn't happening.
So my pal Melody went and she brought back this shirt
so it's really funny because it says I beat the Blurch
and I ran 5k and it's like no you didn't hoe.
But oh well I still have the shirt
and it's one of the only green things I own so
it seemed appropriate to wear tonight.
A little warm for today though. We did get quite
toasty. I have
not been outside all day. How sad is that?
I foraged today. Did you?
For dandelion greens. Okay.
Well it was definitely
eaten a lot in the US during the Depression
because people ain't got no money
for food. But dandelions
the leaves are full of calcium
and iron and the
blossoms are actually edible as
well. Good source of fiber and beta carotene.
Are you vegan? No. Fuck no.
Okay. Hey listeners
do you see this? A little
traditional dish. This is
dead boiled cow.
And it has been in my mouth
it is almost as salty as I am.
Right. Almost. Almost.
Almost. But nothing can meet
those levels besides dead maybe the
ocean. Boiled bovine.
Anyhow. Hello to
everybody in our chat room because again
we do tape live at twitch.tv
slash vog network and we do have
lots of folks in chat. Some folks
also noticing on twitch tonight we did a special
our border tonight is green.
Just a little wink and a nod to the day
today and Bobby joined in on that too
so that was kind of fun. So yeah there you go.
Let's get into some video game discussion.
After all we are a show that talks about video game
and gaming culture. And I
guess this first kick off topic tonight is
a little bit about gamer culture. But this
has been all over the news. In fact I'm looking at an article
that actually came in on Reuters
about this. And it has to do with
influencers.
Influencers. And those people
that can influence people. I hope the camera
can pick up my eyes rolling.
It's a little further back now Loki.
You might have to roll them really good. That's why I'm just
subtitling
that with my eyes are rolling.
Before I even say the name
of the influencer why are you rolling your eyes
over here. Because it's not a non story.
I mean obviously you pay people
like any brand you pay people
to sponsor stuff.
Alright let me tell you what you're talking about.
So long story short
Ninja whose real name is Tyler
Blevins it seems like was
paid one million dollars
to promote
Apex Legends which
one might argue successful
campaign because Apex Legends has
been doing very well for itself. Not necessarily because he did it though.
That's true. You don't know if it's
because of him or just because of the strength of
the game itself. I think it's the game.
I think a big part of it is the game too.
I think
I want to get to the rest of the story but I think a big
part of Apex Legends success is
the fact that people were kind of
like I don't know about you guys but
like I can only be
sustained by one video game for so long.
And I've joked about this on the show before is that
I have and I don't mean to make light of like actual
conditions or anything. So if you can think of
a better name to call this and I'm open to it.
Oh my god. Let's not be so
super PC about everything.
Like we're going to start
now.
I'm just saying.
I have gamer ADD so I'll play
one thing for like five or ten minutes.
I am totally offended by that. My son
has ADD.
Actually ADHD.
I don't care. I'm just joking.
How about just general
lack of attention span.
My point is that I can only play one thing
for like five.
But you guys know I do this. I spend a bunch of
money on a game. I play it for a little bit and then it's like
on to the next game. There's very few games
that are able to hold my attention. Now
before because I'm sure there's chatters already
chiming in. What about the MMOs?
Because I do play things like Warcraft.
I play Final Fantasy 14.
And I kind of tend to stick to those for a long time.
But I think part of what makes those games a lot
different is the more social elements
of those games. But anyway.
I was getting to a point with this with Apex
Legends specifically. So with Apex Legends
the deal is that I think
a lot of folks who are
kind of like ready for the hot new thing after a couple
months. I think they were kind of done with Fortnite.
Not necessarily like done with Fortnite
like oh I'm over this game. But it's like
when this new kid shows up on the block that's
oh it's like a similar
formula but a little
different. And you know a different way of doing it.
Like I think a lot of people were like oh let's move
on to this. Because it's like kind of what I enjoy
but something new. Kind of
what happened to PUBG
once Fortnite came along.
Not to say either of those games are doing
terrible for themselves or not even like do well
but you know you can only be number
one for so long. Or maybe like not even
necessarily
Fortnite but like
maybe even Black Ops 4 or something like that.
There's lots of different games
out there. I think getting
Ninjas because he's very
well known for playing
Fortnite and whatnot.
And maybe the thought was okay
you get an influencer like this who has
a lot of the attention of the Fortnite crowd maybe
they'll see this and then want to try the game
out because it is free to play.
So I think that really helped a lot
is being that it's free and
not trying to sell you a $60 game that they're
going to throw the same type of microtransactions
and sort of monetization
schemes on top of.
Very true. I think the free thing really helps.
Although Bobby Blackwolf in our chat points
out PUBG was the
first big Twitch success story which I would
agree with. It wouldn't have gotten any traction if
they didn't have big Twitch streamers playing it.
Although PUBG wasn't free if I remember
right. It was kind of on the cheaper end of things.
PUBG isn't free yeah. Yeah it was like a $20
game I think when it was first in early access.
It's still. Yeah it's still. It's still like
20. They might have upped it a little bit.
Kind of like Minecraft. Remember Minecraft was cheaper
and then the price went up when it got really popular.
And I think PUBG is a very similar sort of
story. I think it was cheaper in the beginning than it is
now but it's not. It's certainly not $60.
It's still a budget title if you will.
Yeah. So and that
probably helps it as well.
Anyway.
Let's see. It was noted
that Ninja had
excuse me. Ninja
had tweeted about the game on February 5th
and then he had 13 million followers
on Twitch and went to play the game
on Twitch and he was paid for
1 million and this was according to a source
that gave that to Reuters.
I think that's how you pronounce that Reuters.
So anyhow and he may not have been the only one
that was actually paid
for this either.
It sounds like there may have been other folks too.
Yeah. So I mean
but this is the type of thing that they do
though. I mean even with like Battlefield
5 I think they had paid influencers as
well. There's
a lot of games that they have paid influencers
on and I think
the only reason it's notable is because it's like
oh it's a million dollars but I mean honestly
it's the same as like beauty care lines
paying celebrities to promote
their stuff on Instagram or whatever the
case may be. The same thing. Or paying
Kylie Jenner to promote Fyre Festival.
Yes exactly
like that. I'll be honest I mean even though
I'm not like a huge huge influencer
I got offered like
some crazy ass discount to
show off a cat ring.
I wanted to buy one anyway.
I mean the only reason that they were asking
people to pay for it is because the money goes back to charity
for homeless cats. So I was fine
doing it. So basically they were only charging
me the donation.
And
there's another
channel out there that's called Pretty
Pastel Please and she's in Australia
she used to work
actually she still works in advertising I think
but she talked about the whole influencer
thing and how it works behind the scenes too.
So it's exactly
there's a product to sell and there's someone that's streaming
it then
money's gonna go into
it. Right I mean and this isn't
gonna change it and it's a smarter
advertisement anyways because what are you gonna do actually put
out like TV advertisements or anything like
that. I mean it's
this is
this is the easiest way to get
to your target audience is by
going to where you know the
eyes are obviously twitch streamers
YouTube streamers
social
media platforms it's
gonna be it's basically targeted advertising
for this type of stuff and to put
stuff elsewhere
I mean doesn't really make sense
you're not gonna get as much of a return on
investment for that stuff so it just
makes sense. It's like I mean
to take it a lot more simply it's like when people choose
billboard placement they're gonna put
the billboards in the place
that the message needs to get out number one the most
like if it's for advertising not just the
you know y'all suck
you know you homophobes shut up. But I'm
talking about like the advertising ones
they're gonna put them like for restaurants
on the side of a highway so that
hungry people will go on
driving hangry and go get a burger
You know I think in the interest because you were talking
before I was having my coughing fit
sorry guys you were talking a minute
ago about how you've been offered this kind of
influence stuff and I think in the interest of disclosure
so is VOG Network and myself
personally in fact we're talking
about doing a game stream on
VOG Network right now with
a particular smaller publisher
but it's one of the it's a much smaller thing
it's like you know sure you give us an advanced
copy of your game for free we'll play it you know
for a couple hours just you know for the fun of it
you know because hey free game and you know
something that we can you know premiere to an audience
hopefully but I think
what strike I mean there there's also
I think a big step difference between that between
like you know ooh free game for playing
it early on stream and one
million dollars there's a big
big I'd do it for a million
right but
to be fair I mean
I don't want to sound like a bitter Betty either you know
it's very you can see how many people follow VOG
Network in my personal channel versus how many
people followed Ninja and it's very
very different
I would love it if 13 million people actually
I don't know if I would love it if 13 million people
followed VOG Network because then your
every little thing goes under scrutiny and all
that stuff and like you know you joked about
earlier when I was you know choosing my words
carefully well if we had
13 million followers I'd probably have to be
oh my god are you telling me that some of
their feelings are gonna be hurt
oh no people with hurt
feelings who gives a fuck
without going too far I give a fuck
I give a fuck too because I think
maybe not a hundred percent of the time
are these things that we see on
Tumblr and stuff always but some of it is
valid I understand that but like
using common sense aside from
you know the obvious things like
being just like completely insensitive
to people you're
gonna get somebody's gonna get
upset about some opinion you have about
something you can't please everybody
I will say this I think
that and this is just
people don't understand the
the difference between uh
intent and impact
and so
I think that we do have a responsibility
to watch some of what we say or make sure that
we preface it saying this isn't
said with malice here's the story
I mean I think call out culture
is a disease
but that being said there are people out
there who need to fucking be called out because they are
doing it out of malice and I think the best
I want to move back in the story but the best example
I can give of this is that you know like back
early when this show first started
I probably have used a phrase
a few times that I picked up off project
runway when he used to say hot
tea mess right
that used to be a phrase that was in pop culture and you probably saw it on
Saturday Night Live but like now in the
year 2019 I realized that that phrase
ain't cool and there's some people who yes
their feelings get legit hurt when they hear that
and so like you know I respect that so that's
that's what I'm talking about you know what I mean like you know
if somebody's going to get but at the
same time okay I have been a
long time running host of the Rocky Horror Picture
Show right and there's some people
that will write essays about how
Rocky Horror Picture Show is problematic and all this stuff
and I wasn't it meant to be
in a way and I say it is a
product of a different time in
1975 this is all there was but
et cetera et cetera so some people
I think want to
be mad just to be mad but
some of it is legitimate so we have
to navigate this delicate
place in between anyway
where was I oh yes Ninja has 13 million
followers and I don't a Ted Talk
um anyway
some other streamers were paid for this as well
EA paid Shroud who I guess is a popular
Polish Canadian streamer with
6 million Twitch followers
but that guy actually declined
because didn't want to
oh no I'm sorry I'm sorry that guy declined
to disclose the terms of the deal so it sounds like he
did it but we don't know how much money he was paid for it and so
forth but um
interesting
that this is a part of our
gaming culture now is that
some of these people that we do choose
to elevate with our Twitch
follows and the biddies and the subs
and all that stuff some of the people that we
do choose to elevate
um were
are making coin off it
basically I still
don't see why
PDP is still around
that is a whole nother Oprah that I don't
want to get into right now
so I should just really duct tape his tongue
to the top of his mouth and never remove
it anyway
um let me go to our chat over at
twitch.tv slash vog network
um
um let's
see uh some people are talking
about me uh leaving the room
uh bobby's saying we need to influence more so we need you
alive uh quest buster
in uh our twitch chat says
apex legends is something that
uh shroud probably would have paid
played anyway also he was
consulted for the game months ago as a
secret project which he publicly
admitted and you know I've heard of that type
of thing in the gaming industry before not just
with influencers but I've heard of it with
reviewers you know this is a thing
is that some game
websites and some big game websites
will take money
to do a
a review of a game basically that is
confidential between the site
and the publisher it's not the
real review it's a mock review basically
but it's like the actual like the way they would have reviewed
it if they played that product today that
review is never published it's sent to the publisher and the
publisher or the developer uses
it to implement feedback and make the game
better and then the real game
is reviewed by somebody
else on the same site obviously
you could understand that once somebody takes
a deal like that and has reviewed the game
one time that's not the same person that can write the
review later on but that whole like
consulting with a
personality is not particularly
unique to the gaming industry
what I think is unique is that now it's not
just like game reviewers but it's game
players and people who
in some ways you could say
review games live on stream
I guess that's that's
kind of one thing I think I've seen
done on Twitch before maybe have done myself
is that I'm getting my first impressions
of a game live on stream and
if I had 13 million followers
that's something I might be able to make
a little more money doing so
I don't know do you guys
think this is a dangerous thing for the industry
or it seems like based on
kind of like what I was hearing a minute ago based on the
fact that Instagram influencers are paid
and other types of industry
leaders are paid for endorsements
you know lovely celebrities
are paid for makeup campaigns and things like that
that maybe we're okay with this because
this is what we do
as long as they're following the law and the fact that
they're disclosing that's an advertisement
and that type of thing I don't see a problem
with it which they all did
so as long as they're doing that not trying to do
some shady shit where oh
I'm being paid to say something good about this
but I'm not telling you that it's an advertisement
that that's the only problem
which YouTube had a big thing with that
I want to say about a year ago
yeah it was the FTC
coming down on like all sorts
of different things and it was
it's they've been better about it
because I think some people were unaware
of what the law was but
it's been I think it's been
alright as far as people disclosing
stuff just as long as it's very upfront
like hey this is a paid advertisement
or you know paid sponsorship
with this you know
we're talking about this game
here's why um
then I'm fine with it
I don't know I don't watch Ninja
so I don't give a shit you know either way
and honestly to
I don't think yeah
it's good that he did that
and he's promoting that
but don't think really the game
needed that it was pretty
strong on its own but
do you think maybe that and
I don't think we want to say one person alone
did this but maybe the influencer
campaign as a whole let's say and all these
streamers that they may have worked out deals
with to do this do you think maybe that helped
this punt out the gate
because this game landed with a bang
as opposed to a slow build
maybe a game that took a little while for people
to discover and then it kind of
I guess but what might be more like
a Minecraft type situation it would be interesting
to see like how
you know how much of an influence those influencers
had like how how this
boosted the numbers to be interesting to see
but I don't know yeah it's a bummer because apex legends
they don't ask you where did you hear about our game
they don't really well they could have like I don't know there
could be maybe a link in the video or something like that
that has some sort of like tracking
tag or something enough that's the way
twitch usually does things if
you're playing a certain game maybe I have to
admit I wasn't watching those streams so I don't know
but I do know that sometimes like as an
affiliate there are certain games
and it's not all of them there are certain games that
if twitch sells them on the store
if you're playing them on your stream there'll be a little
link right under the stream to buy the game
and then that streamer gets a little cut of the money
and then I'm sure they can measure all that
analytics as well so I don't
I don't know but well I guess you know
I think they've got that whole twitch prime thing
right now is running with apex
legends so maybe that's a way that they're
trying to measure their audience I don't know
there's a lot I don't know I think this is a lot
of uncharted territory
one other thing I want to bring up in response to what you
say because I thought it was interesting because you talked about during
the whole YouTube scandal that you had a lot
of people who didn't know what the law was
which you know well they claim not
to know what the law was yeah fair enough
but I think when it does come to the law
you know not everybody
is very good at interpreting the law
all the time I think YouTube
tried to make strides to
dumb down the law and make these
videos for creators to help YouTube
makers understand the law
I think that's part of what they felt
their onus was to do which is fine
but I mean it also goes to
conversations about as our technology moves
more and more and more our laws
don't always seem to get updated
fast enough we talk about this all the time when it comes
to copyright, trademark
and IP laws
you know the dancing thing
that's come up before right the Carleton
is in the game and how do we handle that
right that whole thing
is just like this uncharted territory because the
laws are being updated as fast as the technology
yeah this is causing this
very interesting sort of story and they're not going to be unfortunately
because you have people that are
have a lot more money that want to control things
so they can keep all that money and
it's not going to change
yeah very interesting
let's see other comments in chat
5th Dream in chat says to me it just seems like
business as usual they do it on
TV always so
and Questbuster follows that up with
same here I'd be more surprised if
EA didn't do something marketing wise 5th Dream
so maybe this is just this interesting
new territory maybe you're going to see I think it's
kind of happening already but maybe you're going to see more
and more folks on
Twitch you know getting
some sort of
maybe either commutation be it
you know free game or maybe
well maybe we'll see that with EA's
Battlefield 5 thing that they've got
the new battle they have the new
was it
Battle Royale mode that's coming to
Battlefield 5 that they
had a trailer out for this week
they'll be showing that off because
everybody's got to jump on that
bandwagon all I got to say
is you can't be an industry leader if you're following
people so
alright
let's move on to what sorts of
games have been influencing us
this week as we talk about how is our
gaming week and the types of video games that we've
been playing this week Dark Soccer we'll start with you
how was your gaming week I
played a bunch of pinball really Pokemon
Go I touched
Ingress once
just to see if it was still there
I'm still playing
idle pouring I don't really mention it but I'm still
playing it
I am borrowing
Horizon Zero Dawn
I haven't started it yet but I figured I would
start it on stream or something
I was actually planning on starting to
stream this week but I have a birthday party
on Wednesday night and I'm going to see
Renae on Thursday so
which by the way thank you so much for
that shout out about women in games
here in Sacramento that was awesome
oh that was something
that Bre did right? Oh sorry that was Bre
why did I say Renae? I don't know but thank you Bre
because Renae was also floating
an article this week but it was about a different topic
I posted Renae's thing my brain
is like broken it's fine sorry
I have a donut
we miss her though she should come back to OLR
when she's ready I miss everybody
but no but I'm
going to go hang out with Renae and so maybe I'll play
games while I'm in San Francisco
while I was at
did I talk about the
Munster's release party at coin op?
you did a little bit last week
I didn't know if I had mentioned it but that was lit
so
we actually had a tweet that came in this week
about some folks were appreciating the pinball
talk that came up on OLR and I was like
dark soccer is a big pinball fan how many machines
do you have in your house now?
three in the house no six in the house
I'm at the house
collectively no I'm actually having to do the math
we are giving back
pinbot 2.0 we're borrowing it
we're trading back
Adam's family to get our twilight zone back
so twilight zone creature from the black lagoon
judge dread
I thought she was counting
like the ones in the house versus the ones in the garage
and I'm like same thing
the shadow and
one other I can't remember
so we have
I think eleven
right now it's enough where they're not only in your
garage but you have a spare bedroom
we move more in the house because Dan's Mustang is coming home
so we have to clear out the garage
so there's room for the Mustang
they're no longer rusting
it's a 1969 Mustang coupe
so do the math
it's huge
damn muscle cars though what's your favorite table
you own I already know this I actually have two
well World Cup soccer
is my favorite but my second favorite
is theater of magic what's the worst table you own
fuck I really hate
judge dread is
grown on me but I do not
like creature from the black lagoon
a lot of people love it it's just not
that fun for me and probably my least favorite
of all time would be the hobbit the new one
because it's slow as fuck
do not like a slow table
but you know it turns out that I have a type
with designers well I love everything
Steve Ritchie has done I seem
to be a John Papa Duke girl so
because my two favorites are Papa
Duke tables alright
I thought I thought it was appropriate to engage
in a little pinball talks there you go heck yeah
but we have Ghostbusters and I've been playing the
crap out of it for me I'm still waiting for
pin bot to hit virtual console because I love the
NES version of pin bot even though I know a lot of people hate it
I loved it they're actually we were
watching some pinball game reviews
like for NES versions the version
of the getaway that came out for
for one of the home
consoles it was pretty terra bad
I think getaway was
the NES I think they did that
one after pin bot because I know there was a
getaway that came out pretty pretty not good
yeah Bobby Black Wolf
is a little bit inspired
perhaps saying I still really really need to finally
clean out the room we're turning into our
arcade so I can finally start down the path
of Dark Sakura and Dan and collect
pinball tables absolutely
well you need to come over before
we get rid of brighter pin bot 2.0
yeah I want to come play do you know what that is
not the 2.0 I played your
you had a regular brighter pin bot at one point
oh wow so basically
brighter pin bot 2.0 has an extra board added
to it that has new rule sets
and it's linked to usually a color
DMD that has
different game modes and different things
and a new soundtrack like a digital soundtrack
it's pretty freaking amazing
so
after the show everybody
look on YouTube
and find video of a brighter
pin bot 2.0 just soundtrack
the soundtrack makes me think of
old Space Mountain
and by the way Dick Dale died
I heard, sad
alright, Loki how was your gaming week
what did you play? I didn't play a whole lot because
like I said I was working in Unity trying to get myself
back into the swing of working
in Unity again
so I finished my
code along tutorial
thing it was like some tank combat game
so that's done
I'm not really doing anything that I'm definitely not
publishing that because that's just
there's nothing different than what they
provide it's just kind of following
along to kind of get into the groove
of working in Unity
and also it kind of showed me a little bit
of the audio mixer which is something that they added
a while ago but since I haven't used
it before I didn't really
know what it did so that was kind of cool
to learn that a little bit
and then let's
see I played a little bit of Dance Dance Revolution
Extreme I saw your
live stream yeah a little bit
it was funny because I haven't noticed this
because I have a legit
extreme but I'm running a mod
disc right now because I was playing
other mixes but I don't know
if it's the drive or the disc I
burned but it doesn't run very well
on the other mixes so
I put it back to extreme because I just didn't
want to mess with that crap anymore
so I have extreme and I'm running mods
in it but I didn't realize that the extreme
version that's on that mod disc
is a modded extreme
so it's got extra modifiers on there
like the 0.5 speed
wave and there's some
other thing it was the stuff that was in like
extreme
it's not extreme plus because I think
extreme plus is the one with the marvelous
the marvelous ratings
there's one it's
what the hell
is it called Megamix it's like
Megamix but Megamix also had one
that I can actually adjust the clock speed
of the game so that the songs that speed up or slow
down so it's like
oh that's like a Beat Saber type of thing
so it's Megamix mods so it's got some of those
in there but
I didn't realize it was in there until I
was playing it I was like wait a second 0.5
speed that's not normally there like oh
crap this is a modded one so
I tried that in
Max 300 and nope
cannot play it like that it's
it doesn't work well for me so
I was
just playing other stuff though so I have been going through the
mods some more because I don't
remember like some of these
and I also have to remove some of the ones I have duplicates
on there or just they're broken like I have
a dynamite ray of one that I think I
made maybe that's off by
like at least a whole
measure so that kind of sucks
and then I
played
Pokemon Go a little bit
I didn't play too much on PC
I played
a little bit of this game called
Jelly Mario which is
a weird
web game you can play so it's
Jelly Mar
.io and
go check it out it's free
and you basically have to
traverse Mario and
he's just this big jelly thing and everything in
the world is very
jelly like and it's
very hard especially when you get to the
castle because you have to dodge
all the fire bars and
sometimes you just can't get the
momentum right to be able to pass
through that so let me play that on stream on Tuesday
because I'm planning on streaming
on PC on Tuesday either
maybe Jelly Mario and
Saints Row 2 but I wanted to do
Saints Row 2 because I love Saints Row 2
and it's a great game and I watched some other guy
that I follow call me Kevin
play it and it looked hilarious I'm like
I remember how hilarious that game was I want to play that
so we'll be doing that
and I'm going to try to stream
more DDR during the week
I wanted to stream more actually
earlier in the week but I was fighting with
stupid OBS
because it decided that oh hey you don't have permissions
to run this anymore for no reason
so I had to
download it again and it finally worked but it took me
30 minutes to figure that out
but yeah I need to
get back into the swing of playing DDR every day
instead of just like once or twice a week
alright that's it
my giveaway probably a little more scaled
back than I'm used to I don't want to talk a lot
about this yet until I've really truly
made it a habit but I'm trying to
change my fitness journey and that all
started this week so I'll leave it at that for now
until I actually stick with it
because I don't want to be that person that's like you know two days
into it like I'm making these greats and then
I fall off the wagon so check
in with me in a few weeks but
meanwhile so that's been cutting into my time
a little bit but meanwhile I'm still
playing the good old MMOs that I have
been sticking by like World of Warcraft
which is funny because I don't
you know when I used to play
and was super into wow I would do
raiding and I would do all this stuff I've been playing
kind of by myself but one thing I've
kind of noticed about World of Warcraft that's kind of
grown on me is that there's so much more you can do by yourself
like I've geared my character up to
I hit the point where my resto
shaman is now out geared my
warlock that I was running for a while
and my shaman
whose named Porkchop by the way
in memoriam of the
very first queen to ever be booted from
RuPaul's Drag Race
so Porkchop is
level 300 and plus I just love
a panda shaman named Porkchop
oh she's still around I haven't like
I don't think I've deleted a character
that was like above level 10
if I play though I'll probably move my
dragon huntie
I mean honestly
demon huntie the only thing that matters about
Horde and Alliance or I'm sorry the only
thing that matters to play with other people is Horde and
Alliance like your server like just doesn't
matter anymore it really doesn't
I want to like play in areas
yeah I know but you get moved over to other servers now
like the whole thing like if you and I
party you'll suddenly be on my server
shit yeah yeah no and like
servers don't even fucking matter anymore it's great
like I wish Final Fantasy 14 would steal that
technology but anyway yeah
I do a lot of world quests
and I just do a lot of like queuing up by myself and things
like that and that's just kind of like my mind numbing
thing to do but I have played other games
too and one I haven't talked about on the show yet even
though I started it last week and I played
a little more this week so I'm
continuing my PlayStation VR adventures
and catching up on my backlog on PlayStation
VR I started playing Skyrim
VR so I've been playing that a little bit
so that's a game that you've actually played that I have yet
in the play yet oh right high five
okay so
well here's the thing once I found out
you don't have to actually use the
move controllers because I was like
that sounds like a ridiculous and like look don't get me
wrong like move plus VR
is great for like Beat Saber
this print
vector I was talking about last week
I did download that radial G game
as well I played that a little bit that actually doesn't
use the move so I don't know why I brought that up just then but I did
so
so but I'm like I don't want to play Skyrim
with a freaking move controller it's like this is too
much I don't need to this is not how you play
Skyrim
you don't need to do it that way right so
I just want to like controller
but just instead of my TV VR
because the Skyrim world
is gorgeous it always was even
from the very first version of the game
so I wanted to see what that looked like in VR so
I'm playing just with
the plain old controller and I'm
playing in VR and it is
it's a very good looking game like I found myself
doing the same thing I think a lot of us did
when we first played Skyrim I was stopping
to stare at the flowers because I'm like they're so
purple and they're 3D and they're
cute so here's the interesting thing about
VR because obviously VR brings
all these you know
concerns about is somebody
going to get motion sick and things like that
so what they do
they actually have all sorts of ways
you can control it but
you can turn by looking
and move in those directions but
what you do is that the right stick
instead of being a full pivot to
look around and move instead it like
turns you automatically like maybe 30
degrees one direction so like if you tap
left on the right stick it just turns you
30 degrees one direction and I think
now I believe you can change it and
make it a full rotation
but then that means you're rotating it's going to be different from
where you're looking and that's what makes people sick so that's
not the default but they if you want
to play the throw up ride you can I guess
but I'm getting
kind of used to the whole being able to move
on the right stick and like change
my perspective and it actually kind of
works and I dig it it's
you know the way you actually target things
then is to look so let's say like I've been playing
a mage and let's say I zap a wolf
which you know as you're walking down from that first
cave you run into a couple wolves so I zapped
a wolf with lightning and then
to loot the corpse you have to kind of like look at
the wolf so that your little crosshair
goes on it and then you can loot it so it's
That sounds annoying as fuck
I'm into it
I don't know if I could play the entire
20 hour experience this way it's a
lot but like
20 hours or whatever
How long does it take to do the main story?
Main story only
I don't know I've never finished
Let's be clear I meant main story only
Have I ever finished the main story?
Which main story?
Like just the main quest that gets you
to the game's ending
so to speak
There is a main questline and it's separated from side quest
when you're looking at your journal there's very clearly a main questline
The Alduin main questline
or the main questline with the two
factions
I think the Alduin
is considered because the factions
can't you do both technically?
I think
My husband Alan is the expert on that
because he has played Skyrim
every single
minus DLC he didn't do all the DLC
but every single quest
except for the ones that generate
because there's like the generating quests
Oh god those never end
but I'm still pretty impressed at that
type of achievement
It's interesting and I like watching
different scenes so they do some things
different so that very first opening scene
where you're in the cart and then you watch that
guy get killed by the executioner and the dragon
shows up they do it a little differently
because again they don't want to
move you without you
having some control over it so what
happens is that it kind of just quickly fades out
fades in to these different perspectives
so like you'll be standing there and it
fade out fade in you're looking up at the
sky and you see the dragon land fade out
fade in you're looking somewhere else
and I was kind of like wait a minute I don't remember it
being that way in the regular game and then I thought in my head
oh they're doing that because they don't want to
make somebody sick from motion that
they aren't controlling so they can't
deliver that the same way that you could in
a traditional monitor so it's kind of interesting
like those subtle little differences but
they didn't like take away anything or whatever
in fact I think it's good that they didn't just
slap Skyrim in VR and say play
they had to think of some of these things I thought was
very interesting so
um let's see
going into chat again at
live excuse me at twitch tv
slash vog network uh Bobby says
I stopped with the move controllers pretty quickly
in Skyrim VR but that's how you play
Twilight Princess right? Yes
but there is also a difference is that
Twilight Princess was designed from
the ground up for that whereas
Skyrim they kind of had to shoehorn the
move thing back into it like I'm sure
it's a fine experience
it's just not what I want to play
because I don't associate Skyrim with that
whereas Twilight Princess
for me quintessentially
a Switch game yes I know
it was originally developed for Wii U but we all
know that they put a lot of thought into
the Switch instead on that and that
you know it was going to use those types of controls
you know at some point
early-ish mid-development or whatever
they made a conscious choice to
have a lot of Switch functionality in there as well
so anyway
let's see
oh I'm sorry I was
why was I thinking that you're right they said
Twilight Princess and I immediately went to
um
my mind immediately went to the new one Breath of the Wild
my bad
so Twilight Princess on Wii well again
I still think the same argument applies
it was designed with the Wii in mind even though
sure it was also a game it was like the exact same
thing actually so maybe that's why my
brain kind of confused the two for a minute
anyway um
Bobby says they also fade
in the edges of your vision when you
move which also helps decrease
motion sickness it does not eliminate
motion sickness for people who are extremely
prone I noticed that too I noticed
the edges narrowed in really quickly
when you did that and I felt
I didn't haze
the game for that because I'm like okay there's very much a reason
they're doing this like it's very
obvious like because when you look around you
have freedom so like it's not a system
this is a conscious decision I would hope that
I could turn that off because like I
don't have a problem with motion sickness I played
Minecraft on
um the Oculus
uh
Gear VR thing and
I used you know the controller
like you know you shouldn't really
this is not necessarily
recommended to use the controller for this and
I was like nah this is cool I can't speak
to that specifically but I can
say there is a pretty extensive VR
customization menu and it wouldn't surprise
me if that was something you could turn on and off
but you know I
think it's smart that it uses
the safest settings by default
yeah if that makes sense so
anyway um I'm talking
a lot about a game that originally came
out many years ago so let's
move on I think that's it for our gaming
weeks uh I think it's time we get into some
gaming news I don't have a lot of housekeeping
because I don't know of any shows off
Memorial Day but that's way
the day before Memorial Day will be our next
show off because I won't be here so I'm out of town so
we won't have a show that weekend so enjoy your
three day Memorial weekend I'm in Chicago that
weekend when is this Memorial
Day so end of
May oh I'll be at DragCon
oh okay there you go so
I'll be doing
I don't know staycation programming
streaming playing games
kids kids alright
let's get into some gaming news Loki
so GDC is right around the corner
and of course the thought
or the tease has been
that Google is going to announce some sort of
game console or streaming service or
both or who knows
so of course a little bit more
credence to that Google has
announced via their Google
developers Twitter
page that hey guess what
id Software is
joining them alongside
during this whole
presentation not only that
they've revealed that also Ubisoft
is going to be
partnering with them as well
so definitely
seems to hint the fact
that hey you had this whole test
of like you know streaming
Assassin's Creed
and now you have them
partnering with them and
you have other game companies partnering
with them that yeah probably
there's going to be some sort of announcement at GDC
I think that's kind of expected
at this point but I guess we'll
have to wait and find out March 19th
at 1230
so by this time next week we'll know
we'll be able to talk about it more in depth on the show
but any thoughts I mean you talk about
this whole streaming thing so does it seem like
maybe Google is going for a
streaming console that will stream
but not is Google making the Phantom
that's what I want
if it's going to be
exactly like the Assassin's Creed
thing was I would see it being built into
the Chrome browser
that may not be the case
for like say
you know like Android or something like that
maybe they'll have an app to go along with that
or something maybe it's going to
they're going to put out their own standalone
app or like kind of Google
TV type thing that's going to have
that built into it
we'll have to wait and see but
I think since they were testing the whole browser
compatibility with that
that that's probably going to be the route at least
one of the routes that they're going to go
so we'll have to wait and see because I mean think about it
most people a lot of people use
Chrome and you can just
hey install Chrome and
boom you have access to these games you know if you want
to pay a subscription or
whatever the case may be
and then you get to play these games
on a PC and it doesn't even have to be a high-end
PC it can be just one that
can run that
that has somewhat decent specs I think
and a decent internet connection
let me ask this kind of weird
question is that
we know that Google and for those that
are on Twitch my watch is yelling at me to stand
so I'm going to stand for a little bit so if it looks weird
sorry but
let me ask you like
because we don't know exactly what this
console is going to be doing
and we would be just
theorizing things
and we could get proven wrong but what I can
ask is what
would Google need to do
and I open this up to our chatters and Jamie
if you have an opinion as well what would
Google need to do to convince
you to buy another console
and have another console in your house what
could they do knowing what you know about
Google what could Google do
differently that hasn't been done
before
I don't know if there's anything they
can do they just have to have good
games good exclusive games I'm not going to
buy another console to play Assassin's Creed Odyssey
or Doom or something
like that that's already out on
numerous other consoles
honestly I don't really
see any reason to buy it because I have everything
else I already want most of my
gaming lately has been on my
PC well and to be fair they
haven't made the pitch yet so we can say that
now but if it's a system what
needs to be in that pitch to sway you
it's going to take something really
huge I mean that's all it is because
I mean when Sony came
out you know for a first time with a new
system they had
a lot of good backing they had stuff coming
out that people wanted to play although Toshinden
doesn't necessarily count but
then you know
it's really a system is
only as good as the games that are on it
it's got to have the right
games to grab that attention like for example
if they had Namco behind
them and Namco's like we're going to do
Klonoa 3 exclusively for Google's
platform I'd be like bitch
mine
well I mean yeah and to that
fact I mean remember Game Center and stuff
when they were trying to really hype that up on
the whole iOS site I mean they
had you know it doing
or was it Epic Games
I don't remember doing the
one medieval
like first person game that they had on there and
that was just kind of it was cool
does anyone remember it now? No
so like
I
it's just hard like saying oh yeah we have
all these games that are popular on other
platforms but we're creating a new platform why
do I need to go to a new platform to play
I want to know what
you're going to do differently are you how you're
going to make this more interesting than these
other platforms what are you going to give me that
the other platforms can't give me what
new like exclusively brand
new games are you going to have on this platform
that I can't get anywhere else
here's my thought and again I don't want to go
too far down this path because it's all theorizing
anyway but if it's you know
being able to play games
that are already available what can
they do to make you want to do that
put out a $40 console
and I know that sounds ridiculous but
you know keep in mind what that little Google
Chromecast those aren't particularly expensive
right what if there's something that incorporates
gaming with that and it's like super cheap
and so it's like hey instead of buying
a $300 Xbox why don't you buy
this $40 Chromecast I get that
if it's that again
this is crazy I don't think that they could pull
$40 because Chromecast is basically
just a receiver your computer your computer
is sending the data to Chromecast
I feel like I did this exact same thing last year
what if there's a Microsoft Xbox
they have like Google TV boxes
aren't that expensive like my box
what was it the my box they have
the Huawei one I have
it's um
it's like 80 bucks I mean it's not that
expensive and but and it
does like gaming stuff on it
like I can purchase games on there like through
the Google Play Store I have you can
install the Steam Link app on there
you can um
you can stream to it just like you can
with a
you know one of those dongles
so assuming that that's
powerful enough to run whatever app
that they have to be able to stream this stuff
then yeah that would work just fine
um I don't think
you can't obviously be a very
expensive console if you're gonna do that but
once again I don't know
if I need to really purchase another thing
because I have smart we're in the land of smart
TVs nowadays here's the thing too and my
wish list would be that I hope Google takes a good
hard look at why Steam Link failed but
I mean we keep talking about this but I think at the end of the day
this is going to be more the streaming and the
existing games and all that might be
one element of this it might be a way to
um buffer the launch library
or whatever of Google's games but
and I think this is very important isn't it
out there now like on Twitter or somewhere that
Jade Raymond is at Google that's
because you know she left
her last thing when the Star Wars right
she was on the Star Wars thing that got cancelled right
and she disappeared and nobody really
kept tabs on where she ended up well it came out
this week she's at Google so
whatever this is likely
involves her and whatever
she's working on now so
I don't think we're just talking about
existing games I mean and I don't know
she could be a vision person maybe
she's not designing a game I don't know we're not
gonna know until we hear this one yeah and I hope
that's the case because you're gonna need to
have exclusive stuff you having all the other
games things are good as well
but you need to have something that's
exclusive to your platform because you can't just
say well we have all these other games
that the same those consoles have too and you're like
well crap I already have that console
that has those games or I have a PC that has those
games the only thing I see that it's a pretty
decent angle that they could go with is like
you know what say you
don't have one of those consoles say you own
a Nintendo Switch and that's all you own you know
and they can't run these in your PC you know
you have a decent PC but it's not
a gaming PC and you can't run this stuff
well this box will help you be able to
play those games that you can't play
elsewhere and we can do it pretty cheap
and then that's you know and
hey we'll throw a subscription service in there as well
that's how I can see them being
successful with it but
we'll see I don't know they've tried
so many times with doing like exclusive
they tried to make like iOS
is gonna be like this big gaming
centric thing they've had exclusive games coming
to it and no one gives a shit about
that as far as being like oh my god
this is gonna replace my gaming consoles
I think what
it is is I think
my prediction take it or leave it
is I do think Google is about to launch
they wanna be the Netflix of games as well
so they're gonna launch a competitor to Xbox
Game Pass essentially I think Google's
looking to do that and they're gonna do it through
something that probably
integrates into your TV pretty easy but
maybe something they can also deliver through Android phones
although I don't think that will be very great for the gaming experience
but we'll see maybe Google
will prove me wrong
but I think they're going to launch
their own type of competitor for that
and just like Netflix has to create
their own originals which
hopefully they don't cancel cause that was in the news this
week but I digress but just like Netflix
makes their own originals like Stranger Things and
shows that buff up the service
I think they are creating a few of their own
in house type of games to
buff up whatever this is
but something very interesting
Google did have a game developer before
Niantic, Google let him go
when that whole alphabet split happened
now granted what Niantic develops
are not things for the television
when Niantic's been developing of course Niantic
is the developer of Pokemon Go
but at the time Ingress was kind of their bread and butter
but it turns out they were also
creating this Pokemon Go at the time the split happened
so you know
Niantic's not creating games on the television but
I think it is interesting to note
that Google did have a game developer
that they uh
and one that ended up being a pretty big deal
after Pokemon Go that they let out
they let walk out the door
so they may still have an investment level in it
I don't know all the finance
but I think Nintendo is an investor
Google probably still has some money in it
we'll see
and off topic a little bit did you get to see the screenshots
for the new Harry Potter game
um
oh yes I did
I didn't make our show tonight
so some screenshots came out for Harry Potter Wizards Unite
which is Niantic's next game
I still don't know what you do in the game
they're partnering with
going off script for a little bit
so they're partnering with the Warner Brothers
the Portkey games
and it really looks like based on the screenshots
Portkey is helping them with the art assets
to give it that Harry Potter look
because the game looks pretty nice
and it doesn't look anything like Pokemon Go
or Ingress for sure
and basically there's no teams
so Harry Potter will not be a team based game
it sounds like you will join a house
for your character
but it's not something you're locked into
and it's not something where it's like
Slytherin versus Hufflepuff
or whatever
it's not going to be like Ingress or Pokemon Go
or very team or faction based
and it seems like it's about collecting what's called
foundables
there's a lot of talk of things in the Harry Potter lore
that since I don't follow it as closely
I didn't get it as much
but it sounds like it's kind of like a successor
to the ongoing story
but not the Cursed Child
kind of like in between that
and something where you're looking for
these foundables because there's some sort of
war that's brewing in the world where they have to
bring all these collectables
back and you play some type of
magic force
and I apologize to the Harry Potter fans
which Jamie I think you follow these books more than I do
for sure
but you should look up the stuff that came out
on the game this week because there was very clearly some sort
of Niantic press day
that the embargo lifted and all these websites
did their previews the same day
so there's some more info on the game out there right now
I'll take a peek, where my interest has been
peaked, aha!
I think it's great that
they're taking a no teams approach because that tells me
it's a very different game from the other two
right out the gate
I wonder though if they would have your house based on where you live
so if you're in the US you get
the Ilvermorny
it does not sound like that's
the case, it does sound like the
four traditional houses come into play
because in the story
you're going out into the world
to collect everything, so you could still
be like, yeah I think that's how
they wrote it in the story, but never say never
Dark Soccer and again I am no Harry Potter
expert so anything is still possible
alright, okay
yeah I didn't understand based on the screenshots
I know that they showed that you can do spells
to attack werewolves and crap
you have to save Harry
from being attacked by
there was this game I played on
iOS, it's probably on Android too
I think it was called Magica or something
I don't know if that was the name, but I remember
it was a game where you would trace
it was also a real world based
game and you would draw spells to
cast them in battle and stuff
and it seems like that is being included
I don't know, we'll see, I mean hey it's free
you can try it out
let's see, see a Tiberian chat
says clearly developed by a Hufflepuff
diplomatic looking for things
not about Flashy showing off
interesting
so, well we'll see
of course I'm going to try the game when it
comes out, I have played really
great AR real world
games and I have played trash
AR real world games, I played Garfield
Go for like a minute
I played Garfield Go for a couple minutes as well
I played that Draconius Go
that was like the rip off, actually the
Draconius thing brought some different ideas to the table
that game wasn't trash, it just
was kind of clunky
you know what my sister plays a lot
actually is that Jurassic parking
she's like really into that
that wasn't bad, I didn't dislike
it, it was just a little, I don't know
I don't like it when the stuff is randomly
generated, I think part of what's always
drawn me to my Niantic games
is that they are based on real world things
I would have never known were there if I
hadn't bothered to look
you know, in the early days when I first started
playing Ingress, I was like
I never had any idea that these things
were in my neighborhood and I think that's exactly
what Niantic was trying to do with that game
is get you out into your
neighborhood and know that these things were there
now granted, it's all user based
so, for example
they call the thing down the street, I want to say what they
call it, but you know what they call that in the game
and I don't think it is what they call it
it's certainly not, so
I don't think everything is necessarily educational
so, it's yeah
taking liberties with
I'm surprised that the other thing
that's at the other park
is not something because
that's more significant than
a box in the ground
it has been tried to be submitted
multiple times because I keep seeing it
and are you talking about a thing
that looks like a, and I'm sorry we're having to be cryptic
I have a right to my privacy
I don't even know what the hell it is
does it look like an electrical thing?
yes
that has tried to be submitted at least three times
because I keep seeing it in the freaking OPR
and I can tell you without question
who's doing it and why they want it
but it's
look, the playground's fine
gazebos are fine, that ain't fine
there's hazardous
don't go here all around it
that can't be a point of interest
anyway, Bobby Blackwolf points out
what's happening now around here is I'm seeing
pokestops for things that no longer exist
yeah, that happens too
I mean, the game's been out a while
you could report them invalid in Ingress
I don't know if you could do that natively in Pokemon Go though
no, because I had to do that
there was some murals and stuff
that were near my house
that there's no mural there anymore
I was kind of wondering
that inside, but then you look at the photo
and it's outside and it's clearly not there anymore
alright, well I want to move on
I do want to go to the next story we have here
which is about
the Valve Store and the Steam Store
and a potential kind of
privacy sort of issue
that may have happened with the Epic Store
here's the deal
Valve is out there implying that
Epic's launcher has copied
user data from Steam
and now they're going to launch an investigation
whatever that means
apparently what happened is that Epic
did confirm this
was taking their launcher and it made an encrypted
local copy of your
local config.vdf
Steam file, because what it was
doing is that when you would say yes
I want to import my Steam friends
into the Epic Store
game, it's using that
file to do it, but Epic is saying
in a quote they said
information from
this file is only sent to Epic if you
choose to import your Steam friends
and then only hashed IDs
of your friends are sent and no
other information from the file
and that's only
accessing that information after you choose
to import Steam friends, but of course
Valve, not happy about it
in a statement to bleep the computer
it's been there forever though, I mean like
it's been like that for months
in a statement to bleeping computer
Valve said, we are looking into
what information the Epic launcher collects
from Steam, the Steam client locally
saves data such as the list of games you own
your friends list and saved login tokens
similar to information stored
in web browser cookies, which makes sense
if you have 500 games in your library you don't want
Steam loading that every time
But isn't that the same as like if I
downloaded the Firefox
web browser and it wants to import my data
and cookies and stuff like that, I mean that's basic
Yeah, it's basically the same thing, you're right
And why are we throwing a fit about this?
I think they're just, whatever
You think they're making an issue just to make an issue?
I think they're making an issue just to make an issue
And maybe that's
part of it, I don't know
Kaijuto in chat over
at twitch.tv slash vog network though says
Epic fail
I don't know, again, I don't know if this is any different
from what other places are doing, but maybe they
weren't super transparent in what
they were doing, but it would make sense
that if you want this
launcher, this store
to access your Steam's
friends list, then you are giving it some
sort of permission to access Steam
Right? I mean that would be implied, right?
It just doesn't just magically know
And I don't, I did do the
import, because whatever
I did it in GOG too, because GOG
used to have that thing, I think they sunsetted it
But they used to have that thing where like if you own
a game on Steam, you'd like get a copy
of it on GOG, but it was limited to
certain games only, but still there were a few that
came over, so like I let my GOG
access my Steam, where
was the stink about that?
I don't remember that
It's because it's convenient now, because everyone's
upset about privacy
and people breaching privacy
agreements and stuff like that
Hey look it, they're bad
Bobby wants to point out the difference, Bobby
sometimes understands the tech stuff
better than I do, that's for sure, so he
explains what the difference is
Epic is preemptively getting this
data, and then asking
if you want to import it
Firefox doesn't go after the data
until you tell it to, that's the
problem, is that Epic is preemptively grabbing
that file going, I'm just gonna
put this right back over here
for when this user says they want to
import their Steam friends, because who wouldn't want to do that
Fine, I mean I guess they could just
easily not
do that, I mean that seems like a very easy fix
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
Are they even saying that Epic has
already fixed it? I'm trying to see if in this
story they mention that Epic already fixed
it, but this might have been too
no, I haven't
seen any, because this story was just from
yesterday on the 16th, so I haven't seen anything
yet, but I imagine that's something
that Epic's probably gonna do would be the easy
fix, would be to just stop grabbing that file
until you say yes
import my Steam friends
Anyway
Let's move on, DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
This one actually is going
to be a little bit of cultural
explanation
is needed behind it, but
there's a game that was coming
out, it's part of the Yakuza
series in Japan
that's called
Yakuza slash Ryugagotoku
the game's called Judge Eyes
and actually it was going to be coming out
in the US under the name Judgment
it was developed by Sega, well they took
it down off of their website because the
actor who plays a crime boss
in the game, the real life
actor, Pierre Taki
was
caught for possession
and use of cocaine
and
for a scandal
like that, drug use scandals are
pretty much, they're almost
career ending, it's what
happens is that instead of here where it
could drive sales of something
you know, or people want to know more
about it and the person's out in the limelight
and getting Lindsay Lohan style fame
there, people are
pretty much erased from the public eye
yeah I know, I was like, over here it's like
what, Lindsay Lohan's doing cocaine?
what a shock, you know
I'd be more surprised if she wasn't
doing cocaine
well in Japan you
sort of are publicly erased
so in that case
the game Judge Eyes
has been pulled off of Sega's site, all their
marketing, social media has been
completely removed, they've halted
sales of the game digitally, they've
pulled back their shipping orders
for the game, they are taking a big
hit to take this off the market
and then of course whether or not it's going to have
US release still
remains to be seen
I mean it did have, for the main character
it was actually handled
acted by and voiced by
Kimura Takaya who's
a member of SMAP
so I mean we're talking big names
and if anyone
might not know
Pierre Taki from his own
acting, he's also
part of a synth pop duo called Denki Groove
which I know that some people
listen to some of the Japanese
synth pop so
I mean the game looked to be
pretty interesting, I had
even heard about it before
all this went down, but I'm really not
surprised that for
how it's going down in Japan that this is happening
this way, you know other situations
like this
is that there's
been other actors
there was, I'm trying to see
Taki was also the voice of
Olaf
yeah and I was about to say because Sia Tabiri in chat says
didn't something similar happen to one of the voice actors from Kingdom Hearts 3
yes it's actually the same story
but it's only going to affect the Japanese release
of the game because the voice acting is not
the Japanese voice acting is not
in the US release
it's another thing too is that anyone who does work
for a company is seen
almost directly
as a representative
of the company and so
they distance themselves from it
which basically is where that
public erasure comes from
is to protect
the reputation of the company
oh it's very much a culture thing, I mean not in Japan
but in some other countries
you can get put to death
drug smuggling is like a
death penalty charge, didn't you all watch Broke Down
Palace?
if an American were to go to Japan
and have pot on them
they would be
deported immediately
and also usually banned from returning
to the country
which again, the marijuana
perspective is changing significantly
in this country, especially where we live
we're in California, there's a pot store not that far
from here and I drive by every day on my way home
from work
there was a delay in the release of some Studio Ghibli
stuff because
the musician Asuka who did
some vocals for a music video
was arrested for drug possession
and another anime, Kill Me Baby
were pulled from public circulation
because the voice actress
Takabei had cocaine
speaking of the international
thing though, I know we're joking about
Lindsay Lohan and I have no idea what her
drug status is
but does
it seem to only affect people
and celebrities from that country
because isn't there still a lot of
you know, like American pop culture
stuff that makes its way into Japan
and do they still hold
the American celebrities to that same standard
because I don't think they do
I don't think so, I mean I don't know
Well that's kind of messed up
Either that or it's just only
I don't think it matters so much
if it's a reflection on
an American arm of the company
because
I guess they expect that shit from us anyway
I don't know
Stupid Americans and the cocaine
But I mean, in the long
run it's just like
I don't know
Yeah
It's a completely different
It's a cultural difference and we have to be respectful
of that but at the same time, you know
we are a video game show, it's interesting to talk about how this
wow, I mean because of this culture
this game that was supposed to come out is being delayed
not to make it better
Big marketing too
The site for this, just looking at how it was built
Good lord
There was some work that went into that
And we're talking about Instagram line
Yeah
You know, some of the big marketing outlets
And honestly enough, there is a part of me
that wishes we had that same sort of
idea here
Because then
there wouldn't be such a big
I'm going to do this terrible thing
because it's going to bring attention to me
How far down the rabbit hole
do I want to go?
But here's why they don't
Because we also have a problem in this country
about it being equal
based on what you look like
if you know what I mean, right?
Anyway, I got to watch
Far Down the Rabbit Hole, but I think
that is an issue that we have to
deal with here
that is why we don't do that
I'm saying
I think that
public and business
ostracization
for people who are like that
until there's been a period of recovery
is a good idea
so that they aren't having
this big public spectacle meltdown and setting
an example for other people
Well, isn't it also sort of the American way that we protest?
I mean, that's kind of what happens
That's different. I think that's entirely different
They've been having a protest
recently in Japan for LGBT rights
for a right to marry
So, just saying
Protesting happens there, too
Burn some bras
for equal marriage
I don't know
What I'm saying is that
this is a different thing than a protest
This is
keeping a company
reputation
clean, and distancing
themselves from something like that
instead of using it as a marketing tool
Some other comments in our chat
over at twitch.tv
Bobby Blackwolf pointing out
you have to get special waivers to take prescription
Adderall in Japan
Can't buy ibuprofen over the counter
Oh, really?
But you can get toothpaste that rebuilds the
enamel on your teeth, and they don't sell it here
But here, you can't get Tylenol 3
whereas you can go into Canada
and you can't
Dear Canadian friends
Anyway
I hear also in Valve you can't get Tylenol 3
either
Fuck off
Anyway, Bobby Blackwolf in chat says
they accept that pot is something that
Westerners do, they do not
accept that pot is something that Japanese
do
Interesting way of putting it, and that's probably
a very succinct way of saying it
SHA100Matt says, I think Russell Brand
got deported from Japan
for something like this. Whatever happened to that guy?
I know someone first hand
who I used to work with that got deported, and he's half
Japanese
I think his was like a limitation
that after like six years
he could return for family visits
But still, that's wowie
He got deported for pot
Alright
Taking drugs into other countries is just
generally not a good idea
unless you have a prescription
and you have all those forms
that was brought up previously
which is probably best you don't bring drugs
Besides, if you're high on drugs, then all those genitals
become unblurred, and they can't have that
What?
For porn
Oh, Jesus Christ
Remember Final Fuck X
I'm like, there's a joke
you tried to tell that I'm just
not getting
Alright, anyway
Please can we move on
Next story
Let's move on. Let's talk about that number three
in Valve, shall we?
Well, Valve is not going to be putting out
a sequel for Left 4 Dead anytime soon
but that doesn't mean that you can't live without
Left 4 Dead, because it's going to be back
Left 4 Dead is coming back
as Back 4 Blood
It is a spiritual successor to Left 4 Dead
that is going to be coming out
by Turtle Rock and Warner Brothers
and
it is basically
very similar to
Left 4 Dead
They don't really have many details about it yet
not even any pictures, but
I'm sure it'll be something we'll be hearing about very soon
maybe E3 or GDC
So, I'm looking forward to that
because Left 4 Dead was a pretty awesome game
Too bad we never got a third one
But here you go!
Well, now we get something that's similar
Isn't that interesting when that happens
when the publisher
doesn't want to make the next game
so the team is just like, alright, we'll just
go make our own studio and make the game
we want to make. Interesting
It's been a few years
since Left 4 Dead 2, though, so it'll be interesting
to see what kind of changes
they put in the game
new engine, certainly
some more social elements, who knows
We'll see
Alright, especially because
Left 4 Dead was one of those first
horde mode type of games that ever existed
and now there's been a ton of hordes
Like a purely co-op
type of game
Now we've had Gears of War, Mass Effect multiplayer
Horde mode was kind of like
what we had for a while instead of Battle Royale
So it'll be really interesting to see
what they
now have learned in these years
that that genre was really
in the spotlight
That's something I'm trying to shoehorn
Battle Royale in there
Shehulk in chat says, yes, big fun
Left 4 Dead 3
Yeah, no, people really
I know Alan was a big fan of Left 4 Dead games too
A little scary for me, but I might try it again
I might try it again. My tastes in gaming
have evolved a little bit
and you can make it even worse
How so? Like make it scarier?
Or can it make it cute?
I was going to say rainbows and puppies
and kittens
Yeah, I saw some pretty weird stuff
Okay, that would be alright. If a kitten
jumps up and surprises me, I'm okay with that
But it's a mean kitten
No, I don't like mean kittens
It's Goose
Did you see it, by the way?
See what? Captain Marvel
Then I'm not going to spoil
I'll never get to the movies
No, I'm going to take you to see it
One day this week, we're going to go
You are going to enjoy
Free movie, awesome
It is the best
Do I have to see the other Marvel movies?
No
The last Marvel movie I saw was
The First Avengers
Maybe for one of the after credits
But I can explain that because I haven't even seen
Age of Ultron
I haven't seen the Thanos movie
Although everyone spoiled it for me
Okay, well yeah, that one's been all over
I've not watched it yet
But, I mean
I haven't watched
Black Panther yet either
Captain Marvel is the best
I do want to see Black Panther
No, it is the best
You haven't seen it, so you can't say anything about it
Okay, fine, I'll watch it and then we'll see that
it's not the best
It speaks to women's experiences every fucking day
And every man should be
required to watch it
Okay, sure
I don't watch a lot of superhero movies
at all, but I do want to see what is
coming out that I do want to see
Is that us? That looks scary
as hell
That I want to see, that's for sure
Alright, um
Let's see, going in chat
Let's see, Tigerclaw says
If you're a cat lover, you must see Captain Marvel
My retort would be if you're a cat lover
you must see Carly Rae Jepsen's new music
video, because
that was also a cat thing and it's incredible
and so you should see it
Okay, let's see
Let's move on and talk about the
Overwatch League
And this was
kind of one of those things where I said
I jabbed the Overwatch League a little bit
I should say jab, I said it was room for improvement
when I was first talking about the Overwatch League
It's nice to see them taking this
step into this next story
And the fact
that Overwatch League has been successful enough
to do this I think is pretty cool as well
It says a lot about where esports might be going
But next year they are saying
according to Commissioner
Nate Nasner
Overwatch League teams
will be playing in their cities
next year, so
right now if you weren't already aware
there's the Blizzard Arena in
Los Angeles
and that's where all the matches are being
played, but for next year
if you are the San Francisco Shock
which would be the closest team to us
there's going to be a place in San Francisco
where you go to see them play because
Yeah, don't they have like their own esports arena?
I mean that's, I thought
I know at least Oakland does, I'm sure San Francisco does somewhere
I'm just not up and up on where all the places are
Who it was that had the
arena, because I know that they were doing the
DDR tournament from there and
That was in Oakland
Yeah, which I mean, you know
The San Francisco 49ers play in Santa Clara
which is like 45 minutes away on a good day
so it doesn't always have to match exactly
I don't know where they're playing this stuff, we'll find out
Yeah, but
you know, but what's going to be interesting about this is that
you have teams in China
you have teams in Europe
all over the US and Canada
so it's going to be like these time zones
I'm like, dang
this might be a little rough on
some of the players because these time zones
are all going to be all over the map, right?
So, it'll be interesting
to see what the schedule looks like to make this happen
but I think this is
this is a good next step for esports
I think it is important, I think if you want to
grow esports to have the availability
for people to go watch and see the game in person
and really see what it's all about
I think that is going to be a great step
so, you know, maybe I'll go
to San Francisco and see one of these someday
and see what it's all about
I still have some
reservations on what the team
rosters look like and so forth, but we'll see
maybe that will improve in 2020 as well
yeah, so this has always been something
that they are going for
I'm looking for the original tweet here, here it is
from Nate Nasner who says
there won't be even more
there's 20 teams today, there might be even more
by this time next year, so
we'll see
let's see, Bobby in chat
is saying
I wonder if it's like the current structure
where there will be a weekend where a bunch of teams
are in a home team city
to play each other, that's what they're doing in
Atlanta in June for the Atlanta rain
instead of doing home and away matches
I'm unsure
I don't know what
that's, if it's going to be one for one
or what they'll do with that, it'll be interesting to see though
so
let's see, and yeah, as you see 100 Matt
as far as the team thing goes points out the New York
Giants and Jets play in New Jersey
and that's how it works sometimes, yep
so, anyhow
we'll see what develops with the Overwatch League, I think
I think they're on, not that I want you guys to
leave, but I think they're on right now
and you know, I think they do
a lot of stuff throughout the week
there's a lot of programming there, so it'll be
it's going to be interesting to see if that gets
bigger and bigger and where that ends up going
so, alright, let's move on
Darsakra, you have a kind of neat rumor
for us, right?
Well, there's been some interesting
revelations regarding
what should be, what could be the PlayStation 5
more rumors, but it's based
off of a patent that Sony filed
in October last year
and also, I think, quickly it's worth mentioning
this rumor, you got, you're reading this in like, what
Esquire or something, it's a big magazine
so, like, this isn't just like some dude said on Twitter
this is like, magazines are picking this up and running
with it, yeah
So, basically, they think that the PlayStation 5
is going to include
deep learning technology
basically using the player's skills
and habits to adapt the games
the patent reads like this
with a quote
Generally, a video game and video game
assistants are adapted to a player
for example, a narrative of the video game
is personalized to an experience level of
the player, similarly, assistants and interacting
with particular content of the video game
is also personalized
the personalization learns from
historical interactions of players
with the video game and optionally
other video games, in an example
a deep learning neural network is implemented
to generate knowledge from
historical interactions, the personalization
is then set according to the knowledge
so, basically, it's like Psycho Mantis
on steroids
Is this real, I mean, it sounds fancy
and high tech, but I have to ask the hard question
is it really, though? I mean, don't get me wrong
this sounds neat, um, you know
I love the idea of a game, especially like
for kids that are playing it, that like gets easier
if they keep dying in the same spot or whatever
or maybe if you're really good at it gets harder
but then I can't help but think, like, you know
like, let's say, like, an elliptical machine
can increase
or decrease the workout based on how you're
performing and where your heart rate is at
so, I mean, and that's just
a little machine
like, it's not a Playstation 5, so I'm just saying
like, it sounds like, ooh
it's this, like, big technology, but it's like
it more sounds like it's a way of thinking
a system, a core thing
to maybe put in that all games would consider
It doesn't seem like that's something that a system
should be doing, that's something that a game developer
should be putting in if they want to implement
that, because... Or maybe the game contains the algorithm
but the machine has the hardware for it
And maybe it's something like
6-axis, not to put a negative spin on it
but developers can choose if they just
want to put it in or not very easy, right?
Or, let's say that Steam
gives you easy access
to put in mods and achievements and things like that
like, it's your choice if you want to, how much
you want to run with that type of thing, I could see that
but, if it is Sony's
thing, you can bet your ass
that things like Last of Us 3
Uncharted, whatever they do
all these games I'm making up, but you know
our Sony's powerhouses
would likely implement this
you know, because they're Sony's games, so of course
they want to show off Sony's tech
Right, right
What do you think, Barasaka?
Would you be more interested in
PlayStation 5 or something like this?
I just said that I think it's going to be implemented
through the games, with the hardware being on the system
and I honestly think it would be great
I mean, but I'd also like the opportunity to be able to
turn it off and have it not transmit data
Okay
I don't want it to learn and then send my
habits to Sony
Okay, makes sense
But that could be something they're thinking about is
the portability, so that like if I play at a friend's
house, but then you're right, you'd have to
send to Sony and maybe that's
I don't mind analytics for
like anonymous analytics
Um, you know
in the case of your computer with anonymous analytics
they use that to determine how to
you know, release software updates
how to make the things better, when to do
full security updates if a lot of people are
reporting the same issue, you know
that's fine, crash reports
whatever, but I don't want
personalized data
I don't mind if it's anonymous, like
my 23andMe stuff is pretty much anonymous
I don't care, but
if it has my name on it
which I opted out of anything that put my name on it
I would have a problem with it
Same goes with this, I don't want
my habits directly
related to me to go out
to whatever
they can store Let me ask this very
real question, because this is actually how
I conduct myself on Playstation
What if you could put your fake name on it?
I still
wouldn't want that because my fake name now is
so traceable It's still individualized
in a way Yeah
it would still be, because I mean
at the very least they would have whatever billing information
that you put in through it, because your real name is on
your billing information
It's still linked over
If you're paying for like pay station network
I, you're right
I think Sony probably has that for me, but you do
since their little hack and that whole thing
I believe you do not have to store
a credit card on Playstation servers But
if you've ever had one stored
your name is still there on the account True
Historically
the information is there
You know, I'm what, either Dark Sakura
or Kurotsubasa, like every fucking where
people usually know that
if they see the name, there's a big chance it's me
So, just saying
Let's see, and yeah, if you see Rob Roberts
you know it's me or the gun guy
Apparently if you Google
Rob Roberts you get a guy that sells guns
How about that? Alright, let's see
Dungeon Buster I get a porn star for
Jamie Summers Do you really?
And then some lady in Columbus
But you were supposed to be the Bionic Woman
Where's the Bionic Woman? Because I spell my name differently
Oh, that's right, that's right, okay
Dungeon Buster or Quest Buster in our chat
at Twitch TV says
Xanac, a throwback here, Xanac
adapted its difficulty depending on how the player
did during the NES days
The game would sometimes change in small ways
change up patterns, etc.
That's true, but that's
not really learning
Because it wouldn't retain
that information and it wouldn't
alter it, it wouldn't remember
that that was your difficulty level
Okay, that's maybe the little click for me that I needed
to understand how this is like
new and fancy It's just programming
In this case, this would be machine learning
It would learn your habits and
adapt whatever game has the capacity
to use that to your habits as a gamer
Okay, so like
They say, this bitch is a rage quitter, we're only
gonna let her play up to level 4
Interesting, so how you perform
in Uncharted
may dictate the difficulty level where
Last of Us starts is what this could be
Possibly, that's how I translated it too
Okay, okay, I get it
Going further, if it looks at your habits on the
network, are you
a rage quitter? Are you
someone who gets a lot of abuse
from complaints? You could start
into whatever game
you might be streaming with all of these
marks against you, it could really go
a lot further than that
Interesting, and of course there's sad little man babies
out there who'll try to be pissy to female gamers
and you know
like what happened with movie ratings
and everything, who will
There's people who've done it to me and the things
were completely unfounded, they were just
crying little man babies, so
I drink male tears, I moisturize with them
Keep crying
babies
Let's try to see if there's other comments in chat
Shehulk in our chat says
since the big Playstation 3 data lost
10 years ago, I still get notices
from possible theft from Sony
and you know that whole data theft, it is
going to have to be something that's in the back of Sony's
minds about, you know, again assuming this
is true, but you know
a lot of magazines
and things seem to be running with it, is that
Sony will have to be mindful
about how it uses that data
because it knows it's already been in trouble
for a breach of data once before
so, I mean
but I guess maybe the question would be
is how good you are or aren't at a video game
sensitive data
but I guess it really depends on
what is it that the Playstation is actually
collecting
Anyway, SSJ100 Matt suggests
self-destruct the consoles
of chronic toxic players
Hey, I always like the idea
of them getting their own little island
Have fun at Toxic Fantasy Island
That's exactly what it is
Toxic Fantasy Island
And then we nuke it from orbit
Complete with tattoo
We just nuke it from orbit
Right. Now then we airdrop a bunch of therapists
That could be the intro
to one of our future shows
Toxic Fantasy Island will not be seen tonight
Just airdrop a bunch of therapists
that's all
Let's move on. Something else to talk about
Loki
I don't know. The whole Toxic Fantasy Island sounds awesome
So this is also
something that's pretty awesome
and surprising that's coming to Steam
Halo the Master Chief Collection
is coming to PC
and it's also coming to
not only the Windows Store
or Microsoft Store or whatever we're calling it
nowadays, but the Steam
Store as well
and on top of all of that
they're going to be including Halo Reach now
So it is
going to be
it will run at 60 FPS
it will support up to 4K
and they're going to be adding
on Xbox One the Halo Reach multiplayer
will be available as a free add-on for anyone
that owns the collection
and they said the single player campaign will cost extra
They don't have a date on the Halo Reach stuff
but they're going to be putting out
I guess stuff piecemeal
so it's going to be
Halo Combat Evolved
Anniversary, Halo 2, Halo 3
Halo 4
and then I guess
I don't know. Halo 5 will be added later
So I think when I bought
my Xbox One
I got a digital copy of this
because I don't think I have the disc
I think it's a digital copy
so does that mean I'll get it on PC for free because it's digital?
Maybe. You can play anywhere
I don't know if it's a play anywhere game
I thought everything was supposed to be play anywhere now
Probably most of their games are play anywhere
I hope
Kaishido in chat says
all they need is Halo Reach 3-2
those games were so much fun
so yeah a lot of fans are Reach out there
so I'm sure very happy to hear that
I haven't answered for all that
I have an answer for that
No
You were never a Halo fan anyway
The only thing I liked about Halo
was Red vs Blue
and the shiny stabby weapon
I like the shiny stabby weapon
Oh yeah I do like the shiny stabby weapon
Halo 2 is like a throwback to college for me
I used to like to play that online with some of my college buddies
and we would use the shiny stabby thing quite a bit
My fond memory was
Dan's bachelor party
because you were at my bachelorette party
I was
We had to go to the house to get my stuff
and they had something like
5 TVs hooked up
doing Halo LAN
Okay
Before we get to our next story
this question keeps coming up in chat
and so I have to address it
and they're noticing on the camera there
S2100 Matt says
Yes I am
OLR bringing rivals together
Okay
Where every foodie has a voice
I haven't started my Dunkin yet
because I have a little banana for a stomach
Thank you surgery
I had to finish my corned beef
I told myself I was gonna eat so much
dead bovine until I got sick
Guess who's sick right now
That would be me but I'm not like
super sick I stopped right before like
throwing up sick
So I am stuck
So the donuts are being saved right?
The donuts are being saved they are gonna be breakfast
And that was a low key contribution
Thank you which I greatly appreciate
The Boston cream is gonna be my
I'm about to go to bed snack but I need a sugar rush
which isn't a good idea before you go to bed
And then my double chocolate
is gonna be breakfast tomorrow
Where I will again
get the shakes from reactive hypoglycemia
Low key was kind of
offer for me too but
since I am trying to be better about fitness
I decided to pass on the donuts and while I
still do drink the coffee
I had just had a Starbucks so I
didn't want to have lots of coffee
By the way though speaking of
fitness I am
thinking about going back to Nerd Fit
Where they use their leveling up system
I'm trying to remember what that was
That name sounds familiar
It was people to eat keto and all this
but
their exercise program
used like levels and then they would do like
this like special
challenge thing for like certain
exercises and you turn it in and you get a badge
and some shit but I'm thinking about
going back to like a leveling system
for working out because I am officially
not
the first week in April I've got
the okay to go back to powerlifting
and
I'm gonna fill my arm
wings, my extra skin that I have
left over with meat
not just you know dead bovine
I've been using the watch tracking
for fitness quite a bit that's been doing
really good for me which reminds me I was gonna
send a private information request to you
Jamie but I guess you don't have yours, oh no
yours is right there, there it is
I'm not competitive
Some people have been sharing theirs with me
I've been interested in what some
other people are doing but I'd rather just talk to people
and find out what they're doing
cause I like to think I'm fairly adaptive
with my fitness regimen
I just found out that it will beat people
when you close your rings I didn't realize that
that was a thing but like so I was at
the gym yesterday and as soon as I get
off the machine I have multiple text messages
from people I'm sharing data with that are saying
like congrats or whatever and I'm just
like wait did my watch like
tell you that I'm so I thought that was
it was weird but I was like well that's
kinda nice I guess those little
those little bits of motivation can always be cute
so I just
really only
track myself
cause the only person I can be accountable to is myself
yeah being competitive
doesn't really do anything for me
I'm not competitive with it it's more like
I want to
these are good goals
like the standing thing I was doing earlier
they're good goals to have
I do it for myself I don't need to share that data
with other people to feel good about what
I'm doing or maintain my goals
I'm not
there's some people out there who are truly
I would say
motivated by competition
that's not me that's why most of the time
if I'm playing a game I prefer a single person narrative
I prefer and so what I'm
gonna be doing is as I level
up I'm going to be
using like a game or something
and do say this is my level up game
but I will be sharing my level ups
with everybody in the form of content
alright well speaking of leveling
up moving on to
a next story before we get to our classic
segment the
Xbox Live by Microsoft
is coming out for iOS and
Android so maybe this is another way if you want to be
competitive with achievements this is
something you could do or you maybe don't want
to be competitive you want to just be able to send
messages to friends on the on their
I'm telling you though this like combined with the
Google thing they were talking about before streaming
like if I could like purchase Game Pass
you
know on an Android device
and be able to like play those like
Xbox games on my TV or
on my PC
that would be useful
to me because I don't want to buy another console
well what this is
this news is about is that Microsoft is going to allow
developers of mobile games to use Xbox
Live features it's a new mobile
SDK that is part of Microsoft's
initiative to allow game developers
you know of all sizes indie
small large to
use Xbox Live on whatever platform you want
to create on which we already
kind of knew Xbox Live is
making strides in going into Switch games
which was a big deal when we first talked about that
the only place you're probably not going to see Xbox Live
is on Sony which you know
you understand why that is the way
it is but anyway you can choose
from features like
achievements, clubs, gamerscore
friends list, family
settings that's interesting too
talking about adapting to
automatic settings
that's very interesting that let's say
you know this is a kid account right off the gate
so maybe it shouldn't show
dramatic blood effects or whatever
I don't know it goes with a particular game
or because it's Loki you should show
extra dramatic blood effects
on the game. It's not dramatic if it's not
extra so
anyway very cool
this is coming and I'm sure we're going to hear more
about this at Game Developers Conference
but it was confirmed that this is
happening by the way in kind of a related
story of sorts it should be
mentioned about this too there is a brand new
app that came out for Windows
called Wireless Display and it
will let you play PC games
on your Xbox
with varied
success it seems like it's something that's still early
on now as it is today
you can play Xbox stuff on
your PC there's a little Xbox
app for Windows 10 I've actually done that and it
works well enough as long as there's not a lot
of other network traffic going on like I don't do it
if Alan's trying to play Overwatch because
technically I guess you could still do that if
you had your output
HDMI output from your PC into your
Xbox remember they have a pass through sure
you could but this
is a way to do it through the network
through your house basically
but they're saying not every game
really works very well with this some folks have done
some testing and said some games work
some games don't
but I imagine it's going to be interesting
the more and more this technology gets refined
although at the same time I don't usually
want to play something like World of Warcraft on my television
I want to play it on my PC but I guess
again for people that are playing things like I don't know
the new Devil's May Cry game let's say you're buying that
on PC then being able to
have that on your TV
is interesting but again
it's apparently working with some mixed success
right now seems like it's technology
that will probably get refined in the coming weeks
as more and more people complain about things
and so forth so
anyhow
some comments
on Microsoft She-Hulk over
at Twitch TV slash VOG Network says
Xbox Live community is robust
much more social
than Sony or Nintendo
well that's you know I think we've joked here on
OLR that maybe Microsoft
should just build Nintendo's online forum
well Nintendo used to have a pretty robust
online forum and then they got rid of it
they did well it wasn't
you know the whole
what do they call it
the thing that they discontinued where you could do all the
cool pictures and everything oh SwapNote?
no not SwapNote they have
Miiverse oh Miiverse
okay
I get what you're saying Miiverse was an interesting idea
but it really ran clunky it was kind of
it wasn't it was I'll say
Miiverse was best when it was integrated
directly into the games like Mario Maker
that was a good use I will give you that that was
a really good use of Miiverse
Splatoon kind of had that as well in fact
what they did is they just kind of like
took that part and put it in
the new Splatoon that's on Switch so
you know it's interesting
I guess you could say the legacy of
Miiverse lives on in that regard
I don't know but anyway
other games continue to
live on here at Orange Lounge Radio
as we move into a segment we like
to call the classic game of the week or
as the case may be in 2019
once a month Dark
Sakura dips into the gaming vault and says
hey here's a soundtrack
that you should be paying attention to the game
may or may not be great but
the soundtrack is definitely something
worth noticing so what is our special
classic soundtrack of the month
this is going to
be a game I will eventually review
but it's Abadox
The Deadly Inner War
and this
particular game
okay there we go
this particular game
came out
this music doesn't go for this level
I know what I did is I took the base music
and I just put it over gameplays they have something to look at
alrighty well anyway
but it's actually the first level has my favorite music
otherwise it's all ground beef
yeah it'll cycle through the
different songs in the game
but yeah the first level is actually my favorite music
in the entire game too because the game's hard
and I died a lot so
but anyway
it's I mean it's pretty
it's not like one of the best games ever
it was by Natsume
with the main
programmer having worked on Contra
actually the music
but it was
Sada Kyohei who
he did a lot of work for Konami
it really
was very influenced
by Contra
and some of the other shooting games
and this is the song you were mentioning
earlier I believe
this was like my favorite piece of music in this whole game
and it sounds like a fucking Contra song
it does
it's like I was showing this to Dan
and he's like oh yeah that's definitely a Natsume
game I was like yeah but listen to the music
he's like that sounds like Contra-ish
I'm like yarp
you know that heavy
rhythm in it that you had from
a lot of the Konami games
but at any rate I mean
my second favorite piece of music in this game
is the ending music which I never got to
but people in my
my papa was really
good at this game and he beat the game
it was this
and you know
Jackal that he and I used to play a lot together
before he died and so
this
I just had to pick this music I don't really have too much else
about the programming of the music but I thought the soundtrack
was worth a mention because for such a
you know
middle of the road game
the music in it was really good
yeah and this has been kind of the
neat thing about this little feature that you're doing
even though the first month you did Guardian Legend
which of course is a must right
you really kind of have been picking games that are like
okay maybe the games were eh
but the soundtracks are A
plus and I think that's always kind of neat
you want to play a game because
you just want to hear the damn music
it's so good
also I was just giving it a look
for Famicom information
the box art in Japan was so
much better than the crap we got here
She-Hulk and Child wants to know
is the soundtrack on vinyl?
I don't think so
this game really wasn't a super popular one
it was unique in the US
because it was a Milton Bradley published game
which kind of goes with
which you associate more with board games
exactly but Milton Bradley
did a decent number of releases for
games they did but none of them were
like A plus
like games you remember
but I mean wasn't Milton Bradley
the Game Genie
or not Game Genie that was Galoob
the
dammit the
Power Glove
didn't they do I do not recall
I
don't remember who did Power Glove
I don't know I'm looking it up right now
so they
did the power they were
partly responsible for the power pad
the power pad? yeah
so
Milton life force
the games that were
done by Milton Bradley
that were published or distributed
Cabal California Games
Captain Skyhawk
Gordon vs. Bird Marble Madness
Time Lord
which is sadly a Doctor Who game
World Games
yeah not very many games
but they were and by the way
Rob World Games is by Epix
I do yeah that I do know
trust founder of the Epix
game store shut the fuck up
god
that happened on Bobby's show anyway
we're bringing it around
and keep in mind Milton Bradley actually
had a console in 1979
they had the micro vision oh really
yep hold on let's see something
real quick while we're here this is
turned into the Milton Bradley segment of the month
well I mean it doesn't
hurt to educate people sure
so ugh stupid accepting cookies
I'd rather have a real cookie
thank you um so yeah
not much is coming up but yeah you know
they they did
different stuff I mean like I said
they had been in the video game business off and on
and had you know purples and things
like that but yeah so
there you go
alright your classic soundtrack
of the month how do you say Abadox
Abadox oh wait you might
remember the commercial it's the kid playing on his
bed and then like purple slime shoots
out of his TV at him and it was supposed
it was advertised
as like the most disgusting game
oh yeah cause
that was all the shit that was on TV it was like
the Double Dare
Fun House was even grosser and like all the
like gross splat and all that
stuff this game ain't
ain't disgusting I played R-Type
alright
uh we're gonna move on to a
viewer submission I'm very hyped about
this cause we haven't had one of these in a while since
um Matt did one of these for MAGFest but I did
put the call out and I said hey listeners
if you're interested in like you know highlighting a game
or telling us a little bit about you know a game that you're playing
or what have you I'm looking for some listener
segments and leave it to good old Flaco
Jones who sent us this submission
tonight where um he's gonna talk to us a little
bit about the game Paladins and
uh pay attention cause he gets into the reason why
and I think it's uh it's really cool so we're gonna go
to uh this segment here courtesy of
our pal Flaco Jones
Hey everybody this is
Flaco Jones uh I wanted to make
this video because well first of all Rob asked for it
and I thought it'd be cool to focus on a
free game cause he said you know focus on free games
would be good and this came
up recently because on OLR they were talking
about Overwatch and how it doesn't
support cross play and how could they ever support
cross play I'm like well there's a game that does
support cross play that's a lot like Overwatch
and so this game popped in my head I'm like oh I should
make a video for OLR so they can actually see
the game in action so
uh this is Paladins I'm actually gonna make
my camera go away so
that I can focus on showing the game play
and I'm gonna edit stuff in so it's not just staring
at menus the whole time cause I'm pretty much gonna be
talking over the menus
so uh this is it it's free game
and because it's free
you can go to the store and you can
see all the stuff they try to sell you
and there's DLC where you can
actually get all the champions
current and future for just $30 which I think
is a pretty good deal but I personally have never
spent a dime on this game I
do my daily quests I grind out gold
I use gold to unlock champions which are you know
like heroes and Overwatch
champions in this game I'm gonna be comparing
it to Overwatch a lot because the games
are very similar it's been accused of being
Overwatch clone not gonna
fight that accusation but I'm gonna say
it still stands on it's own
alright so and I wanted to briefly
show you since we were talking about
cross play you go to controls
you go all the way to the bottom and this is where the cross
play is uh the settings
are right here so you can say I only
wanna go against people using a gamepad
or I only wanna go against everybody and have
shorter queues I do
gamepad I think it's more fair and the reason
they do that they don't even say console is because
based on whether you have a gamepad
plugged in or not that's how it queues you
and if you try to queue in this gamepad and then pull it
out and try to trick everybody
and use your keyboard and mouse that won't work
it'll kick you out of the
games they said so in their patch notes so
yeah I play gamepad only
I think it's really cool they allow that
because it doesn't matter what platform you're playing on
PC you're playing on Switch
you're playing Xbox One you're playing
you know Xbox One supports
keyboard and mouse as well so if you're playing keyboard and mouse
as Xbox One you still would be with
the allow all people not with the gamepad
people and it would show on your input method right there
um I didn't mention
Sony I wonder why that is oh because they're not
supporting it right now so they're not supporting
cross play right now
I think it's gonna happen but
you know there's been some controversy over
who's fault it is but the developers of this game
said they're ready to go the balls
in Sony's court so hopefully Sony approves that
pretty soon cause I would really like to play this
on Playstation uh
let's see uh what do we got here
oh yeah so if you wanna learn how to play
there's uh these training
modes over here they have
trainings for all the different modes which I'll get into those in a second
and they have a shooting range and the shooting range
you can practice as any champion and that's
kinda cool even champions you haven't unlocked yet
so I like that
there's no tutorial here and I think
that's weird and so I looked it up and sure enough
there is a tutorial on the other consoles
just on Switch they didn't put it on there because the
file size would have been too big so they
cut that out
that's too bad but you know so if you really
wanna learn how to play it is a free to play the game you could
download it on a different
console and play it on there and if you prefer to play on Switch
you can play on there but again it's cross
platform and cross progression
so anything you do saves across all the platforms
except for Playstation
so let's see I said I'd get into the modes
so here's the different modes let's go to Quick Play
and look at our settings so there's Siege
there's Onslaught and there's Team Deathmatch
Siege kinda plays like the
Overwatch hybrid maps those are the maps
where you capture the objective and then once you capture the
objective you escort the payload
Onslaught
all that one is is take the objective hold it until
whatever team gets 400 points
first the longer you stay there you
earn points and getting kills also
earns you points and then Team Deathmatch
speaks for itself 5v5
you know just try to kill
as many as you can so there's like
there's one more big difference between this and
Overwatch which is
when you start this game first
you'll have you pick a talent
every champion gets
three talents to choose from you select
one and it's kind of like your focus for that
game after that you
get to pick your loadouts now loadouts
are here in the game if you go
into a champion you can go
into their loadouts and you can make
new ones or you can use there's always a
preset one there so if you're uncomfortable
with this just use the pre-made but once
you get good at this game you can kinda build your own
so I think that's pretty awesome
and then after you pick that when the game
starts they have this thing called the item shop
which I've heard is a lot like League of Legends
I don't play leagues I don't know but as you
play this game you earn credits for
doing well at your character's job
if you're healing a lot you'll get credits that way
if you stay in the objective a lot you'll get credits that way
if you're a damaged player and you're
getting a lot of kills you get more credits that way you spend
your credits on this thing called
the item shop and the item shop
is kind of I think this game's answer to
hero switching that Overwatch has
you can't switch heroes in this game
so with the item shop you can kinda see what the
other team is running or even
compliment what your team is running and get items
from the item shop to boast
up those certain things so you can have
better healing you can
take less damage from direct damage if the
team has a lot of AoE damage you can
lessen the AoE damage just a little bit you can lower
your cooldowns you can increase your
ultimate you know
generation so there's all sorts of things
you can buy
in the item shop and there's not anything you can
pay to win they just you just earn it
like everybody else does by playing the game
and it's only for that match you don't get
they don't carry over so there's no
pay to win or anything in this game which is kinda nice
so let's look at the champions
this is the bread and butter
of the game I have a lot of champions as you
can see here I have all but it looks like
nine right now but there's actually rotating champions
which I don't have all of them actually I think
I only have one I have two of them
so that means I'm missing
eleven characters out of the forty
forty man roster is really good
so again they
have these four that rotate every week it's not always
gonna be these four I'm gonna focus for this
video on the ones you get when you
start the game for free you've never played it before
and that is the reason
it's four is cause there's one support
that's their healers
one frontline that's their tanks one damage
speaks for itself
and one flanker which is the damage that
attacks from the side or behind
let's look at Genos
so Genos
is the free healer
that you get if you've never played paladins before
and here's how the abilities
break down I'll show
some video while I'm talking about it so you're
not just staring at this screen the whole time
so star splitter is his main attack
everybody's main attack is his right trigger
it's just like a machine gun
you know everybody in this game pretty much
shoots even the healers and they do pretty well at
it you don't have to do a lot of weapon switching
uh which is pretty cool
so and then his left one is his heal
the left trigger is his heal and that
his heal kinda works like Zenyatta
so he puts a heal bloom on
somebody it stays on him as long as you keep him in line of sight
and it does a good job
uh Stellar Wind is the
right shoulder button the right shoulder button on almost
every character I'm pretty sure
every character actually is like a quick
getaway button it's like some kind of speed button
so in this case
it's his Stellar Wind he moves 65%
faster and you can even
get a loadout where you take less damage
in that mode which is nice too
so it's a really good way
to escape from people something I kinda wish Zenyatta
and Overwatch had was a way to escape cause he really
doesn't he's kind of a sitting duck
uh and then the left button there
the left shoulder button is his void grip
you can also use that to escape with him but it
holds enemies up in the air stuns them does a little
damage if your teammates around they can kill the person while
they're in the air it's really cool kind of support
ability and his ultimate
is through time and space it channels this
tunnel of like death
and it shoots anybody that's
standing in the tunnel there's like a kind of a cast time
so you have time to get away from it if you're paying attention
but if he's got you trapped and you're in the middle of a fight
if you're standing in that tunnel
you're dead okay
so let's go to the next free character that's gonna be
Lex Lex is the free flanker in the game
let's look at his abilities
he's got magnums
think like reaper's guns they just shoot one
at a time bang bang bang bang they're good medium
to close range
his left trigger is in
pursuit that just kind of
unloads his weapons even faster
in like a short area kind of like McCree's like
you know when he shoots off his guns really
fast
his R is a combat slide again
you can use that to escape or you can use it to close in on somebody
and finish him off
his left shoulder is retribution
you cast out on people they take more damage
you earn credits when you kill them when they have retribution on
you can spec for that to be better as well
and then finally his ultimate is the law
it's a lot like McCree's ability
where you kind of focus
on everybody in a little like area
when you shoot it off
everybody that's in the area
if they're 65% health or below
they get executed it's great
otherwise they take 600 damage still pretty good
so let's go to next is
Ruckus Ruckus plays a lot
like D.Va from Overwatch so you'll hear me say
D.Va a lot so Ruckus has these
mini guns they're kind of like D.Va's
hand cannons
they shoot really fast the longer you hold
the button the more damage they do it's kind of cool
Ruckus's left trigger is
a missile launcher so again kind of like
D.Va shoots some barrage of missiles
at people
advance is his quick getaway move
you press it and he has rocket boosters
again like D.Va that'll get
him in or out of combat to find
him in the situation a 5 second cooldown is pretty low too
you can advance to get in shoot a bunch
of people in advance to get back out and go back to your healers
it's kind of nice his left shoulder
is a shield called emitter
gives him like a bubble, absorbs damage
it's really nice again if you're in there being
a disruptor like you're supposed to do whether you play Ruckus
or D.Va they're similar
play styles and then his
ultimate is Hexafire
it's just like a one where he just
unloads all his weapons in like
pretty much a cone in front of him
and it does really good damage
if you can focus someone down
if you get a lot of people gathered in one area and you
unleash that thing and especially if you use your
emitter first so you're safe you can take
out like a lot of people at once
so
finally there's Viktor and Viktor
plays a lot like Soldier 76 from
Overwatch sorry about all the comparisons but it's just
easier to describe it this way since more people know
Overwatch I know I'm feeding
into the whole ripoff thing but you know
whatever I don't really care
so his assault rifle is like his
main gun but on this one if you hit the left trigger
you actually look down the sights so you get a little bit more
accuracy but he does move
slower because you're not just shooting
off the hip you're looking right down the sights
his R like Soldier's
you know right shoulder button is
like a hustle so he moves he can run really
fast but he can't shoot while he's doing it as soon as you start
shooting you come out of your sprint
sprint is what they call it for
for Soldier and then
frag grenade is his left shoulder button
he'll throw a grenade it does a lot of damage
you can hold the button
cook the grenade so that when you release it it
blows up more quickly if someone is closer to you
it's a really nice ability and then barrage his
his ultimate ability is really strong
and it just
kind of like Soldier again focuses on
everybody gets kind of in his sights
and if they kind of stand there too long
you can unload like a bunch of shells
on them and do tons of damage so
that's pretty much all the
characters that you get
when you start the game and they're not bad characters
not like they just give you a bunch of pushovers
they're very offensive minded
characters which makes
sense because if you just get into the game and
you just want to play a shooter
and you're not comfortable healing your tanking
well the healer and tank that they give you here are very
damage friendly all those characters are
really easy to use and you can kind of start
building a foundation in the game and
then be better after you
learn how to do them and you start unlocking other heroes
you start figuring out what's better but I'll still go back and play
those guys because they still do pretty
good damage so again
it sounds like a big commercial for Paladins but if you
ask me I still think Overwatch is a better game
I play it more often
I dabble in this game but
it is really fun
you can't really beat the price of free
if you're willing to grind
it's a good game and even if you want to pay for it
30 bucks isn't bad to get all the heroes
and it supports crossplay so if you want to
play with your friends this is a good game to play with your friends
because no matter what console they're on except Sony
you can play with your friends so again
I'm Flaco Jones
you can find me on Twitch twitch.tv
slash Flaco underscore Jones
and uh
that's it back to OLR
hopefully that wasn't too long
No it was fantastic
thank you Flaco and it's
there was a lot of work that I know
goes into that video especially because it's very
clear he like had to play the game like multiple times
and multiple characters to put the right shots in and stuff
so I really appreciate the time you took to
put together that infomercial high res
appreciation time too no
I'm just I'm giving a little crap because I
that's what I asked for I wanted people to submit games
um about uh or submit
things uh videos for
for games that they're like passionate about that they have
you know a lot of um you know
enthusiasm about which you know even though kind of
Flaco admits eh Overwatch
might be kind of the game I go to more often
maybe this game is still worth your
attention especially when it's something that's free
uh and they do these kind of different ideas
and things like that so I actually I've played
um a little bit of Paladins
as well and I thought it was I thought it was
interesting I mean it was just again it was just like
okay I mean I I kind of
went back to Overwatch but I thought
you know okay this is something I could get into
also maybe I need to try it more on PC
because I played it on console and I'm just
more of a keyboard mouse guy at the end of the day so I do
kind of want to give that another go because
one thing that I had a problem kind of figuring out
was oh like what do all these
heroes kind of do and stuff but Flaco
did a very good job kind of demonstrating that in that little
video especially for oh these are all the characters
that you're going to start with and uh so forth
so yeah shout out to our pal Flaco Jones
against Flaco underscore Jones
over on Twitch you should all go
follow him if you aren't already
that would be incredible and thanks again Flaco
for that submission very cool and if you
have a submission get in touch with me on
Twitter at Mr Rob Roberts we love
seeing the listener submitted stuff
um yeah it's great
um otherwise we've just been filling in with
with video clips of the news or whatever else
we can think of but it gives us a chance for us
folks here in studio to take a little bit
of a break so um
also in chat I notice
Flaco's actually in chat right now
and getting some kudos there in chat
and rightfully so
Flaco says a 12 minute video
and 45 minutes of playing for
cover shots yep that's it
but it looks like there might be some other
Paladins players in chat because Nifty's asking
which character do you main so
uh pretty cool good stuff
alright um let's move on with some other news that we
have scheduled for tonight's show uh some rapid fire
news let's get some news uh kinda quickly out here
uh as we travel around the studio
and the world and check out quickly
some other uh headlines we might have missed
uh I think we're starting tonight with Loki
yeah so at the South by Southwest
gaming panel they um had some
details regarding um a new game
from Sega uh Team Sonic
Racing uh which I think
has been teased before but they showed a little bit more
on it so they showed that
um you know
the different customization they have in the different
cars you can do which is kinda cool so there's
quite a bit of customization available
um
I'm assuming based on
what they showed they said you know you can
encourage and see it allows you to unlock different
things in the game and different customizations
I almost saw that as like monetization
type of thing but apparently you earned it in
game so we'll see um yeah I wanna
say in previous games it was kinda like that
yeah in game in game currency only
um there the game is
gonna be released on Xbox One, PlayStation 4,
Switch and PC on May 21st
um the other thing they showed is there's
gonna be this Team Sonic Racing
Overdrive cartoon
that's gonna be coming out now
when they say cartoon
not necessarily like on TV
cartoon but it's more of like a
web series or something that they're gonna do
um which you know makes sense
they've done something similar
with like say
um Angry Birds have like
a little web series and stuff that they did as well
which actually ended up on Netflix at some point
I know cause I've seen it
several times thanks to my kids but they're doing
something similar to this there's not actually
any spoken dialogue in the show
but it's just kind of like
grunts and whatever
it's just I don't know it's very
basic so that they can release
it globally without having to localize it
um so there's that
and I guess that'll be around the time
that the game comes out so we'll have to
see but the game's being developed by Sumo
Digital so
I think they were the ones that did um
weren't they the ones that did the
ModNation Racers and stuff like that
the name sounds familiar I just can't remember what
else they developed off the top of my head I know that name
that name sounds very familiar but it looked neat
it looked neat so I'll check it out when
it comes out
cool and then um
D'Artasuya thinks it was Outrun by the way the new Outrun that they did
oh maybe
um and then of course um
Game Pass we talk about that
quite a bit uh new game that's gonna be
coming well not new game but a new
game to the service is coming out
April 4th will be Minecraft
will be added to Games Pass so you'll
be able to jump into Minecraft if you haven't
already I mean
geez it's like 2019
um but you'll be able to do that for free
well free on top
with excluding of course the
$10 a month fee for Game Pass
but it's an additional
piece that you get with that yeah when's the 4k
graphics pack by the way
whatever happened to that didn't they announce that at E3 2017
where's that 4k graphics pack
well I know I'm crazy
4k graphics for Minecraft but the stuff they were
like the weather and all that stuff is really good
like I'm like well if you want to do that it's already
available on PC now you just have to
do with mods yeah
of course of course Java version
alright um I don't know how I got
the story on Mortal Kombat 11 but how about
that um so there's more information
on Mortal Kombat 11 came out this
week and um
apparently they're mentioning that
NetherRealm is talking about how player data
shows that and this is interesting because
Jamie you kind of brought this up earlier about how you prefer
to play games but the player data they're getting
shows that single player mode is one of the most
popular ways for people to access
and experience the game so
that's why NetherRealm was kind of putting
as much for a fighting game which you
typically think of as two player this is why NetherRealm
puts as much as they do into single player because
their data shows a lot of people are playing it that way
and Mortal Kombat does have
kind of a rich you know compared to other fighting games
especially the newer Mortal Kombat
games really do have a very rich story
to them so I'm not terribly surprised
to hear that more people are
experiencing it as a result
um also believe it or not
some fatalities were too over the top
and not really functional so they were yanked
or redesigned what
how about that uh they are not commenting
on other characters from other
properties so all this
BS about Shaggy or any
uh IP that is not there
Shaggy in Mortal Kombat I mean they could
make it happen it is Warner
it's not gonna happen but it
but Velma on the other hand she came
to kick some ass no I'm just kidding they're not
putting cartoon characters in a fucking game
uh you know no just like Joker
no I was gonna say you'd have better
luck going for the Injustice series
I was gonna say they're not gonna put
but they had Ninja Turtles well I was in
Justice as well I was in Justice as well so
yeah you you should find Shaggy for
Injustice 3 take your Shaggy
it would be an Injustice not to put
him in there
and Scooby Doo and
OLR is cancelled forever good night and Scrappy
in fact Scrappy can just be like one of those
bonus games now I know this is
this is not necessarily in the same
series but you know much like they have
and uh Capcom
Street Fighter series you know where you destroy the car
you can destroy Scrappy
mmhmm
alright um let's see
the story is roughly 8 hours long
what? $60 for an 8 hour game?
uh
nevermind it's a fighting game
it's a fighting game exactly um
the crypt is back but they're saying
a nice surprise for players when you see
the direction it's taken uh
and let's see features will be added to the game
after launch even in the first few months
uh and Kronika's mission
is in the story involves
finding time and starting all over
so merging the timeline so that
the past meets the present
so that could be because Mortal Kombat has a very
I don't know if you guys know but Mortal Kombat has like a whole like
Prime and Kelvin thing going on
the newer games are in the Kelvin universe
I'm referencing Star Trek obviously
but the newer games are in like a different universe because of what happened
in the reboot Mortal Kombat 9
mmhmm so interesting
it'll be interesting to see how that all goes down universal shenanigans
yes so uh
anyway that's Mortal Kombat and quickly let me also
mention that uh the other story I had here is about
the uh indie game The Messenger
and I have to admit I didn't know a lot about
this game until I was uh scavenging
for the news this week and then I kind of watched a trailer
and this looks really cool because
The Messenger it's kind of like a it's a Metroidvania
type of game I know we hear that a lot
but it kind of seems a little bit like Ninja
Ninja Gaiden kind of
but like uh amped up
a little bit and um
it's um something where you
can actually switch between
8-bit and 16-bit mode
by hitting a certain
type of like marker
on the like you've hit an orb and like
it changes it from 8-bit to 16-bit
and that kind of it's a time bubble is what
it is and it flips it between it and it changes
the graphics and the sound with it and it
changes the mechanics as well so I think that's kind
of kind of neat anyway
it's coming to PlayStation 4 on
March 19th so this coming week
so maybe it'll be a great time for me
to check it out uh
but anyway Dark Sakura
um I don't know how many people in chat
have played Dragon's Dogma I started it
and didn't like it um
but they are going to be doing
a uh anime
that will be out on Netflix
produced by Sublimation
and um basically I mean in the game
you fight a dragon and
it steals your heart and you die and then you come back
to life and so you're trying to
get revenge on it well that's the story the
plot of the anime
um but it was said by um
Koishikawa Atsushi
who is the representative director
of Sublimation they're really looking
forward on it and the last line is what
gets me we're excited to bring our
unique cel-shaded animation that carries
hand-drawn textures to anime
fans around the world
so I think it should look interesting
um but anyway
uh other news there has been
another unearthing apart from ECW
Wrestling which everybody fucking knew
existed um
there was an Alien vs.
Predator football game
for the Sega Genesis
at least there was going to be one
like football football or as an American
football as in not real football
yep we got
we're gonna settle our differences
on the 50 yard line yep
that would have made a better movie I think than
the Alien vs. Predator movie and it was just
a concept it was actually just on
like you know uh
a flyer and it was
called like Alien vs.
Predator Hardball no Cosmic
Hardball and
yeah it looks pretty stupid but
but let's be
real some of the greatest video games are
really really stupid I think I
would have actually enjoyed this
um but
I mean this would be this is like the best video game
never made that's why I gave this story to you
because even though I know you're not a big football fan I'm like
but I bet she would have played this
I would have I like
I also like super high impact that's true
and I like Tecmo Bowl so even
people who aren't into sports games there's always
something there's always something that brings you in
but the thing that's funny about the tweets about it
is people arguing if the Xenomorph would wear a
football helmet
well for safety they have those big
long armored heads I want to see this
done as a movie
but done in the style of Space Jam
did you see Alien vs. Predator
where you took the head off of one and used it as a
shield no I don't
I don't really watch I saw
that that movie was rad I've seen
I actually think I've seen most of the aliens
movies at this point I saw Alien resurrection
in the theater with Winona Ryder I needed
to see that only because I wanted to
listen to what it could have been
yeah I don't I didn't
know anything about the controversy or any of that stuff I just
it was written by it was written by
Joss it was changed up a lot and
while I am very very very very
very disappointed in the person he turned out to be
at the time I was like should I need
to see this and then I
heard they ruined it so I never saw it
Cia Tiberi in chat says Freddy vs. Jason vs.
Alien vs. Predator Ultimate Football
why did you leave out Ash though? I'm just kidding
well because he would just own them all with his chainsaw
hand and Michael
Myers come on Cia Tiberi
jeez
and now doing seriously on that one I don't
think that those are series that could be
combined because the slasher
movies are different than the creature horror
right but Mortal Kombat
10 brought or I guess
you are supposed to say Mortal Kombat X in that one
but it did bring over
because Predator is in
that right and but it's mostly humanoid
yeah I guess that's true so it would work
in that and they do have some kind
of creature people magic
it wasn't one of the Call of Duty
games didn't they have like you know
this whole thing with like Predator in there and
I thought like they also had
I don't know I feel like
these horror movie icons just randomly pop
up in all your favorite video games like I'm waiting
for like Hello Kitty world featuring
you know yes yes
predator I'm done
I'm down with let's see that
Hello Kitty vs. Predator Team Sonic
Racing you know who you need
to be in those carts predator
the predator why not
it's canon because
you know we saw in the trailer or something
some sort of video we saw that the predator
was driving a tank so there you go
ok Dar Sacro what video
game do you want to insert the predator in to make better
DDR
dance or die
dance or die well could you just
I mean I'm sure they've done a skin
for like a dancer being the predator
but I would just jam with the predator
as my avatar on the screen
I like dance or die
or like 2DX and he would literally scratch
the thing
and if you lose he like stabs you
let's see
I want the predator to show up at Mario Party
when my friends
piss me off Smash Brothers
is an assist
pulls out Mario's spine
let's travel around the world
and check out some
actual video games that are coming out around
the world with our world release date
starting in the US Loki
we don't have a whole lot coming out this week
we've got Super Robot Wars T
on the Switch and Playstation 4
we have Sekiro
Shadows Die Twice now that's a pretty
big one on PC, Playstation 4
and Xbox One
we have Unravel 2
on Nintendo Switch
and that's it
alright heading over to Japan
and checking out the releases in Japan this week
and honestly do you need anything
else after I read this one Dead or Alive
Extreme 3 Scarlet is
out on Playstation 4 this week
I mean what else do you need
as in the Scarlet Letter
no but
you know what the Dead or Alive Extreme
series is, it's Barbie
for Men basically
it's what these games are
half of those games out there
anyway
Jamie are you going to play some Dead or Alive
Extreme?
they just dropped the beach volleyball thing
probably not
I mean it really is just dress up for hormonal men
anyway
Atelier Lulua
the Alchemist of Arland 4
is also out in Japan this week on the
Playstation 4, Super Robot
Tyson T is also out on the
Playstation 4 this week and
Chocobo's Mystery Dungeon
is out in Japan this week
as well, everybody
instead of everybody it's every
B-U-D-D-Y so cute little play
on words there and then on
the Nintendo Switch this week that same
Chocobo Dungeon game is also out in Japan
as well as Atelier Lulua
and how about that
I did not realize this but Dead or Alive Extreme 3
is also on the Switch
the Switch is also getting Super Robot Tyson
T and that is your Japanese
release dates. Dark Sakura
how about the UK?
Well for the UK it looks like what
we've got is on the 21st
the following
Unravel 2
we have Air Complex Collection, Sekiro
Shadows Die Twice
Fate slash
Xtella Link
our world is ended
that's actually it
so all on the 21st
alright
now we're going to move on to our mailbag
every week you guys send us emails
or maybe you don't, participate at
OrangeLoungeRadio.com and we
log into the email bag and read our
favorite emails here live on air
there's only one when I check so
alright cool. Alright so the first one
is from Rama. Hi Rama
um good evening everyone
so Rob as per our brief discussion
ABC is bringing back Card Sharks
and Press Your Luck
have you thought about streaming on Twitch yourself
playing game show video games
I think that would be pretty fun
yes I
well okay yes and no
so I have not thought about myself playing
game show video games although I think
that's a pretty rad idea and I think I'm going to do it
I think I will play those games it would be fun
to play with people online as well
have I thought about streaming
game show content before
yes
that's all I'm going to say for now
also my next two questions for the entire
staff. One, what game show would you
love to host? Fuck me
Press Your Luck, I
oh my god without hesitation that would be such a fun show
to host and I wanted to be a game show host
when I grew up by the way and this is about as close
as I get to live out that fantasy so
I really wouldn't want to do any except
maybe Family Feud because I think
I could out Steve Harvey, Steve Harvey
okay I'm pretty good at
looks with the really fake like
I can't believe they said
that he doesn't do an I can't believe
they said that he just gives people this look
like bitch what
which is what I would say
okay bitch what no
you can't say that on TV go back
to your desk
uh Sia Tabiri in chat says would you
do like a Jackbox games night that actually
seems like a really obvious idea that we just haven't done
yet I think we'll have to we should plan like a vog
Jackbox night that'd be fun
yeah yeah we gotta get your game show
Loki my game show
what game show do you want to host? I would host
Double Dare
no
Double Dare is kind of boring
Bumper Stumpers to come back
what? Bumper Stumpers
it was like a license plate
base game yeah we had to translate the
license plate but it was like answering trivia
questions with license plates or something like that got it okay
um we'll just do like
uh I'll say Starrcade
yeah well fuck why didn't I say
that that should have been my number one pick
uh he
he put a sandbag on the question
by bringing up pressure luck earlier in the email
so Starrcade
but it's a clue it's a it's a
tie both alright two
what game show would you like to be on
Rob we know at Supermarket Sweep so you can't say that one
pressure luck
I would also
say Starrcade
it's not on TV anymore so I guess
you can say Supermarket Sweep I'm the only one forbidden
from saying Supermarket Sweep I don't know what things
cost at the supermarket anymore
honestly I want to be on Jeopardy before
Alex Trebek dies
oh my god Bobby Black Wolf nail on the head
The Mole I didn't even think
of that as a game show but I guess at its core it is
The Mole is the greatest reality
show they ever made and it is a crime
that it is not on TV because
none of you assholes were watching it
and it was a great like
Anderson Cooper as a fucking bitch
hosting a show was
divine
it was great I love The Mole it was there was
never a better reality show I really like those reality shows
like that but it's except for Drag Race
it's different it's not
it wasn't I don't know
I can't explain it but a show like
The Mole felt more James Bond
than it did Real Housewives of Atlanta
if that makes sense
I mean there was the episode
or the revival season where the one
chick told the guy I'm gonna kill you in your sleep
but that was you know that was
just one moment I don't know
a good game show would be To Catch a Predator
it's not a game show
no but I already know
prizes but then we could bring the
predator in no no no
and it's a whole different show then I always
feel like the family got
something when they caught the shit
to catch a predator with the
predator well if
you see the the the human predator
gets stabbed by the predator
that would be awesome alright anyway
a fifth
dream today says Rob should replace
Julie Chen on Big Brother I
really appreciate that comment but first
I don't know what show would y'all see
me on cause I don't really
think I would be on a game show
truth or consequences
focus on the consequences
it was a very old show
I'm just thinking the consequences part
what was the other one with Chuck
Woolery one of those other USA
Network ones not Scrabble
there was Bumper Stumpers Scrabble
and there was
he hosted when
Millionaire was really big he'd agreed
this was around the same
era in the late 80s
Love Connection
Love Connection wasn't the other one I was thinking of
I would be on Hollywood Squares
but I want like what's his
face to come back from the dead
and be on it with me
oh god
Paul Inn
I want to be on there with Paul Inn
and Carol Channing
if I could do like
you would also have to be brought back from the dead
you want to do zombie Hollywood Squares
no I don't want it to be zombie
but you want all these celebrities back from the dead
no I want it to be like time travel
kidnap Hollywood Squares
but somehow
drag queens are involved as well
and also not only
would I have Carol Channing
I would have Stalker Channing
and Channing Tatum so they could be a diagonal
this is the weirdest Bill and Ted
I've ever seen
we're kidnapping all of these people
from different timelines that put them on the Hollywood
Squares
that should be my comic
is the
time travel kidnapping Hollywood Squares
I don't know why I'm laughing it's so stupid
and the top square
it's brilliant that's why we need to make it a movie
and the bottom square would be the predator
it's such a stupid plot
but what else are people doing
is remaking movies
so that's it for now take care
and see you all on the flip side
oh it was an email of course it was
well did you hear how I ended it
no I'm sorry I missed it because I was laughing
that's it for now take care and see you all on the flip side
alright
delete and next
Dear Orange Lounge Radio
I hope this email finds you well
as I am currently typing it while in the bathroom at work
thank you
you're listening to KTMI
too much information all the time
randomly an OLR quote
came to mind that had me giggling
uh oh I said it too
a long time ago Jamie shouted Uranus
during an OLR episode
to which Rob countered with something along the lines of
not having this conversation
as host of the show do you have a
favorite funny memory of it that comes to mind
every so often thanks for eating
and I love you guys sincerely Garth Wolf
I don't know oh that's a tough one
I like drinking and
seeing the wall
kicking and
oh god I try to forget that
eating half a box of waffles
thank you Loki
can you imagine if episodes 1 through 100
like 1 through 100 would be like
the pre podcast era
when like there was no
structure to this show
there was absolutely no structure to this show
and it was just like we take a break every now and then
it was floppy boobs
it was a mess can you imagine if that had been on Twitch
like that's why I was saying earlier
I don't want 13 million followers cause somebody would find
those shows
it would be like triple D's with no bra
that's what they're like
painful and floppy
I mean but there were some good times there really were some good times
in those eras
the first thing that comes to mind
that I think of regularly
and it's still like I'll be in the most
random place and I think of it
and Deep Fried Rice by Loki
it's a Loki moment but it wasn't on the show
it was when we were interviewed
on the news and the only
clip they put in of Loki without
even his name on it is just him
going oh it's so much fun
yeah
the greatest thing it's on YouTube
somewhere I think on the old ass
orange songs radio YouTube channel we haven't touched in like 10 years
my old newspaper finally destroyed itself
like I had the newspaper I had
saved with all that
it's all like destroyed
mine's very yellow
but I have it in like this plastic
thing that keeps it kind of straight
so where they had a picture of my foot
okay real quick
for the listeners who haven't heard this story and I apologize
cause some of you have heard this several times
but many years ago when podcasting
was first becoming a thing and like
it just got onto iTunes
and was getting out there of course everybody
wanted to talk about podcasting so our local news
station I guess put like
Sacramento podcast into iTunes
and found us so they came out
and we did like a fake show for them
that they could shoot and then they interviewed
each of us about the show and so each of us
kind of have a little talking head moment in the
clip about it and I think I'm
probably saying something about like why
L.R. started dark sakura talks
about you know why she does it as a
hobby or whatever and then the only
thing they usually they don't even put his name at the bottom of the
screen or whatever it's like it's some type of follow
up to a comment it's just him going oh it's
so much fun and then that's it
and when we
saw that back on the news Loki's reaction
that was like fucking really
there
was at least like several
minutes of footage and they like took
like this fraction of a second that's what
it's like to be on reality TV by the way
there's just that that whole anyway
um but with the new
segment which I really now that we are a video show
one of these days I need to like clip it and put it on
but I just technically it's not ours
let's do it next week who cares no one's
gonna care they're not gonna who cares
um but what was the other thing I was
gonna say with that um
is um oh they
never also in the story they
never mentioned the name of our show
remember that yeah that was stupid
they never said orange lounge
radio is this show they never said
the name of our fucking show and the whole thing
they show the dude
searching for it so you can see
him type in orange but they never say
these guys host orange lounge radio they say
these three they say Rob Roberts and Jamie
Summers and Matt all host
this show out of the apartment in Rancho
Cordova and blah blah blah blah blah
but they never say it's orange lounge radio
which was just
kind of the um
the the the the
topping of the cake yes
anyway
somebody thank you tiger claw dug up
dug up the article and put it in our chat
so there it is
oh lord
SSG100 Matt reminded
me of another moment it was
peppermint time and mint but that was
a that was a horde house joke
I'm really
just trying to think of stuff
cause it's like just little clips just from
around the show but maybe not
during the show like like the fried
you know corn flaked coated
rice balls when
Loki got a deep fryer
and waffles
and dunk
see I don't the funny moments
are good and and I
I appreciate those as well but I also
remember like a lot of like a lot of not to be
too sappy but a lot of the serious stuff like
jumps out like we
did a live broadcast
from Pier 39 on the internet
before anybody
did something like that
like we did that and that was what probably
would have been the year 2003 that we did that
uh that's awesome
um some of the great emails
that have come through the years
you know the part of the motivation that's kept me
doing the show where who's become our friends
oh god for sure friends that we made
people that will email and say um
I had to help accepting
my sexuality because you're out there presenting
yourself Rob and I saw some of
myself and you and that people telling me to
get in the kitchen but that's not a
positive thing but you know what
I positively think those people are morons
well you know what though
I think despite the fact that that's shitty
and I'm not gonna talk positive
you know how much of a shit I give about it well I think
but it helped you I think in the beginning you
were kind of like what the fuck is
like you know but it kind of like I think helped you
like I cranked the
feminism to 11 yes
it's like that art project
complicit in my own
discrimination and then
hyper feminist
not shutting up
uh see it to bury in chat with
a newer moment saying I remember that time
rob mangled the carlton dance and
loki refused to floss see that's something a little bit newer
and uh thanks
or no thanks to the twitch clip
clipping feature which I just saw my earlier
laughing fit popped up as a clip
around your butt I'm sure now some
of these moments are probably gonna be frozen in time
so that'll be it'll be interesting to see the
the result of that but that's okay
Matt also brings up that we broke the news of bin laden
oh yes
some of the serious shit that happens like right in the middle
of our show we've really had a lot
of shit happen though on this show
oh we've had some heavy topics we've had
some very heavy topics cause the world's been
through shit just in the last few
you know couple decades cause we've been doing this show
almost two decades coming up
17 years yeah
you know 17 years this june yep
and we've all all of
bless you we've all gotten married
yeah
matt spawned yep
we you know made others tiny
humans based on his dna olr's futures
yep well more like nelly did the hard work
but yes loki
contributed something yeah
um we
have moved a bunch of times
I bought my first house yeah
I got I've been through a couple of
jobs we have um pets
that have come and gone like you know obviously
shermy was the mascot of orange d'andrea for a very long
time when we were doing that yeah I was not to make you sad I'm sorry
it's okay no but I think it's but but
but I love shermy's big belly the
great thing is shermy is a part of olr's history
and you know the ferret just
like now we have mr smoosh he's kind of
filling that role so yeah
midna hasn't been on the show yet
yeah cause we haven't really been doing the show
I would bring her over but she would cry
the whole time yeah mom
mom that's how she
meows mom real
real quick uh just a couple
more self-indulging moments here and then we'll move
on I swear uh ssho 100
matt says uh you also oh I'm sorry I
did read that comment um but uh
metal mayhem says I still remember
rob's epic diva fit
you know that's not a moment I really look back on
fondly but and do you that all
was on um
justin tv yeah that was
the time when we were doing this for the first time on justin
tv that whole diva fit happened and I
remember cause part of what made that so
funny slash interesting is that I
stormed off and loki just
without skipping a beat goes alright
then let's go on to the next snake
story like uh he's he's trying to be
professional in the moment or whatever and then I think
he reads the story and then I come back and I'm like I've got something
to say well also
dj rama s points out that we spawned other
shows oh yeah that's
that's quite the compliment abs
absolutely she hulk misses the fus
well
but keep in mind that there was a period of time
for sure where gamers
didn't necessarily need to be associated with negativity
if you want fus just read my twitter
we
can still do them once in a while we haven't done one in a while
what are you doing real quick I don't have the music
we'll just do a quick one you wanna do a quick fus
can we just like insert music here
insert music here
okay alright so
fu goes to
capitalism
and misogyny
your turn uh my fu of the week
goes to myself for not going to the gym
today because I slept for 10 hours
um because I've been so tired today
uh and fu to
um uh just
yeah I think I think today was definitely
a crash and burn day I think yesterday and today have
both been like just crash and burn days
between like Vegas and go go go
and all this other stuff like I think I've just
like emotionally and physically like
crap and then I hosted a show Friday night too so
I think I emotionally and physically crashed and
burned these past couple days and it's not the best feeling
in the world but um
doing this show is pepping me up I do have one
more cause it's very important alright hurry my uterus
for cramps well
sorry to hear it okay alright Loki
last not least um
I guess my fu
was uh to
my migraine but it's gone now so I don't know
I'm glad your migraine is gone
you were right the caffeine helped apparently all that
caffeine did it along
with the other stuff um and that's
just for now alright
that was it for emails right yes
okay then I suppose this video game podcast should
get back into some uh video game topics
huh let's let's do
it back into the gaming news oh uh but please feel
free to email us in the future participate at
orangesontrader.com but meanwhile Loki
so Valve's gonna start cracking down on
some of these review bombs that have nothing
to do with necessarily
um maybe reviewing
the games it's more of like
I guess people using the platform to
um
attack other
things that they don't like
like for example I guess
would be if
said company was coming
out with a decision that somebody didn't
like so they took you know their previous
game they released and review bombed it because they didn't
like a certain decision or something like that
so what they're gonna do is try to identify
those and then remove those
uh from the way it calculates
uh the review scores
based on those types of reviews
uh they're saying that the reviews themselves
are being left untouched but
and if they want if people want to dig into
them you'll still be able to do so but
they're making it clear that you know
the ones that are
gonna be I guess highlighted or whatever are gonna be
not those ones that are off
topic well good
I like when I go in to read game reviews
I don't need to hear about what people think about the
policies of the company or the
company or something that was said on Twitter
or some comment that somebody affiliated
I just want to know is the game good
yes or no that's what I
want to hear about so I'm glad they're
gonna try to do something about it I mean it seems
like that's an awfully big undertaking for a store
like Steam which is barely managed as
it is to undertake but to do anything I
know I was like we'll see
it's a nice thought
did they ever take down the rape game
oh sure of course they did good but
the you know the fact that
it went up in the first place
because Steam
doesn't really moderate a lot of things so it's
interesting to see that Steam is suddenly gonna moderate this
this is yeah a little
like hmm how's that gonna
work I don't know anyway
uh Kaijuto in our chat over at
Twitch TV slash vog network says I don't like
the review bombs but I think Valve is making a
big mistake you have to let the community
police that stuff people are smart
they know a bomb review from a normal one
they need to not attach the game score
to the review I think review
uh user review should be unscored
for sure I think that would be a great way to
start but anyway
yeah yeah
uh interesting retort by Bobby
Blackwolf that I think is very succinctly
put uh Bobby Blackwolf
response to Kaijuto saying a person
is smart people are
dumb a fucking
that is a very succinct
good comment
gold star comment of the week
I can't believe we're gonna
keep it in the family so to speak
and people will claim that nepotism is coming
into play and the fact that he does the show
before ours but I think Bobby is deserving of the gold star
of the week for that comment
alright moving on
uh let's move on to uh something that
uh ooh it's uh
a little rough for the folks involved uh
over at Axiom Verge
uh it has to do with developer versus publisher
uh of course if you haven't
played Axiom Verge it's uh really cool
it's a little uh super metroid-ish type of game
uh it was free on epic store
epic game store
the epic game store for a little
bit um it was free there but
not anymore but you could buy it and it would be
worth your money if you haven't picked it up one of several
other ways um the game is still
supposed to get a physical release on Wii U
I don't know why you would
bother at this point but I guess because they promised
it or what have you they're gonna deliver
well I think that's through that uh
the one company oh limited run? yeah limited run
okay so it's a collector release
okay that makes a lot more sense uh yes
the distributor limited run
game and the business manager
have said that the publisher Badland
game still owes them a quarter million dollars
so what happened is that
limited run says that Badland owes it
$78,000 for physical copies of the game
that it never delivered and then Badland
did not pay Tom Happ
the one man band that made Axiom Verge
uh the sum of about $200,000
that was also
there was supposed to be money that was gonna pay for medical treatments
for Tom Happ's kid
which I seem to remember has come up with
this game before is that you know
he's been using the money to pay
a lot for medical related things for his
kid which you know is obviously
you know nobody likes to see a sick kid so a lot of people
are happy to support this game to know that that's where
some of the money is going uh and so
this is you know now it's getting ugly because it's
on Twitter and now um let's
see uh Adelman who is uh
the business manager with limited run
the game's Dan Adelman says Badland has
literally stolen money from a disabled toddler
that's basically what he's saying on Twitter
yikes so uh
anyhow this is uh very ugly
between the two of them nobody was
commenting in an article that Kotaku ran earlier
this week and uh don't know
what this is gonna do if this
is gonna impact that Wii U release
I don't think it will but um
it'll be interesting to see how that whole uh
dragging through the mud and all that will
possibly change things so they're
saying we were still planning on dividing up the proceeds
on the original terms
so uh 6,000 copies of the Wii U
edition were made there's a soundtrack an art book
and other extras so it
paid Badland oh it's coming on the Wii U
yeah I kept thinking Switch
it's out on the Switch right man
why are you so late on the Wii U? Collectors
that's why I said the whole time
right so anyway
I kept hearing Wii U or like hearing Switch
instead of Wii U I was like oh okay Switch that makes sense
and it's like Wii U wait what
why no
alright
anyhow
oh Bobby is admitting that that quote he said
came from some movie but I didn't recognize
it cause he's thanking the chat for
not saying what movie we may have to revoke the star
cause it's not an original quote
alright
you get a half star alright let's move
on uh Dark Sakura what do you have for us
we're almost uh to the call segment but not just
yet but Dark Sakura well there's been a
rash of arrests made um
in uh
Ahmedabad
Ahmedabad I always
mispronounce it but there were
people who were arrested across the state
after playing PUBG
um because um several
um the games of actually games
of that line online multiplayer games
were banned on
the grounds that it was leading to
violent behavior among children and
and younger people they arrested
three people in different
parts um of the
area after they were caught playing the game
and um the police
commissioner issued a notice
banning even more of that
uh starting uh it actually started
on the 14th so they
were booked under section 188
the disobedience to
fully uh to order
duly promulgated by public servant
of the Indian Penal Code
so stupid but that's
what's going on in the world this is like the movie Footloose
all of a sudden you can't so you can't
play PUBG in public
any first person online multiplayer game
wow
yep interesting cultural
differences being discussed tonight
that's for sure between March
12th and 13th Rajkot
City police arrested ten persons
including six college students
for playing the game despite the ban
wow
alright I guess uh
for all the things we complain about
sometimes it sure could be a lot worse
we may not even be able to play video games
let alone talk about them the way we do
here on Orange On Radio
alright well thanks for bringing that to our attention
meanwhile we got a couple more stories for you guys
and we're going to be taking calls via our Discord server
if you would like to uh be on
the show tonight head on over to the green room
at our Discord
vognetwork.com slash Discord
Loki? Well one game you won't be
arrested for playing is
Where in the World is Carmen
San Diego and you can actually play
this for free now thanks to Google
Earth so if you go to Google Earth
um they actually have an option now
catch Carmen San Diego
and you basically play a little game
that's you know Where in the World
is Carmen San Diego and follow
clues and has it been updated for Modern
Maps? Well it's a great
advertisement tie-in for
the new Netflix series is what it is
yeah so it's pretty
awesome and you get clues and you go
off to find Carmen
San Diego and
yeah that's pretty cool
I think that's a cute modernization
I mean you know using Google
Earth but still at the core
having uh Carmen San Diego
be about you know learning about these different cities
and the the artifacts and the
uh museums and the places
of interest that are in these cities and kind of learning
what's where what's the capital of what I mean
that's you know that's what those games are all about
I'm surprised that's not a thing that's
like a Niantic game
you know like not necessarily
world traveling but like within
your area within your neighborhood like trying
to find Carmen San Diego
or one of her henchmen or something like
that um I don't think Niantic hasn't done anything
like that like you know and maybe they're
worried about flooding
where in your hood is Cory Santiago
yeah I don't know yeah where in your neighborhood
where in your neighborhood is this
I have heard about live event
producers so it's been this article that's
been floating around my Facebook um because
people think of me when they think of Clue the movie
which I appreciate it is my all time favorite movie
um but I guess they're doing like
a live Clue event here locally
like it's like some type of late but it's not
it's not really the board game Clue it's just like a murder
mystery thing that's like themed on Clue I guess
but my point is I think
they use a phone app that
you like you pay money to play
this event and then you get all the updates through the phone
app and I've heard of this being a thing
lately because this isn't the first thing that I heard of
I also remember seeing something for like
an amazing race
style thing but it's
all through the phone but here's what they do
like they offer like a big prize to the winner
but they let like thousands of people
sign up for like 20 bucks a pop
and like the winner gets maybe like $10,000
so it sounds like a lot of money but it's not nearly
as much as these guys are making off it so
they give that prize and then not only that
but like if you get stumped along the way and some
of the clues are like really hard you have to pay
for more clues oh that's lame get it
so pay to win
that's a thing but that isn't
keep an eye on that stuff because
somebody's making money
off these live event games
not Niantic but definitely these like
neighborhood event
day type of things
so that's a thing you probably see you probably
seen these advertised on Facebook in your neighborhood as well
so anyhow
alright is that
hmm I have regrets
oh from eating that donut that you were showing off
amazing but like there's a few
foods that will always make me sick and I know
better and I don't give a shit
ice cream
and donuts
it's like me and coffee my doctor told me to stop
drinking coffee and I was like we're gonna have to negotiate this
cause you and I both know it's not gonna happen
so we negotiated
anyway
one more story and this is about
Snapchat cause I'm sure
lots of you guys here in studio use Snapchat
right
I don't know I guess
I've used Snapchat it's very
similar to Instagram has the stories
which they kind of stole from Snapchat
but Snapchat is another way
and Snapchat is also kind of like
a lot of people associate
it with like people
sending nudes to each other because they're supposed to
self destruct in 24 hours or whatever
so this is of course you know
cause that's how the internet works
that's how anything works right we've talked about the whole
time to penis before so of course
they put a thing like Snapchat out where it's like
the picture self destruct in 24 hours
you know that
it's supposed to tell you when a screenshot is taken
but there's all sorts of ways
nothing you send is
truly that type of private
but whatever
oh it's that type of private alright
I left myself wide open with that joke
alright anyway my point with this
is Snapchat they are trying to get away
from being known as the app where you send nude pics
they're trying to do more event based things
and stories like on Instagram
and maybe this is something they want to do as well
supposedly Snap is going to be launching
a gaming platform
as well it's
it's a rumor right now it's apparently
code named Project Cognac
within the Snapchat walls
externally developed games
that will work inside the Snapchat app
they are saying that it will be similar to like
Facebook's games in the messenger
which I think I've talked about and then
never played in messenger
on the phone like I know it's a thing I did the
Pacman thing like once that's it
but supposedly Snapchat would be something like that
it'd be like an instant game so I guess you could
like play it against friends it may also involve
streaming of eSports events
you know around the world which you know that's
a little more like that is one part of
Snapchat that's interesting that I don't think
I think Instagram
does this but it's harder but on
Snapchat there's like a big map of the world
and if somebody's made their story public
you can watch public stories
so you can go to places of interest like
museums and stuff and see
people in real time like submitting Snaps
from these places of interest and I think that's
one of the cooler features of it
but anyway they want to put gaming into it
so because Snap has been
struggling to increase their user growth
probably because Instagram
is offering a very similar thing but Instagram
is also owned by Facebook
which is a whole other thing so anyway
it should be noted that Snap had recently
acquired an Australian gaming company
called Pretty Great
and also a web based startup
called Play Canvas
so they think the unveil
could be around April 4th
which is when Snap has a
developer conference scheduled in Los Angeles
but it's certainly possible that
something could come up around
GDC as well but it seems like
Snap may decide to
keep that for their own conference
that they are having on
April 4th so there it is
with that
that is the last scheduled story we have for tonight
so I think we're going to go to some listener
calls and participation
if you want to ask us a question in chat over
twitch.tv slash vog network you sure can
but we also want to talk
to some of our listeners and take some calls
and then we'll get last minute stories as well
so I see a call sitting on the
line and they've mentioned what they want to talk about
and this sounds like a topic I would like to hear
about so let's get to it. Hi you're on Orange Launch Radio who's this?
Hey this is Marcus
or PixelPakas
it's so great to hear from you
we see you all the time in chat but not
as often on the phone it's great to hear from you
what's on your mind tonight PixelPakas?
Not much
I just sort of wanted to talk about this event
I went to this weekend
called Arcade Expo
and it is
a convention or whatever basically
where they have
over 1000
pinball machines
and arcade machines
it's one of these type of things
like we have it like California Extreme
and I know Bobby
really loves the Southern Fried Game Room Expo
they do in Atlanta. Where is this expo?
So
it's in Southern California
kind of in the middle of nowhere
if you know where Banning is
I do because I saw an
ad for this on Facebook because I was looking
into going to it but I didn't
because I had a conflict on Friday night
yeah so
it's there where there's basically nothing else
except for I guess
this is actually a
museum of pinball where they hosted it
which I had never heard of before either
at least that one I know there's one in like Vegas
but I think they're totally separate
either way it was like
tons of
games
open for hours you know from like
11 to 2 AM
and it was just kind of
awesome how much
there was and
it actually wasn't super crowded basically
if you wanted to play a game you wouldn't have to wait
in a long line for the most part except for like a
couple new pinball machines like were super
crowded everything else is
you'd be able to either just walk up and stop playing
or you would just wait for one person to
like finish their game and then you could jump in
so
it was really great
they had a bunch of other stuff you know
it wasn't just the
pinball and arcade machines they had
some panels
some like movies that they were
showing you know all gaming related
chiptune artists were there as
well playing music at night
they had some arcade machines outside
so you could play like Under the Stars
or whatever lots of food
themed food
they had tater tots shaped like
tetrominoes
so it was
just a really cool fun event
that I had never heard of before
until like this week and
decided to go to it
well that sounds like a lot of fun
it definitely sounds just very similar to
the California Extreme event that happens
up here Santa Clara
right? It was at the same hotel where
GamerX4 was at right?
right next to the convention center near the stadium
I think that Hyatt is where they have it
and yeah it's a very
similar thing except I thought the gaming
out Under the Stars that's unique that sounds
really cool
now I know like when I go to these types of events
I'm like oh my gosh I've never got to play this
before and now I did and that's awesome
like was there a game that you like had
never played before that you got to play at this event
that made you excited?
yeah so probably
the most interesting thing was
that I got to play Computer Space
which is one of like the oldest
arcade games
right?
and I had seen that
online the pictures of that like
crazy looking cabinet and stuff
but I'd never had the opportunity to actually put my hands
on it and play it so that was really cool
and then there was just a bunch of like
old pinball machines
I've never played anything
particularly old in the pinball
scene so this is like
the stuff where they don't have
all the fancy audio and graphics
going on it was just sort of like
a board with some lights and then they just
have like dinging bell noises when you hit stuff
yeah with the scores
on the wheels instead of an LED
display yeah old school
like 60's style you know we own one like that
Spanish eyes oh I didn't know you owned one
we loaned it out to somebody but
when I was at the Vegas Hall of Fame and I didn't
include this in the video last week but there was like a little like
ice skaters table that was kind of cute
that was like that
remember the Buggles?
based off the Beatles?
really? no I don't remember that one
that's one of those 60's ones
like if you go to these pinball halls of fame
and there's another one
I think you can see one in Alameda
that I've yet to go to and I really need to
I think Dark Soccer and I need to do a road trip out there someday
and
yeah it's always neat because usually
there'll be like one row for tables
from the 60's and 70's that are these like
old older styles and they're really neat
yeah
there was a whole bunch of the older style ones
and no one was really on them so
it was like me and
a bunch of them just like ringing
bell noise you know constantly
in this corner of the hall but it was fun
I really enjoyed
the whole thing apparently
they do other events at
this Museum of Pinball
so even if you missed it on this one
there's going to be something else later this year I think
where they have another sort of similar event
so I would definitely recommend it to anyone
who's anywhere
near to Southern California
it was a blabber
if there's something that you think would interest us
here at O.R. you know my Twitter and all that
because I mean we're far but we're not
that far so like
you know for an event like that if I had not
already been committed to hosting an event on Friday
night which I was I
would have seriously considered coming down for that
because I saw the ads on Facebook and I
looked into it and I was like oh this just sounds like
California Extreme but it's in LA
ish I know it's like out there but
you know us in Northern California
we call everything like past
the grapevine is LA
so
so it sounded
it sounded really neat I would have gone
yeah it's definitely worth it
so I just wanted to sort of share that with anyone
I was considering
doing one of those listener
video things but then I was like
tired and slept too late so I didn't do it
alright that's okay next time next time
but yeah I mean a lot
of big cities or metro
areas have an event like
this and you know the size of it
probably depends on the size of where you are I just
mentioned a moment ago you know Bobby has
worked a lot with one in the Atlanta area the Southern
Friday game room gaming I always say
game room they changed the name gaming
so Southern Friday gaming expo
and actually vog network
sponsors that and if I am not mistaking
we'll be doing so again this year
so and I know he's a big
proponent of that and I would love to go if I didn't already
do one like week long trip
to Atlanta every year I'd love
to go to that event it sounds like a lot of fun but
a lot of areas I'm sure there's one in
the New York area I'm sure there's one
in Chicago somewhere
I mean all the big cities have to have something like
this I'm sure
yeah but that's all I just wanted to let
everyone know so thanks for taking my call
I appreciate it thanks so much and please
keep us in the loop of anything else that space
might be doing that we should be interested in
for sure alright take care buddy
bye bye
alright let's get to another call
hi you're on Orange Laundry who's this
hey it's Bellingham how are you
hey good good to hear from you what's up buddy
I just had a
follow up call to
um let's also
stay wild and listen
uh sure
I'm sorry I'm sorry if I'm sounding slow
or look confused your audio
sounds distant tonight I don't know what
is weird but try to get your
question or comment out we'll do our best
um
well if you remember last week
I called in about
possibly buying Diablo
I do
remember that yes because we had
spotlighted that in the little break segment
last week so what happened
I well
two two things I well I
bought it on Thursday
this is something I
rarely ever say
I if a I paid
full price
which is not
full price really for when the
game first came out but sure
well full price is
opposed to what they normally charge
you know I charge for the game
on the platform
which is rarely for me because
I usually 99.9%
of the time I wait
for sales so
me paying full price is like
extremely
okay yes and I do remember we were talking
about this and I said you know weigh the pros and the cons
and blah blah blah so you jumped in
and so uh the question
I would have is was it was it
worth it though
yes you know let's put it this way I've been
playing it more than Magic the Galar
so
I know whoa
are you never even
my fellow
you're not like a secretly a clone are you
you know that's something
uh
that's something I always never
say I mean you know I think
from like breaks
to take care of like IRL
stuff I've been playing that
constantly so for me
you know there's a little bit of a difference
between you know the PC
version versus uh
the PS1 version
that I remember from way
back in the day
you know I'm
I'm loving it you know
so
one thing I would recommend is
that you know for
people that
the game back in the
day you know be it the
PC version or the PlayStation
1 version
it's you know it's
available again and it works
on modern machines
are definitely worth recommending
idiots you know granted yeah
it's you know
like the 20 plus year old game and
it's not like the latest greatest game
it's now
you know high risk graphics
or anything like that but still it's
fun to sell a game it's
definitely well worth the price point
you know you can't go wrong
god
you know so
well I mean you're cutting out a little bit so I
want to jump in just because uh it's it's a
little hard to um understand and some folks
in chat are confirming it's not just me
but it sounds like you know you are
uh rediscovering this I still
I'm still a little puzzled as to why
Blizzard didn't just do it through their own
app it seems like a really weird missed
opportunity but um okay
I mean uh maybe this
will convince them to make Diablo 4 a little
faster uh as opposed to a
Diablo uh mobile phone experience
which would be just lovely if they would
uh get on that so
alright well um uh
Metal Mayhem I'm gonna let you go uh just because
we're having a little hard time understanding you but thank you so much for the call
take care and uh have fun gaming
alright
uh don't see anybody else in the green
room right now so let me
see if we have any other
uh
stories last minute stories yeah to make our show roll
but uh No Man's Sky beyond
oh my god how did I not get this in show roll
yes this is kind of a big deal they announced
um so basically it's the next
free update that's gonna be coming to No Man's
Sky and it's gonna have a ton of stuff
to it it looks like they're kind of turning
it into a No Man's Sky
MMO type of thing
um so
yeah they basically said we
don't consider No Man's Sky to be an MMO
it won't require a subscription it won't contain
microtransactions and will be free
to all existing players
um but yeah it's definitely
teased and it's a new big significant
update that they're gonna be doing
and it's gonna be coming out uh around the summer
so
um it's part of
uh yeah and that's just apparently
one part of um
I guess beyond which is gonna be
three different updates
so
looks pretty cool
it's pretty amazing that they're
still continuing to support that game as strong
as they are especially after such
a backlash that that game had they kind of
stayed committed to the game that they envisioned
putting out and you know I
think many folks have been happy with the more
recent you know uh changes that were
done I know I did some streams a while back
as did Bobby uh when the the last
No Man's Sky Next or whatever they called
that uh the first time it was out came out and you
know I think a lot of people were kind of happy with that game
and where that's at but to hear that they're going
even further is is
is so cool I love it
looks pretty cool yeah I'll be curious to see how that
works as an MMO though I'm not I'm not
too sure about it but we'll see we'll see
so um
Kaijuto says yikes
I hope the game can be played offline
that's all I care about
can't it I don't think No Man's
Sky can be played offline can it be played I
well cause you can lose connection to the server and you
still keep going so I think the game will
try to put itself online cause it's for the database
of what all the planets are named and the species and things
like that even in the earliest versions of the game
you weren't necessarily interacting with other people or whatever
but like I think the game will
function when offline
it just won't download
the database of what everything is
named and so forth and you may have
conflicts with names and all okay
Kaijuto says yes you can play offline I do it all the time
I don't know why they would suddenly shut that off then
yeah I don't see why
and then there's a new game coming out from
Avalanche uh Generation
Zero which is like a survival game
a co-op survival game it's
um similar to I guess a little bit
like um Horizon Zero Dawn
but you're
it takes place in the 80's
and you're like these kids that come back from vacation
and everybody's gone and there's
these like robots hunting people down
and it's about you surviving
so they said you can play the game single player
but it's going to be incredibly hard because it's
scaled for you know four player co-op but
um it looked interesting
uh very similar like the
robots you kind of go against look
very similar to like Horizon Zero Dawn
um but different
obviously and that's coming
out on the 26th as
part of an early access thing
I think it's only on PC though
doesn't say if it's console but
and then finally
uh Paxis is right around the corner
oh gosh and
with Paxis I'm kind of surprised that hasn't happened already
I thought it was in February when I went
no March 28th
no the snow was going really late in the year
the year I went yeah March 28th
in Boston and Gearbox
already has a nice little teaser on
their official Twitter
showing it says March 28th Boston
in Massachusetts it's
fucking Borderlands 3 or it's
another Borderlands thing because it's
it's what it looks like somebody pointed out
it's Exit 3 on the little
teaser image so it's uh yeah
it's Borderlands 3 which
is anyone surprised that Gearbox is
I'm not surprised and I'm excited
excellent so alright
well I don't see any other um calls in our
green room waiting to go um I don't know
if you had anything else last minute to bring up Dark
Saga but no
alright then I think we might be at the point
we're ready to wrap it up so um
I do want to thank everybody for uh listening to
OLR tonight and participating with our show
uh be it through the chat through the call-ins
or just your support by listening on the podcast that we do
every week um you can always help us
spread the word tell a friend or two about the show
uh we are the uh show where every gamer has a voice
but we can't get all the voices out there to
air if they're not here joining us
and uh not only does that all help
if you just directly tell somebody but a nice five star
review on a site like iTunes uh
or Google or wherever you found this podcast and
now that we're on Twitch those hosts
are great so please
consider uh putting VoG network on your auto host
list that would be fantastic
and really help spread the word as well we appreciate
all you guys uh that support the show
through subs through biddies uh through
just listening and uh being aware of us
we uh we appreciate it all
uh I think it is about that time we go around and get
everybody's final thoughts so we can wrap this
up for the night uh Loki your final thought we'll
start with you my final thought is I'm
gonna keep working on
game development it's
really hard but finally
I don't know I'm just
I'm trying to stick with something
uh my final thought
is I wanna keep going with this routine
that I've set for myself but I also
wanna make sure I get in some gaming time
um this week cause I haven't
really been playing enough single player games
uh so I'll try to work on that this week
last but certainly not least dark soccer
your final thought I want a nap
I'll just go to bed
except reasons
you should come over and play DDR
I I would be happy to
I need to I need to work that out I really
know what I was talking about but now especially now
the weather is less shitty and before it gets too hot
yes we need to make that happen yes absolutely
okay well that's it
I feel like I'm about to
explode you're gonna explode from
from eating everything I almost got you two
of each so I'm glad I didn't yeah no
the other one's gonna be part of breakfast tomorrow
I figured you could just eat some now and eat
some later yeah that's what's gonna happen
alright well um
if you do explode explode into
a glittery mess but not in the house
alright I'm not gonna be like
you know uh Monty Python's meaning
of life alright it's just a way for
thin mint fuck off
that's not gonna be me that's
it everybody thank you so much for
listening to Orange Lounge Radio we will see you again
next week good night
see you next week
you