[SPEAKER_08]: Look at what you see in the face, the mirror of your dreams.
Make believe I'm a hero, hidden in the light, written on the pages.
Keep the secret, we'll fall behind the clouds And dance among the rainbows
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: On tonight's program, Orange Lounge Radio, episode 143.
[SPEAKER_14]: We are back from E3, and oh my gosh, it was a hell of a show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course, lots of people there.
[SPEAKER_14]: You had to push your way through crowds and stomp all over people to get to things.
[SPEAKER_14]: You had to wait three freaking hours in line if you wanted to play Zelda.
[SPEAKER_14]: And unfortunately, not all the cast members made it out alive.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alive.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, unfortunately not all of us made it out of E3 alive.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, we'll have more details on all of that when we come back.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I'll tell you what, tonight it is all about the music games at E3 and it was a hell of a show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Surprises that just blew the roof off and smacked you up.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll talk more about that when we start the show after these opening credits.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_14]: And this is episode number 143 for this May the 22nd, 2005.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio, radio that gamers really want.
[SPEAKER_14]: And this is Orange Lounge Radio Live, your home for all the news and discussion on rhythm and music games, as well as the gamer community and the pop culture world.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're plugged in and fully interactive through our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_14]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_14]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I'm kidding, she's actually not here tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: She died at E3, it's so sad!
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I'm kidding, she didn't die at E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: She just, she extended her vacation a little bit You see, some of us went to E3 a couple days before it started And some of us decided to stay a couple days after it was over So, Jamie is on her way back this afternoon, or I'm sorry, this evening actually from LA So, she's not here, but who is here is the one and only Loki I am here and I have pizza, that's always good
[SPEAKER_12]: I did slash pizza and I got my Pizza Hut.
[SPEAKER_12]: By slash pizza it means I drove my car over to the Taco Bell slash Pizza Hut Express and got myself pizza.
[SPEAKER_12]: The old-fashioned way.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not the EverQuest way.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, hell no.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not going to sign up for EverQuest just to get that lazy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Besides, there's no Pizza Hut near my house and that makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, speaking of EverQuest, this is completely off the subject, but...
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually got to meet some of our quote-unquote competitors, although not really, because, you know, all of us online radio stations are in it together.
[SPEAKER_12]: People in the same industry.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, people in the same industry.
[SPEAKER_14]: I met the folks from MMO Radio, who talk about nothing but EverQuest and, what are the other, I don't even know, World of Warcraft and Guild Wars and all those types of games 24-7, so...
[SPEAKER_14]: If you think it's weird that there's stations out there dedicated to DDR Just know that there's other stations out there dedicated to other types of games Anyway
[SPEAKER_14]: We've got a fun show for you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just me and Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: We actually don't have any other guests tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know Rice Princess is actually here around.
[SPEAKER_14]: She's watching movies with my roommate though, so I don't know if we'll be able to get her on.
[SPEAKER_13]: She's watching Fargo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are they watching Fargo?
[SPEAKER_14]: Why are they watching Fargo of all things?
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess they want to, I don't know, watch someone get thrown through a wood chip.
[SPEAKER_14]: How about watching a movie that wasn't really overrated?
[SPEAKER_14]: That sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, we're going to take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course we've got lots and lots and lots and lots and lots and lots of E3 news to talk about tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: But we're going to start off with a quick break.
[SPEAKER_14]: And in this break we're going to feature some music that was made big at last year's E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: From songs.
[SPEAKER_14]: But what is neat about tonight, you guys, is that do we have songs from the new mixes?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have one new song to play for you guys from EX2.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we have a bootleg copy of a song from Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is too cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: I can't wait to hear how this turns out.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll be back with more details on that after this.
[SPEAKER_14]: Started off with a little bit of your reign.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll be back.
Thanks for watching!
My resistance is waning
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Gaming Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: So uncensored that even Tom Brokaw could get a job with us.
[SPEAKER_11]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello, everybody.
[SPEAKER_14]: We are back on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: In that break, arguably one of the best remixes ever done for DDR.
[SPEAKER_14]: Midi Head, in my eyes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Before that, Junior Senior, Move Your Feet, Elvis Rubberneckin from Ultramix 2, and the Kiriyama Oka with Your Rain, the Rage Mix from...
[SPEAKER_14]: DDR Extreme USA
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, we have a lot of E3 to talk about tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just Loki and I here tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura has the night off.
[SPEAKER_14]: She's on her way back from LA right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Her and some folks from DRFreak went over to Disneyland yesterday.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was actually originally going to go with them, but I had to back out at the last minute, basically, because I'm in a bit of a financial situation right now, so I couldn't afford to go to Disneyland, amongst some other things going on.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're better off.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, it's overrated.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, so...
[SPEAKER_14]: How about a little bit of how was your week, how was your day, except for the fact that we're going to talk about E3 a little later.
[SPEAKER_14]: So is there anything you want to share outside of E3 for how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, let's start off with, first off, we drove down there.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was eight hours of fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then we got there and we went and saw the More Friends concert.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, More Friends, More Music from Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was Snap, Crackle, and Poppin' Fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think that's the best way to describe the concert, was Snap, Crackle, Pop.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a good one.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's just put it this way, okay?
[SPEAKER_12]: If you were to have, like, say, I don't know, they had complete retards working their audio.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because, you know, the singers would be singing, you can't hear them, or the mics wouldn't be turned on.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like they honestly got some tech guy out of high school to do it.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, it was awful.
[SPEAKER_12]: As far as audio goes, it was cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Black Mages were cool and everything, but it just wasn't mixed right and it didn't sound good at all.
[SPEAKER_12]: Especially at the end where they combined the rock band with the orchestra with the choir.
[SPEAKER_12]: It just drowned out everything.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just awful.
[SPEAKER_12]: In that sense, but it was a cool concert.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then we went to Arcade Infinity and I played the tambourine game, except it sucked.
[SPEAKER_12]: Only because they didn't have the thing on the floor where it told you where to stand, so I couldn't tell where the sensors were, so I, you know, kept losing.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I got to play Night of Fire on tambourines, and I looked like a complete dumbass.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just me or is the tambourine game the gayest game ever made?
[SPEAKER_14]: And I can say that because I am gay.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's exactly like some of the Amigo, it's just... But I mean, don't you look a little bit fruity playing that game?
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess...
[SPEAKER_14]: Trust me, I looked over.
[SPEAKER_14]: You looked pretty fruity playing that game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, okay, I had played Dance Maniacs all day.
[SPEAKER_12]: I had to get my Dance Maniacs fill.
[SPEAKER_12]: And after my hands started hurting from hitting the damn sensors on accident, I decided to just go ahead and play the tambourine game since it was there, you know, try it out.
[SPEAKER_12]: And no, it wasn't good.
[SPEAKER_14]: It sucked.
[SPEAKER_12]: The one heavy metal song that was in that.
[SPEAKER_14]: The only one I remember I actually really like.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hate to admit this.
[SPEAKER_14]: I really like the Vanilla Ninja song that's in Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_14]: I need to copy it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played that too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: But anyways, the heavy metal one that was completely obnoxious.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played that about three times.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really loud.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because the Guitar Freaks there is really loud.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just extremely loud.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's so unexpected coming from playing at Golf Land where everything's quiet.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pappa Music Yo-Ha
[SPEAKER_14]: So, finally I figured out the only way you can really pick from any song is you have to go into challenge mode, but that just kind of ticked me off that I lost a dollar because I didn't know better.
[SPEAKER_14]: I also played a game of 2DX Red.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you play any 2DX Red?
[SPEAKER_14]: Nope, don't play 2DX.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was fun, I guess.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was able to play Injection of Love, and that made me happy, so.
[SPEAKER_12]: What else did I play?
[SPEAKER_12]: Nothing really.
[SPEAKER_12]: They had taken out my Gal's Panic game from AI, so that made me sad.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, really, that was all I played is Dance Maniacs and Guitar Freaks there.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't care to touch Poppin' Music just because, I mean, honestly, why are they making Poppin' Music 13?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just, it's the same fucking game all over.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just, oh, look, we changed it now.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a different theme.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's got a... It's the same game.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's got a rabid fan base and apparently it's still doing very well in Japan, so... I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't know what to tell you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: To go to Hooters to eat.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess they were taping the Jimmy Kimmel show or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: And just all these people were out there because, you know, free Audioslave concert.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'm going to be honest, guys, I didn't even know who Audioslave was, really, until I looked up and the guy was singing Spoon Man.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I was like, oh, it's the guy from Soundgarden.
[SPEAKER_14]: He must have like a new band.
[SPEAKER_14]: And finally I figured it out.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, how sad is that?
[SPEAKER_12]: Apparently their new album came out that day and they were promoting it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Apparently, that's what I read.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I get it.
[SPEAKER_14]: But yeah, so we had to fight our way through a crowd so that we could go to Hooters.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because they don't have Hooters in Sacramento, so it's a big deal for us to get to go to Hooters.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was Hooterific.
[SPEAKER_14]: And honestly, what's the big deal with Hooters?
[SPEAKER_14]: I know I don't like to talk about local stuff a lot, but they're making a big stink about putting a Hooters here in Sacramento because they're saying, you know, oh, it's going to corrupt the children, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's the big deal?
[SPEAKER_14]: I've seen bigger whore waitresses at Chili's than I saw at Hooters.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to talk about big whores selling burgers, look at the new Paris Hilton Carl's Jr.
[SPEAKER_12]: commercial.
[SPEAKER_12]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh man, I can't believe that she's just like, did you know, and I'm not sure if you're aware of this, that's actually going to be on TV, and I saw this last night before they were, you know how they have the commercials before the movies and stuff?
[SPEAKER_12]: They were trailering, get this, it was I Want to Be a Hilton.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's going to be a new reality show where the mother is actually going to try to, like, it's refining, making them refine.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm like, yeah, and like your daughter's really refined.
[SPEAKER_12]: Refined and proper, my ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, yeah, it's going to be a new reality show coming to TV.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's crap.
[SPEAKER_12]: I wish the Hiltons would just disappear, honestly.
[SPEAKER_12]: All of them.
[SPEAKER_12]: Your hotels aren't that good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Get affected by aliens.
[SPEAKER_12]: Their hotels are not that good.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, I stayed in the Hilton once.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was nice.
[SPEAKER_14]: All the celebrity sightings this year were from far away.
[SPEAKER_14]: In combination of everybody that was in our group, I think we saw Gary Coleman...
[SPEAKER_12]: Sinbad again.
[SPEAKER_12]: We saw Jason Mewes and the Waynes Brothers.
[SPEAKER_14]: At E3, not at our hotel.
[SPEAKER_12]: At E3, yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Our hotel, my ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although, our hotel is a step up from Jersey.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that's pretty much all that really happened.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just, you know, not too much exciting stuff, really.
[SPEAKER_12]: Lots of walking, feet tired.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're on G4 TV.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh yeah, if you guys haven't heard the podcast yet, which by the way, we were doing podcasts every day from E3, and you can download this at www.orangeauntradio.com, click on Orange Aunt Radio to-go edition.
[SPEAKER_14]: We actually did live broadcast Wednesday, Thursday, Friday from E3, and I believe it's Thursday's edition we talked about this because it happened on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're standing in line to get autographs.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, we're standing in line to get autographs.
[SPEAKER_14]: For my dad, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's for my dad.
[SPEAKER_14]: I, you know, I'm not starstruck or any of that stuff, you know, it's not a big deal to me, but my dad really loves the attack of the show, because he's loved the screensaver since the beginning, so I thought, okay, that would be a nice gift.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh my god, if only this were like last year or something, and Leo Laporte hadn't been fired yet, then I'd be starstruck, but... Maybe me too, a little bit, maybe me too, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because Leo's awesome, Leo, but...
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, so, yeah, we were waiting in line, and they were filming G4TV.com ups on their little, like, platform there, because they were doing a lot of filming at E3, and so they were filming an episode of that, and they actually were, you know, filming the line as we were waiting to get in, just for bumpers for the commercials when you come in, you know, they do a little, you know, talking over the picture and whatnot, but, um,
[SPEAKER_12]: But they basically filmed us for quite a long time on that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: Somebody in the chatroom says, were you guys in one of the panning shots below the platform thing?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, that was it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, so we're down there, and we're in a couple of them, and I hear Brad and Irene are also in one for another show, too.
[SPEAKER_14]: They were in the live crowd shot or something at the very end, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I slipped them, Kevin and Sarah, one of our media samplers while I was there as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we're trying to figure out if, like, he actually listened to it, which we kind of doubt, because, you know, people probably slip him all sorts of weird shit, and he doesn't, you know, he doesn't care.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we're wondering if one of the interns is listening to it, or if one of the bums who found it in the trash out back ended up listening to it.
[SPEAKER_14]: We don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever, but yeah, that was pretty much our E3, I believe.
[SPEAKER_12]: That pretty much sums it up, other than actual E3 stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_14]: What kind of stuff did I do over the week?
[SPEAKER_14]: Pretty much the same thing, because we were pretty much hanging out together all the week, except I haven't had a car the past couple days, which kind of sucks, so I haven't been able to really go anywhere, because my car's getting repaired from the break-in when they stole my stereo a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: Funny E3 stories.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't really have a whole lot to add to that except for me almost passing out because I had to wait for 45 minutes to get a damn hamburger in one of those lines downstairs where there's food.
[SPEAKER_14]: Man, E3 is just so freaking crowded and they don't have enough stuff to handle everybody, it seems like.
[SPEAKER_14]: I wonder if they actually put a limit on how many people can go to that.
[SPEAKER_14]: They obviously don't.
[SPEAKER_14]: It really seems like anybody can go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, if Sinbad's in there, I mean, come on, Sinbad.
[SPEAKER_12]: he's not in the industry nor is Gary Coleman although I could see maybe that he you know would get one of those legacy passes I don't know if he'd been there he'd get invites anyways Gary Coleman I think was in a game like a couple years ago it's possible I don't know but I don't know I think it's just kind of cool to see that they actually have interest in that kind of stuff though that's kind of neat
[SPEAKER_12]: Where was Elijah Wood?
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought he was this huge gamer because he was on MTV promoting the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_12]: Where was he at E3?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess he had better things to do, more important than gaming stuff because he was such a hardcore gamer.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know...
[SPEAKER_14]: Apparently, I don't know if this is just a rumor or what have you, but one of my friends posted in LiveJournal about this, that the Xbox 360, because you got me thinking about that, that you couldn't really see the consoles at the Microsoft booth.
[SPEAKER_14]: You couldn't see the consoles at all.
[SPEAKER_14]: You just saw them running and you saw the controllers.
[SPEAKER_14]: We didn't see the actual console.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yep, the consoles were there.
[SPEAKER_14]: But no, he said he looked into one, like he looked into one of the cases, and he saw a freaking Power Mac G5 in there, not an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: So isn't that ironic if there's some secret Apple and Microsoft teaming up thing?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, first off, yes, the G5 processors are in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Second of all, the test kits look like a G5.
[SPEAKER_12]: And third of all, there were the actual Xbox 360s there.
[SPEAKER_12]: They were just, it was built.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some of them were there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Pretty much it was like a, looked like this white kind of pedestal thing, and then there was a little cutout, and the 360 was in that cutout.
[SPEAKER_12]: But that was it.
[SPEAKER_12]: But yeah, they were actually there, and it was probably running off of development kits, which they've had the pictures online for, and they look like G5s.
[SPEAKER_12]: They pretty much are G5s, but it's because it runs off the same chipset, PowerPC stuff, so... Crazy.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you actually get to play anything for Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_14]: I watched people play stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: I played one game.
[SPEAKER_14]: I played that Top Spin 2, the tennis game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I watched people play...
[SPEAKER_12]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Need for Speed, Most Wanted.
[SPEAKER_12]: That looked pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: I also, what was it?
[SPEAKER_12]: I was watching demos for different things.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it was just like, it was cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it's really good graphics.
[SPEAKER_12]: I did go online though and watch the rest of those, pretty much everything that you would have to wait in line for, for the PS3.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like they showed the new Gran Turismo game mock-up.
[SPEAKER_12]: The re-rendered Final Fantasy 7 intro, the Spider-Man, Doctor Octopus stuff, and just the amount of details on there is pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_14]: That'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, so...
[SPEAKER_14]: Now that's it for How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I have nothing really to add to what Loki had.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, let's talk about the music games.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is honestly the biggest year for music games of E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, starting off, the big surprise that just blew everybody out of the water and people were like, OMG, it's finally happening, Beatmania USA.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now Loki, I know you're not a really big Beatmania fan, but even you must have been impressed by this news.
[SPEAKER_14]: What did you think?
[SPEAKER_12]: I just thought, ooh, yay, it's Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm gonna go play DDR now.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, it was just like, I was hoping there'd be some different songs in there other than just, like, really old Konami originals.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, you know, this is test location stuff, but it did look pretty good for test location, like, you know, the E3 demo version or whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: It looked pretty polished and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: And honestly, I don't know why people judge that as the final product, because it wasn't... I mean, if anyone remembers Ultra Mix 2 last year and how much it sucked, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_14]: But yeah, this... Yeah, and then Ultra Mix 2 ends up being one of the best games they ever put out, arguably.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, it's just, it's mid, you know, it's not even finished yet, it's just partial.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it was pretty good for what it was.
[SPEAKER_12]: At least the controllers will be hopefully cheaper to bring in.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's something where everybody wins.
[SPEAKER_14]: Even if you're not a fan of Beatmania in the US and you're against the idea and you're like, I don't get the point because I have every Japanese mix anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I heard that they're going to be redesigned too.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I think it's some type of new pressing of the Japanese controllers because they still said on the turntable itself, I actually have a picture of them that I'm going to be putting in the Orange Lounge Radio galleries in the next couple days.
[SPEAKER_14]: It actually says Beatmania 2DX on the little turntable.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that makes me, because of the fact that they're not calling it 2DX here because there hasn't been a Beatmania 1 technically.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, granted, we had Hip Hop Mania years ago, but I think they're just overlooking that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because, you know, obviously the new modes, it doesn't really need to be 2DX.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: It was interesting, though, because they were actually plugging Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you watch the little trailer, because Konami, at their booth, they show trailers for all the games that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, you know, you'd have the DDR trailer and the Beatmania and the Castlevania and the We are the Winx, We are the Winx, that trailer as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Those are all playing.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's interesting about the Beatmania trailer is that it actually said, Bringing the Arcade Experience Home.
[SPEAKER_14]: There were USA cabinets, though, but not for 2DX.
[SPEAKER_14]: There was, remember, Hip Hop Mania.
[SPEAKER_14]: Right, there was Hip Hop Mania, which I thought was kind of weird, because, okay, A, the game is not being called Hip Hop Mania, and let me be the first to say, thank God they aren't calling it Hip Hop Mania, because I, for one, would have been really disappointed if they did.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, they can't call it Hip Hop Mania just because it would confuse people.
[SPEAKER_14]: How about the fact that there was no hip hop songs in the demo, really?
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe one, and that's a stretch, but most of it's trance, and they can't really call it Hip Hop Mania.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_12]: That there was a song that's going to be in Happy Sky that's going to be in the US one also.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's a DJ Amuro track.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I listened to the mp3 of it, or what it was supposedly, and it's not even a good fan-made one.
[SPEAKER_12]: It has piano in it, so I guess that makes it a DJ Amuro track or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sure they'll do stuff like that because obviously they haven't listed any licensed stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you never know, there might be licensed stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to be a little weird for them to get licensed songs in there because of the fact that an artist is going to have to give up key samples and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it worked in Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_14]: So there's no reason it can't happen because Amplitude has good stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: It worked in Amplitude and I'll see if the figure.
[SPEAKER_12]: The other thing is they've got a good relationship with a different drummer.
[SPEAKER_12]: Beep Maniac
[SPEAKER_12]: Happy Sky, and you know, it was in already, Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be a pretty easy sell, I would think.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway, you guys, actually on our website, www.orangelonsradio.com, I actually posted up an E3 preview of Beatmania USA, and there's actually screenshots from the actual game and everything, so you can check that out, and as part of it, it actually has the song list.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you guys want to check out the songs that are going to show up, these were the songs that were in the demo, but you know,
[SPEAKER_14]: Granted, if they're in the demo, they're probably going to end up in the full game, 99% certainty.
[SPEAKER_14]: The seven key songs you're going to see in Beatmania USA, Dancing Into The Night, Nothing Ain't Stoppin', I Was The One, Shining Polaris, and In My Eyes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, a lot of people were complaining at E3 because the difficulty level was very easy.
[SPEAKER_14]: In My Eyes was showing up as a flashing seven, but the note patterns were something you would see in a beginner note chart.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guarantee you guys this is not the way the final release is going to be.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guarantee it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not going to be like this.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're going to see the same level of difficulty you see in the Japanese mixes.
[SPEAKER_14]: The reason why... Now this part I'm speculating.
[SPEAKER_14]: The reason why it was done this way, I speculate, is because...
[SPEAKER_14]: You've got people that have never seen this game before at E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: 99% of the people in attendance at E3 probably never saw this game before.
[SPEAKER_14]: Probably only 1% of the people in attendance did.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it was something to make the game very easily accessible to them.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: anything that was in the demo now granted it's in light 7 mode but still all the songs on E3 appeared to be in beginner mode so even to have light 7 note charts in there I think shows you that there's more to come this is a very very early build just to kind of show off the game I wouldn't take anything in this too much as gospel you know what I mean so stop getting worked up over the fact that you know it was an easy mode
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, let's see, also, if you put the game, now this is, this is where we get something really interesting and really different from the Japanese releases, and I think, honestly, this is a throw to the fans.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't, I don't think this is something they had to do, I think this is something that they did for the fans, is they actually put, in 5 key mode, typically...
[SPEAKER_14]: In Japan, for those of you guys that haven't played these games before, in 5 key mode, it's the 7 key songs, but they just put the 6th and 7th key on autoplay, so you only have 5 keys.
[SPEAKER_14]: And the reason why there is a 5 key mode is because the original Beatmania only had a 5 key mode.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was a 5 key design.
[SPEAKER_14]: So what they've done for the US release is they're actually putting, when you go into 5 key mode, instead of having 6 and 7 just be autoplay and it's the same list of songs, no, no.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're actually going to get a completely different list of 5-key songs from the 5-key games.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it's kind of a way for us to catch up on what we missed on Japanese 5-key releases.
[SPEAKER_14]: So really, in reality, you're getting two games in one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Kinda.
[SPEAKER_14]: You see what I mean?
[SPEAKER_14]: Labasanova de Febieng, Overblast, Hunting for You, Metal Gear Solid Main Theme, and Paranoia Max Dirty Mix
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm sure they'll have it where you can download, or not download, but they'll have more note charts.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sure they'll open up in 7-key and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: So eventually probably everything will be played all over.
[SPEAKER_12]: It may have different note charts for 7 and 5 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, so...
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm very excited about this.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, again, this is a very early build that we saw at E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: The actual release of this game is not coming until 2006.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we do have a little ways to wait.
[SPEAKER_14]: A lot can happen between now and then as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: From what I'm hearing, though, it's going to be early 2006, like first quarter, but you never know what might happen with these games.
[SPEAKER_14]: It could be first or second.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I would say you're definitely going to see this game first half of next year coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it should be exciting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, one thing that it's kind of getting slammed for...
[SPEAKER_14]: is that the early press release on it, and the one sheet that was sent to the press about the game, states that there's going to be 50 songs in the mix.
[SPEAKER_14]: And people are saying, well, if there's different song lists for 5 key and 7 key, that means there's going to be 25 songs in 5 key and 7 key.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's kind of eh.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I have to admit, if it's only going to be 25 songs in 7 key mode, that's a little bit eh.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I'm hoping that maybe... Now, nobody said it's going to be split right down the middle.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think one thing that could be interesting is perhaps there's only 10 songs in 5 key mode, 40 in 7 key mode.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think that's something that's kind of feasible.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I think that might be a little more satisfying.
[SPEAKER_12]: And also, I mean, it doesn't mean that they're going to be stuck in those modes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like I said, it's not going to take that much effort to make another note chart for...
[SPEAKER_12]: One song that was a 5 key to 7 key.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it's not that hard.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just, you know, a little editing.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, I don't see why that would be a problem.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, anyway, it'll be interesting to see what kind of songs we get in this game as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Obviously, the interface is Night Styles interface, but we're seeing songs that date, you know, all the way back to early, early mixes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Shining Polaris is what, uh,
[SPEAKER_14]: 5th Style?
[SPEAKER_14]: It was on 4th Style Consumer.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was a 4th Style Consumer track.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that goes a little ways back.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dirty Mix.
[SPEAKER_14]: In My Eyes was a little bit, what, 5th Style?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm having a hard time remembering some of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: 4th, I think.
[SPEAKER_14]: We should expect to see songs from a wide variety of the different Konami styles.
[SPEAKER_14]: What would be very cool, though, and I hope they do, and I don't know if they're going to end up doing this or not, but I'm hoping in 5-key mode we get at least one or two songs
[SPEAKER_14]: from seventh mix or the final because those mixes were never released in Japan.
[SPEAKER_14]: So if we got some of those songs, that would be very cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: That would be a really nice thing for Konami to do for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_14]: audience, I think, would be to give us at least one or two songs from seventh mix or the final to show that they care.
[SPEAKER_14]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Beatmania USA
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's talk about some of the stuff that was actually going on at Konami's booth.
[SPEAKER_14]: It wasn't just a bunch of games being... Let me take that back.
[SPEAKER_14]: You had the games being shown, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: You had Ultramix 3 and Extreme 2 and Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_14]: What some of you folks may not realize is that these games... I'm sorry, Karaoke Revolution Party as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: These games were the center stage at Konami's booth.
[SPEAKER_14]: They were the featured games by Konami this year.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not only that, they had this huge setup with this light-up wall, and they called it Club Revolution, and these were the centerpiece games that Konami was featuring this year.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not only were they featuring the games live on center stage, they actually hired, this is something a lot of people haven't talked about on the forum, so I want to make this very clear, they actually hired this dance troupe, this really famous dance troupe called the Groovaloos, to come in and do about 10 shows throughout the three days of E3, maybe a little more, 10 to 12 shows.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they're also the same people that are motion captured for the dancers for Ultra Mix 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, they're actually going to be motion captured dancers.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a little unclear which game because some people were saying Ultra Mix 3 and some people were saying Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it's Ultra Mix 2, I want to say.
[SPEAKER_14]: You mean Ultra Mix 3?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I think they actually started with probably Ultramix 2, because if you remember, they changed the whole... They re-motion captured everything for Ultramix 2, remember?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, regardless, one of the new games, maybe both, while we know, has the Groovaloos being motion captured on it.
[SPEAKER_14]: So if you like that dancing in the iPod commercial, that's what E.M.M.I.
[SPEAKER_14]: and the new characters, Blues and stuff, that's what they're going to look like.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, it's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: So...
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: is that they highlighted all the games.
[SPEAKER_14]: So they actually got one of the girls from the Groovaloos would sing like Karaoke Revolution Party.
[SPEAKER_14]: One of the songs featured in Karaoke Revolution Party is Crazy in Love.
[SPEAKER_14]: So she actually got up there and started singing from Crazy in Love.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the other guy also sang, you know, play that funky music, White Boy.
[SPEAKER_14]: But this is the thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Karaoke Revolution Party is going to have this new mode we'll talk about a little later called Sing and Dance Mode where you can sing and dance at the same time.
[SPEAKER_14]: When she was doing the sing and dance, if you watched her, the dance she was doing lined up with the arrows.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, in a way, even though she wasn't playing the actual game, they actually showed the video, the Karaoke Revolution Party video, I mean, they had it all synced up, and the dance she was doing was the exact same dance that was on the screen.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, my point, the reason why I'm telling you all this, those of you folks that said that Konami does not support their US audience can now officially shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Seriously, you got served.
[SPEAKER_14]: at E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Groovaloos served you.
[SPEAKER_14]: They did.
[SPEAKER_14]: You just got served.
[SPEAKER_14]: Konami has thrown all of their support by highlighting Karaoke Revolution Party, DDR, two of them, and now Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_14]: All coming out in the US.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you still, after all of this, think that Konami does not support their US audience when it comes to these music games, nothing is going to satisfy you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_14]: So honestly, quit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just quit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nothing they do is going to satisfy you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Go away.
[SPEAKER_14]: We don't need to hear from you anymore.
[SPEAKER_14]: Quit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do us all a favor.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because it is obvious and apparent that Konami obviously invested a lot of money into this stuff and that they are throwing their full support behind these new games.
[SPEAKER_14]: So shut up.
[SPEAKER_12]: I wanted one of the songs that they were playing there and I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Someone told me, though, that it was the music from one of the menus, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, actually, the very first song the Groovaloos did was supposedly some type of stage-like music or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: I wanted it because I can remix it with no limit.
[SPEAKER_12]: It would work perfect, but I can't find it because it's only in their little dance thing, and it makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it's all right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Soon enough.
[SPEAKER_12]: But anyways, what I was going to say... For the...
[SPEAKER_12]: I know we haven't really touched on this yet, Extreme 2 and stuff, but this is kind of a little off the topic of Japanese DDR.
[SPEAKER_12]: We had the little thing where they're saying, you know, oh, hey, it's a new mix.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, the teaser thing?
[SPEAKER_12]: Teaser thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, I know everyone is going, well, yeah, of course, it's Extreme 2, but we know this for a fact because the exact same footage, which they have still on their website teasing it, the exact same footage was in the intro for DDR Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: So...
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a fact.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Extreme 2 that they're plugging there.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's obviously other information that we'll cover probably a little bit later in the show regarding Extreme 2, at least rumors and that sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: But anyways, DDR.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, I think we're going to take a break at this point.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to come back and do some DDR.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to talk about Extreme 2, and I think before we come back and talk about Extreme 2, I'm actually going to play one of the brand new songs from Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is a premiere.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think anybody else has played this song yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: So this is a brand new premiere for you guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just have to find it here.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I have played it.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have some interesting things to say about Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll get into that.
[SPEAKER_14]: And what else?
[SPEAKER_14]: There's other music games there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nobody even noticed, I think.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we're going to talk about that all when we come back.
[SPEAKER_14]: For now, though, let's get into the song from EX2.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, this is the song.
[SPEAKER_14]: This song is Naoto Suzuki featuring Martha, and the song is called, and I'm going to mispronounce this first word here, Polovician...
[SPEAKER_14]: Plovzian, Dances and Chorus
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's really all I know, is that it's some new game that Konami's putting out.
[SPEAKER_12]: It looks spiffy from the video, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: The video looked pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_12]: It looks like a Castlevania-ish title-ish.
[SPEAKER_12]: It'll be nice to actually hear the music since the bass that they had around there was a little too loud and I couldn't hear it.
[SPEAKER_14]: So here it is, you guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: World premiere for you guys here on Orange Lounge Radio from DDR Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is the full version of Polovstian, and I'm sorry, I'm totally butchering that word, Polovstian Dances and Chorus.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_08]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hiho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter B, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, we are back, and that was one of the brand new songs from DDR Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: The full version there, Palovstian Dances and Chorus.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now remember, that's going to be trimmed to DDR length.
[SPEAKER_14]: So if you guys kind of thought, eh, it's a little bit repetitive there, and kind of gets slow in some parts, don't forget they're going to trim it so that it's more DDR friendly.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you can kind of, you know, the fast parts there with the vocal, that's probably what you're going to see in the final release.
[SPEAKER_14]: Honestly, I did play that song in the demo, but it was so darn loud at E3 that I...
[SPEAKER_14]: I couldn't tell you what parts of it specifically are in there, sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I do remember it was fun and it had a pretty sweet video.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's exciting that they're going to other games other than just Silent Hill for some of their music.
[SPEAKER_14]: So Konami's tapping into some of their other games.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then we'll get into Ultramix 3, which actually has a song from Castlevania in it, which was originally in Keyboard Mania.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll get to that in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: So let's talk about some of the DDRs.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll start off with Extreme 2, since we played the song there in that break.
[SPEAKER_14]: We will open up the Skype line in a little bit here for you guys to call in if you have questions for us about E3, some other things.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's talk about Extreme 2 first off.
[SPEAKER_14]: What did you think of Extreme 2?
[SPEAKER_14]: You got a chance to play it, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll probably be buying it.
[SPEAKER_14]: What are some of the differences between Extreme 2 and Extreme 1?
[SPEAKER_14]: First off, the interface went back to the old style.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, now it doesn't, not meaning that it copies Extreme One's interface, but that Konami basically got the hint that you guys didn't like the interface in Extreme USA, so they've changed it back to that style.
[SPEAKER_14]: The standard song wheel.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, the song wheel that you guys are familiar with since DDR Max.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, rest easy, it's gonna stick with that, so.
[SPEAKER_12]: A lot more modes in this time.
[SPEAKER_12]: I actually got to play the Extreme 2 in two different locations.
[SPEAKER_12]: The first one being at Konami's booth, which had, you know, free play mode was the only thing available on it at the moment.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was able to actually play a few songs on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Tried playing on, what was it, doubles and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: But once again, Konami only had softpads, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: That was no good.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then I got to play again on the Sony Entertainment booth.
[SPEAKER_12]: I got to play at the EyeToy support.
[SPEAKER_12]: And by the way, there is a new EyeToy coming out.
[SPEAKER_12]: It looks a lot smaller.
[SPEAKER_12]: It looked pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I got to try the new hands and feet mode, which now is available in all difficulties.
[SPEAKER_12]: Unfortunately, it hasn't gotten any better.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought Hands and Feet didn't, or if you played it on Heavy, it did not have the hands.
[SPEAKER_14]: I could swear there was a way you could get them in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's been so long since I played.
[SPEAKER_14]: But regardless, it's a lot easier to figure out in Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's more logical, the way they have it set up.
[SPEAKER_12]: They need to put it in edit mode, that's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the only thing they need to do, and that option will be awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because if you can do your own hand motions and set up, you know, that would be an
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: The iToy thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: In fact, I don't think anybody mentioned the iToy thing at Konami's booth.
[SPEAKER_14]: This was something more at Sony's end they were kind of whoring out was the iToy thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: They had it set up in their iToy area.
[SPEAKER_14]: The big push for Xtreme 2 at Konami's booth was the online support.
[SPEAKER_14]: So this is definitely not a rumor anymore.
[SPEAKER_14]: You will be online with Xtreme 2 because this is what they were selling is that you're going to be able to do the online mode.
[SPEAKER_14]: And in the feature I'm going to do later this week, we actually have screenshots from the online mode that'll show you kind of what it looks like.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, over at Sony's booth, I actually played In the Heat of the Night Heavy with hands and feet.
[SPEAKER_14]: Huge crowd of people watching.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you see that?
[SPEAKER_14]: Just like tons of people.
[SPEAKER_14]: The reason why I was able to do In the Heat of the Night Heavy, because it has a very easy step pattern for a heavy song.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a very logical seven footer.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just, you know, you're just basically running back and forth on the pad.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it's very easy to do the hands.
[SPEAKER_14]: You just kind of throw up your hands once in a while.
[SPEAKER_14]: People love it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look at that fag go!
[SPEAKER_08]: Look at it go!
[SPEAKER_12]: I tried doing Undo-Twa on that, and once again, Sony Softpad came to the rescue and failed me, and here's why.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I was playing hands and feet mode, and it was pretty hard as it was to coordinate myself to do hands on Undo-Twa because it has a really strange step pattern to it, and then the damn pad stuck to my shoe.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_12]: I love those softpads.
[SPEAKER_12]: Honestly, Konami needs to make some better hardpads.
[SPEAKER_12]: If not, I don't care if they're as good as the red octane pads, but please, so they at least have something else that they can demo at E3 next year.
[SPEAKER_12]: God, I hate those softpads.
[SPEAKER_12]: I hate them, I hate them, I hate them.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can't play anything, you fail everything.
[SPEAKER_12]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_12]: They suck.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know how I got started on those pads, but they suck.
[SPEAKER_12]: Give me something better.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, let's talk about some of the songs that are actually going to be in DDR Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: A lot of people very excited that Erotic is finally making its way into a US mix.
[SPEAKER_14]: And this is very interesting, just because a lot of people, especially previously, were like, you know, well, In The Groove's the only way we're ever going to see Erotic songs at home.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then Konami kind of pulls this one out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, nope, we're going to put In The Heat Of The Night on there.
[SPEAKER_14]: DDR Xtreme 2
[SPEAKER_14]: E-Rotic, In the Heat of the Night, of course, as we mentioned.
[SPEAKER_14]: Genie in a Bottle, but it's a cover of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's by the NC featuring NRG Factory.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, I'm wondering if that isn't one of those Karaoke Revolution crossovers.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really?
[SPEAKER_12]: It was kind of a clubby...
[SPEAKER_12]: Sean Paul with Get Busy
[SPEAKER_14]: Love and Liberty by Naoki Underground
[SPEAKER_14]: Un De Trois, of course, as mentioned.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then some other songs as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Can Be Real, Vision F, La Bamba from DDR Extreme, of course, showed up there.
[SPEAKER_14]: A new song by Sotov called Saturday Night Love was in there as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't quite hear it, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it's hard to hear.
[SPEAKER_14]: Too loud.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tons of characters are going to show up in Extreme 2 as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you see the new character select screen on some of the screenshots that are online?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pretty big.
[SPEAKER_14]: Crazy amounts of characters in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rumor is, and I didn't see this, and I haven't seen this in the press release either, but I was reading in some of the forums, rumor is that it's supposed to have some type of store mode where you earn points and buy things with the points.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, that sounds sort of like the mode that they had in Extreme for the Japanese one, I think.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, it wasn't Extreme, it was...
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: One of the screenshots that actually we got in the press kit actually reveals some other songs that weren't in the demo.
[SPEAKER_14]: And the other songs that weren't actually in the demo were Be Lovin' by D.Crew is going to show up in the game as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you remember Be Lovin' from DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then Yuzo Koshiro featuring Julie Rougarde with a song called You Gotta Move It.
[SPEAKER_14]: So those songs are going to show up in DDR Extreme as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: DDR Extreme 2 also having a Mission Mode thing in it, or I guess it's like Dance Master Mode, where you're kind of like climbing around this tree.
[SPEAKER_14]: Again, these are things that were not available in the demo that they had at E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: These are just things we're getting off the screenshots that were available in the press kit.
[SPEAKER_14]: A very souped-up version of Mission Mode called Dance Master Mode.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then just some, of course, new backgrounds and new screens.
[SPEAKER_14]: New grading system.
[SPEAKER_14]: It kind of clicks around.
[SPEAKER_14]: It makes a little like beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, when it's scrolling through the different grades.
[SPEAKER_14]: It kind of sounds like the Price is Right wheel or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then there's an online play.
[SPEAKER_14]: We can see the options on the screenshot.
[SPEAKER_14]: Head-to-head, ranking challenge, practice, data options, and logout.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's really interesting, though, about the screenshot, and I don't get this, but at the very top it says, 32 weeks from beginning...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: See you right there.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the shot.
[SPEAKER_14]: Obviously, no, we can't... Yeah, I'm actually scanning through some of the screens... Whoa!
[SPEAKER_14]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_14]: That was weird.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're actually scanning through some of the screenshots in the press kit right now, and you actually can see screens that are in that teaser that was on the Japanese site.
[SPEAKER_14]: So this is...
[SPEAKER_14]: This game, for those of you that are interested in what's coming next in Japan, it's going to be a port of Extreme 2, as if you couldn't figure that out already.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, and I just wanted to point something out here, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I heard this, and I have to see it in my screenshots there.
[SPEAKER_12]: But apparently, in one of the backgrounds here, we have a familiar little background.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm trying to find it here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank God they didn't have the pictures of those people dancing with the eye toy like they did last year.
[SPEAKER_12]: You've gone through all the pictures now, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, anyways.
[SPEAKER_12]: Apparently, and I didn't see this, but apparently someone saw a video that was on a website or whatever and had the familiar dancing bears.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know those familiar dancing bears from Romeo and Juliet?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_12]: And someone thought that that song might be in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: I hope not, because that song's not in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I think, weren't they in the video to be loving?
[SPEAKER_12]: I think they were.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I think people are smoking crack, but, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, so that's going to do it for us talking about Xtreme 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's move on to talking about the other dance game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, and I'd like to mention the Xtreme 2 logo does look very nice.
[SPEAKER_12]: It does.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was very disappointed it wasn't purple.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, you didn't get your purple interface.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a very bluish green.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, it looked nice, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, let's move on to talk about the other dancing game Konami was showing off.
[SPEAKER_14]: They were not showing DDR with Mario at Konami's booth, by the way, but we will get into that.
[SPEAKER_12]: They like to disavow all knowledge of DDR with Mario.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's DDR Mario Mix is actually what they're calling it, and it didn't show up until you actually walked over to Nintendo's booth.
[SPEAKER_14]: In fact, I have kind of a funny story.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll get into that a little bit, but let's talk Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: What did you think of Ultramix 3, Loki?
[SPEAKER_12]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played it.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_12]: Some pretty cool new songs that were on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have a new MidiHead remix that was in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, and we're going to actually play that very soon.
[SPEAKER_14]: MidiHead is going to do a new remix.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's called Jelly Kiss, MidiHead Smack Mix.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also, in Ultra Mix 3, we're going to have Akumajo Dracula Medley.
[SPEAKER_14]: That is the Castlevania Songs compilation that is in Keyboard Mania.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's crossing over.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have been begging for this song for two years, and it's finally there.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would like to thank...
[SPEAKER_14]: I am directly responsible for this song being in there, but I'll just keep going.
[SPEAKER_12]: And for all you people that were bitching and moaning before, yes, your damn stupid Max ripoff song, Sakura, is in there now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, Sakura is showing up in Ultimate Extreme, which has a lot of people bitching that it's not showing up in Extreme 2 yet, but a lot can change.
[SPEAKER_12]: God, people, are you never happy?
[SPEAKER_12]: Honestly, that song is just a stupid Max remix.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, come on, folks.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, just because it's in Ultramix 3 does not mean it's not going to show up in Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: We just don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a limited song list.
[SPEAKER_14]: Another song people have been bitching about for forever.
[SPEAKER_14]: Finally coming to the USA after years and years.
[SPEAKER_14]: Butterfly, SmileDK.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which I had to laugh.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: Didn't people say, oh, SmileDK hates Konami now?
[SPEAKER_12]: Who was that freestyling Kyle Snyder's routine?
[SPEAKER_14]: Lil B. Lil B. Yeah, he was up there.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: So Butterfly is going to be in Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Finally, like how many home releases is this later?
[SPEAKER_14]: 11 home mixes later or something?
[SPEAKER_14]: We get Butterfly.
[SPEAKER_14]: Breakdown would be for you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Togo featuring Sana on Miracle Moon, LED light style.
[SPEAKER_14]: Daikin Kai is going to show up.
[SPEAKER_14]: You guys love to whore that song out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Firefly, Destiny Lovers, The Legend of Max, Emotion, Kiss Me All Night Long, Eversnow, and Candy Star.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pretty impressive song list so far.
[SPEAKER_14]: Lots of songs playable in the Ultramix 3 demo.
[SPEAKER_12]: Other things different about Ultramix?
[SPEAKER_12]: There was a brand new freestyle mode.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: I got to play that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you for watching, and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_12]: And they give you a grading at the end.
[SPEAKER_12]: But you basically can do whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's counting your calories as you burn, too.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to be a very neat kind of addition.
[SPEAKER_14]: It sounded kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they give you suggestions like, why don't you try some hold notes or something like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it was very strange.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was something new that was in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then the brand new thing, which is really strange, Quest Mode.
[SPEAKER_12]: Quest Mode is...
[SPEAKER_14]: More interesting than I thought it would be.
[SPEAKER_14]: Quest mode actually seems very similar to the mission mode that's showing up in Xtreme 2, except instead of just this giant tree, you have this states and capitals map.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you have a map of the states of the union with all the various capitals, and you start quest mode in Orange Lounge's home of Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that was done for us, by the way.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_12]: And what's also great about that is you have to pick up your dance crew, I guess, along the way.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: So if you live in a state capital, you'll be able to play in your home ground on the quest mode in Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's get into this.
[SPEAKER_14]: We actually have an E3 bootleg exclusive, and you know this is Loki's fault.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, what did you do here?
[SPEAKER_12]: I recorded the MIDI head remix with this really crappy mic and a really crappy digital recorder that I have.
[SPEAKER_12]: and therefore you get this really crappy quality recording but it's the only one you're going to hear unless you were there.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we got to preface this.
[SPEAKER_14]: The reason why we had to record this for you guys is the Jelly Kiss remix is very hot.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is very hot.
[SPEAKER_14]: Middyhead is incredible at his remixes.
[SPEAKER_14]: He's so good at remixing the songs.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played this song about 25 times while I was there.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, honestly, I wish I had a better mix for you, because this doesn't do it justice, but it's still hot.
[SPEAKER_14]: This will just have to kind of, at least you can get an idea, but trust me guys, this is a very crappy quality.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is like crappy location test quality, okay?
[SPEAKER_12]: This is like Beatmania 2DX test location.
[SPEAKER_12]: with a microphone, okay?
[SPEAKER_12]: At least I actually had a microphone and didn't just use the microphone on the tape recorder, because that would have sucked even worse.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see how bad this is, because I haven't heard how bad the quality this is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, it's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_14]: I might have to cut this off if it's too bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, come on.
[SPEAKER_12]: You've got to play a minute.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a minute and 47 seconds.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you don't like the quality, you just turn down your speakers, but trust me, you guys, this song is so hot.
[SPEAKER_14]: Jelly Kiss, Smitty Head Smack Mix, bootleg version, Orange Lounge Radio exclusive.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_08]: Get down!
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Julie!
and many more.
[SPEAKER_08]: Honestly guys, that recording doesn't do the song justice.
[SPEAKER_14]: But you could hear that the remix is really good.
[SPEAKER_14]: You could at least get an idea of what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_12]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not great, but I tried the best I could to clean that up, and it just was not doing me any good.
[SPEAKER_14]: Please don't base your opinion of that song off that recording.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's really for the hardcore fans to whet your appetite a little bit for the real thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: At least it gives you an idea of what it's going to sound like, and it sounded really cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: When I heard it, I was like, oh, I've got to play this.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't doubt it.
[SPEAKER_12]: But...
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: Wasn't much, but the mic was like $10.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, yeah, the mic.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, gosh, it was that same microphone we use for our podcasts away from home.
[SPEAKER_12]: $10 mic.
[SPEAKER_12]: See, like if I had professional recording equipment, actually what I would have preferred to do, but obviously I had no access to do this, would be to pull one of the audio connectors out of the speaker and actually hook it up directly to it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ideally, you know, if I had known somebody that worked there that would let me do that, that would be awesome because I had the tools to do that.
[SPEAKER_12]: But yeah, right, like they're actually going to let me bootleg this song.
[SPEAKER_14]: What you did was crazy enough.
[SPEAKER_14]: I couldn't believe, because there was a Konami person that walked right by you as you were doing that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I couldn't believe that they were cool with it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I not only did that once, I did that twice.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because the first time, somehow my erase button got stuck down.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it got erased the first time.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I did that, the first time was on the stage.
[SPEAKER_12]: I did that right there.
[SPEAKER_12]: So no one really cared, but you know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I really wish I had a plug that could have gotten a game copy of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some folks in the chatroom are begging us to put that bootleg copy up somewhere.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll have to think about it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I really don't want people to think that this is what the song is actually going to sound like because it will be much better.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hopefully, MidiHead, he likes to put these things up on his site.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hopefully he'll do something for the fans over there.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll beg and plead.
[SPEAKER_14]: Everybody go to MidiHead's site and beg and plead.
[SPEAKER_14]: But he might not be able to.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't beg too much, because if he says he can't, then he can't.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, Konami might be wanting to put this on a VRare later or something, so... Oh, it will be on a VRare.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, he might not be able to do it, so don't bug him too much.
[SPEAKER_14]: If he says no, leave him alone.
[SPEAKER_14]: But if there's even a possibility he might do it, bug him.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's go to a break.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's do a break because we need to stretch a little bit here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just a rundown of the different modes that are going to be in Ultramix 3 as well before we get a break.
[SPEAKER_14]: Party mode, freestyle, quest mode, workout mode, challenge mode, playing online, Xbox Live, training mode, edit mode, jukebox mode, which is something we didn't mention but it wasn't playable in the demo, that's why, but we imagine it's just the videos and nothing else.
[SPEAKER_14]: Kind of like jukebox mode in 2DX.
[SPEAKER_14]: And options, of course.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love playing the options mode.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to go to a break, and when we come back from this break, what we're going to do is we're going to talk a little bit about DDR with Mario, or DDR Mario Mix, as they're going to call it in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to talk about In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_14]: I still want to talk In the Groove, and we want to get Loki's thoughts on In the Groove as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Loki also tries a bunch of different hardpads in succession, making him very tired.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, yeah, yeah, that's, oh, yeah, we got to talk about that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some of the other Kenshiya Hall tour that we did, a little Kenshiya Hall tour that we did.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I want to also touch on how I almost got in trouble a few times at the Infinity Gaming booth with their Feel 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, we'll talk about that.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, in this break, I thought what we could do is actually do some music from Ultramix 3, because we actually have a lot of the songs already in rotation on Orange Lounge Radio, our music program that runs 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, and we're not here.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we're going to play some of the songs that are going to be featured in Ultramix 3, in case you guys haven't heard them yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: And should we also mention that one of our cast members is no longer with us?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, we should mention this.
[SPEAKER_14]: One of our cast members is no longer with the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: They have been snatched up by the Katamari.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, they have been stuck on the giant Katamari and gone forever.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that is one of our ferrets.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's actually the ferret in question is the ferret that was broken and Loki actually operated on him.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was one of the ones I operated on, and it's also one of Jamie's favorites.
[SPEAKER_12]: The one that's all, you know, it's all, woo-ha!
[SPEAKER_12]: Which made me even happier to get rid of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry, Jamie, if you're listening.
[SPEAKER_14]: So now we have old ferrets still here, but the new ferrets... We still do have one of the ferrets here, and this is Jamie's absolute favorite ferret.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, he's still here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hmm, actually, that might be one of the old ones, or the new ones.
[SPEAKER_12]: Isn't this the old school ferret?
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought that was the very first ferret.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, that might be the only one.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: So one of the ferrets is gone.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like our chat room.
[SPEAKER_14]: www.orangeentrader.com Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're always hilarious in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Somebody in there saying, Dark Tetsuya, port of 40.
[SPEAKER_14]: In memory.
[SPEAKER_14]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll be back after this with DDR Mario Mix, In the Groove, Little Guitar Hero, our trip to Kenshiya Hall, and more.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Music, Music, Music
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Kaizenbo, Karlaienbo, Kaizenbosu, Kaizenbo, Kaizenbo Kaizenbo, Kaizenbo, Kaizenbo, Kaizenbo, Kaizenbo
DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_18]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio Because real radio makes Captain Jack cry
[SPEAKER_14]: We are back here at Orange Lounge Radio and we're going to be talking about now DDR Mario Mix.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, did you get a chance to play some DDR Mario Mix?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I looked at it and it looked like crap.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, no, honestly, I didn't get to play it just because, I don't know, it just wasn't my thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, it looked a little easy.
[SPEAKER_12]: It looked kind of very Disney Rave-ish and I just didn't want to touch it.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it looked interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Different.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, this is the thing about DDR Mario Mix.
[SPEAKER_14]: They actually weren't showing this at Konami's booth.
[SPEAKER_14]: You actually had to go over to Nintendo's booth to see this.
[SPEAKER_14]: And what's really interesting is I asked somebody at Konami's booth, who I know kind of well, what's up with DDR with Mario?
[SPEAKER_14]: And they were like, oh, it's a Japanese-only release.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm like, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Then I walk over to Nintendo's booth, and there it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're showing it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm like, you lied to me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Too many people lied to me this E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're a dirty liar.
[SPEAKER_14]: Too many dirty liars at E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_14]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_14]: I would say it was about the equivalent of a 5-footer, and I AAA'd it my first try.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's about the skill level you're going to see on DDR Mario Mix.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'm not one of those people that can AAA every song.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've AAA'd some songs, but nothing that crazy.
[SPEAKER_14]: So DDR Mario Mix is definitely not for the hardcore DDR player.
[SPEAKER_14]: Unless you happen to be a fan of Mario as well, then you might like this mix because it's going to have a lot of songs, especially for you in this.
[SPEAKER_14]: But as far as the DDR person that's looking for the next 10-footer and is hoping that it's going to be the star medley and Mario is going to be a 10-footer, I highly doubt it.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is a mix that's going to be for kids mostly.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's look at some of the...
[SPEAKER_14]: songs that are going to be in Dance Dance Revolution with Mario.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was really, did you actually take a look at the song list at all?
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, a little bit, not, very briefly.
[SPEAKER_14]: But did you see any songs in there that weren't from a Mario game?
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now I realize it's DDR Mario Mix, but with Nintendo putting this out, you would still think you'd get maybe, I don't know, a Donkey Kong song, or a Zelda song, or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: All Mario songs.
[SPEAKER_14]: Starring Wario, Boo Boogie, Rollercoasting, Hammerdance, Blooper Bop, In the World Pool, Fishing Frenzy, Jump Jump Jump, Destruction Dance, Garden Boogie, Underground Mozart, Here We Go, Up Down Left Right, Always Smilin', Rendezvous on Ice, Deep Freeze, Cabin Fever, and Frozen Pipes are the songs in Dance Dance Revolution Memorial.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also should be noted about DDR Mario Mix, um,
[SPEAKER_14]: D.D.R.
[SPEAKER_12]: There was one, it's very similar to Mario, or the one where you would... Actually, it was exactly the same as the one for the DDR Extreme, where you would run using left and right and hit up for a jump.
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course, you know, with Mario, obviously.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Honestly, what I think would be kind of cool is later on when the next game comes out, which will be kind of similar to Donkey Kong's Jungle Beat, where it uses the DDR pad, but it's not a music game
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, maybe.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, I'm hoping, hopefully something like that will come out justifying this purchase.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, I don't want to knock this, because I think Nintendo has always been, they do a lot of kid-friendly things, so I think this is going to be a good thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not going to sit here and knock this mix, because I think it's going to be a good thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think a lot of the Mario music is very good.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it's going to be a fun thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think if you have a lot of parties, and you have friends over that don't play DDR very much, this is going to be a mix that can really enable them to get into DDR a little more.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nintendo knows one thing, it's how to make a party game, and...
[SPEAKER_12]: So I don't doubt that one bit that any sort of party mode on that would be perfect.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I'm not going to say, you know, DDR Mario Mix sucks because it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just different.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not for you hardcore players.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's for kids and, you know, people that, you know, are not familiar with DDR but maybe are Nintendo fans.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think this could expose DDR to a whole new audience, which, you know, is a good thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_14]: Questions from our chat room.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, does Nintendo have a release time frame for DDR Mario Mix?
[SPEAKER_14]: We don't know of anything because we didn't get a Nintendo press kit.
[SPEAKER_14]: But Jamie's in our chat right now and I'm wondering if she was able to schmooze her way to get a press kit.
[SPEAKER_14]: We think by end of year.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hasn't everything we've been reading saying like October, November time frame-ish?
[SPEAKER_14]: By the way, Ultramix 3 and Extreme 2 are looking at the same time frame.
[SPEAKER_14]: Will be released end of year-ish.
[SPEAKER_14]: Definitely in time for the holiday season.
[SPEAKER_14]: I do remember Nintendogs is out August 22nd.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's one thing I did hear.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nintendogs, by the way, on the podcast I named Nintendogs my favorite game of the whole damn show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nintendogs is going to rock.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't wait for that game.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's going to be freaking awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: So cute.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just love dogs.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, but really, I can't wait for that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mario Kart Advance or not Advance, DS kind of disappointed me.
[SPEAKER_12]: But anyways, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was just going to check real quick.
[SPEAKER_12]: Check some of the websites.
[SPEAKER_12]: See if we can answer that question.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, if I can't figure out when it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nope, to be announced 2005.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to be out this year.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would say bank on October, November, that time frame.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think that's a good... It's got to be out for the holiday season, honestly.
[SPEAKER_14]: By the way, if you're a Nintendo fan, another title not to miss that's coming out next month, Meteos.
[SPEAKER_14]: Awesome puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see, what other Bomani games are we talking about?
[SPEAKER_14]: I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think that's all the official Bomani releases that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that takes us to the one of Bomani.
[SPEAKER_14]: So down in Kenshiya Hall...
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, Kenshi Hall.
[SPEAKER_14]: What did you think of Kenshi Hall this year?
[SPEAKER_14]: Kenshi Hall blew.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was a little weak compared to last year.
[SPEAKER_14]: And a lot of that was because Game Infinity got promoted to West Hall.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: So Game Infinity wasn't in Kenshi Hall this year.
[SPEAKER_14]: But there were some interesting things there.
[SPEAKER_14]: One...
[SPEAKER_14]: GetUpMove.com
[SPEAKER_14]: All they had set up were the metal pads and no TVs.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they had boxes for In The Groove, display boxes.
[SPEAKER_14]: They were kind of promoting In The Groove, but nothing to show.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I was kind of like, well, that's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was a little surprised.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was like, wouldn't you want to show off your game that's coming out really soon?
[SPEAKER_14]: And I asked.
[SPEAKER_14]: I flat out asked the guy.
[SPEAKER_14]: I said, you know...
[SPEAKER_14]: I know there's things that have happened in the past few weeks that possibly have delayed the home release.
[SPEAKER_14]: What can you tell me about the release date of the home release?
[SPEAKER_14]: And he told me that he could say it was pushed back a little bit, but mid-June is the target release now.
[SPEAKER_14]: And he didn't say it was pushed back because of what was going on.
[SPEAKER_12]: In fact, the rep told me... Yeah, if I were to guess, I would say it's probably not because of that.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's probably because of the USB support that they were trying to fix.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be my guess.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think the people are saying it's because of Sony's delay or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: We don't really know what the delay is, but we don't think it's related to the lawsuit anymore, which I guess I was proven wrong from last week.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was convinced that this was going to delay the home release, but hey, I was wrong.
[SPEAKER_14]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: I also said I would love nothing more than to be proven wrong on it because I think the home release should come out, so it looks like it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: And from what the rep had told me...
[SPEAKER_14]: They are going ahead with it because they feel that the lawsuit is more to do with the refitting of DDR arcade cabinets.
[SPEAKER_14]: Red Octane was named nowhere in that suit, so they are proceeding with a home release because they feel that the lawsuit is strictly aimed at the arcade releases.
[SPEAKER_14]: So they're going to release this sucker in mid-June.
[SPEAKER_14]: My advice?
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: it's the rubbery parts that were inset were inset too far and they were too rubbery and they actually there's no it's good for sticking to the pad but it's not good if you want to actually do any freestyling or stuff on it I did not like their new pads I thought they stunk I would not spend my money on them and I would not even touch nor play ever again in the groove or in the groove 2 or any sort of incarnation of in the groove it sucked ass and I do not support it at all
[SPEAKER_14]: Now tell us how you really feel.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, okay, here's how I really feel.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that the interface is playing such a stupid port of Step Mania to the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: So all you people that want to play Step Mania on the PlayStation 2, there you go, here it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_12]: But as far as you're wanting original music, you're not going to find it in the groove.
[SPEAKER_12]: In the groove is just a bunch of rehashed, really amateurish music that you're going to find there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, sure, there's some good licensed songs in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good, play those.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's about all you're going to enjoy as far as in the groove goes.
[SPEAKER_12]: But hey, if you want something harder for you,
[SPEAKER_12]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Let me just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's better music games coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't waste your money.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't have the... When I first played in the groove, I wasn't like, OMG, this is the best thing ever, but I wasn't anti-in the groove like you were.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it grew on me.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think you should give it another chance, because in the groove, it grew on me as I played it more and more.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry though, but these people are going, Oh, it's not DDR!
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it is DDR.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's exactly DDR.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I can't argue with you there.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's very, very much DDR.
[SPEAKER_14]: But the dance pads, I completely disagree.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think the Afterburners are great.
[SPEAKER_14]: I loved playing on them.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's where I don't get it, because I thought they were great.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, the Afterburners are an okay pad.
[SPEAKER_12]: They just have a fatal flaw in it, and that's that they're inset too far.
[SPEAKER_12]: Raise them up just a few millimeters, and you'll be perfect.
[SPEAKER_12]: They'll be a great pad.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just right now, they're too far, so you're gonna... You're playing on them, it's awkward, because they're inset too far, and that's why.
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't like them.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played on a lot of different hardpads.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's... Trust me, there are pads worse than the afterburners there, and we played on those right afterwards.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, now, now, you... Even though you're knocking on the afterburners, what happened after you left Red Octane's booth?
[SPEAKER_14]: You went to DDR Games' booth, and you played on that metal pad, which has a bar, by the way, so this would be great for you and the groove players, except...
[SPEAKER_12]: Except the thing is flat and you can't tell where you are.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's soft pad syndrome.
[SPEAKER_12]: You basically float all over the pad and you miss stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not only that, but it wasn't very sensitive at all.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the other thing I didn't like about the Afterburner.
[SPEAKER_12]: It didn't seem sensitive at all.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, I was testing it to see... Is it maybe just that the Afterburner was worn out from all the people playing on it?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's possible... When I played at the premiere, I thought the pads were...
[SPEAKER_13]: and Ristine.
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought they were awesome guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: My complaints with it would be that one, the arrows are rubbery.
[SPEAKER_12]: They should be just like a metal type thing because honestly if you're playing with shoes you're still going to get grip but if you want to actually slide on them you can actually do that as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: That I think would be beneficial for them.
[SPEAKER_12]: The reason why that they're rubbery is that you stick too much and so it kills your ankles when you do that because it's just not quite like plexiglass and you get the same syndrome if you play on a pad that's sticky.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hello, Dark Sakura, how are you?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm exhausted.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm tired.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been in the car all day.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I know how that feels.
[SPEAKER_14]: It kind of sucks driving in the car all day long.
[SPEAKER_14]: How was Disneyland?
[SPEAKER_00]: Disneyland was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: They turned off the fast pass at Roger Rabbit, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: That kind of made me upset.
[SPEAKER_00]: But other than that, I went on Indiana Jones twice.
[SPEAKER_14]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: What was the best ride you rode while you were there?
[SPEAKER_00]: Indiana Jones, without a doubt.
[SPEAKER_14]: Heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we've been talking about E3 tonight, of course, obviously, that's what this show's been about.
[SPEAKER_14]: What were your impressions?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, we went to Timbuk2.
[SPEAKER_14]: What were your impressions of some of the stuff at E3?
[SPEAKER_14]: We've talked about Beatmania and the Konami DDRs, and we were moving into In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_14]: What were your thoughts on some of those games?
[SPEAKER_00]: Beatmania, of course, was great.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, can you believe I got my first AAA on the stage in front of like a bajillion people?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, good deal.
[SPEAKER_00]: As far as the other stuff, of course, Katamari Damashii was cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Call of Cthulhu was really freaking awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I got to play Popokurus, which is a new... Agitech got the license on that one, and they announced it at E3, and it was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a 2D RPG game.
[SPEAKER_00]: For anyone who's into the import scene or into anime, they probably are very familiar with this one since it's very, very big.
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually turned off the show.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, maybe that'll help.
[SPEAKER_00]: I already did.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I looked at the... Actually, I focused on the Mario one in particular.
[SPEAKER_00]: I took a bunch of pictures.
[SPEAKER_00]: They'll be up on the site soon.
[SPEAKER_00]: But as far as the other... I really didn't get to play them because of the injury to my hip from my car accident.
[SPEAKER_00]: I tried to play and it just ended up hurting way too badly.
[SPEAKER_00]: Although I do like the new mix of Jelly Kiss.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: We actually played Loki's Bootleg earlier.
[SPEAKER_14]: It wasn't so bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you say Loki's Booty?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, Loki's Bootleg.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_14]: We did not play my ass.
[SPEAKER_00]: You broke up and it sounded like booty.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, we did not play Loki's Booty.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: What did you think of... Now, did you go down to Kenshiya Hall?
[SPEAKER_14]: We were just talking about some of the stuff we saw in Kenshiya Hall.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Red Octane's booth?
[SPEAKER_00]: The Red Octane's pads were ass-worthy.
[SPEAKER_00]: I played on the DDR game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ha!
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't get this.
[SPEAKER_13]: I outvoted here.
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought the Afterburner pads were awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_00]: If they wanted to do a good pad, then Konami needs to release the DX pad for the US.
[SPEAKER_00]: Apart from that, I have not played on a single metal pad other than ones that are homemade.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_14]: RedOctane
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm okay with people bar-raving.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, yeah, but that goes to the same people who complain about using speed modifiers on DDR.
[SPEAKER_00]: If they didn't want to use it, they wouldn't have put it in the damn game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, when people say, well, you know, oh, it shouldn't be there, blah, blah, blah, you use your speed modifiers in 2DX.
[SPEAKER_00]: What's wrong with using them in DDR?
[SPEAKER_13]: Right.
[SPEAKER_13]: And what's wrong with using the bar?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because the bar's there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because it's a cop-out.
[SPEAKER_00]: It means you're weak.
[SPEAKER_00]: You are weak and you rely on the bar for your support.
[SPEAKER_00]: You should stand on your own feet and beat the game yourself.
[SPEAKER_14]: I got sunburned.
[SPEAKER_00]: I put sunblock everywhere except I forgot that my neckline with that shirt is just a little bit lower than I was thinking of because...
[SPEAKER_00]: I have this really cool shirt, but it sags just a little bit because it's just enough too big.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so I didn't put any on my neckline.
[SPEAKER_00]: And my shoulder was getting sore, and I thought it was from the shoulder strap on the camera rubbing up against my skin.
[SPEAKER_00]: Turned out I was sunburned, and it's actually a little swollen.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it hurts.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you do anything else in L.A.
[SPEAKER_13]: besides Disneyland and E3?
[SPEAKER_00]: Um... Um... We went to AI.
[SPEAKER_00]: I played lots of pop-up music Iroha.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I just played all the, like, Goonies and all the anime stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought Iroha was a little overrated, but that's just me.
[SPEAKER_00]: I played, um, the Beatmania 3 seventh final deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just because I was waiting for Iroha, and it was really hard to hear, and it wasn't all that much fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, I also, uh, we went to Roscoe's house to chicken and waffles on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I, I had been really good on my eating all day because I was going to have some grits and country gravy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Believe it or not, the grits were substandard.
[SPEAKER_00]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not good grits.
[SPEAKER_00]: However, the chicken livers were pretty awesome and so was the turkey, the, uh, chicken gravy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: I had fried chicken liver.
[SPEAKER_00]: And say what you will, fried chicken liver's good.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like my comfort food.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know, I don't think I'm brave enough to try one, but maybe someday.
[SPEAKER_14]: I used to eat the livers all the time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you sing anything at karaoke?
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually did, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_00]: They had, you could choose Chinese, Indonesian, Japanese, Korean, and English songs.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I actually went on the Japanese list and found the opening to Lane on the Japanese list.
[SPEAKER_00]: There was a bunch of other songs that were sort of half new in Japanese, but this one was all in English, so I sang it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: If it was at the place on Thursday I would sing that one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anything else you want to share about E3?
[SPEAKER_14]: Things you saw at E3?
[SPEAKER_14]: Stuff you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_00]: I saw the PS3 demo and the Xbox 360 demo.
[SPEAKER_00]: and I took a bajillion, bajillion pictures of the Playstation 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: The demos were pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's like a motocross game that had a pretty excellent demo to it.
[SPEAKER_00]: They did a demonstration for the new Tekken thing with Jin and he was all sweaty.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was like, ooh, sweaty Jin.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, pictures of that online.
[SPEAKER_00]: I played the crap out of Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_00]: I played Frisbee with the puppies.
[SPEAKER_12]: They have sweaty gin online.
[SPEAKER_00]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_12]: A picture of sweaty gin online.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's on IGN and it's super big so you can see all the sweat and pores and everything.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, hooray.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you on the site yet?
[SPEAKER_14]: Do you know?
[SPEAKER_00]: I haven't checked.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been home for all of two and a half hours.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll have to check some of that out and let us know.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was long enough for me to post my picture, which I'm going to link in the chat room of the reject false icon sticker on Pac-Man's mouth.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: I put a lot of stuff on the Katamari.
[SPEAKER_14]: I ended up getting four mouse pads and I gave one to Iguana Girl because she didn't get one.
[SPEAKER_00]: I gave one to Julie because she was nice and babysat my big fat cat.
[SPEAKER_00]: and I kept two for myself.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to take one to work.
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually managed to snag three and I am going to give one to somebody but the other one I'm actually going to give away on the show at a later date.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I've still got stuff to add to the bag of swag.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_00]: I haven't.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why don't you go ahead and tell them?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, we're planning on doing a contest.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're not really sure how we're going to make you embarrass yourselves for stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, you know, a lot of this swag is going for bucks on eBay.
[SPEAKER_00]: I found out those slimes are going for $40 a piece.
[SPEAKER_14]: The what is going for $40?
[SPEAKER_00]: The slimes that they were giving out at the square picture thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, you can like just order them from Japan for like $5.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to sell mine now.
[SPEAKER_14]: How much are those Beatmania t-shirts going for?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, um...
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll tell you what, we've got Julie over here on eBay right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do you see any of the Beat Mania t-shirts up there?
[SPEAKER_00]: Let me take a look here.
[SPEAKER_00]: She's actually found one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let me see how much it is on eBay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, like I'm ever going to give mine to anybody.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I had people giving me pouty faces and puppy dog eyes.
[SPEAKER_14]: I had people giving me pouty faces and puppy dog eyes for my Beatmania shirt, and I said, this is the one thing I'm keeping for myself.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, I got yelled at for getting a Karaoke Revolution shirt for somebody else, because I had this total bitch yell at me saying, you dug your claws into me to get that shirt.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't even touch her.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know what the hell she was smoking.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then her boyfriend called me an asshole.
[SPEAKER_14]: The DS trailer for Twilight Princess is going for $76 right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, if you got a press kit from Nintendo, they actually have a DS cartridge with the Zelda trailer on it.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Metal Gear Solid... Oh, what is this?
[SPEAKER_00]: We're still looking for this shirt.
[SPEAKER_00]: Someone put their stupid Tylenol Ouch shirt on.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're giving out free massages at the Tylenol Ouch booth.
[SPEAKER_00]: I had a really cute massage.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know those glossy things that they were giving out for free at Konami's booth?
[SPEAKER_12]: Metal Gear Solid 4?
[SPEAKER_12]: Those are going for $10 a piece.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've got two of those.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have two of those as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe I should put one on eBay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or maybe we should put one in the bag of swag.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, we're going to give away a bag of swag, which could end up being worth hundreds of dollars by the time... We don't want the promo.
[SPEAKER_12]: We love Katamari Mousepad, $5.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_12]: DS Stylus for Mario Kart, $10.
[SPEAKER_14]: I will try to get a picture of the Beatmania shirt a little later.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, all it is... I actually have... I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have mine still rolled up.
[SPEAKER_00]: I took a picture of it in the bag.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'll try to...
[SPEAKER_00]: We're going to dinner and going to see episode 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: It has a little Konami one in the front over where your heart would be.
[SPEAKER_00]: If I had one.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a freaking Beatmania shirt.
[SPEAKER_00]: What more do you need?
[SPEAKER_14]: In the USA.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was really cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: As soon as we find a way to properly embarrass our listeners to get swag, we are compiling a bag of swag for you guys, and we will send that to whoever the lucky winner is.
[SPEAKER_00]: You don't have to go on eBay like some people do, because I'm laughing at whoever's bidding on some of this crap, although I'm sort of getting ideas now to take advantage of this.
[SPEAKER_00]: And according to Julie, hardly any of it's being bid on.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it's kind of people are expecting more from eBay than they're actually going to get I went off earlier and people said in the chat room I was actually sounding like you because I went off for a few minutes on Konami supporting their US audience and what they did at E3 really shows that they support their US audience by bringing in the Groovaloos I was going to ask what was your opinion on the Groovaloos and what they were doing
[SPEAKER_00]: I thought that they were cool, and one of them was on Roundhouse.
[SPEAKER_14]: He wasn't actually dancing, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: He was the MC guy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, well, I remembered him.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: I remembered, you know, once it was mentioned to me, I was like, oh, yeah, that is him, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_00]: But no, I was really impressed with them.
[SPEAKER_00]: They were great.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, and it was just even, you know, and there were people, you know, you know one of them won the giveaway?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: And there were people complaining, and
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually came back and heard about that later, about them complaining about them winning, but they don't work for Konami.
[SPEAKER_00]: They were employed by Konami simply for E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know that they actually ended up, the powers that be at Konami, ended up vetoing that win, and somebody else walked away with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's really crappy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Which, by the way, the most unenthusiastic winners ever...
[SPEAKER_14]: By the way, Konami, not only did they bring in the Groovaloos, we forgot to completely mention this, they actually gave away every day a 30-inch high-definition television set, all of their Revolution games, and what else was it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Was it DVD?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it was a sound system, a Logitech super nice surround sound system.
[SPEAKER_14]: Every day they gave one of these away to the most unenthusiastic winners I've ever seen in my life.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I found my pictures of the Cybersex game.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is just another example about how Konami supports their US audience because they gave away thousands of dollars in prizes to promote DDR.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a 360 faceplate that someone got and that's going for $100 on eBay right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I heard about that, the 360 faceplate.
[SPEAKER_00]: Micro racers are going for money too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I saw those.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anything else you want to share with us, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, really, um, haha, we got to go to E3.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, no, seriously, it was really good.
[SPEAKER_00]: I got very worn out walking all over the place.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now I'm sunburned from Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_00]: But in about two minutes, you guys should be able to check out the picture of the Beatmania shirt in my swag bag.
[SPEAKER_14]: Somebody posted somebody else at the show wearing one, but go ahead and post your picture anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: Give them a nice chance to see it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mine's actually the rolled up one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, my free copy of the Magic the Gathering online card game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I'll be tossing in a Katamari mouse pad.
[SPEAKER_00]: and actually I don't have, I gave away my spare styluses so if you've got an extra or something.
[SPEAKER_00]: But we've got some stuff that we can throw in the bag and I did, by the way, check the Nintendo press kit, which I did get a copy of.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's actually autographed stickers in there by Miyamoto.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Were you able to look up, if you have a Nintendo press kit, I don't know if you have any information on DDR Mario Mix.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, for Mario Mix?
[SPEAKER_00]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have it right here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let me get to that page one more time.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was really fast.
[SPEAKER_00]: It got a large page.
[SPEAKER_00]: Donkey Konga 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll read you what it says.
[SPEAKER_14]: I played Donkey Konga 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what song I played in Donkey Konga 2?
[SPEAKER_14]: Headstrong, which is some rock song.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was like, what the hell is this doing in Donkey Konga?
[SPEAKER_14]: But it was cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, let me read the little blurb on here, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mario must recover the stolen music keys before the unstable power of music destroys the entire Mushroom Kingdom.
[SPEAKER_00]: Shake your thing to over 25 dance-flavored songs from classic Nintendo themes to familiar favorites and recover the missing keys.
[SPEAKER_00]: With five difficulty levels, dancers of all abilities can get into the groove.
[SPEAKER_00]: The special workout feature tracks the calories burned while playing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Strut your moves and break a sweat to the beat.
[SPEAKER_00]: No date.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I do remember being told sometime this fall.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I'm almost positive we're going to see October, November.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have stickers autographed by Miyamoto in this thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: I got to meet him.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, did you?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: I ran into him, well actually, he was actually walking away from Kanai.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not going to be able to get the picture he sent us because we actually need to go because we've got to eat before going to the movie.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I did get to meet him and I got to, you know, actually we were about to collide so I said, and he looked really surprised and said thank you and have a good time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, good job.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, um, did you get a chance to meet Togo?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_14]: Aw, I got a picture with Togo.
[SPEAKER_14]: He was cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, um... We are off to go see, uh, episode three.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, have fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, but, uh...
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sorry, I can't be at this show tonight.
[SPEAKER_00]: I only got back like... I have one more thing to add, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was just announced today on PSP Hacker that someone's working on a PC Engine emulator for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: PC Engine emulator for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've got to see this.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought you'd like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to let you go, Jamie, but have fun at the movie, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: Have a good time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bye, everybody.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see you next week, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see you next week?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep, and reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, see ya.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, that was DarkSakura, who's not here tonight, but she was able to bless us with her presence anyway, one way or another.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see, what we're going to do is we're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_14]: Karaoke Party we still got to talk about a little bit because we haven't really, somebody in the chat room is asking about it right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: We never really did get to that.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we'll talk about Karaoke Party.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want to talk about a new music game coming to your cell phone.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hinted about this one earlier.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a brand new music game coming to your cell phone.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll talk about that when we come back after a quick break.
[SPEAKER_14]: So let's do that break.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we'll start it off with In the Heat of the Night, which is going to be in DDR Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we'll be back with more.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is just going to be a potpourri break, I think.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we'll be back with more Orange Lounge Radio after this.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the Heat of the Night
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
I'm a bitch, where do you want to get stuck?
[SPEAKER_08]: I did it, we did it, hell yeah, man, we did it
[SPEAKER_08]: You've got to breathe your mind
Music Music Music Music
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Remix Remix Remix Remix Remix
[SPEAKER_04]: Solid Snake Solid Snake Solid Snake Can you hear what I'm saying?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well it's time to kick a man that wants a bag I'm gonna kick your ass, beat him, kill him all Down, what am I gonna do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Down, what am I gonna do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We put your thing down, flip it, and reverse it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's true, it's true, it's true.
[SPEAKER_14]: We are back and we are going to open up the Skype line, you guys, so you guys can call in and talk to us and ask us questions and give us your feedback on what you think about the various releases at E3 as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we're going to get to that.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you want more details on how you can be a part of that, www.orangelongeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: Click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_14]: But first, I want to give you guys a few notes on some other little game releases that they had at E3 on some other games that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_14]: Guitar Hero, they weren't showing anything at Red Octane's booth to the public.
[SPEAKER_14]: And in fact, when I asked about it, or when Loki asked about it, we kind of got the runaround just saying, oh, well, we'll have more information out soon to the press.
[SPEAKER_14]: I can't say anything right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, turns out they're actually showing the game behind closed doors, and one of our staffers got back there anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we can't tell you about Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, I'll let you talk about this one.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're a big guitar fan.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, this game, it's very similar to Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's actually some wonderful screenshots online right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Basically, it looks like Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_12]: In the middle, you've got all your stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's kind of coming towards you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I wouldn't say it's exactly like Amplitude so much as it's Amplitude and Karaoke Revolution kind of combining with each other.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because you have to remember, Harmonix also helped with making Karaoke Revolution, so it's kind of obvious.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's more like Amplitude, only because the stuff's coming towards you.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's that sort of perspective.
[SPEAKER_12]: However, it is like Karaoke Revolution because on the side, there's a meter that's kind of a crowd meter, very similar to Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_12]: Basically, it's five keys.
[SPEAKER_12]: However, depending on what difficulty you play, it's anywhere from three to five keys.
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought that was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: and now the songs that are going to be in it very similar to what Harmonix did before when they released Karaoke Revolution they were actually doing covers of classic songs they get these guys to go in the studio and re-record them same deal for Guitar Hero is what's going to happen same deal for Guitar Hero except for the ones obviously that are
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, that BeAGuitarHero.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: Right, BeAGuitarHero.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you have a friend who's in a band who might appreciate some exposure from being in this game, or you're one of these people, have them go check out this site, BeAGuitarHero.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, considering how much you went off on Red Octane a little bit earlier, does this redeem them a little bit, you think?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I wasn't going off on Red Octane.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was going off on Rockser for the really crappy game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Red Octane, they're doing no bad because they're trying to actually...
[SPEAKER_12]: Distribute a dance game, which I give them credit for that, because at least they're trying to do something.
[SPEAKER_12]: I wish they'd picked a better game, but hey, when there's nothing else out there other than DDR, what are you going to do?
[SPEAKER_12]: But as far as them actually distributing this game, this is actually a very good move for them, because there are no other Guitar Freaks-type games, and I think this will actually exceed Guitar Freaks, which isn't that hard, since Guitar Freaks really hasn't changed much since Fifth Mix, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: But hey, it's more of a challenge, and there is the same stuff in there that you would expect from Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it looks like they've actually kind of got some hold notes in place.
[SPEAKER_12]: And from what I hear, the controller, even though it is 5-key, it actually allows you to slide your hand along the different buttons to be able to hit them easier.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it's actually like playing a guitar, which is nice.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I managed to...
[SPEAKER_12]: We need a little more information out of the guy when we're there asking him questions.
[SPEAKER_12]: All, of course, very vague answers.
[SPEAKER_12]: I asked him if there was going to be a drum hero type game, and they're all, we're working on something.
[SPEAKER_12]: And also, so maybe a drum game coming soon?
[SPEAKER_14]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_12]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, that's something, and...
[SPEAKER_12]: Definitely, there's some pretty cool shots, like I said, online, and we'll probably have some more on our website.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're hoping we can get some more exclusive shots for our website very soon, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we're going to have those, probably, and it looks very similar to Carriker Revolution, just like, because you've got the CG guy on stage, the crowd, very similar, so it'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tycho Drummaster is available for your cell phone!
[SPEAKER_14]: This is something that they were showing at E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Namco actually has a lot of cell phone games they're doing now, and one of their series they're pushing is Arcade Classics.
[SPEAKER_14]: The folks at Namco Cell were actually very nice to me, and I've got to admit, and they didn't have to be nice to me for me to say this, but their cell phone games are pretty nice, considering that they're cell phone games.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, in the end, they're still games on your cell phone.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're not going to knock your socks off.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not going to be a Game Boy quality game, but for a cell phone game,
[SPEAKER_14]: They're pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: And in other news, the N-Gage arena, empty.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: The sad thing is, these Namco things running on Java on a cell phone is better than anything I've seen on an N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_12]: And honestly, I did walk through the N-Gage booth.
[SPEAKER_12]: I checked it out.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're releasing a new version of the N-Gage, N-Gage 2, I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played Civilization on N-Gage and couldn't figure out what the heck I was doing.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just... It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um...
[SPEAKER_12]: I know there are other competitors out there that are not exactly engaged and not exactly a Sony product that are portable, that are probably doing better than they are.
[SPEAKER_12]: But hey, whatever, you know, they refuse to die, so at least let them try.
[SPEAKER_12]: But...
[SPEAKER_14]: Tycho Drummaster, how's this work?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think this is something that's going to appeal to everybody, but, you know, for those of you guys that have wanted a music game to take with you on your cell phone, something to do when you're bored, Taiko Drum Master has a dozen songs from the original release.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, granted, it's a cell phone, so it's not going to be the same quality, but still, you know, it's something.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it has the animation still and everything, and same types of rolls and combos and everything you remember from the original Taiko Drum Master.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is available now.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're saying, per their press release, it's available now.
[SPEAKER_14]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_14]: See if your carrier has this.
[SPEAKER_14]: I imagine it's not available through all carriers, but I do know I'm a Sprint user myself, and we do have Namco releases on our cell phones.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I believe this should be there.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I'm going to look for it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have, what was it, AT&T.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I know they carry Namco stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: That I was looking for movie tickets on Fandango, thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the picture cost me $7.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you, AT&T.
[SPEAKER_12]: I will never use your web feature again.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's actually someone in our chat room saying that it's only on Verizon and available for a specific number of phones.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't see anything in their release that indicated that.
[SPEAKER_14]: But the lady at Namco was kind enough to give me her card, so I will write her and ask.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe they're going to port it to others in the future, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I will write her and find out.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's what I will do.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_14]: What else do we have?
[SPEAKER_14]: What was the other game I wanted to talk about?
[SPEAKER_14]: Karaoke Revolution Party.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you look at this at all, Loki?
[SPEAKER_14]: I know you're a big Karaoke Revolution fan.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh yeah, don't you know me.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm a huge Karaoke fan.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I stayed far, far, far, far away from this game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, far away.
[SPEAKER_12]: I did not touch this game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I did not look at this game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I stayed far away like it was my kryptonite and I was Superman.
[SPEAKER_14]: XBOX, PLAYSTATION 2, GAME CUBE
[SPEAKER_14]: GameCube will be getting a Karaoke Revolution release for the first time so that was kind of a big news right there you will be able to get this on GameCube a little bit unclear if the sing and dance will be in the GameCube version but they will get at least the sing part I think they will get the dance part as well we'll see some of the songs that were in it the only ones I remember were Crazy in Love Material Girl was in it because I actually did that one Endless Love Play That Funky Music White Boy
[SPEAKER_14]: The interface has changed.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is why they're not calling it Karaoke Revolution 4, but they're actually calling it Karaoke Revolution Party, because they actually went and did some remodeling to the interface.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, I know my material girl, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: So I was able to easily do the sing and dance mode because I already know the lyrics and the melody and everything.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't really need the bars.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because you have to, the way the dance mode works, it doesn't look like normal DDR.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you've ever played Karaoke Revolution, the bars scroll horizontally across the bottom of the screen.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then it guides your pitch.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, the arrows show up and they scroll horizontally at the bottom of the screen as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it's a little different.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dancing Stage Unleashed 2
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, last week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Basically, for those who don't know, that is the UK version of Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: And pretty much it's the same stuff that we had on Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course, new licensed stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: With stuff featuring, like, I See You Baby, which I have no idea what that is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hot stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hip teens don't wear blue jeans.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that that I See You Baby, Shakin' That Ass, isn't that song?
[SPEAKER_12]: I bet it's that song.
[SPEAKER_12]: I bet it is that song.
[SPEAKER_12]: A Town Called Malice, Circles, Get It On, and Hanging on the Telephone, which, very interesting enough, we actually do have, well, DDRUK being the ones that are on top of the ripping of different stuff for the Sim scene.
[SPEAKER_12]: So all the official stuff are already out for that, even though it was released like the other week.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we'll have some of that stuff to play for you guys pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_12]: And ICU Baby is...
[SPEAKER_12]: The one you think it is, and it's a Fatboy Slim radio edit.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's going to be pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: But yeah, we'll have some of those songs available for you pretty soon, actually.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe even a show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also, I want to put out there that Song Pack 11, I don't know if it's out, but at least it's been announced that it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have not been able to get on Xbox Live in a couple weeks, so I have not seen myself.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sure somebody in the chat room will correct me, however.
[SPEAKER_14]: One way or the other.
[SPEAKER_12]: Diamond Jealousy by Akira Yamamoto, Guilty by DJ Setup, Helpless by Teiko, Hold On Me by Tiger Yamamoto, and Open the PA by Akira Yamamoto.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ishihara
[SPEAKER_14]: Now can we open up the Skype line?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, let's do that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's take some calls.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you want to call in on the Skype line www.orangeloungeradio.com Click on Interact With Us and you can call us and talk to us and interact with us and ask us questions.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you have anything you want to know about E3 or you have any comments on a lot of the various news that's come out lately because there's been a lot of freaking news lately go ahead and let us know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's take a call.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh, this is RPGKing7 up in Canada.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello, RPG... I'm surprised you got in.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello, yeah, I'm surprised... Well, you've been hammering us all night, so I'm not surprised you got in.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's on your mind, bud?
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, well, I wish I had gotten down to E3.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm really jealous of you guys that you got to go there, but you live on the west coast, I'm out here on the east coast.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, here it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you want to know what E3 is like, you're up in Canada, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Start walking to LA, and when you get to LA, you'll know what it feels like to be at E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because you do nothing but walk around all day, and occasionally stopping to play a video game.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: It's pretty neat because what you get to do is it looks like Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_14]: It looks amazing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sound, I couldn't tell you because you can't hear a damn thing inside E3, but it looks very similar to Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_14]: Basically, you play on the bottom part of the screen, and the top part of the screen is typically what would have been your subscreen in Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can flip it back and forth, though, between that and your map.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's kind of cool because I think that's sort of the type of game that DS was really made for.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also what you do is as you move through the game, when you get to certain points...
[SPEAKER_14]: You discover these magic seals And the magic seals are what you're supposed to do to defeat the boss So like the first one was very easy The first magic seal in the demo I played was just a little V shape You just draw a V, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: So it teaches you how to draw the seal And then what happens is when you go and fight the boss When you beat the boss, the seal flies up on the screen And you have to draw the seal like you learned it And if you don't do it, you don't beat the boss And I think you have to do it all over So, yeah
[SPEAKER_16]: That actually sounds pretty cool, yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: Nice use of the stylus.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, and I think it's using the stylus without being kind of cheesy about it like a lot of DS games to date have been.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think this will satisfy a lot of folks that have been wanting some new Castlevania that looks more like Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_14]: This falls right along with the Castlevania Advance games.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think this will be a great addition to the series.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it continues the storyline of Aria of Sorrow as well, so...
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, which is really cool, because Arya of Sauron is one of my favorite ones.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, and somebody in the chatroom is saying it's actually due out at the end of October.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would have guessed that it would have been out a lot sooner, because the game looked almost complete from what we saw, but I guess it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it looked pretty well done, so maybe they're just waiting on it, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, I was excited to hear that 1998 and In the Heat of the Night are going to be on Xtreme 2 because those are hands down two of my favorite songs on the Arcade Mix's Xtreme and Fifth Mix.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm really excited to hear those are going to be on it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, you could hear the giant hooray.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, it was kind of a mixed reaction.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was a hooray and dope kind of coming from the crowd when you saw that In the Heat of the Night was on Xtreme 2 because the people that like Erotic, yay, finally we get Erotic, and then the other people that hate Erotic are like, nah.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I, for one, am happy about it.
[SPEAKER_16]: I also wanted to ask you about Phantasy Star Universe.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm sure you've covered a lot of this on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_16]: I've only gotten to listen to the Wednesday podcast.
[SPEAKER_14]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: We talked about it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually played one of them.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it was Phantasy Star Universe I played.
[SPEAKER_14]: I heard they were showing another one in the Sega Theater.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I did play Phantasy Star Universe a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's very different from the online.
[SPEAKER_14]: The way it moves is very different.
[SPEAKER_14]: A lot more action-packed.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think than the previous Phantasy Star Online, at least the one I played.
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually did a fight with a dragon, and I was playing with three other computer-controlled players, and I really couldn't get a sense of whether this one's supposed to be online or what the deal is, but the party I had was computer-controlled, and we were all just beating up on this thing, and it was pretty challenging.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um...
[SPEAKER_14]: A lot more action-packed than I think the Phantasy Star Online was.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just kind of different.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't go into it expecting Phantasy Star Online 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: They've changed some things in it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I liked it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was kind of fast-paced and I liked that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think there needed to be more fast-paced online games.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because one thing I've always didn't like about Phantasy Star Online is it's a little slow.
[SPEAKER_16]: at least in my opinion it's kind of slow I think you'll be satisfied with Phantasy Star Universe then they've really kind of upped the pace a little bit I also want to go to Kingdom Hearts 2 looks amazing I've been following all the games on GameStop and GameTrailers.com both of them have gotten really good E3 coverage over the few days Kingdom Hearts 2 I checked out as well did you play Kingdom Hearts 2 at all, Loki?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, he's saying no.
[SPEAKER_14]: Kingdom Hearts 2 I actually played.
[SPEAKER_14]: They had two, actually four levels playable in the E3 demo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Two boss battles and two levels.
[SPEAKER_14]: And both were either the Mulan levels or the Hercules levels that you could play.
[SPEAKER_14]: The one I chose to play was the Hercules level.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you actually have Oren in your party when you're playing.
[SPEAKER_14]: It has this new mode called Drive Mode, where I guess you're building up this meter as you're playing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I couldn't really see how it was working.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I had not one, but two levels.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: Zelda, Twilight Princess, just
[SPEAKER_16]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: All I know is that it is Link that turns into the wolf because we saw an extra clip of that.
[SPEAKER_14]: And what can I say?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's everything you Zelda fam boys and girls are wanting it to be.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I include myself in that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm looking forward to the game myself.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's the game they should have released three years ago if they wanted the GameCube to be super successful.
[SPEAKER_14]: But hey, better late than never, right?
[SPEAKER_16]: Right.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, we're going to let you go so we can get some other calls in, all right?
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, all right.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thanks for listening to me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_14]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, so some E3 questions there, some various things.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm actually surprised I actually played all the games he called in to ask about, because I didn't play that many games.
[SPEAKER_14]: There was a whole lot there I didn't see.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you guys have any questions, you can give us a call on the Skype line, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: Click on Interact With Us, and you can actually call in.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have to download this program called Skype, but it allows you to call us for free.
[SPEAKER_14]: We like free things.
[SPEAKER_14]: Free!
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey Sky, Siggy here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello Siggy, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I'm about to beat Mania USA.
[SPEAKER_14]: I knew you'd have something to say about this.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Big credits to Jason Enos for that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, I actually had a chance to talk with Jason Enos.
[SPEAKER_14]: We didn't get an interview with him this year.
[SPEAKER_14]: I talked to him off the record about some things.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't want to talk about everything we talked about on air.
[SPEAKER_14]: But one thing I mentioned was that, you know what, way to go.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm so happy that B-Manian is here and you're going to make a lot of people very happy with this.
[SPEAKER_14]: And his response to me was something like, yeah, well, you know, I've been trying for six years and it's finally here, so I'm happy too.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, absolutely, send Jason Enos some flowers if you kids are happy about this, because this is great.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, and when I saw the song list for 5-piece, oh, Old School Beat Mania.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is that not a cool feature for us in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_14]: to have?
[SPEAKER_14]: Is that not cool?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, hell yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, what a way to acknowledge...
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, about, you know, I recently saw a picture on DDR Freak, someone posted the greetings for, you know, some Light Seven song, and like 167,000 points for a triple A, that's kind of ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, I, again, I wouldn't, I heard of that too, and I saw that picture as well, and I triple A'd a song as well, I wouldn't,
[SPEAKER_14]: Take those ranking things as gospel just yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is an early build.
[SPEAKER_14]: The thing was stuck in beginner mode, really, even though it didn't look like it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know how much they're going to futz with the grading system.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's too early to tell.
[SPEAKER_14]: I kind of would think they wouldn't touch it at all, and maybe just the fact that they were doing what they did by putting the beginner songs in there was what caused those mathematical things to come up with triple A's and what have you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: La Bossanova de Fabian Shining Polaris Anything else you want to share?
[SPEAKER_14]: Other E3 things?
[SPEAKER_14]: Observations?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, just only Beatmania
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just happy with that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know.
[SPEAKER_14]: A lot of us people that have been 2DX fans for a long time, and I've just been a casual 2DX fan, a lot of you guys are being very hardcore, a lot more hardcore than I am.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think this is great that you guys are finally getting this.
[SPEAKER_14]: All of us are getting this.
[SPEAKER_14]: I haven't really been checking a whole lot of web forums and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: What has the reaction to this been?
[SPEAKER_14]: Has it been overwhelmingly positive, like about time?
[SPEAKER_14]: Or are the skeptics already ready to
[SPEAKER_15]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_14]: what they were able to do with this is that they were actually able to kind of set the standard the way they wanted to by unveiling this at E3 and showing us all these cool new features I think if they had announced this a month ago and said we are going to show this at E3 and I think this is the reason why this didn't happen people would have made up what they wanted to be in the game and they would have been disappointed when they didn't get that
[SPEAKER_14]: So I think by Konami unveiling it, you know, by keeping it a secret and then unveiling it at the very end and showing this is what you are going to get, look at all these amazing things, it kind of curved that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I think it kind of helped the reaction overall.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I can't blame Konami at all for trying to keep this a secret.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they did.
[SPEAKER_14]: This obviously has been worked on for quite some time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, actually, something we were actually clued in on, but we wanted to keep it a secret, but I can talk about it now.
[SPEAKER_14]: I gave you guys a hint last week about it, though, but actually, Konami registered the patent for Beatmania some time ago in the US.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yeah, I read that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, yeah, so, um, I, somebody had asked me to talk about it on this show, but kind of knowing that Konami, um,
[SPEAKER_14]: If they were going to put out this game, would want to keep it a secret, I decided, or we all decided really, that we should just kind of wait and see what happens with it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because otherwise people will just start making stuff up.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, it's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, anything else you want to share?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, nothing much else.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just want to share something, one of our comments in the chatroom, MPQ says, no matter how much it sucks, buy it, just so Konami knows people will buy Beatmania here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yeah, about the controller, the US release of the controller, were you the one who mentioned some improvements that would happen?
[SPEAKER_14]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_14]: I think we will see some improvements made to the controller.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because they're going to have to redo the controller anyway to get the 2DX logo off the turntable.
[SPEAKER_14]: So why not fix the sticky key thing while you're at it?
[SPEAKER_14]: I would say that we're going to see some improvements.
[SPEAKER_15]: It would be nice if they put microswitches on it, like cheap microswitches, not exactly from the arcade type of microswitches, you know, prevent the sticking.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's an interesting thought, completely change the way that the buttons, kind of, the sensor system, basically.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, I'll be interesting, I'd be interested to see that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, and if they do put microswitches, I would buy it, I would buy it, definitely.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think what's interesting is that a lot of I need a new 2DX controller very badly for my import copies but now that I've heard that Beatmania is coming out in the USA I'm just kind of going to wait for the US controllers to come out because there's no sense in paying $100 to import a controller now when they're going to release them here probably $40-$50 I don't know, don't take my word on that who knows how much these things are going to cost but it'll be cheaper than importing it, that's for sure
[SPEAKER_15]: Speaking of beat me, setting that aside, about PlayStation 3, I read from either IGN or GameSpot that they have 6 USB ports, are they really replacing the old controller port for that?
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't read up on PS3.
[SPEAKER_14]: What do you know about this?
[SPEAKER_14]: It had a lot of USB ports.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know just for the pictures of it, it's got a buttload of... Well, it's also got a bunch of weird things to it.
[SPEAKER_12]: For one, it's got two HDTV outsides, so you can actually have two HDTV setups.
[SPEAKER_12]: One for the actual gameplay and one for almost like a dual screen.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like a DS, basically.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like a DS, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's going to have...
[SPEAKER_12]: I saw three Ethernet ports on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, I don't know what the hell that's about either, but it's just a lot of weird stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm actually pulling up the picture right now for my reference.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I remember also...
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: It just looked interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know that it's going to be Wi-Fi as well, but I don't see why you need so many damn USB ports.
[SPEAKER_12]: But then again, I don't know why you need so many damn USB ports on a computer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, it's going to be that we do know that every next-gen system is going to be wireless and their controllers and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I kind of assume that the USB ports are for four for controllers and two for...
[SPEAKER_14]: and whatever USB stuff you want to put in.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's a good shot of the back here right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I see, I count them, three Ethernet ports, two USB ports, the AV out, which is like your standard AV out, the digital audio out, the two HDTV outs.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's only on the back.
[SPEAKER_12]: Then you've got, and I honestly don't know why there's three Ethernet ports.
[SPEAKER_12]: That makes no sense to me.
[SPEAKER_12]: But
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever, and then as far as front ports go, I remember there's at least a couple USB ports that are underneath this little cover thing on the front.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm trying to see if I can get a picture here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyways, yeah, so there's a ton of stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know why, but I'm sure they've got a reason for it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think, okay, you have to remember with the next gen systems too, what everybody is doing, not just Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_14]: Microsoft's kind of been saying they're going to do this.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're going to expand and not just be about gaming, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Microsoft wants to be an entertainment center where you can download music and do things like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I think you're going to see this on a lot of the next gen systems that there's more things to plug in there for your media setup at home than just your controllers.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I think that's kind of what this is all about on PS3.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, and then I saw, you know, and then I read they're going to replace memory cards with memory stick duos.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think they would do that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Probably USB drives of anything.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, Siggy, we're going to let you go so we can just get to some other stuff on the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: But have a good one, buddy, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Later.
[SPEAKER_12]: Later.
[SPEAKER_12]: I do know what some of those USB ports are going to be used for.
[SPEAKER_12]: Interfacing with your PSP.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, that and wireless is going to be poor, too.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can bet on that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Guys, imagine the member of the Pocket Station.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yep, I met most of you that don't remember that, but that's what they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, what we're going to do now is we're actually not tonight going to have a cage match.
[SPEAKER_14]: We actually kind of ran out of time.
[SPEAKER_14]: And also, even though DarkSakura was able to send me her file, we're just running out of time.
[SPEAKER_14]: We don't have time to do it.
[SPEAKER_14]: We figured you guys would want to know the E3 coverage more than that.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we'll table the cage match to next week.
[SPEAKER_14]: But we can't possibly get through a show without doing some FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_14]: So let's get into the FUs of the week if we can here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, I did get some from Jamie, so I'll go ahead and start off with hers, FUs of the Week here.
[SPEAKER_14]: So here we go.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you guys want to send in your FUs of the Week, send a private message to Sky in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_14]: And after the FUs of the Week, we'll go back to the Skype line and do some Ask Orange Lounge, actually, as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: So here we go, the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why is it, Loki, that we do the FUs every single week?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because we have to.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura would like to say an F you to Drama and Sunburns and the Fast Pass being turned off for Roger Rabbit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki, your F yous of the week.
[SPEAKER_12]: My first F you goes to Audioslave for having this giant concert in the middle of Hollywood and Highland, and that really sucked.
[SPEAKER_12]: And also, fuck you to E3, or mainly just the convention hall, for stopping accepting credit cards after a certain time.
[SPEAKER_12]: and it's like during the middle of lunch rush, they're just like, yeah, we just don't want to do credit cards, we're going to do cash only, of course you don't realize that until after you've gotten your food, so you're fucked if you don't have cash, luckily I, you know, had cash, so that was no problem, and basically also fuck you the Motel 6 for their crappy beds, because they're just uncomfortable as hell, and yeah, that's
[SPEAKER_12]: Fuck you to Rockstar for not actually showing any of their games and wasting a big space in E3.
[SPEAKER_12]: And also to Nintendo for not having a revolution there because I wanted to see that.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_14]: F you to that bitch at Konami's booth, not working there, somebody who was an observer, that said I tried to dig my nails into her over a t-shirt, and she whined and complained like a little baby and got her boyfriend mad at me.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was so stunned that somebody would be so trite that I didn't even know what to say back.
[SPEAKER_14]: But if I could say anything back, I would say something along these lines.
[SPEAKER_14]: Your girlfriend is lying to you about me digging my nails into her.
[SPEAKER_14]: She is making it up.
[SPEAKER_14]: She's probably lying to you about being monogamous with you as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: So screw you, lady and stupid boyfriend.
[SPEAKER_14]: How dare you call me an asshole.
[SPEAKER_14]: I wish my posse was there to beat you up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also, I'd like to give an F you to $8 hamburgers at E3 that aren't even that good.
[SPEAKER_14]: And having to wait in line for 45 minutes, I'm not even kidding, 45 minutes to get a freaking hamburger is horrible.
[SPEAKER_14]: So an F you to the fact that the next two days I had to eat lunch at 10.30 if I wanted to avoid lines.
[SPEAKER_14]: Horrible.
[SPEAKER_14]: And even then we had to wait like, what, 15 minutes for a pizza that one day because I kept dropping them?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, the second day we got pizza, dumb bitch there didn't even understand how to cook pizza, which was quite funny because I loved just watching it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, pulled over as they, like, hit the end and started backing up into the oven But I got my pizza, and thank you to the stupid Mexican bitch Um, she, um, gave me sort of food poisoning, so I had bad gas all day long Thank you, thank you, thank you But the pizza's still good, even though it's doughy Alright, let's go on to the chatroom FUs, shall we?
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually haven't gotten a whole lot of chatroom FUs This might be a short segment tonight, we'll see
[SPEAKER_14]: MPQ says, F you to my wireless mouse.
[SPEAKER_14]: The receiver broke.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now I have this mouse that works perfectly except for the fact that it can't be plugged into the computer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also an F you to Shaza Ambamani style.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're being a retard.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're pissing everyone off.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stop being stupid or go away.
[SPEAKER_14]: I avoid webform drama very much, so I don't know what to tell you on that one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_14]: Next F you comes from Ron Chan.
[SPEAKER_14]: F you to my job for cutting my hours again.
[SPEAKER_14]: Screw you guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to Anamazement this weekend.
[SPEAKER_14]: Miklatov says F you to moving.
[SPEAKER_14]: The end.
[SPEAKER_14]: and Illusion says F you to the never ending star testing that was stretched over this entire month it's still not done F you to In The Groove being pushed back though they say it doesn't have to do with the lawsuit and by they I mean VXJasonXV Illusion if you've been listening earlier in the show I talked to a Red Octane rep and they said it doesn't have anything to do with the lawsuit F you to no cage match oh screw you there is so time left there's an hour left in the show
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know what clock you're looking at, but I see there's 15 minutes left.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank God we're not in that time zone.
[SPEAKER_14]: Crouton6 says, F you to Loki for hating in the groove.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, well, fuck in the groove for sucking.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkKnight says, F you to early morning meetings at work and poor road trip planning.
[SPEAKER_14]: Having to schedule some time off for a racing event that was actually moved to next weekend.
[SPEAKER_14]: And having to work Saturday, missing the cookout of cookouts.
[SPEAKER_14]: Damn you to hell, Job.
[SPEAKER_14]: Raichan says, F you to cheap power supplies that die on Friday the 13th.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ooh, that's a sign.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, the power supplies suck.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's all the F yous we got.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, one more.
[SPEAKER_14]: One late one that just came in.
[SPEAKER_14]: LemonLineJump.
[SPEAKER_14]: F you to myself for making myself sick.
[SPEAKER_14]: I ruined my own Monday.
[SPEAKER_14]: How do you ruin your own Monday?
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um...
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess what we're going to do is do a quick break, then we'll come back and do some Ask Orange Lounge, because I'm sure you guys have some questions after E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: And to make Loki very happy with me, I think what we'll actually do in this break is play some music from In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatever, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we'll be back after this quick break, just a couple songs here, and then we're going to do some Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_14]: So send your questions over to Sky in the chat room, and we'll be back after this.
Come play with me Come play with me Come play with me
Free like a bird in the sky
Play with me!
Come play with me!
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: After this song, we'll be having a Let Them Move marathon.
[SPEAKER_08]: No!
[SPEAKER_14]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Crap-free Bavani Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello, we are back here on Orange Lounge Radio Live, wrapping things up here with a little bit of Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_14]: In that break, you heard some in-the-groove music, Nina with Fly With Me, and Mind Reflection with Remember December.
[SPEAKER_14]: What was that last one?
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a fan favorite, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_14]: I do not care for that song at all, but the fan's
[SPEAKER_14]: Ask me to play it, so I do.
[SPEAKER_14]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I do like the Fly With Me song, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: I do like that one.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just don't like Remember December, personally.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's get into Ask Orange Lounge, where you guys, the listeners, get to control the show by sending us questions, and we answer them.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just that simple.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's really an easy concept, honestly.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_14]: some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_14]: What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_14]: I hope they have some questions to ask us about E3 and not so much random stuff this week because that gets annoying.
[SPEAKER_12]: I like how you add the extra syllable in orange.
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Orange Look, that's the best thing I gotta do by improvising here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, at least you had better grammar than that one distribution company.
[SPEAKER_14]: Crouton6 wants to know, is there any known way to hook up my $400 2DX arcade-style controller to a freaking PS3?
[SPEAKER_14]: If PS3 is backwards compatible, which I believe they have said it will be, PS2 and PS1 backwards compatible, you can bet that there will be some type of converter that will turn one of the USB ports into a regular controller port.
[SPEAKER_14]: Guaranteed.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's got to be something.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, otherwise you can't be backwards compatible, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, yes, you can, because you can still play the old games with the DualShock sort of controllers.
[SPEAKER_12]: But here's the thing, though, what you can do.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know they have this, too, as some sort of Wi-Fi thing you plug into your normal controllers, and it's just like, you know, basically... There'll be a way.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_14]: There'll be a way.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's got to be something.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's why you need to save your old PS2 and don't sell it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Illusion wants to know, were we supposed to set our watches an hour forward daylight savings time?
[SPEAKER_14]: About three weeks ago that happened, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_14]: I believe so.
[SPEAKER_14]: Spring forward, fall back, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, we did that a while ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: What the hell, dude?
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, he says, I wasn't here for the first hour or two hours.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know, I'm lost in time.
[SPEAKER_14]: I really don't know when I came in.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway, can you guys give me a quick summary on what happened?
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, for those of you who joined late, we talked about E3 and what we did.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, actually, no, we can't tell you, but what you can do is you can check into the reruns that we play on DDR Freak Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Friday.
[SPEAKER_14]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nice plug there.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can listen to the Rewind on DDR Freak Radio Friday nights.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just to sum up, we talked Beatmania USA and the DDRs.
[SPEAKER_14]: We played a song that's going to be in DDR Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we gave away a million dollars and you didn't win.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we played the bootleg copy of the new MIDI head mix from Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: And what was that song from Extreme 2?
[SPEAKER_14]: Plovotlian Dance and Chorus?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not even going to try to pronounce it.
[SPEAKER_14]: We played it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dark Knight says, Sky, was the G4 bit with you guys for G4TV.com show or another show?
[SPEAKER_14]: Where you're going to see it, from what I understand, if they even use it, which I don't know, it's G4TV.com, the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: and it's like when they're coming back from commercial they'll probably show the booth and we're clapping and I'm wearing a bright ass green shirt and a t-shirt so you can't miss me and then Loki's standing right next to me and I don't remember what you were wearing that day I don't remember either and Mikotov was standing with us as well so you can see him too I don't remember no I think the last day of war it was like a just a normal shirt but yeah I had a bag an Xbox 360 bag I think I had one too
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_14]: MPQ, should I bother going to Episode 3?
[SPEAKER_14]: Do you think it's worth the trouble?
[SPEAKER_14]: I haven't seen Episode 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not, like, huge on Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_14]: I will see the movie, but I'm going to wait until the frenzy dies down.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, it's worth the trouble, from what I hear.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's what the fans have been looking for.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, and also, in other news, War of the Worlds is supposed to be what people were expecting for Independence Day and Signs.
[SPEAKER_12]: In other words, it's not going to disappoint you.
[SPEAKER_12]: New trailer online, by the way.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_12]: It looks spiffy.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll have to look into that.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_14]: VidPower, on a scale of 1 Sucktastic to 10 Fantastic, rate your overall E3 experience.
[SPEAKER_14]: I give mine a 7.
[SPEAKER_14]: Honestly, I give mine about a 6.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ranchan
[SPEAKER_14]: RonChan says, OK Sky, please explain the ferret because I'm lost.
[SPEAKER_14]: The ferret is basically these little toys that we bought a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: One of them was given to me as a Christmas present years ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: We've been doing Orange Lounge Radio for like three years.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_14]: One of those was given to me like three years ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Jamie found it one show, like it was sitting on my dresser or something, and she started playing with it.
[SPEAKER_14]: And she was giggling and thought it was the cutest thing ever.
[SPEAKER_14]: And she hasn't stopped since.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was like two years ago.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then one day, just to be funny, I bought about six of them.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, I hate you.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I repaired them because they had dead batteries.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I had to cut them open and repair them.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then one of them got stuck on the Katamari.
[SPEAKER_14]: Where did you find...
[SPEAKER_12]: Those people want to buy them.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're not going to find them anywhere.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're called Scoozies is what they're called.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like S-C-U-Z-Z or I-E or Z-I-E.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can find them on eBay.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're kind of expensive.
[SPEAKER_12]: But those are where I found them.
[SPEAKER_12]: I found them at Discount Toy Store.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's basically the discount outlet store for KB.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I bought what was left.
[SPEAKER_12]: And there was hardly anything left.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they were dead.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like Dark Knight's summary there.
[SPEAKER_14]: She uses the ferret to annoy Skye to death.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yep, you got it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yep, you can find them on eBay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, Ron Chan also wants to know, Loki, your favorite Nintendo character?
[SPEAKER_12]: My favorite Nintendo character?
[SPEAKER_12]: Um... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll just say Zelda.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or Link.
[SPEAKER_12]: Link's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't have a really favorite Nintendo character.
[SPEAKER_12]: Unless you want to include... What's his name from...
[SPEAKER_12]: Was it Super Joe from Bionic Commando?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because technically he was on Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_14]: My favorite would be, without a doubt, the Eggplant Wizard, but not from the cartoon.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not the cartoon Eggplant Wizard.
[SPEAKER_14]: That guy was disgusting.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Eggplant Wizard, as portrayed in the original 8-bit Icarus, was awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: If not the Eggplant Wizard, and that's why they need to make a new Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_14]: Please, please, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pretty, pretty please with sugar on top.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_14]: Put it on the DS.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just make me a new one.
[SPEAKER_14]: King Hippo, a close second.
[SPEAKER_14]: KingHippo was a badass.
[SPEAKER_14]: Doobs is asking, what happened with Kingdom Hearts 2?
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it's too late for a question.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, you're not too late for a question.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I did talk about Kingdom Hearts 2 with a previous caller, so I hope you were listening.
[SPEAKER_14]: Again, Kingdom Hearts 2, it's like Kingdom Hearts 1, but with a better camera and Aurons in it, which is very cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it looks like the graphics are upgraded, too.
[SPEAKER_14]: And overdrive mode, or drive mode.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's really amazing, actually, what they've done with that engine, like,
[SPEAKER_12]: and thousands of characters on the screen at one time.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_12]: So yeah, pretty awesome game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Definitely get it when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's all the questions we got tonight for Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, Dubz is confessing he wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_14]: He was gone.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, that was the best part too.
[SPEAKER_12]: You just reminded me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Remember when they were having all the technical issues with...
[SPEAKER_12]: with more friends and the one guitarist from the Black Banjos on the guitar.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: of the animations you see in the video.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which I will be using for my own reference.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: They are in Photoshop format, super high quality.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you want to build a website, get your hands one way or another on a Konami press kit because they've got these great Beatmania concepts.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just the industrial things, the spinning things you see, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what would also be awesome to do with that?
[SPEAKER_12]: To make your own Beatmania skin for Stepmania.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not doing it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I ain't putting that effort in.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's why you see it in there, because they didn't realize that those were not game screenshots, but it's just concept art.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you want to make a Beatmania-themed webpage, seriously, that's exactly what it's for.
[SPEAKER_14]: At least my impression.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, I'm really sad that none of the trailer video is on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Jam with the Band for the Nintendo DS
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't see it anywhere.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't see it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't see it either.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess I didn't show it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Unless I somehow completely missed it, which is possible.
[SPEAKER_12]: We did play a music game on Gizmondo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, what was that Gizmondo music game you played real quick?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was some guitar game.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was like a guitar game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sort of like, I don't even know how to compare it, but it's very, it's like a rhythm music game with action game mixed in it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura actually played it a little more.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe she can fill you in on it next week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't forget to ask.
[SPEAKER_14]: Last, last one real quick.
[SPEAKER_14]: Doobs wants to know, if you didn't talk about this already, what happened with the Katamari?
[SPEAKER_14]: We don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: We imagine they rolled it out the door.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's probably sitting in Namco's big office somewhere.
[SPEAKER_14]: They probably think it's funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: But our media sampler's on it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Our media sampler's on there, and then a few inches away, the ferret.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, so, kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which will have pictures of that online soon, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_14]: It'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'd be curious to know what they are going to do with that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, I did check out my camera and the pictures that it took, and they all suck.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, not much in pretty much everything that we have.
[SPEAKER_12]: That I took a picture of, we have a better copy in the press kit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Jamie said something that she took something like 600 pictures.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's insane.
[SPEAKER_14]: I took like 70 or 80 at most.
[SPEAKER_14]: She took like 600.
[SPEAKER_12]: I took 117, I deleted most of them.
[SPEAKER_14]: The only thing I know how to say is, what are you doing this weekend?
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'm sure that's useful in some sense, but... All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: We've got to wrap up the show, you guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some folks in the chat room are asking about the sex game.
[SPEAKER_14]: They want to hear your story with the sex game.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to have to tell you guys to go to the podcast because it's all in the podcast.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thursday and Friday's edition.
[SPEAKER_12]: Their website, unfortunately, does not have anything about the game or at least it's all in Korean and I couldn't figure it out.
[SPEAKER_12]: I will purchase the game because I actually told Nellie about it and she wanted to play it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Even after I told her about the peripherals.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, we are out of here, you guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: Final thought, Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: I drank too much water.
[SPEAKER_14]: And my final thought is I'm hungry, and I feel like one of those McDonald's fruit and walnut salads for some weird-ass reason.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ice cream would be really good, too, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: I got to eat yogurt.
[SPEAKER_12]: I got this thing of yogurt, and it's getting old.
[SPEAKER_14]: Final word of the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_14]: Have a good one, and we'll see you next week with more Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura will be back.
[SPEAKER_14]: We hope to have guests in the studio as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't forget to check out our podcast and other live shows.
[SPEAKER_14]: There will be a surprise live show this week as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tune in.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe our live general community will have more information on that.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: And tonight's fortune cookie, DarkSakura didn't send me a new one just yet, so you get a classic fortune cookie from our archives that I love.
[SPEAKER_14]: Final word of the show, Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: One word that sums it all up.
[SPEAKER_12]: Beatmania
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sensimia Street?
[SPEAKER_08]: How to get to Sensimia Street?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, Kermit the Frog here, and welcome to Sensimia Street.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd like to tell you what today's letter is, but I am really f***ed up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Big Bird, do you know what today's letter is?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure, Kermit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Today's letter is... Joint.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, Big Bird, joint is not a letter.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is a word.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, kids.
[SPEAKER_05]: Today's letter is three.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm, Big Bird, uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: Three is a number.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: The number three, which is how many joints I've smoked today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kermit, are you with me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank God I'm stoned.
[SPEAKER_05]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guys, guys, show go on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, Elmo.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about we say our ABCs, Big Bird?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: A, B, C, D, E, F, R, G, Q, K, C, R, S, F,
[SPEAKER_05]: I forgot what we were doing, Kramit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you just call me Kramit?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kramity Frog here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all the time we have for today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Goodbye, kids.
[SPEAKER_05]: Today's show was brought to you by the letter... Bong.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the number...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay kids, that's it, we're off to tape our podcast, so those of you guys that are already subscribed to the podcast, if you haven't already, we did like three episodes from LA, so freaking get on your iPod or Doppler or whatever and catch up on the stream, and then we're going to tape a new one tonight as well, so you get lots of podcasts this month, you lucky bastards!
[SPEAKER_14]: And right now though, our live stream, you're going to get dumped from the live stream, but don't be too