[SPEAKER_05]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, you know, typically this week would be the calm before the storm.
[SPEAKER_25]: Very quiet week before E3, when all the companies would announce their new stuff.
[SPEAKER_25]: But boy, we didn't luck out that way this week.
[SPEAKER_25]: I thought I'd be able to nap through tonight's show, but did things just explode this week or what?
[SPEAKER_25]: Just mass hysteria throughout the Bomani community this week.
[SPEAKER_25]: If you've been living under a rock somewhere, I guess we'll have to explain it to you.
[SPEAKER_25]: And it's not just one thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: I realize one thing has been dominating the news this week, but there's more to it than that.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I think that's going to be the running theme tonight.
[SPEAKER_25]: There's more to it than it seems.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the other thing is, I told you.
[SPEAKER_25]: But did you let me know?
[SPEAKER_25]: So there's two themes tonight.
[SPEAKER_25]: Look closer than it seems, and Jamie told you so.
[SPEAKER_25]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge, episode 142, right after this.
[SPEAKER_23]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_09]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_24]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_25]: We are live, and this is episode number 142 for this, May the 15th of 2005.
[SPEAKER_25]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio, radio that gamers really want, and this is Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_25]: Your home for all the news and discussion on rhythm and music games, as well as the gamer community and the pop culture world.
[SPEAKER_25]: We're plugged in and fully interactive through our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_25]: Joining me, as always, are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_25]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm is Jamie Summers, better known as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, everyone!
[SPEAKER_25]: You're very perky tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm such a faker.
[SPEAKER_25]: As opposed to the fucking bitch you were last week.
[SPEAKER_25]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_25]: I just wanted that reaction.
[SPEAKER_25]: Aw, I love you.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know I love you.
[SPEAKER_25]: I loved you.
[SPEAKER_25]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_25]: Look, it's a three-hour show, lady.
[SPEAKER_25]: We got a lot to talk about tonight.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Tech Master Loki on vacation tonight, actually.
[SPEAKER_25]: From what I understand, the woman is making him put out tonight so that he can attend E3 next week.
[SPEAKER_25]: or something like that.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think it's actually not as crude as I put it, but you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think she'd be thanking us for taking him off her hands for a while.
[SPEAKER_25]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_25]: The politically correct version of that story doesn't equal as good ratings.
[SPEAKER_25]: So what's very interesting about tonight's show is that it's just DarkSakura and I. There are no special guests here.
[SPEAKER_25]: Flashback!
[SPEAKER_25]: As of yet, do we still have the folks coming that you were mentioning earlier?
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't have a confirmation.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, we don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't want to go eat at a buffet at the casino.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, that's a good place.
[SPEAKER_25]: So anyway.
[SPEAKER_25]: So it's just going to be DarkSakura and I tonight, feeling the love.
[SPEAKER_25]: Which kind of works out because I know everybody and their mom wants to get on the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because of some news story that was going on.
[SPEAKER_25]: Something about... Something about like...
[SPEAKER_25]: A jaw suit?
[SPEAKER_25]: Or a raw suit?
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_25]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Raw suit!
[SPEAKER_02]: Raw suit up!
[SPEAKER_25]: This is going to be an interesting show tonight.
[SPEAKER_25]: So definitely check out our Skype line, www.orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_25]: Click on Interact with us.
[SPEAKER_25]: And we'll be back after a quick break to talk about many things going on this week, including, you know... That.
[SPEAKER_25]: That.
[SPEAKER_25]: of which we say, you got served.
[SPEAKER_25]: Literally.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bitch, I told you so.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, we'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_25]: In this break, some potpourri.
[SPEAKER_25]: Some potpourri.
[SPEAKER_02]: In frilly pastel colors.
[SPEAKER_25]: And in fact, we're going to have Bimani coexisting with some like one or two in the groove songs.
[SPEAKER_25]: The way some people would like to see it.
[SPEAKER_25]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can't we all just get along?
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll find out.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_25]: Starting off
[SPEAKER_25]: from Keyboard Mania, Sensation I'm feeling a sensation and I gotta go clean up so we'll be back after this
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_17]: My name is Susha.
[SPEAKER_17]: I give you my kiss.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is proud to present a celebrity interview.
[SPEAKER_25]: Can you introduce yourself for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm Miss Cleo.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, it's great to have you on the show today.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hello, how are you today?
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm great, thanks.
[SPEAKER_19]: Did you have a question?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, yes, actually I wanted to know... Can I please have your first name only and your birth date, please?
[SPEAKER_25]: Uh, well, no, I actually just wanted to know what you thought of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, what do you think of Loki, one of the three hosts of Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_19]: Is he incarcerated?
[SPEAKER_25]: Uh, actually, no, he's not.
[SPEAKER_25]: But what do you think of the ever-ranty DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_19]: Hi, dear, how are you?
[SPEAKER_19]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_25]: I see you two must know each other.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, what do you think of Skye?
[SPEAKER_19]: Did he used to play football when he was in high school?
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, actually, no, he didn't.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, what do you think of Intern Zero?
[SPEAKER_19]: I want you to really remember the pill, all right?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm seeing some forgetting, possibly.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I'm seeing a new baby in the next three months.
[SPEAKER_25]: Right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, well, thanks for being on Orange Lounge Radio today.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, I don't mean to sidetrack your question here, but who are all of these nosy people?
[SPEAKER_19]: Outside influences I'm seeing around you by the moon card.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get away from me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio, helping to free your mind and spirit.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm Miss Cleo.
[SPEAKER_19]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_25]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_25]: So, the only thing that's keeping us sane tonight is just acting a little crazy, so you'll have to excuse... I don't know about you.
[SPEAKER_25]: Listen, barnyard.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know if it's just me, but I've been kind of like in a weird funk all week.
[SPEAKER_25]: Why don't I just talk to myself tonight?
[SPEAKER_25]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, well, I don't blame you.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know, tonight is supposed to be the show, we're packing during the show, the Survivor finale's on and I'm having to miss it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You reality TV whore.
[SPEAKER_25]: I know, and don't freaking spoil it for me in the chat room, I swear to God that'll be like an instant ban for life if you spoil it for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody die!
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, everybody die.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hurricane!
[SPEAKER_25]: That's how it ends.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to televise it too.
[SPEAKER_25]: And then Loki's not even here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have enough anger for this show.
[SPEAKER_25]: Petite love.
[SPEAKER_25]: We want ice cream.
[SPEAKER_25]: We have to acknowledge it.
[SPEAKER_25]: We just... We...
[SPEAKER_25]: It was supposed to be that everything is quiet the week before E3, and now just the shit hit the fan.
[SPEAKER_25]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_25]: In so many ways.
[SPEAKER_02]: The shit hitting the fan had excellent timing.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's talk about How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day?
[SPEAKER_25]: We always do start off the show this way.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was a little worried about doing How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day?
[SPEAKER_25]: Because usually we have a studio full of like ten people, and we would have never gotten to the lawsuit stuff.
[SPEAKER_25]: But since it's just you and I, I suppose we have the time.
[SPEAKER_25]: So, How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day?
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, first of all, to be grammatically correct, that would be you and me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, that is one of my grammatical pet peeves.
[SPEAKER_02]: But everybody does it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, my week has been homework, homework, homework, homework, and homework.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been doing two weeks of homework in one week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, I finished... What the fuck did I do?
[SPEAKER_02]: I did, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: My color harmony painting, I finished that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Turned it in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gotta be.
[SPEAKER_25]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I burped off camera.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_02]: I cut out a bunch of pictures for my montage.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still have a few more to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is my final on Monday.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to do fan art as my digital illustration.
[SPEAKER_02]: How cool is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was up until 5am writing a tutorial on how to make live journal icons in PaintShop Pro.
[SPEAKER_02]: My tutorial looks pretty damn good, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Had Adventures at Target at closing time.
[SPEAKER_28]: I went to Rapture on Thursday, which was very fun.
[SPEAKER_28]: Rapture.
[SPEAKER_28]: Not in the blondie sense, this is in the...
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, let's all wear black and listen to industrial music and get very drunk.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a good time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I drank whiskey for the first time in like a year.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Guinness.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guinness and whiskey.
[SPEAKER_02]: Makes me happy, girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just been getting ready for E3, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Getting stuff together, getting crap off my laptop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Went to Fry's today.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought Pulp Fiction on DVD today
[SPEAKER_02]: It was $14 for the special edition, but I already had it on Laserdisc, the four disc set.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I have and watch Laserdiscs, and our Laserdisc player still works.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, and I went to, not Fry's, but to Dimple Records, it's one of the local resale places, you know, used records and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yeah, records are those big discs that are hiding in your parents' garage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't Copy That Floppy
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_25]: I can't even remember our own shows inside jokes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Do not copy the CD!
[SPEAKER_10]: You'll go to hell if you do!
[SPEAKER_25]: The reference I'm making, of course, is to an old Captain Jack CD.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm going to have to find this now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, of course, is funny since you have it copied.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is irony.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also spent the week downloading a bunch of Radiohead and The Bees.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Super Furry Animals, which everybody got to hear at the beginning of my show on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, of course, no show on Tuesday because I will be in a car.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, can't do that.
[SPEAKER_25]: Can I interrupt for one sec?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_25]: Please?
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey folks, this was CG Radio presenting you Captain Jack's Greatest Summer Hits.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keep the spirit, the sun is shining wherever you are And don't forget, copy kills music So, don't copy, buy our records Bye-bye, the party never ends Copy kills music Thank you, Captain Jack Ow, music dead Copied Ironically, that was copied from the original album I can't think of anything else, so I'm just not going to say anything
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm going to caress the ferret.
[SPEAKER_25]: By the way, you need to figure out which ferret is being sacrificed to the giant Katamari at E3, because one of them will be stuck on the Katamari at E3.
[SPEAKER_25]: Get over it.
[SPEAKER_25]: For those of you guys that haven't heard...
[SPEAKER_25]: E3 Catamari Ball X-Rated Clothing
[SPEAKER_25]: Aferit onto the Katamari at E3.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll take a picture and of course post it on the net.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should put business cards on there too.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm putting Reject False Icon stickers on there.
[SPEAKER_25]: And we might put one of our media handouts on there as well.
[SPEAKER_25]: We're set for E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_25]: DarkSakura has twice the business cards she had last year, because she was the only one of us to give away all her business cards by the end of the second day.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I gave away some of yours.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, and she started giving away mine, and I only had like five left.
[SPEAKER_25]: So Jamie now has twice as many cards at least this year.
[SPEAKER_25]: And you know I whore us out.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh yeah, so I'm excited about that.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyway, sorry, um, my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_25]: I played a lot of PSO Blue Burst, because that's in beta right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played that too.
[SPEAKER_25]: And that makes it, yeah, we all played.
[SPEAKER_25]: Me, you, Miklatov, and one of your friends from the Gorillas boards, right?
[SPEAKER_25]: We were all playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, um, well, my character is like super gothy for a while.
[SPEAKER_25]: Ooh, sorry, I just, I really like this thought from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_25]: MPQ is asking, put Ultra Kate on the Katamari.
[SPEAKER_25]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I wanted to do?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: If I have one of those little PDF files of the Prince cutouts, if I can take my X-Acto knife to it, if someone can put it together, we can actually stick the Prince on there.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's install Linux on the Katamari.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_02]: We should put like a big Linux penguin on it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Or as Petra said, put NetBSD.
[SPEAKER_25]: But I think Linux is really the one that, you know... We should put the Linux penguin on it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, chatroom, okay, chatroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, go ahead and PM me with suggestions for what should go on the Katamari.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we'll, uh, we'll, uh...
[SPEAKER_25]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_25]: We have an email address set up so you can send us questions.
[SPEAKER_25]: If you want us to be the investigative reporters and go investigate a game for you and find out some details and bring back or you just have a question about E3 in general or you want a picture with something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_25]: You're going to send us an email and then we will do that and give you the answer on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kalamari on the Katamari.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_25]: We should do a list list tonight even though it's just us.
[SPEAKER_25]: Just us?
[SPEAKER_25]: We could have my roommate participate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you want to participate in the listless tonight?
[SPEAKER_25]: My roommate has no idea what he's in for.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, then we'll have to think of something.
[SPEAKER_25]: But you have to remember... We need to do things to put on the Katamari.
[SPEAKER_25]: Chris, well, see, but Chris, do you even know what Katamari Damashii is, Chris?
[SPEAKER_25]: Um, yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, he does know.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, he does know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do know.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, so then maybe we can do that as a listless later tonight.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll get somebody on Skype, too.
[SPEAKER_25]: In fact, I already have somebody of mine.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll get a special guest on Skype.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can do this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who needs that angry person with his spiky hair and trench coat?
[SPEAKER_25]: He's probably getting laid right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: Crickets, Crickets, Tricks, Tricks
[SPEAKER_25]: But you also took my class ring, which was in a front compartment in the car, and then a Commodore 64 monitor, which I don't know why it was in the backseat.
[SPEAKER_25]: It just was, okay?
[SPEAKER_25]: Just shut up.
[SPEAKER_25]: So, yeah, my car barcode got broken into.
[SPEAKER_25]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know what else sucks is calling the police department to file the report, and then you ask them, have you heard of any others, any other break-ins in the area last night?
[SPEAKER_25]: And they go, well, you know...
[SPEAKER_25]: We're really understaffed right now and I haven't gotten to the messages from last night yet because we're all volunteers here and I'm the only one here.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I'm just like, I feel safe here in lovely California.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially for a complex of this size.
[SPEAKER_25]: No, it's the city.
[SPEAKER_25]: It was the city's police department.
[SPEAKER_25]: The city is staffed by volunteers.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's retarded.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm going to cry.
[SPEAKER_25]: So, by the way, if Orange Launch Radio, if we get shot or something and we die, you'll know why.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because the police is staffed by volunteers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Send all angry letters to Sacramento City PD, blah blah blah, blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyway, that's my week and my day, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_25]: How was your week and your day?
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, great.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's talk about the big news this week.
[SPEAKER_25]: Huge news, let's just get into it.
[SPEAKER_25]: I know a lot of you guys are tuning in tonight because you want to hear our thoughts on it.
[SPEAKER_25]: In case you've been living under a rock or something, I'm going to play for you guys our first news break.
[SPEAKER_25]: We actually did a news break earlier this week because we actually had some new news.
[SPEAKER_25]: So, let's see if I can find it.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm well prepared for this right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: Give me just a minute, guys.
[SPEAKER_25]: We apologize for this technical break.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't, but Rob does.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm all embarrassed and stuff.
[SPEAKER_25]: I thought I had that file ready to go.
[SPEAKER_25]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: The spirit laughed at you.
[SPEAKER_25]: Here was the news break, our very first Orange Lounge Radio news break from earlier this week that tells the story of what's been going on.
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge Radio news break.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sky here with an Orange Lounge Radio news update for this May 11, 2005.
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge Radio has learned that Konami of Japan has filed an injunction against Roxor Games, claiming trademark and patent infringement against Dance Dance Revolution with Roxor's own game, In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_25]: In a press release posted on Konami of Japan's website...
[SPEAKER_25]: Yada, yada, yada, yada.
[SPEAKER_25]: Plug for the website.
[SPEAKER_25]: You're obviously already there.
[SPEAKER_25]: So...
[SPEAKER_25]: That was the first bit of news that came out, is that Konami of Japan put that press release on their site that says, you know, we've finally discovered that there's this game in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_25]: that might be kind of infringing on some of our rights here.
[SPEAKER_02]: At that point, I fell out of my chair.
[SPEAKER_25]: Laughing or what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Laughing my ass off.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: But I want to get your clear thoughts later, because you're not really an in-the-groove hater, because you were just here last week saying, it's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Right?
[SPEAKER_25]: But I was still laughing my ass off.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: And then a little later in the day, actually, what happened over on DDR Freak is that Cutris, one of the admins over there, actually dug up, like, all smoke and gun style, managed to dig up the actual copy of
[SPEAKER_25]: Actual copy, like you would see on thesmokinggun.com when celebrities get busted and stuff.
[SPEAKER_25]: You dug up the actual copy of the injunction.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_25]: Now I could sit here and read the whole damn thing, but it's boring as hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: I read it over on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what did you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, well, being that I did just get out of the business class last semester, a lot of it, you know, see, this is everything that I had pointed out.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are using freaking DDR cabinets, which are a patent of Konami.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had no legal precedent to use it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The thing is that I think where Konami is getting the big issue from this is that with all those other little two bit ones, they're not going to make a whole bunch of money on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not trying to mass market it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's at the point that Endergroove is trying to go to the home market.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think you're hitting on a big thing here, because I know a lot of what I've been reading.
[SPEAKER_25]: And this news just exploded on the internet.
[SPEAKER_25]: I mean, god, the DDR Freak thread hit like 300 posts in a day.
[SPEAKER_25]: It was insane.
[SPEAKER_25]: They're lit up.
[SPEAKER_25]: The boards are lit up.
[SPEAKER_25]: And people are going, go Konami, go!
[SPEAKER_25]: And then people are saying, you know, fuck Konami for killing in the groove.
[SPEAKER_25]: And people are saying, boycott Konami!
[SPEAKER_25]: And people are saying, boycott the boycotters!
[SPEAKER_25]: And it's just very polarizing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I boycott you!
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: So I decided to boycott the thread.
[SPEAKER_25]: No, actually I didn't.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's like my soap opera.
[SPEAKER_25]: I've been checking it every day.
[SPEAKER_25]: Every day, religiously, like every hour on the hour for updates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next on As the Arrow Flies.
[SPEAKER_25]: I mean, as Jamie said earlier in the show, I'm a reality TV whore.
[SPEAKER_25]: This is as good as it gets.
[SPEAKER_25]: Which company is going to get voted off the planet?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the thing that I really liked is that when they were speaking of the cabinet, they pulled up the full schematics of the damn cabinet and outlined each point and how each point is particular specifically to an EDR machine, which is why I think that there wasn't an issue with the pump-it-up machines because they were different enough to bypass EDR.
[SPEAKER_25]: Here's the interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: You've brought up a couple points I really want to emphasize because I feel very similar.
[SPEAKER_25]: A lot of people, when this news first came out, said, STFU, before the documents came out, people were saying, shut the F up.
[SPEAKER_25]: This has nothing to do with the home version.
[SPEAKER_25]: The home version release will not be affected by this.
[SPEAKER_25]: This is strictly about the arcade, and this is only going to affect In the Groove arcade cabinets, and it will have nothing to do with In the Groove 2 because this is all about In the Groove 1.
[SPEAKER_25]: I say wrong.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'd say this has everything to do with the home version.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're putting this out right before they're getting the releases done.
[SPEAKER_25]: The timing is crazy.
[SPEAKER_25]: I mean, really, at first, the timing of this almost makes it look like Konami has Rockstar by the balls right now, basically, with the In the Groove home release coming out.
[SPEAKER_25]: Poor Red Octane, really, who kind of is caught in the middle of this now.
[SPEAKER_25]: Nowhere named in the lawsuit, but, you know, all this money invested in a last-bush premiere party.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: So they've got Rockstar by the balls right now, just before E3 when this is supposed to be unveiled.
[SPEAKER_25]: Obviously, probably what they're trying to do is get this to settle out of court, which I can say with probably 98% certainty will probably happen.
[SPEAKER_25]: I can't honestly see this going to court.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm wondering, though, with such a small company, Rockstar's basically just getting off the ground.
[SPEAKER_25]: Where are they going to get the kind of money to... They have that other game, Tux Racer or something, but who'd have heard of that before this?
[SPEAKER_25]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I said, just getting off the ground.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other thing, you know, is that they could be sitting on perhaps, you know... And this is speculation.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been trying to think of all kinds of things that might be the background motive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because basically, Konami of America is pulled out of the arcade market as far as EDR is concerned.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't necessarily mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: that the powers that be at the main place in Japan might not be thinking, hey, we can market over there too.
[SPEAKER_25]: What do you think about this argument that's coming from a lot?
[SPEAKER_25]: And I'm kind of trying hard not to take sides here because I respect what In The Groove tried to do.
[SPEAKER_25]: It tried to revive a dying arcade dance scene and it was put together by fans.
[SPEAKER_25]: But
[SPEAKER_25]: So I respect the game for that.
[SPEAKER_25]: And even though I've said negative things about the game before, I've also said positive things about the game.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I've always said In the Groove is a great first release.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's not as bad as the haters say, but it's not as good as the people who lavish praise upon it say.
[SPEAKER_25]: There's room for improvement, but they have some great ideas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Opinions are opinions.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I respect what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_25]: But this honestly doesn't come as any surprise to me.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think, unfortunately, I can't say so much about the staff, the folks there.
[SPEAKER_25]: But at least the community has been very arrogant.
[SPEAKER_25]: Very arrogant ever since the release of In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know, people have asked, is this legal?
[SPEAKER_25]: And people say, yes it is.
[SPEAKER_25]: Shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_25]: Lock.
[SPEAKER_02]: That has put me off.
[SPEAKER_25]: much more than the game itself that attitude put me off so bad and that's why I can't help but kind of grin a little bit that this is happening and I'm sorry and I apologize to the folks that have worked so hard on this game but that arrogance that such ass arrogance
[SPEAKER_25]: To see that get called out to the bike racks three o'clock after school is satisfying.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to be quoted on this on every last single in the groove board that those assholes post on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I fucking term all of you.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, you're not the only one that told me this would happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, but I have ego, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I told you!
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can stick your nose up in the air as much as you want to, but it's going to be shaved off by the low-flying airplane that is Konami.
[SPEAKER_25]: We can say I told you so on a million things.
[SPEAKER_25]: Now, I know I said, at least a couple months ago on the show, when Red Octane first announced they were going to publish in the groove for home, I said, Konami's going to notice.
[SPEAKER_25]: Didn't I say something like that?
[SPEAKER_25]: I said, if Konami's going to make a move, now's the time.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because in the groove is now...
[SPEAKER_25]: Steppin' on Konami's turf.
[SPEAKER_25]: Konami, obviously, even though people say Konami does shit for their fans, they do shit for DDR, that's a load of crap.
[SPEAKER_25]: When you consider that there are three DDR games, not one, not two, three, more games than we've ever seen at E3 are going to be shown next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can name a person who has worked his ass off for all of the US fans of DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I honestly have to give big kudos to Jason Enos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Without him, we would still be paying, you know, 70 bucks to import the damn game and 80 bucks per dance pad.
[SPEAKER_02]: And instead, now we get unique mixes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Japanese players are importing our mixes.
[SPEAKER_25]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now it's the other way around.
[SPEAKER_25]: And really, Festival, it's some, you know, this is debatable, but Festival in some ways was a copy of Ultramix, which was made here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now the market belongs to us.
[SPEAKER_25]: I say bullshit.
[SPEAKER_25]: Konami doesn't care about their American audience.
[SPEAKER_25]: Now, okay, granted you've got the arcade scene, and yes, the arcade scene was hurting.
[SPEAKER_25]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_25]: But, somebody phrased it this way on a web board or something, and it does make sense, is that if Konami and Andomero settled out of court, neither one has to say what the terms of that settlement were.
[SPEAKER_25]: Although, I'll tell you what, and so maybe, maybe, maybe that was part of the settlement.
[SPEAKER_25]: But we don't know for sure.
[SPEAKER_25]: And it really, it looks like Konami got the better end of the deal, because if you look at the press release on Konami's site, now granted it's spun by Konami...
[SPEAKER_25]: It says that Andamiro actually ended up paying them.
[SPEAKER_25]: So I find it very hard to believe that it's Andamiro keeping Konami out of the U.S.
[SPEAKER_25]: arcade market.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think it's just the fact that the U.S.
[SPEAKER_25]: arcade market kind of stinks right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, on top of that, they closed down their arcade division.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, but they still have put out silent scopes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_25]: If they really wanted to do it, they could, but it would have to be something where
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know, the cost has to be justified.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I've said this on an earlier show, and I still stick by this.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think the reason why you see Xtreme in arcades, and Konami kind of turns its back on it, even though it's not supposed to be in the US, I think the reason why you see it in the arcades is because, hey, licensing music in the US is a whole lot more difficult than it is in Japan.
[SPEAKER_25]: The folks in Japan don't care.
[SPEAKER_25]: You've got all these bands, Captain Jack, for the more recent games, with all the folks on Dance Mania, Wildside, whatever, that would never have been heard in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_25]: if it wasn't for DDR.
[SPEAKER_25]: So none of them care.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had that big agreement with Toshiba EMI.
[SPEAKER_25]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_25]: And so I think Konami kind of turns its back because it's cheaper to just let folks bring it over here and then make money off the home releases.
[SPEAKER_02]: All that is, is publicity.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they were going to be imported anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how I see it.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's also a very interesting point you bring up, is about the publicity.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because people say, well if Konami doesn't give a shit about the arcade machines anymore, then why is this such a big deal?
[SPEAKER_25]: Publicity is the big thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because if you consider that what Indigroove was in its first release, what Indigroove was, was a conversion kit that would allow you to change a DDR machine into an Indigroove machine.
[SPEAKER_25]: Theoretically, what they would want to do, you have to admit, this is a goal of RockSource in the end, is that they want every DDR machine changed into an in-the-groove machine.
[SPEAKER_25]: Thusly, DDR has no exposure and no presence in the arcades anymore.
[SPEAKER_25]: Thusly, there's no free advertising for the home releases.
[SPEAKER_25]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_25]: Even though DDR Extreme is two years old, people still play it all the time.
[SPEAKER_25]: It is still huge exposure for Konami.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, this is the equivalent of saying that you're wearing a t-shirt that advertises one thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the equivalent of Rockstar coming up and spray painting the t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can't see the logo.
[SPEAKER_25]: And a lot of people...
[SPEAKER_25]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, I was going to say something about In The Groove and the community and what people say.
[SPEAKER_02]: In The Groove community, you should all pile together and give me a dollar each.
[SPEAKER_25]: Damn, I lost my train of thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: Derail!
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's look over some key quotes.
[SPEAKER_25]: Quote, according to instructions provided with Defendants in the game Groove Kits, the purchaser is instructed to remove the original main circuit board from the DDR game and replace it with Defendants in the Groove game circuit board.
[SPEAKER_25]: So that's one of the big things they're hitting on, of course, is the fact that, and people were kind of wondering...
[SPEAKER_25]: How's Konami going to get Rockstar on this?
[SPEAKER_25]: And then it came down to the hardware thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I think hardware versus software is a huge issue here.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because I know we had the in-the-groove scene always going, it's legal, it's legal, it's legal.
[SPEAKER_25]: Unfortunately, I think they were more concerned with the software end of it.
[SPEAKER_25]: And the software part of it probably is legal, because you'd barely see it mentioned in the lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_25]: But the hardware part of it... Whoops.
[SPEAKER_25]: So...
[SPEAKER_25]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_25]: Defendant provides materials bearing its own name and or trademarks to purchasers of the In the Groove game to be placed over the plaintiff's marks and other identifying material on the DDR game.
[SPEAKER_25]: On information and belief, purchasers fail to cover plaintiff's marks and or other identifying material in all instances.
[SPEAKER_25]: The In the Groove game, as refitted by purchasers, therefore displays both plaintiff's marks and defendant's name and or trademarks.
[SPEAKER_25]: And a lot of people say in the scene here, they say...
[SPEAKER_25]: How can you confuse DDR and In The Groove?
[SPEAKER_25]: They're so different.
[SPEAKER_25]: And to which I say, it's not all about you.
[SPEAKER_25]: We are a small part.
[SPEAKER_25]: We're a loyal part.
[SPEAKER_25]: We're an essential part.
[SPEAKER_25]: But we're a small part of the dance game music scene.
[SPEAKER_25]: We really are.
[SPEAKER_25]: As I was talking about last week, when we were talking about Oops I Did It Again being on DDR Extreme 2, the reason why that's there is not for you.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's for the 10-year-old girls having slumber parties.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_25]: So it is the normal person who is having a birthday party in an arcade that doesn't know the difference any better between one machine to another does think that that game is DDR.
[SPEAKER_25]: Case in point, you might remember that our very own Loki, and, you know, even though this was questionable, whatever, actually installed, like, a Stepmania thing in a cabinet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Now, he didn't make money off of it, which is probably why, you know, everything, you know, and it was only one machine, so, you know, everything...
[SPEAKER_25]: Whatever, and it's gone now, so it doesn't matter But he installed Stepmania, and it was re-skinned And it had the mines, because it was the newer version of Stepmania It was different, and he put it up and running And we all went to Roseville Golf Land one day to check it out And I overheard some girl that just looked like she was there She said to some person that was there, yeah, this is the new DDR, let's go play it It wasn't the new DDR, it looked like DDR though
[SPEAKER_25]: and it had DDR written on the machine still because they had been too lazy to put the new marquee up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know the other thing that I was thinking that Konami needs to really watch out for is the acronym DDR and Dance Dance Revolution becoming a generic term.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the 80s, I'm going to use this as an example, Xerox released an ad that said something to the effect of Xerox is not a generic term
[SPEAKER_02]: Make sure that you're only using Xerox products when you say, I'm going to Xerox something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if someone says, I'm going to Xerox something, they're thinking, oh, you're just going to go over to the copy machine, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, the term refrigerator was actually a brand name, and now it's a generic term.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Frigidaire, that actually has become a household generic.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just all, you know, Weedeater, that's now a generic.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, we...
[SPEAKER_02]: Think of our dancing games, and the first thing that we all think of now is DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think that what it is, another point is that they may not want the average player to confuse in the group with DDR, to have it become a generic.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's a very interesting point, and I don't think I've seen that point brought up anywhere yet.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because...
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, there were quite a few lawsuits concerning generics that people have actually lost.
[SPEAKER_25]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oreo, Kleenex, Band-Aid, Aspirin, Coke, Trojan.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know about Trojan, but the rest of them work.
[SPEAKER_25]: Thank you guys in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aspirin was, that's correct, I think, cicatrice, aspirin was a trademark before World War II.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, okay, another one, you know, Motrin.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now we think of that for ibuprofen.
[SPEAKER_02]: so many things that we consider they were individual brandings before DDR is easily going on that path because we think what's the first thing that you're going to think of when someone starts naming off different dancing games the average person is going to go back and think DDR because that is where it all came from
[SPEAKER_25]: NeonFM NeonFM
[SPEAKER_25]: It's like comparing Sonic to Mario.
[SPEAKER_25]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_25]: And I'm like, no.
[SPEAKER_25]: I beg to differ.
[SPEAKER_25]: This is like comparing Mario to Gianna Sisters.
[SPEAKER_25]: And for those of you that don't know what Gianna Sisters was, it was a game that came out on the Commodore 64 in, I think, 88 or so, a couple years after Mario was out.
[SPEAKER_25]: And it was very much like Mario, except they changed it to girls.
[SPEAKER_25]: But this is the thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: This is the irony.
[SPEAKER_25]: The music was better in Gianna Sisters.
[SPEAKER_25]: Gianna Sisters had slightly new elements, but it still had things that looked like Goombas, and still had things that looked like Turtles, and you still got mushroom-like power-ups.
[SPEAKER_25]: Gianna Sisters lost and got pulled from the market.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another point, Pac-Man and Casey Crazy Chase.
[SPEAKER_25]: Or Casey Munchkin.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it was Casey Crazy Chase.
[SPEAKER_25]: I thought it was Casey Munchkin.
[SPEAKER_02]: For people who don't know, there was a system that came out in the early 80s called the Odyssey 2, which I own one,
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have a TV to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there was a game that came out called Casey Crazy Chase.
[SPEAKER_02]: And basically it was freaking Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just, you know, really crappy graphics because they didn't have a way to do graphics exactly the same as they were in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, not like today where home games are better.
[SPEAKER_02]: But still, you know, now they actually pulled a bunch of copies and destroyed them.
[SPEAKER_02]: so that's why if you happen to see an Odyssey 2 cartridge for KC Crazy Chase I suggest you buy it because that would be holding a piece of gaming rarity right there very interesting one of the resolution pieces that Konami wants is they want these things destroyed yep
[SPEAKER_25]: So if in the groove home version comes out, buy it right away.
[SPEAKER_25]: No matter how you feel about the game, buy it right away because it could.
[SPEAKER_25]: We don't know how this is going to affect the home version, but I do want to point this out because a lot of people are saying this is not going to affect the release of the home version.
[SPEAKER_25]: I beg to differ.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think this thing is going to get delayed if nothing else.
[SPEAKER_25]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_25]: Granted, as somebody pointed out to me this week when I had a really big ego and I was like, I called this, I called this.
[SPEAKER_25]: When they released the home version, they were going to get sued.
[SPEAKER_25]: Somebody said, Rob, you also said that in the Groove Home version was No Way in Hell ever coming out.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was like, okay, good point.
[SPEAKER_25]: So if this does come out, it would be interesting, but I could almost say with certainty this has to get delayed, at least.
[SPEAKER_25]: Red Octane has got to be scared a little bit right now, or at least waiting to see what comes next.
[SPEAKER_02]: If anybody is, I actually would love to get a statement, an official statement from the folks at Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't we all?
[SPEAKER_25]: The official statement, if you go into the Indigroove forums right now, is a locked thread where somebody said, what's with this lawsuit?
[SPEAKER_25]: And somebody basically said, we have no comment at this time, we are not discussing legal issues on this forum, all further posts on this will be deleted.
[SPEAKER_25]: Not locked, deleted.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm paraphrasing there, that's not the exact quote.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then apparently their attorney has called for silence prior to... Well, probably they don't know what to do.
[SPEAKER_25]: Remember, the folks that worked on this game... Now, granted, Rockstar Games has been in this a little while before, but with what?
[SPEAKER_25]: They're a small-scale company.
[SPEAKER_25]: The folks that made In the Groove were DDR fans to begin with.
[SPEAKER_25]: They don't know what the hell they've gotten themselves into.
[SPEAKER_02]: This has kind of got to be a slap in the face to them, too.
[SPEAKER_25]: They'll never play DDR again, granted, I would assume.
[SPEAKER_25]: But at the same time...
[SPEAKER_25]: You're paying for that arrogance.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_25]: Maybe not necessarily the staff, but you didn't discipline the scene.
[SPEAKER_25]: And the scene has been incredibly arrogant with this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do a little radio station.
[SPEAKER_02]: How much research did I put in to see if Originals was copyrighted in the States?
[SPEAKER_02]: I did the research for our name.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are they going to get away with not doing any research prior to making the product?
[SPEAKER_02]: That is just good business.
[SPEAKER_25]: Konami also knows about us and they don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but we also do good things for Konami.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, we do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: But... You know, we talk about them negatively sometimes, but it's fair.
[SPEAKER_25]: Everything's fair, I think, and we do.
[SPEAKER_25]: We try to bring you both sides of the story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, but on top of that, how could they have not, you know, a little bit of homework?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it shouldn't have even required the homework.
[SPEAKER_02]: They should have known.
[SPEAKER_02]: There were patents out and copyrights not just for the game itself, you know, for content.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was for concept.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was for the hardware.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was for everything else involved with it, marketing.
[SPEAKER_25]: The weird thing is, is there was this giant assumption in the scene that Andamiro held that patent.
[SPEAKER_25]: But that was proven wrong when Cutress posted those documents that clearly show a U.S.
[SPEAKER_25]: patent for the machine, the sensors, the screen, even though the screen looked a little different.
[SPEAKER_25]: Everything has a U.S.
[SPEAKER_25]: patent by Konami, not Andamiro, Konami.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no, you know, and if they had done their homework, they would have found that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually, there are online patent registries where they would actually have the name, the hardware, everything, you can find that all online.
[SPEAKER_02]: For the, what's the patent office?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to think what the... What handles, I'll find it out later.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll see if I can't get it online.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would have just taken, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no mercy to people who do stupid stuff.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's their first time.
[SPEAKER_25]: This whole thing, think about it.
[SPEAKER_25]: You've created this game from the ground up and suddenly somebody wants to buy it, put it in arcades, release it on the PS2, all in the scope of a year.
[SPEAKER_25]: Heads are spinning at the folks who created this game right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know, we all make dumb mistakes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still don't think it's excusable.
[SPEAKER_02]: On top of that, this lawsuit would be on Red Octane's head.
[SPEAKER_02]: Red Octane should have known better.
[SPEAKER_02]: They should have known better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seeing as how they market the actual physical dance pads, the games, they should have known.
[SPEAKER_02]: But software versus hardware.
[SPEAKER_25]: The lawsuit's not really about... It is and it isn't about the software.
[SPEAKER_25]: The lawsuit's specifically not about the software, but I say it's being done in response to the software.
[SPEAKER_25]: So I think Red Octane probably...
[SPEAKER_25]: And they're probably right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Had the hardware not been all screwy the way that In the Groove became in arcades, it probably would have been okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: So I can't fault them.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only way that they're going to get around at least any future arcade releases, sorry, they're going to have to build themselves a new cabinet and change their interface.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: Our chat room is saying shut up already.
[SPEAKER_25]: We're getting confused.
[SPEAKER_25]: There's too much chat going on.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Get over it first off.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, so what happens next?
[SPEAKER_25]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_25]: What's your predicted resolution of what will happen?
[SPEAKER_02]: The injunction is going to stay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this is how ideally it should go.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm thinking, I'm going to do this from the Konami standpoint, and then I'm going to do it from the Roxborough standpoint.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ideally for Konami, the home release of In the Groove will not happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: The injunction will stay, because part of this injunction right now is to protect their interest before there is a court case.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to cease production.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now,
[SPEAKER_02]: I also think that they are going to have to pay X amount of dollar for every in-the-groove kit sold.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they can actually assess punitive damages as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which are basically like being spanked.
[SPEAKER_02]: You did a bad thing, we're going to spank you now.
[SPEAKER_02]: They also have the right to assess profits lost.
[SPEAKER_02]: As in any, because these are full Japanese machines.
[SPEAKER_02]: Konami of Japan has lost money.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's essentially how it is, because these machines have to be paid for.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, but these machines aren't supposed to be, quote unquote, in the U.S., so what happens there?
[SPEAKER_25]: That's kind of a gray area.
[SPEAKER_25]: Could be Rockstar Saving Grace, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: That could be, but also, again, as these machines are publicity, that may have cost them in sales of the home versions.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and again, I'm thinking from a legal standpoint, this might be what they can get away with.
[SPEAKER_02]: The software may be permissible, given that it was built from the ground up.
[SPEAKER_02]: This also has to do with a little bit of trade secret, but it would have to be proven through some type of reverse engineering that the home software is not a complete duplicate of
[SPEAKER_02]: of DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they pull that off, the home release will still happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, they're not going to make it out with the hardware issue.
[SPEAKER_02]: They, I think, can get away with releasing future editions.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are going to have to create a unique cabinet and the boards and sell them as a joint unit, the way that Pump It Up goes.
[SPEAKER_25]: Any future releases will have to continue to use that platform only and be upgrades for that unit only.
[SPEAKER_25]: That is the only way that they're going to be able to continue to release any arcade releases.
[SPEAKER_02]: For the first one, I'm sorry, they're fucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to have to pay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this could ruin them.
[SPEAKER_02]: This seriously could financially ruin them.
[SPEAKER_02]: This could also, however, put them in a more public light.
[SPEAKER_02]: A negative event can turn into positive publicity.
[SPEAKER_25]: That is a very interesting side point is that a negative event can be publicity.
[SPEAKER_25]: This whole thing could be publicity for them.
[SPEAKER_25]: Although, when you look out on the big gaming websites, it's not...
[SPEAKER_25]: That huge deal.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think most game sites ran a little side story on it, but no major things.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if they are permitted to release the home version, if they are permitted to go through within the group too, with this little bit of controversy going on... Example, Madonna's sex book.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the first thing that came to my mind.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: The book was banned.
[SPEAKER_02]: She was sued.
[SPEAKER_02]: All this crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: And how popular did that make her?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to compare the groove to Madonna.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is funny.
[SPEAKER_25]: Get into the groove, boy, you've got to prove.
[SPEAKER_25]: I still think of that song every time I see it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that song is public domain now.
[SPEAKER_25]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm kind of similar to your thoughts on this.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because I think this lawsuit is a direct response to the home release, I think that the home release, and I could be wrong, I think the home release will be affected.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't think this is going to go to court.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think Rockstar and Konami are going to settle.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I think as part of the terms, they're going to recall, but I doubt any of them will be recalled, really.
[SPEAKER_25]: They're going to recall the box or kits or whatever.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think that In The Groove will be stopped.
[SPEAKER_25]: or delayed heavily and Konami will be given a chunk of the profit from the game and I think also as part of it I bet you anything they're going to have to settle where they can't really market the game it's going to have to come out quietly but who knows I might just be thinking crazy but I think that's probably what's going to happen I think though this is my other crazy prediction now tape me in case I'm right I think In The Groove 2 will still come out in arcades under a new name I don't think it'll be called In The Groove 2 anymore
[SPEAKER_02]: There's also the other thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Konami could obtain any rights to the In the Groove franchise.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's also that.
[SPEAKER_20]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: And therefore, again, receive a percentage of the profits.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't want to talk about the lawsuit right now anymore.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm done with my side of the story.
[SPEAKER_25]: Honestly, when all is said and done, I just...
[SPEAKER_25]: Let the courts figure it out.
[SPEAKER_25]: We're all trying to be lawyers right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: The truth is, we don't really know everything going on because we're not behind the closed doors right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: We don't know what Rakshasa's side of the case is, so we can't really make judgments.
[SPEAKER_25]: But I want to kind of close this segment with this thought.
[SPEAKER_25]: Those of you guys that are saying boycott Konami over this, shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_25]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_25]: There would have been no In The Groove if it wasn't for DDR.
[SPEAKER_25]: I mean, that is a case in point.
[SPEAKER_25]: Absolutely, they would never have been in the group if it wasn't for DDR.
[SPEAKER_25]: Konami has not abandoned their US audience.
[SPEAKER_25]: Konami of Japan?
[SPEAKER_25]: Eh, maybe.
[SPEAKER_25]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_25]: People in Konami of America are working their ass off to bring you three new games at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_25]: Seriously, shut up.
[SPEAKER_25]: Boycotting Konami is not going to do anything.
[SPEAKER_25]: Honestly, go ahead and boycott.
[SPEAKER_25]: Get off my machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: The five of you who would be boycotting this, you're not going to make a dent.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, it's not going to work.
[SPEAKER_25]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_25]: We're probably just adding fuel to their fire.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_25]: You're a little boycott.
[SPEAKER_25]: You have no respect for where you got your game from.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so if they do some stupid little boycott...
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just going to open the door.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, well, I need to see what this is.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're helping.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know, honestly, if you want to make a point, get the hell off the DDR boards and start one for In the Groove 2.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because I think In the Groove 2 will happen under a new name.
[SPEAKER_25]: So go figure that one out.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should go back to Spider Stomp.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get out your power pad, play some Dance Aerobics.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll be back after this break.
[SPEAKER_25]: Your calls on this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: Your calls on the whole thing when we come back after this.
S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
DarkSakura
Thanks for watching!
We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: TAC ElectroTunes
[SPEAKER_25]: Whatever, TakuTak, same to me.
[SPEAKER_25]: Rio and StarMind, sorry that's it off.
[SPEAKER_25]: We're going to go right into taking calls on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_25]: If you want more information, www.OrangeLoungeRadio.com Click on Interact With Us and get the more information on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yes, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I'm just marveling at how delicious this black cherry soda is.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, let's get to our first call.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hello, caller, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_25]: Boo, who's this?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, don't play dumb, Rob.
[SPEAKER_25]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_25]: Not too bad.
[SPEAKER_25]: How about you?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, my brain has been broken and repaired several times trying to go through that thread.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've sworn off posting it a couple of times and then ended up having to come back to correct people yet again.
[SPEAKER_25]: How many warning points would you say you've given out in that thread?
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, I think I've only dished out two different warnings and one of them somebody is complaining about incessantly because he says that it wasn't merited at all.
[SPEAKER_21]: He said that basically the reason the lawsuit existed was
[SPEAKER_21]: was that they were about to put out a new arcade version and that he saw something about it in a California arcade, somebody showing him pictures on a laptop.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I'm just like, how exactly do you think that's legitimate?
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, that's a little weird.
[SPEAKER_25]: Or it kind of goes back to, and somebody had called in, I don't remember if it was last week or the week before, talking about somebody had posted in their live journal that, I don't know, their uncle's sister's brother had posted something about the new machine is coming out for sure this year.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think that was Cucumber.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think he said they were gearing up for a location test in September.
[SPEAKER_25]: No offense against the dude, but I mean, why should I believe him?
[SPEAKER_25]: I guess is what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_25]: I mean, no offense, but why should I believe him?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I don't really have any idea what kind of trust he gets in the community, although nobody seems to have been debunking it over at Aaron in Japan where everyone's elite.
[SPEAKER_21]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_25]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_25]: So what are your thoughts on this whole thing?
[SPEAKER_25]: I remember that you were the one that actually dug up what really happened.
[SPEAKER_25]: What did you think as you were reading it all?
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I guess I have a little bit of an interest in it to begin with because I've kind of taken it as a personal cause to be debunking all of these rumors with the history of the series and everything.
[SPEAKER_25]: That Andamiro, those Andamiro's rumors and stuff?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: They bug the hell out of me.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I just...
[SPEAKER_21]: I really can't believe that people would think that as part of settling a lawsuit where you have the upper hand that you would offer to back out of the business market and not go back.
[SPEAKER_25]: Exactly, exactly.
[SPEAKER_25]: So what do you think is going to happen of this whole thing?
[SPEAKER_25]: Do you think Konami has Rockstar's nuts here or what do you think might happen as of this?
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I could see it going a couple of different ways.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think the
[SPEAKER_21]: The odds are definitely not in Roxor's favor, but this happens to be one special case.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm not generally the sort of person that seems to be privy to inside information or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Usually I'm always hearing about things after the fact.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not only was I happy to find out about this before anyone else, since I got word directly from ZipTie over at Konami, but basically...
[SPEAKER_21]: There's a couple of things that we've learned which could end up turning this entire thing on its ear.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I wouldn't have any preconceived notions with regards to how this is going to go.
[SPEAKER_21]: All the fanboys need to die right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: If I'm hearing you right, you say that there are things that we don't know about that could turn this whole thing upside down.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, and I'm not saying it's going to tilt it in any one direction or the other.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's just... Well, basically, it's going to end up being the equivalent, I think, of somebody running in the courtroom and saying, Konami, I am your father.
[SPEAKER_25]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: No!
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not possible!
[SPEAKER_21]: Which is basically the same thing I say about all the In The Groove fanboys that want to disown In The Groove from DDR.
[SPEAKER_21]: Basically, Konami just comes over and says, No, Rocksaur, I am your father.
[SPEAKER_25]: And that's exactly what I was saying about those people that are like, Oh my god, let's boycott Konami because they're evil assholes and da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know, if someone stole your shit and then repainted it a different color and put it out, you'd probably be pretty pissed off too.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know, even if you...
[SPEAKER_25]: I think you've even said something along the lines before about how with the community
[SPEAKER_21]: It's DDR when it's convenient, and it's not DDR when it's convenient
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to completely underscore something you said earlier.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just to make this clear.
[SPEAKER_24]: Good, that'll make me feel good.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have not had a chance to play in the groove yet.
[SPEAKER_21]: I am very much looking forward to my chance.
[SPEAKER_21]: It looks really nice to me.
[SPEAKER_21]: I saw some people playing it at Anime Boston last month when I was in town for that, and it looks very slick.
[SPEAKER_21]: It has some very good production quality.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think that all the new modifiers and everything, yeah, they're step mania, but give me a bit.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think it's something that DDR has needed for a while.
[SPEAKER_21]: Basically it expands on DDR quite a bit and I really appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think it's really nice to carry the torch for the series.
[SPEAKER_21]: The only thing that's ever really stopped me from having any serious interest in the game is the community.
[SPEAKER_21]: There are some really good people there.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've talked to several of the Rocksware employees and do talk to them on a regular basis and they're really great guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just
[SPEAKER_21]: There are some people in the community that just really need their sticks pulled out of their ass.
[SPEAKER_25]: Their representation on the internet sucks, sadly, for them.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because I'll tell you, at that in-the-group, I was kind of wincing walking in the door of that in-the-group premiere party because I thought people were going to beat me down with sticks.
[SPEAKER_25]: But then I realized nobody listens to this show, so I was okay with it.
[SPEAKER_25]: But I still thought that I was going to be confronted with just extreme asshole-ism.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I can definitely understand that.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, there's...
[SPEAKER_21]: I think part of the problem is just that the people that are really big fans of In The Groove these days are in some ways really resentful of Konami for having, quote-unquote, abandoned them.
[SPEAKER_21]: And so now they're being rebellious teenagers, if it were.
[SPEAKER_25]: Do you think that that might be more fuel on this boycott fire, where if they feel abandoned by Konami, and now for Konami to suddenly go, wait a minute, even though I abandoned you, I'm going to sue this other game that's come out?
[SPEAKER_21]: Why do people completely ignore the home versions?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, there's no bar to raise.
[SPEAKER_25]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_25]: Although, I swear to God, Red Octane is thinking about doing one.
[SPEAKER_25]: They're trying to see how they can do one at a good price.
[SPEAKER_25]: I mean, they're going to have to to support in the groove.
[SPEAKER_25]: Your groove bar, 2.0.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I'm really glad that they're adding the novice system to the home version because that is something that appears to be greatly neglected.
[SPEAKER_21]: I haven't looked over a lot of the step charts myself.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I did get the impression that not a whole lot of pain was put into making of the light and standard steps.
[SPEAKER_21]: Forgive me for not remembering the correct difficulty specifiers here.
[SPEAKER_21]: But basically that's something that I know personally the step authors for Ultramix 2 put a lot of effort into.
[SPEAKER_21]: They wanted to make sure that it was going to be fun to dance and play regardless of what level you're on.
[SPEAKER_21]: There are quite a few songs I can think of on Trick, which are perfectly fun to play, and I don't have to be doing a 7 or 8 foot.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think a lot of the reason, too, that the Ultramix 2 steps were so darn good was because Ultramix 1 really screwed some steps up, especially when it came to the song packs.
[SPEAKER_25]: So I think they really learned from their mistakes, and they almost overcompensated the steps were so damn good.
[SPEAKER_25]: I mean, really.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, not a whole lot wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_25]: No, we all win from that, I guess.
[SPEAKER_25]: So I guess it's going to be a very interesting E3.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know if Rockstar is one.
[SPEAKER_25]: I haven't checked the E3 list, but I'm sure Red Octane is one of the scheduled exhibitors.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_25]: I want to go by their booth Wednesday morning and see if there's any mention of In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think it's going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_25]: What do you think is going to come at E3 from those companies?
[SPEAKER_21]: I haven't heard the latest word.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm sure Michael Wynn has his
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_21]: But yeah, we're going to be going over there so that we can take a look at the forthcoming release of Pump It Up Exceed.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, I was going to hit on this a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'll go into more detail later, but you're right.
[SPEAKER_25]: MadCatz has announced that they are going to be the ones publishing.
[SPEAKER_25]: And you're right, the cringe was the first thing I did.
[SPEAKER_25]: Actually, my very first thought was, I hope they don't fuck it up like they did their GameCube release.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't have a whole lot of background in the Pump It Up scene.
[SPEAKER_25]: I actually have an exceed in a movie theater about an hour from me, and that's all that I've really played of it.
[SPEAKER_25]: But CJ Iwakura made a post on our thread on DDR Freak
[SPEAKER_21]: where he basically had indicated that the bundled pad is going to be the exact same one that came out with the Konami release.
[SPEAKER_21]: So regardless of the fact that it is Mad Catz publishing the game, hopefully those of you who are pumpers out there won't have anything really to worry about.
[SPEAKER_25]: Phew.
[SPEAKER_25]: I mean, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm still a little nervous about having to buy a new dance pad just because the arrows are all different and stuff anyway, which is why In The Groove, had it been released on the home, would have been kind of a nice addition to the library.
[SPEAKER_25]: But with Pump It Up, it's like, great, I've got to get another mat.
[SPEAKER_25]: But if it's a good, solid mat, then, you know, and it's a reasonable price, which I think $60 is what they're currently asking for, it is somewhat reasonable, excuse me, considering everything you get, then, yeah, I'll probably check it out.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I think that's about the standard price, because if I remember correctly, the DDR bundles that Konami has been putting out lately with the Mark II softpad, those are $60, I'm pretty sure.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, they're about $60 as well.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, anything else you want to share with us, Cutris?
[SPEAKER_25]: Very interesting perspective, enjoy having you on the show.
[SPEAKER_25]: You've got to call in more often, buddy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, now that I actually have a working setup, perhaps I'll do just that.
[SPEAKER_25]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's meet up at E3, since you're going to be going next week, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know if Shane gave you the schedule or anything that we've kind of got tentative so far, but I definitely want to make sure that I get to hang out with you guys a lot.
[SPEAKER_25]: I have heard the DDR Freak mod schedule loosely, what's going on, obviously, because DarkSakura is a big part of that.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know if that includes you and Shane or what, but send me an email.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll work something out.
[SPEAKER_21]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_25]: One more quick question before we go.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: non-music game related thing you're most looking forward to seeing at E3?
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, if you had said non-Bimani, then I probably could have answered that right off because I'm really demanding some information about Jam with the Band.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I guess in that vein, I'm really looking forward to whatever Nintendo has set up for the DS.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm actually a
[SPEAKER_21]: Since I'm not sure if they're going to be offering downloadables for some of their games, or if they're just going to be sending out demos for Mario Kart DS and whatnot...
[SPEAKER_25]: How great is it going to be to just be able to download it and play it on your own damn DS?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, that's going to be absolutely fantastic.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not to have to wait in line.
[SPEAKER_21]: And just because of the way this is working, I'm not taking any chances here.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm bringing both mine and my wife's DS with me and all the games.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I'm totally confiscating all of that.
[SPEAKER_25]: You're all ready to go.
[SPEAKER_25]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm going to bring all my stuff too.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll have to have a DS war or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm bringing my 8th style because I must hunt my hero down.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, Akira, if he's there?
[SPEAKER_25]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_25]: Loki said he's bringing his PSP.
[SPEAKER_25]: He's not taking any chances because he knows PSP's online.
[SPEAKER_25]: He says they could have something surprising.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm bringing my PSP, too.
[SPEAKER_25]: I said you're a brave man to bring all that crap with you to L.A., especially after my car got broken into this week, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right, buddy.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, I'm going to let you go so we can get to some more calls, but thank you very much for calling in, and we'll see you at E3, all right?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, sir.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thanks for having me.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_25]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_25]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_25]: Cutress from DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_25]: www.ddrfreak.com Also the home of our replays that we do Friday nights over on DDR Freak Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_25]: They've been very supportive of us in about the past year or so.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, you know, really ever since the beginning.
[SPEAKER_25]: We've got to work together.
[SPEAKER_25]: But just even more so.
[SPEAKER_25]: Like I've really been feeling the love the past year.
[SPEAKER_25]: So it's great.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's take another call.
[SPEAKER_25]: This person's been calling in for like an hour now.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sorry, dude.
[SPEAKER_25]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_25]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, this is SSJ100Mad and Sephiroth1215.
[SPEAKER_25]: Two of you!
[SPEAKER_25]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_25]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know if we can handle that much input, but we'll try.
[SPEAKER_25]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_25]: What's your guys' thoughts on the lawsuit?
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_27]: I think Rockstar had this coming.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think they planned it out already, so... Wait, so you think Rockstar... Are you saying this whole thing is just smoke and mirrors and that Rockstar has planned this all along?
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't know, they can't be this stupid.
[SPEAKER_27]: They had to have known this was going to happen.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm going to go back to what I said earlier about Rockstar's lawyers.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think when they were clearing everything and seeing if everything was okay with this, they were probably focusing on the software element of it because you have to admit, the software looks a lot like DDR and they weren't focusing enough on the hardware part of it and somebody really, really fucked up.
[SPEAKER_27]: Someone didn't get the memo.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, someone didn't get the memo.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know, but I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_25]: Unfortunately, the community has been too arrogant to fill me in any other way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Got their head shoved way up their asses to the point that they're tasting like tonsil or something.
[SPEAKER_27]: I know, but this whole thing kind of sucks that people who pre-owned it like Sephiroth right over here.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, the folks that pre-ordered it from Red Octane have no idea what's going to happen?
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, I know, that's got to be kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_25]: In fact, somebody was actually mentioning to me in the chat room in private message, I hope Dark Knight doesn't mind me reading this, but he said that he actually went over to a GameStop Sunday and they told him it's going to come out May 26th and no info from the lawsuit had reached them yet about it, but I say don't hold your breath because GameStop, electronic boutiques and stuff, never write with this crap, especially when things are getting delayed.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sorry, but you cannot count on that May 26th date.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll have the word as soon as GameStop gets it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, because you had the luxury of being with the manager of the GameStop and everything.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, now GameStop's owned EB, so... Well, that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_25]: Any other thoughts on the lawsuit?
[SPEAKER_25]: Any other things you want to share with us?
[SPEAKER_27]: Nope, just good to be home back in New York, and...
[SPEAKER_27]: Have a good time.
[SPEAKER_27]: We got a lot.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_25]: How about your friend who's there?
[SPEAKER_25]: Pass the mic or something.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_25]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yes, sir.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_25]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_25]: And this is Seproth?
[SPEAKER_25]: No, this is... Is this Seproth?
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hey, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_26]: Your thoughts on the lawsuit?
[SPEAKER_26]: Um, yeah, you know, I think they really just screwed up on how they put the game on the DDR machines, but otherwise I think everything else should have been fine.
[SPEAKER_26]: That should be like the main thing that Konami should have just sued for.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's almost like they learned their lesson within the group too, but it's like, too late, whoops.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, yeah, you got a good point there.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anything else you want to share with us?
[SPEAKER_26]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_26]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: All right, well.
[SPEAKER_26]: Except for, yeah, I'm pretty pissed that, you know, I pre-ordered that in the groove with the Astro Burner pad bundle.
[SPEAKER_25]: You won't be disappointed with the Afterburner pad, I'll tell you that.
[SPEAKER_25]: I have good things to say about the Afterburner pad, it's marvelous.
[SPEAKER_25]: But yeah, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know what though, Red Octane, from what I've seen, they're a decent company, and they'll do something for you when they give you your money back, if it comes to that.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hopefully it won't, something will be able to happen, or Indigroove can still come out in some capacity, but time will tell.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think we'll find out shortly after E3 what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_25]: or I don't know, we could find out next week because what a good time to release that kind of news during E3 when there's so much other stuff to divert people's attention.
[SPEAKER_25]: It'll kind of be a good time, you know.
[SPEAKER_25]: Everybody's looking over here.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, by the way, we settled.
[SPEAKER_25]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, I'm going to let you go so we can get some more calls but thank you guys both for calling in, alright?
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, no problem.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I like this idea, by the way, of the Orange Lounge Radio listening parties so you guys keep it up.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, later.
[SPEAKER_25]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't think he knew what to think of that comment.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's go to this call.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's Ranma from New York.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hello, Ranma from New York.
[SPEAKER_25]: We just got off the phone with some folks from New York.
[SPEAKER_25]: Did you hear what I said to the other guys from New York?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_14]: And when you come to New York, I'm going to show you around.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Actually, I have a really good friend, one of my best friends in the whole wide world, lives in Connecticut.
[SPEAKER_25]: But that's just a hop, skip it, or jump away from NYC.
[SPEAKER_25]: So we're looking into it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sweet, sweet.
[SPEAKER_25]: So what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_14]: One thing about this whole lawsuit thing, I think Rockstar had a pretty good idea of what was going to happen when they did this.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, put it in a DDR machine.
[SPEAKER_14]: Save money.
[SPEAKER_14]: Look what I got you.
[SPEAKER_25]: Maybe you got a good point.
[SPEAKER_25]: Rockstar being the startup it was, just kind of did this as a cost-saving thing, not really thinking about the ramifications of what it could have.
[SPEAKER_25]: Interesting perspective.
[SPEAKER_25]: Basically.
[SPEAKER_25]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_25]: What are your personal thoughts on the lawsuit?
[SPEAKER_25]: What do you think will happen because of this?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll wait.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll personally wait because I know as soon as I say I want my money back, the game comes out and I won't have the money for it.
[SPEAKER_25]: So you actually pre-ordered it at this Anime Expo?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, Anime Boston.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anime Boston.
[SPEAKER_25]: And that must have been last weekend before this whole news came out, right?
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, that's right, because you gave us your wrap-up last week.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, man, that's crappy timing.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm sorry to hear that happen to you.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: One other thing before we go to another call.
[SPEAKER_25]: Thing you are most looking forward to hearing about from E3?
[SPEAKER_14]: Nintendo Revolution.
[SPEAKER_14]: And before I go, I'm posting a link from my website to the whole Nintendo World Extravaganza Saturday.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, the opening of the store.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want to hear about that.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, tell us more about that.
[SPEAKER_25]: How was the opening of the store?
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, I got to about 9.30ish.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was kind of quiet.
[SPEAKER_14]: When they picked up some friends, we got back around 11ish.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was jam-packed.
[SPEAKER_14]: Almost every other person was walking around with a DS, nothing but chats.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm walking up and down the lines taking pictures, and there were two people with PSPs that were getting booed.
Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: Wow, interesting.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, well, wow, definitely check out that site and look at the pictures there.
[SPEAKER_25]: One other thing I want to... Did they have DS downloadable or anything there?
[SPEAKER_25]: No.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, bummer.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was kind of hoping they would.
[SPEAKER_25]: Give us a sign of what's going to come up for V3.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know, but one funny thing was they were handing out free DS silos as you walked in, and they also had little bottles of Nintendo World Water for you to drink.
[SPEAKER_25]: Nintendo World Water.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_25]: Pikachu Beetle Pikachu Beetle Pikachu Beetle Pikachu Beetle
[SPEAKER_25]: Is that from his picture down there?
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, that's cute.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, we're going to do another call because there's another person who's been trying to get in and call, so we're going to take this call.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hello, you're on Orange Dance Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_22]: This is Jaded.
[SPEAKER_25]: Jaded!
[SPEAKER_25]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, nothing much.
[SPEAKER_25]: What do you think about this whole lawsuit going on right now?
[SPEAKER_25]: Konami versus Roxxor?
[SPEAKER_22]: I just think right now it's too early to make any kind of intelligent decisions.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_25]: You bring up a damn good point.
[SPEAKER_25]: And even from somebody who's been sitting here yapping about it for about the past hour, it really is too early to make an informed decision about everything.
[SPEAKER_25]: Although, I gotta hand it off, because of the DDR Freak releasing the actual documents...
[SPEAKER_25]: That helped immensely in trying to figure out, you know, where's Konami coming from on this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I think it actually took some of the evilness, the big bad Konami-ness, like, I think it kind of took some of that out because people looked at it and went, you know, well, they kind of do have a point.
[SPEAKER_25]: They kind of do have a point.
[SPEAKER_22]: Right now, it's just too early.
[SPEAKER_22]: Everybody is saying that it's going to go several different ways.
[SPEAKER_22]: Right now, I'm just personally not believing anything.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm just personally thinking that it's too early.
[SPEAKER_25]: You just have your hands over your ears going, I can't hear you, I can't hear you.
[SPEAKER_25]: Have you pre-ordered in the groove?
[SPEAKER_25]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was just curious if you were one of those customers, because I know if I was one of those people that had pre-ordered in the groove, I'd probably be a lot like that right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: I did not just waste $40.
[SPEAKER_25]: La, la, la, la, la.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Dark Day Dark Day
[SPEAKER_25]: Um, nevermind, I just turned on a light in here.
[SPEAKER_25]: Our webcam, OrangeLensRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_25]: Um, thing you're most looking forward to hearing about from E3 next week?
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm just looking forward to the Final Fantasy Advent Children news.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm hoping they do that again this year.
[SPEAKER_25]: I wish they'd just screen the whole damn movie so we could see it.
[SPEAKER_25]: But I know that won't happen.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because they know that a lot of the fanboys are going to be there.
[SPEAKER_22]: The reason why I'm interested in this is that it's been delayed multiple times, and frankly, I'm waiting for something to happen.
[SPEAKER_25]: Very true.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, I know that we had posted a story earlier that you, being a big fan of Advent Children, probably have already heard this, but for those that didn't hear about this yet, actually, they did announce that there was going to be a date for this.
[SPEAKER_25]: and it's going to be simultaneous, if I remember right, between the US and Japan so those of you that sometimes feel shafted that Squeenix always gives Japan the good stuff weeks before, or I'm sorry, months, even a year before we get it let's see, the date is September 14th, 2005 simultaneous release in America and Japan UMD release, not a part of that, this is only the DVD but that should be cool right
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, well thanks for calling and you know what, thanks for bringing up a point that, you know, we really don't know what the hell we're talking about in some aspects with this.
[SPEAKER_25]: So we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_25]: It was nice talking to you.
[SPEAKER_25]: Nice talking to you, thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_25]: Later.
[SPEAKER_25]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_25]: That was nice.
[SPEAKER_25]: A nice young man there calling in.
[SPEAKER_25]: That was good.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_25]: and Intelligence Perspective.
[SPEAKER_25]: We like that.
[SPEAKER_25]: So we were lucky in that.
[SPEAKER_25]: So we do have a full-blown regular cage match for you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_25]: So without further ado, let's get into the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_25]: For those of you guys still trying to get in on the Skype line, no worries.
[SPEAKER_25]: We will take more calls a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_25]: So just be patient.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sorry you didn't get through yet.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Remember, the way the cage match works, you have to be in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_25]: www.orangeloungeradio.com Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_25]: The way this works, we play three songs for you guys.
[SPEAKER_25]: You pick your favorite, and the winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio's Gaming Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_25]: which plays 24 hours a day, 7 days a week on this station when we aren't live.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, let's get into it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Last week in the cage match, Jamie had put a song in, and you know that right now Jamie is all about the gorillas.
[SPEAKER_25]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_25]: This was interesting because last week a little bit of controversy because the song is very quirky and a lot of people either loved it or they hated it.
[SPEAKER_25]: But what happened last week is that it was up against two trance songs which ended up kind of splitting the vote a little bit causing this one to win.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think it would be a fair thing to say.
[SPEAKER_25]: So we shall see if it hangs on again tonight.
[SPEAKER_25]: Here it is, song number one.
[SPEAKER_25]: Only a clip because it won last week.
[SPEAKER_25]: Damon Albren with a rappy song.
[SPEAKER_25]: How appropriate considering the PSO blue burst I've been doing this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: All rappy.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Damon Albrin, a rappy song, the remix.
[SPEAKER_25]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_20]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_25]: Correct me if I'm wrong, you've misplaced Loki's song.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, shut up.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, so there it was.
[SPEAKER_25]: Song number one, Damon Auburn with a rappy song, the remix.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, here we go into song number two tonight.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's my pick.
[SPEAKER_25]: And this comes off that same dance compilation that I've been putting songs from in lately.
[SPEAKER_25]: And Jamie's already rolling her eyes.
[SPEAKER_25]: But here's the weird thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: I believe this is actually Ayumi Hanasaki.
[SPEAKER_25]: Who showed up on this compilation If it sounds like she's holding her nose, then it is I think it is But she's simply being credited as IU And if it's not her, then it sure sounds like her So I'm picking this song because I like it The song is called Appears So here it is, IU with Appears And I'm going to refer to it as IU because that's the way it's credited on the CD So enjoy
Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_13]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_25]: I.U.
[SPEAKER_25]: with Appears.
[SPEAKER_25]: Definitely, definitely Ayumi Hamasaki.
[SPEAKER_25]: You can't argue that.
[SPEAKER_25]: So I don't know why they build her or something else in Europe, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because her dance in Europe is put out as I.U.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have to rate them.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, yeah, we have to.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was just going to move.
[SPEAKER_25]: Move on.
[SPEAKER_25]: Dear Rob, rate.
[SPEAKER_25]: DarkSakura, what did you think of that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ayumi's voice annoys me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry because she's so nasally.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I really like a bunch of her stuff, and I really liked her for a while, but I can't get too excited about Ayumi Hamasaki just because she's been there, done that, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still solid.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still trance.
[SPEAKER_02]: It gets a seven.
[SPEAKER_25]: I feel a little bit similar where I'm like, well, it's another Ayumi song, but God, I love her trance stuff.
[SPEAKER_25]: I just love those mixes.
[SPEAKER_25]: They make me happy.
[SPEAKER_25]: I give it a nine.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: I know exactly what this is.
[SPEAKER_25]: I have no idea what to expect.
[SPEAKER_25]: Here it is, song number three, Loki's Gin and Juice, Ted Koppel.
[SPEAKER_12]: With so much drama in the ABC, it's kinda hard being Ted K.O.P., but I, somehow, someway, keep coming up with funky-ass shit like every single day.
[SPEAKER_12]: May I kick a little something for the G's and make a few N's as I breeze through.
[SPEAKER_12]: Two in the morning and the party's still jumping cause my mama ain't home.
[SPEAKER_12]: I got bitches in the living room getting it on, and they ain't leaving till six in the morning.
[SPEAKER_12]: So what you wanna do?
[SPEAKER_12]: Shit, I've got a pocket full of rubbers and my homeboys do too.
[SPEAKER_12]: So turn off the lights and close the doors, but... Yeah, so we gon' smoke an ounce to this.
[SPEAKER_12]: Jeez up, hose down while you motherfuckers bounce to this.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm Ted Koppel and this is Laid Back.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sources close to the White House today confirm that the president is laid back.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now that I got me some Seagram's Gin, everybody got they cups, but they ain't chipped in.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now this types of shit happens all the time.
[SPEAKER_12]: You gotta get yours, but fool, I gotta get mine.
[SPEAKER_12]: Everything is fine when you're listening to the T.E.D.
[SPEAKER_12]: I got the cultivatin' music that be captivatin' he who listens.
[SPEAKER_12]: To the words that I speak as I take me a drink to the middle of the street and get to mackin' this bitch named Katie.
[SPEAKER_12]: Katie Curran?
[SPEAKER_12]: She used to be the homeboy's lady.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, that bitch?
[SPEAKER_12]: Eighty degrees when I tell that bitch, please raise up off these NUTs cause you get none of these at ease.
[SPEAKER_12]: As I mob with the dog pound, feel the breeze, biatch, I'm just.
[SPEAKER_12]: Earthquakes rocked Tokyo, Japan today as residents were laid back.
[SPEAKER_12]: Residents in a small New England town are terrified as a mass murderer is laid back.
With my mind on the money and the money on the line.
[SPEAKER_12]: Later on that day, my homie Sam Donaldson came through with a gang of Tanqueray and a fat-ass J of some bubonic chronic that made me choke.
[SPEAKER_12]: Shit, this ain't no joke, I had to back up off of it and sit my cup down.
[SPEAKER_12]: Tanqueray and chronic, yeah, I'm fucked up now, but it ain't no stoppin', I'm still poppin'.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sam got some bitches from the city of Compton to serve me, not with a cherry on top, cause when I bust my nut, I'm raisin' up off the cot.
[SPEAKER_12]: But don't get upset, girl, that's just how it goes.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't love you, hoes.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm out the door, and I'll be... Residents of Baghdad fired shots wildly into the air as protesters were laid back.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm Ted Koppel, and this is Laid Back.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, now here's a question.
[SPEAKER_12]: What is the BH?
[SPEAKER_12]: Right, see, exactly.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just don't, I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't, I don't know what that word is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that, is that how it's pronounced?
[SPEAKER_12]: Right, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just, I, I just, I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sound number three, Darth Punk, Ted Koppel's Gin and Juice.
[SPEAKER_25]: Juicy or not juicy?
[SPEAKER_02]: Juicy like a wet fart.
[SPEAKER_25]: What'd you think, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: The first time I heard that, I thought it was intensely retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: He wanted me to put it as a fortune cookie, and I refused to.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it gets a big whopping .5.
[SPEAKER_25]: Just cause I like how he does the blah blah blah blah and leaves back Cause I thought that part was funny You know, Loki played that for me too, saying it was like the funniest thing he'd ever heard And I was like, this is not the funniest thing I've ever heard Jokes that Diane Mita Zoda makes on G4 can be funnier than this, I'm sorry If you're gonna be funny and do a parody song, be funny I give that song a zero, it's awful
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, let's recap.
[SPEAKER_25]: But it's not up to us, it's up to you guys.
[SPEAKER_25]: Maybe you thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_25]: So here it is, the three songs you get to vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_25]: Song number one, Damon Albrin, a rappy song.
[SPEAKER_25]: The remix.
[SPEAKER_25]: And song number two you can vote for tonight is IU with Appears.
[SPEAKER_25]: and song number three you can vote for tonight, Darth Punk, Ted Koppel's Gin and Juice.
[SPEAKER_12]: George is close to the White House today, confirmed that the president is laid back.
[SPEAKER_25]: There, I got a laid back in there for you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_25]: I liked that one.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's all I like about the song.
[SPEAKER_25]: Place vote now.
[SPEAKER_25]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hurry, hurry.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll add him up and let you know who the winner is.
[SPEAKER_25]: Um...
[SPEAKER_25]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_25]: He sounds like... You remember the two Muppets that sat up in the balcony and made fun of all the other Muppets on the Muppet Show?
[SPEAKER_25]: That's what he sounds like in that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's... Laid back!
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Don't vote for Holic.
[SPEAKER_25]: Votes for Holic are thrown out, okay?
[SPEAKER_25]: There's always a movement in the chatroom to vote for Holic.
[SPEAKER_25]: Remember, the winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: Holic is in permanent rotation already on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: You don't need to vote it into rotation.
[SPEAKER_25]: It does no good.
[SPEAKER_25]: Just wanted to make that clear.
[SPEAKER_25]: I realize some of you like to vote for Holic when you feel that the rest of our songs were crappy or something like that, but just deal.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyway, this is the part of the show where Loki would typically give us the sim scene update and tell us what's going on in the sim scene.
[SPEAKER_25]: However, I have no idea what's going on in the sim scene right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: A bunch of stuff happened, but not really, because it's sims.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'll bet you what, probably this lawsuit has people freaked out about making any sims right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: A bunch of crappy Max remixes were released on Mamani Style, what can I say?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: ParanoiaMax.5007 Let's talk about the real thing, shall we?
[SPEAKER_25]: The real deal.
[SPEAKER_25]: The real thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, in the groove.
[SPEAKER_25]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_25]: Even better than that.
[SPEAKER_25]: Konami has launched something on their website.
[SPEAKER_25]: And what it is, it is a teaser pic for a brand new DDR.
[SPEAKER_25]: And you can see it on our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And in this video it appears to have...
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm sorry, not a video, sorry, a picture.
[SPEAKER_25]: It appears to have maybe some captures from new videos or something.
[SPEAKER_25]: But it does indicate that a new DDR is coming out.
[SPEAKER_25]: However, in the corner, it says it's coming out on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_25]: So I think people got excited at first that this is a new arcade mix.
[SPEAKER_25]: It doesn't look like it.
[SPEAKER_25]: This is probably Japan's version of whatever we're getting with Xtreme 2.
[SPEAKER_25]: Such as Festival was like our DDR Xtreme.
[SPEAKER_25]: This is probably their version of what we're going to get as Xtreme 2.
[SPEAKER_25]: And of course, we talked about Xtreme 2 a little bit last week.
[SPEAKER_25]: EyeToy stuff coming back.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's going to have the Oops I Did It Again rumored online play and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll know more, of course, next week.
[SPEAKER_25]: It doesn't seem like any big surprise that this would be ported to Japan as well and be coming out there.
[SPEAKER_25]: Or
[SPEAKER_25]: Maybe we're getting the port, it's hard to say, but no surprise, really.
[SPEAKER_25]: Things you would like to see in the next PlayStation release of DDR, Jamie, anything?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't really say, you know, because the one thing I wanted was freaking Dance Magic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want Dance Magic mode to come back.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, you know what, and what you almost kind of said, is that In The Groove has a mode like that, although not as many people play it as you'd think, and it was going to be in the home release and everything, and now it's not, well, we don't know yet, but now it's questionable if it's coming or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR doesn't make you a better dancer, so that's one thing out, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really can't think of anything else that they could really... There's that, you know, dinky little RPG mode thing, right?
[SPEAKER_25]: That's in Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_25]: No, I can't... I really hope they're demoing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR Whack-A-Mole!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, that would be... They need to put DDR Whack-A-Mole in.
[SPEAKER_25]: Wouldn't the makers of Spider Stomps sue him?
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's not really whack-a-mole.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, because it's moles and not spiders.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they don't pop up out of the ground.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you're actually stepping on the thing itself, but there's no TV on Spider Stump either.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, aha!
[SPEAKER_02]: I know my legal crap.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's in a different cabinet.
[SPEAKER_02]: No infringement there, no?
[SPEAKER_25]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, um...
[SPEAKER_25]: Loki popped into chat really fast.
[SPEAKER_25]: I guess he managed to tear himself away for a little bit to listen to the little show.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_25]: He says, and I quote, nothing much is happening in the sim scene, just more crappy sim files.
[SPEAKER_25]: See, I called it.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know what, we ought to just fire Loki because I'm able to do the sim scene report myself every week.
[SPEAKER_25]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_25]: We would never do that.
[SPEAKER_25]: He'll be back next week.
[SPEAKER_25]: He'll be with us for the podcast as well.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, last call for the cage match votes, you guys.
[SPEAKER_25]: Get them in here.
[SPEAKER_25]: Um,
[SPEAKER_25]: Also, what we're going to do next break, I think we're going to try and do that list list, except my roommate is getting cold feet now.
[SPEAKER_25]: He doesn't want to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So how about we have two, we can't do two Skype lines, can we?
[SPEAKER_25]: No, we'll just have three people.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll do a three-person list.
[SPEAKER_02]: One person in PM and one person on Skype line.
[SPEAKER_25]: So one person in private message and one person on Skype line.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right, I'll try to figure out who those people are going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm picking people I want.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trivia question.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an easy one.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who is my favorite?
[SPEAKER_25]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_25]: No question.
[SPEAKER_25]: I want to pick up people who are doing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If that's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that we should give a fair opportunity.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: How about we Skype in somebody I want and we'll let somebody from the chat room do it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the trivia question... Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_25]: Don't give the trivia question yet because I'm still... Well, I want them to think about it.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm telling you in cage match votes.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't want them to send it in yet.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, don't... All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hold on, I'll finish up.
[SPEAKER_25]: Any thoughts you have for us, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_25]: Why don't you tell us about some of the spit-off programming we have here on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, on Monday, we happen to have Diversion that starts at a net moon time to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seven o'clock.
[SPEAKER_25]: Actually, Diversion got cancelled.
What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Diversion's cancelled, remember?
[SPEAKER_02]: You didn't tell me this stuff.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is what I get for sleeping through a board meeting.
[SPEAKER_25]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_25]: Coming soon to Orange Lounge Radio, the Dance Mania show is coming to Monday nights to replace Diversion.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: You better drink Diet Coke.
[SPEAKER_02]: The actual show will start at 7.30 and the concept is requesting stuff but people don't request shit so I just end up playing whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course no show this week because I will again be in a car on my way to E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, I will be coming back and uh
[SPEAKER_02]: Filling your head with, I think, an anime marathon, I'm thinking this time.
[SPEAKER_02]: The last time, see, I've noticed that my pre-shows have been turning into sort of repeat performances of what you might hear on Pump Up the Volume.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, if you like what you hear on the pre-show, be sure to tune in.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right, let's do the cage match winner.
[SPEAKER_25]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_28]: We don't have another show.
[SPEAKER_25]: No, we don't have another show right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's just me.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's the Jamie show.
[SPEAKER_25]: Jamie's by herself, and then we're going to have a whole lot of new programming at the end of the month.
[SPEAKER_25]: I promise.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I still love you, and I will stay constant.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: I, however, do not.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_25]: The winning song of tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_25]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_25]: Tonight's winning song is... A tie.
[SPEAKER_25]: Song number one that tied in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_25]: IU appears.
[SPEAKER_25]: Kind of a given considering the crowd we got here.
[SPEAKER_25]: Song number three that tied in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_12]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: Ted Koppel's Gin and Juice.
[SPEAKER_25]: Before you say anything, Jamie, let me remind folks, in case of a tie, the host whose song did not make the tie gets to break the tie.
[SPEAKER_25]: That being said, Jamie, tough decision here.
[SPEAKER_24]: What are you going to go with?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to torture you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to see you crack and bleeding under my whip.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get Ted Koppel.
[SPEAKER_25]: Jamie votes for Ted Koppel.
[SPEAKER_12]: I cannot believe that the song you gave a .5
[SPEAKER_25]: The demon is hot.
[SPEAKER_25]: Dude, he's older and still hot.
[SPEAKER_25]: Dude, you lucked out with that win last week.
[SPEAKER_25]: Even you have to admit, considering the chatroom's reaction, you lucked out with that win last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but I have to make sure that I put in a song that won't win next week because the week after is the week after.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, that was a strategic vote.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's what you were doing.
[SPEAKER_25]: You did that so that you could win next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I did want to make an announcement because I think I can legally get away with it as I'm going to be playing the entirety of Demon Days on the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it will have been released in the UK.
[SPEAKER_25]: Super.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't get you, Jamie, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am a woman!
[SPEAKER_25]: And by rights... Alright, woman, I don't get you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can change my mind and do everything I can to confuse men.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_25]: Um, here we go.
[SPEAKER_25]: The power of estrogen.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's, list, list.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's remind... Shut up.
[SPEAKER_25]: List, list.
[SPEAKER_10]: Make me!
[SPEAKER_25]: The way this list works, we are going to come up with the definitive list of things for Orange Lounge Radio to stick on the E3 Katamari.
[SPEAKER_25]: The definitive list, okay?
[SPEAKER_25]: The way it works, myself, Jamie, and two mystery guests will be coming up with a list of four items each, and then we each take one off the list.
[SPEAKER_25]: And you guys get to vote on the definitive list.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll explain it as we move on.
[SPEAKER_25]: In order for us to get to that point, though, we need a contestant from chat.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm going to get somebody on Skype.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm going to handpick one of our guests to get on Skype.
[SPEAKER_25]: But we are going to have a contest in the chat room to see who gets in there.
[SPEAKER_25]: So the first person to answer this correctly is going to be doing the other list.
[SPEAKER_25]: But please don't answer unless you have some ideas for this list list, because I don't want you sitting there going, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_02]: Send the PM to me so that Rob is not inundated with PMs.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm in the chat room at DarkSakura SSF.
[SPEAKER_02]: The question...
[SPEAKER_02]: Who is my favorite member of Gorillaz?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who is my favorite member of the band?
[SPEAKER_25]: Favorite member of the animated band Gorillaz.
[SPEAKER_25]: If you've been paying attention to this show in the past few weeks, you should know.
[SPEAKER_25]: First person to send that correctly over private message to Jamie will get the privilege.
[SPEAKER_25]: Listeners never get this privilege.
[SPEAKER_25]: This is a special night.
[SPEAKER_25]: You're lucky Loki's not here.
[SPEAKER_25]: To participate in Listless with us.
[SPEAKER_25]: Meanwhile, I'm going to hook up somebody over Skype.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm going to find somebody on Skype.
[SPEAKER_25]: And we will be back after this featuring some music from... Well, more potpourri, I think.
[SPEAKER_25]: But we're going to start it off with Burning Heat.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because that song, Gin and Juice, gives me burning heat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gives me burning itch.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll be back after this.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm finding it hard to believe we're in heaven.
[SPEAKER_13]: Days when I couldn't live my life without you
[SPEAKER_25]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_25]: Hello, is this thing on?
[SPEAKER_25]: Testing.
[SPEAKER_25]: Testing, one, two.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking in the index, but I don't see anything for how to run a radio show.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't understand this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does this thing work?
[SPEAKER_03]: This thing reads like stereo instructions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this on?
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio, broke down ghetto Bomani Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: What the f***?
[SPEAKER_25]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio, and we are going to do some listless.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_25]: So, the way listless works, just a quick reminder.
[SPEAKER_25]: We're doing three, just three.
[SPEAKER_25]: We are each going to pick our top three, myself, DarkSakura, and who is your winner, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Our winner is Ranma!
[SPEAKER_25]: Ranma, okay, and then we're going to get somebody special here on the Skype line right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: Doop-a-doop-a-doo, just waiting for the phone.
[SPEAKER_25]: One ringy dingy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_25]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_25]: Is this Miklatov?
[SPEAKER_25]: Hello, Miklatov?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_25]: Can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know if he can hear me.
[SPEAKER_25]: Are you there?
[SPEAKER_08]: I can hear you.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, but you can't hear yourself?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_25]: Can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm confused.
[SPEAKER_02]: He can hear us.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can hear him.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can hear you.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_25]: You just freaked me out for a little bit there.
[SPEAKER_25]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_25]: How are you doing, sir?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm doing pretty well.
[SPEAKER_25]: Looking forward to E3 next week?
[SPEAKER_08]: To what?
[SPEAKER_25]: Are you looking forward to E3 next week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're breaking up because you're on the computer.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now I think I can hear you better.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_25]: Are you going to stick things on the Katamari?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully we will.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, we're going to get your top three, but you have to wait your turn.
[SPEAKER_25]: So you have your list ready?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's my turn?
[SPEAKER_25]: No, it's not your turn yet.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'll let you know when.
[SPEAKER_25]: You're going to give us your answers, okay?
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: VOTE ONE OFF
[SPEAKER_25]: So then after each one song has been voted off, we will have a list of eight, because we'll have two from each person left.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll have a list of eight, and then the chat room gets to vote on their favorite to come up with a top three list.
[SPEAKER_25]: So tonight's list list...
[SPEAKER_25]: Things we want to stick on the Katamari at E3, or should I say things we should stick on the Katamari at E3.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'll go first.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm actually stealing ideas from the chat room tonight because I think they actually have some decent ideas.
[SPEAKER_25]: And my number three pick is Calamari, as somebody said, because I think the phrase sticking Calamari on the Katamari, it's kind of cute.
[SPEAKER_25]: And it sounds like it actually could be a song in Katamari Damacy 2.
[SPEAKER_25]: So I'm saying Calamari.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Miklatov, what's your number three pick for things that you want to stick on the Katamari?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I would like to put Mad Catz on the Katamari, just so it could be rolled away and shot off into space so they don't have anything to do with Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, so he's going to stick the entire company of Mad Catz.
[SPEAKER_08]: All of Mad Catz.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what I wanted.
[SPEAKER_25]: So you're going to have to get the prints to roll up a big Katamari first, and we're just going to roll over the Mad Catz building.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, hopefully it's Mad Catz.
[SPEAKER_08]: It shouldn't be that big.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can get a little binky-sized one.
[SPEAKER_25]: I have no idea why.
[SPEAKER_25]: He didn't send me a reason why, but he wants to put a Mustang on there.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright A little bit of dinner there, sorry Jamie, your number three pick The Gorilla's Jeep, spelled G-E-E-P The Gorilla's Jeep, why the Jeep?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, at least what's left of it since it's apparently smashed all of the basement under the car park You do understand it's a cartoon, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: You shut up!
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_25]: Did Ranma tell me why the Mustang?
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: He says, Mustang cars rock.
[SPEAKER_25]: I love them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, they do.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_25]: My number two pick for something I want to put on the Katamari.
[SPEAKER_25]: My number two pick is, originally I said, let's take all of Lanky Styles' Paula's Terry CDs and put them on the Katamari so we can be rid of them forever.
[SPEAKER_25]: But actually somebody in the chat room came up with something better, so I went with this.
[SPEAKER_25]: Put all of the shitty Max 300 remixes on one CD and put it on the Katamari.
[SPEAKER_25]: So all the shitty Max remixes, let's just roll them away.
[SPEAKER_25]: So shitty Max 300 remix CD is my number two pick.
[SPEAKER_25]: Mik Latav, what's your number two pick?
[SPEAKER_08]: I would want to put the tiniest picture...
[SPEAKER_08]: of a bear I could on the Katamari, and you would understand it if you've played the game.
[SPEAKER_25]: So if you've actually played the game, you'll understand why he wants to put the tiniest picture of a bear.
[SPEAKER_28]: That really pissed me off when making the Ursa Major.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Number two from Ranma, I'm reading it from the chatroom, he wants to put, he's going to put a Big Mac with cheese on the Katamari.
[SPEAKER_25]: Although you have to remember, no food is supposed to be on the... No, did they say no food?
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess they did.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't think they did.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think they only said clothes and X-rated things, but... No, I think foods included.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, well, I said calamari, so we'll let them say Big Mac.
[SPEAKER_25]: Big Mac, because it would be fun to roll it and see if it is edible.
[SPEAKER_25]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right, Jamie, what's your number two?
[SPEAKER_25]: The retard ferret.
[SPEAKER_10]: Me.
[SPEAKER_25]: And the retard ferret is the one that keeps making the same noise over and over.
[SPEAKER_25]: We actually are going to put that on the Katamari, by the way.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: My number one choice.
[SPEAKER_25]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_25]: My number one choice for things I want to put on the Katamari.
[SPEAKER_25]: I want to put a copy of Katamari Damacy on the Katamari, just to be ironic.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, we could do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not like actually put the game on there, but like do like a blank CD-R with the label on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_25]: I want to put a bumble ball on it, because it looks like a Katamari.
[SPEAKER_25]: A bumble ball?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, he's right, they do look like a Katamari.
[SPEAKER_25]: They totally look like Katamaris.
[SPEAKER_25]: See, he's being ironic, too.
[SPEAKER_25]: Good pick, Miklatov.
[SPEAKER_25]: Um, Ranma, number one.
[SPEAKER_25]: He wants to put a Nintendo DS on the Katamari.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because the DS is too awesome not to put on there.
[SPEAKER_25]: I say that that's about the only good thing your DS can do right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm taking my DS with me.
[SPEAKER_25]: No, I know, E3 will change our minds.
[SPEAKER_25]: The Nintendo DS will be beautiful after E3.
[SPEAKER_25]: Um, but right now I'm kind of pissed because, like, you call Polarium a game?
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: What's your number one, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: A gigantic, huge mungus.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reject false icon sticker.
[SPEAKER_25]: Reject false icon sticker, and why is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because the giant Katamari will probably be made up of a bunch of false icons, and what better to put on it than a big sticker that tells them that they should all go do something useful, like be a real star.
[SPEAKER_25]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Listen carefully, Miklatov and Ranma in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_25]: Listen carefully because you have to figure out which one of these you want to vote off of the list.
[SPEAKER_25]: One of these you have to vote off the list.
[SPEAKER_25]: I will start.
[SPEAKER_25]: Did I start?
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, I did.
[SPEAKER_25]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_25]: Calamari, Mad Catz, Mustang, Gorilla's Jeep, Shitty Max 300 Remix CD, Tiniest Picture of a Bear,
[SPEAKER_25]: Big Mac with Cheese, Retard Ferret, a copy of Katamari Damacy, Bumble Ball, Nintendo DS, and a Reject False Icon sticker.
[SPEAKER_25]: I am going to take off this list... Huh?
[SPEAKER_25]: A huge one.
[SPEAKER_25]: A big one.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm going to take off a Big Mac with Cheese, because that's just kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sorry, Ranma, but I don't even like McDonald's to begin with.
[SPEAKER_25]: Except I do like that walnut salad they have now.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's actually kind of yummy.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Cobb salad's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_25]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Meek Latav, you there?
[SPEAKER_25]: I thought...
[SPEAKER_25]: Miklatov?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, what are you taking off the list?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, a Mustang.
[SPEAKER_25]: The Mustang!
[SPEAKER_25]: Why the Mustang?
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't make any sense to me.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, poor Ranma.
[SPEAKER_25]: Like, his whole list just almost got axed.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_25]: Um, Ranma hasn't sent me which one he's going to vote off yet, so I guess, Jamie, you're going to be next.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me see the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_25]: Um...
[SPEAKER_25]: DarkSakura, here it is.
[SPEAKER_25]: Do you need that a little bigger there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't highlight it, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't need it bigger.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just don't highlight it.
[SPEAKER_02]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh... Uh... God.
[SPEAKER_28]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_28]: Take off Mad Catz, because then... Aww.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_25]: Guerrilla's Jeep
[SPEAKER_25]: a shitty Max 300 remix CD, the tiniest picture of a bear, the retard ferret, a copy of Katamari Damacy, Bumble Ball, Nintendo DS, and a large reject false icon stickers.
[SPEAKER_25]: Place your vote now.
[SPEAKER_25]: Send a private message to Sky with what you want to be at the top of this definitive list.
[SPEAKER_25]: Thanks for playing, Mikotov.
[SPEAKER_25]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hey, what are your plans for E3 next week?
[SPEAKER_25]: What do you hope to see at the show?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually really looking forward to going to play Phantasy Star Universe.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't know it was going to be there.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, his voice is kind of quiet.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's Phantasy Star Universe is what he said.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to that as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: We played PSO Blueburst with us last night.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, it was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_25]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_25]: Now that I'm in the caves, I can level more faster.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for letting me leech all the loot because I was poor.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm poor now because I have 75 Meseta.
[SPEAKER_25]: If I didn't have to pack tonight, I would totally play more.
[SPEAKER_02]: I get to pack tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_02]: My ass is playing.
[SPEAKER_25]: 24 hours from now, I will be at the More Friends concert.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't give a rat's ass.
[SPEAKER_24]: Go to hell.
[SPEAKER_25]: Go to hell.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then I'm hanging up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go back to play some Guild Wars probably.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm hanging up on you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_25]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_25]: By the way, which also got brought up in there, before we go to break, we should mention this real briefly.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's been mentioned twice in the show now.
[SPEAKER_25]: MadCatz will be publishing Pump It Up, to which some of us go, Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_28]: It gets the DMV size.
[SPEAKER_25]: Exactly, exactly.
[SPEAKER_25]: I just hope they don't fuck it up somehow.
[SPEAKER_25]: I just blew our listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm such a hoe.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, we'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_25]: More Potpourri here in this break.
[SPEAKER_25]: Started off with one of Jamie's favorite songs.
[SPEAKER_25]: I know this for a fact.
[SPEAKER_25]: And we'll be back after this with more Orange Lines Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: The definitive list and the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_25]: All when we come back.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hurry up.
[SPEAKER_25]: Finish your votes.
[SPEAKER_25]: Last call for votes on this list.
Thanks for watching!
I just did not have love for you
I need to know, I need to know, I need to know how you feel I gotta know, I gotta know, I gotta know if it's real I need to know, I need to know, I need to know how you feel I gotta know, I gotta know, I gotta know if it's real I need to know how you feel I just didn't find my love for you
I'm giving all my heart to you, my love I justify my love for you I'm giving you my heart, my soul, my love I justify my love for you I justify my love for you I'm giving all my heart to you, my love I justify my love for you I'm giving you my heart, my soul
Music Music Music Music
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: and many more.
The Orange Lounge Radio with the ping pong ball.
Woo!
[SPEAKER_25]: Hi, we're back on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was just barking E3 quarters to DarkSakura there during break.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know I love ya.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm just giving a heads up.
[SPEAKER_25]: I do not want chaos like last year.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was pissed off after that night last year.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't get... I don't... Despite my on-air persona, I don't get bitchy in real life that often.
[SPEAKER_25]: But that got me really bitchy.
[SPEAKER_02]: So just... You're funny when you're bitchy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are damn hilarious when you are bitchy.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because I get totally faggy.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I can say that because I am a fag.
[SPEAKER_25]: I get totally faggy, you know, when I'm bitchy.
[SPEAKER_25]: And just like, uh-uh, uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_25]: Girl.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm just not going through that again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have that stuck in my head because I listen to...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's reveal the definitive list as voted on by you guys.
[SPEAKER_25]: Here it is, the definitive list.
[SPEAKER_25]: Top things you want to see stuck on the giant Katamari ball at E3.
[SPEAKER_25]: Number three, reject false icon sticker.
[SPEAKER_25]: A very large reject false icon sticker.
[SPEAKER_25]: Number two, a shitty Max 300 remix CD.
[SPEAKER_25]: And the number one thing you would like to have...
[SPEAKER_25]: Stuck on the Katamari Dimashiball at E3 is a copy of Katamari Dimashiball.
[SPEAKER_28]: You guys are so ironic.
[SPEAKER_28]: I love you all.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's like Ray Yane on your wedding day.
[SPEAKER_28]: A little too ironic.
[SPEAKER_25]: Don't you think?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, a little too wrath.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_28]: But not really.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm sorry, but if you can have your gorillas thing...
[SPEAKER_25]: Then I'm entitled to this little clip that makes me think of what just happened there in Listless.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are such an Alanis whore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now you guys should hear Rob at karaoke.
[SPEAKER_02]: He gets on stage and the question that passes through the entire karaoke room, Which Alanis song is it this week, Rob?
Cho-Chi.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: But see, and isn't it unfortunate, it doesn't have the same ring to it.
[SPEAKER_25]: And then, that's funny, because the way that goes is that MPQ goes, that song isn't ironic, it's just unfortunate, and dudes go, it's not a tumor.
[SPEAKER_25]: Girl.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't do it the way she does.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, girl.
[SPEAKER_25]: Girl.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, now that we've lost half our audience there, hey, at least we're not talking about the damn lawsuit anymore.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: Here we go, FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_25]: And you have a new FU song.
[SPEAKER_25]: You couldn't just stick with one, could you, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_25]: You have a new one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because people butched about my last one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I used it for other things on the show, so I found something more appropriate.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_25]: And Jamie, why do we do the FUs every single week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we can.
[SPEAKER_02]: What better to illustrate my wrath than to use Dan's ear, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_02]: the wrath of God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Girl, I can't do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, big F you to the bitches who broke into Rob's car.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_02]: FU to missing out on homemade banana, not banana, coconut cream pie with extra coconut in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a bite of it that was hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then FU to being so weak in Blue Burst that like one damn hit from the dragon put me down to four hit points.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to level some more.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, and damn expensive to play FOMORO.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, you have to...
[SPEAKER_02]: Buy this and buy that and buy your... And I miss my hacked item from the Xbox one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I carry around a giant pink purse.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I miss that too.
[SPEAKER_25]: I want to carry a pink purse.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eventually, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: I miss how rap is too.
[SPEAKER_02]: And F you to Loki's song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it is annoying and I picked it just to annoy our listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I love you all.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not really too angsty, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been in a fantastic... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: An FU... This song gets really quiet, by the way, towards the end.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll have to pick something else.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm going to loop it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you to having to pick another song, damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um... Oh, yeah, and an FU to FreeMP3Player.com or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because now I have to wait for them to verify it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: My man wouldn't let me buy a mini-disc player.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I think that there should be a PayPal account or something set up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called the Buy DarkSakura, a mini-disc player fund.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wouldn't that be awesome?
[SPEAKER_25]: For you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need a mini-disc player.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chatroom, you love me, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Buy me one, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's get to Loki's FU.
[SPEAKER_25]: He actually sent me one.
[SPEAKER_25]: I wish I could read these like Loki does his FUs.
[SPEAKER_25]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_25]: Loki's FU this week is towards German spammers.
[SPEAKER_25]: I've been getting tons of German spam all day on my Yahoo account.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's his only FU.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's not as funny when I read them, I'm sorry guys.
[SPEAKER_25]: But now it's my turn.
[SPEAKER_25]: My FU goes to the little motherfucker with no balls that broke into my car this week.
[SPEAKER_25]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_25]: I got the last laugh in the end because that fucking stereo you stole was broken.
[SPEAKER_25]: Fuck you for stealing my class ring.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't give a fuck if I hated high school.
[SPEAKER_25]: You had no right to take that shit.
[SPEAKER_25]: Why do people on this planet think that they can take shit that's not theirs?
[SPEAKER_25]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_25]: Die.
[SPEAKER_25]: F you to the fact that I wasn't able to take a trip to the Bay Area this weekend because I was kind of looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_25]: But there's just more important shit that's got to be done.
[SPEAKER_25]: F you to all the stress that comes before E3.
[SPEAKER_25]: F you to all the work that I'm going to have to be doing at E3 next week because I'm just supposed to go there and play games all day.
[SPEAKER_25]: But no, I'm going to slave my butt off for you guys.
[SPEAKER_25]: So, you know, I hope that you guys just kiss my ass after this because, you know, we're going to work it for you.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_25]: I do it because I love you guys.
[SPEAKER_25]: But damn, E3's a lot of work.
[SPEAKER_25]: An FU to stress, an FU to the fact that I'm short on money right now because of a glitch and stuff I don't want to talk about.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's my FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's get to the chatroom FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_25]: This is the Captain Jack cover of Holiday, by the way.
[SPEAKER_25]: Mikhail Tov would like to give his first FU to his computer for randomly freezing when he's in the middle of Guild Wars or Phantasy Star Blue Burst.
[SPEAKER_25]: Second FU is for that horrible American dad show.
[SPEAKER_25]: The only redeeming factor on it, which isn't even enough to make me watch it, is Greg and Terry because they are adorable.
[SPEAKER_25]: And finally, FU to my car making funny funky noises.
[SPEAKER_25]: MPQ says, I somehow expect half the people to F you the Konami vs. Rockstar thing, so I'm going with something different.
[SPEAKER_25]: Fuck Colors and 2DX, I will never beat that fucking song.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh yeah, and F you to kicking and screaming, total waste of money, I walked out, it was so bad.
[SPEAKER_25]: Doob says, F you to Brazilian people who play MMORPGs because they can't speak proper English.
[SPEAKER_25]: F you to being a high school freshman because when I think, yay, school is almost over, I think, oh crap, three more years left.
[SPEAKER_03]: You just need to learn to speak Portuguese.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think we should just stick doobs in a trash can.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, because he's a Gorillaz fan now.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know how we used to do to freshmen in high schools?
[SPEAKER_25]: You'd stick them in a trash can, you'd can them.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'd tell them that there was a pool under the gym.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so they'd pass us to use it, and then an elevator passed.
[SPEAKER_25]: Even though your school was on one floor?
[SPEAKER_03]: We were two floors.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, our school's only one floor, and people would sell elevator passes.
[SPEAKER_25]: Ranma says, F you to my coworkers for screwing me out of my time off for an amazement on Memorial Day weekend.
[SPEAKER_25]: Don't say shit when I put the screws to you.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, girl.
[SPEAKER_25]: Dark Knight says, a big F you to singlehood, and, um, that's it.
[SPEAKER_25]: LemonLimeJump says, F you to the Domino's cheeseburger pizza for being really disgusting.
[SPEAKER_25]: I could have told you that without eating the damn thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think even those cheeseburger hot pockets are disgusting.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know if you've ever had one.
[SPEAKER_25]: They're gross.
[SPEAKER_25]: I enjoy a good cheeseburger and I love pizza, but that thing's gross.
[SPEAKER_25]: Avoid.
[SPEAKER_25]: Uh, Ninst says, oh, no, never mind, he's, uh, sending me messages on PSO.
[SPEAKER_25]: Uh, Jin4576 says, F you to Kingston, New York, Cyber Station.
[SPEAKER_25]: Your DDR-EX machine is in such bad condition and you don't care.
[SPEAKER_25]: The pad is on a tilt and you think that putting tiles on the bottom of the pad will fix it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Here's some advice, get a new machine or actually try to fix the machine and not half-ass it.
[SPEAKER_25]: And Illusion would like to say, F you to the whole tricky business with Konami and Roxor.
[SPEAKER_25]: Did Roxor do something illegal?
[SPEAKER_25]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_25]: Do they deserve to be sued?
[SPEAKER_25]: But couldn't they have sued them a week after the game was released or something?
[SPEAKER_25]: Fuck whoever predicted that F you, you jerk.
[SPEAKER_25]: It wasn't Miklatov, by the way, Illusion.
[SPEAKER_25]: It was the guy after him.
[SPEAKER_25]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_25]: That was the last F you.
[SPEAKER_25]: I just want to add to that, though.
[SPEAKER_25]: You do know that lawsuits aren't written overnight, right?
[SPEAKER_25]: and the rumor going around is that this thing has actually been planned for months and it's just funny timing or something.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_25]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_25]: LemonLimeJump in the chatroom says, Reject Grote's Pizza.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's really good.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: One thing we want to tell you guys about, because we're getting towards the end of the show, we're going to do some Ask Orange Lounge real quick, because we know it's kind of the E3 edition.
[SPEAKER_25]: So send us your questions for Ask Orange Lounge right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: We're going to do a quick break, then we'll come back and answer those.
[SPEAKER_25]: What we do want to say, though, we have an email address set up.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, actually, no, I've got to make one tweak to it, and then we will give you the email address.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_25]: We will give you that email address when we come back from this break.
[SPEAKER_25]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, I'm with it tonight.
[SPEAKER_28]: You are so there.
[SPEAKER_28]: You know, you were just so on the ball.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_28]: You were on the ball, then you fell off.
[SPEAKER_25]: We're going to take a quick two-song break.
[SPEAKER_25]: Just a quick two-song break.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll be back with Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_25]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your Ask Orange Lounge question, and we will be back after this.
[SPEAKER_25]: Start it off with a little bit of a... I think this could be an anthem song for Jamie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's Bad Girls.
[SPEAKER_25]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi, this is Mel B of RTF.
[SPEAKER_17]: And for an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Mel B can join us on all the fun together.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey, if you're a broke ass like I am, why don't you come to one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's Orange Lounge Radio Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_16]: Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free
[SPEAKER_10]: Welcome!
[SPEAKER_25]: Welcome!
[SPEAKER_25]: Melby, actually, he will not be joining the on-air staff because he can't because of where he is physically.
[SPEAKER_25]: But he will be joining our news staff on OrangeLaunchRadio.com and bringing us news and articles and observations.
[SPEAKER_25]: And unfortunately, this kind of comes at the cost of DDR Spot, the site he used to work for, is gone.
[SPEAKER_25]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_25]: So sorry, DDR Spot.
[SPEAKER_25]: I will hold on to my t-shirt forever even though it's three sizes too big so let's get to some Ask Orange Lounge we don't have a little bit of show left here so let's get to some Ask Orange Lounge
[SPEAKER_25]: Question from the chat room, will Mel be on the show later?
[SPEAKER_25]: He will be on the show as much as he can, but unfortunately since he lives like a well over a two hour drive away, it doesn't happen very often.
[SPEAKER_25]: But we do appreciate when he's here.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll try to get him at least on Skype a little more often.
[SPEAKER_25]: Give us some perspective.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's Ask Orange Lounge Some stupid question What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_25]: Will we find out that we are so very tired because all this prepping for E3 has us really stressed out?
[SPEAKER_25]: That's the most karaoke I do on this show, by the way.
[SPEAKER_25]: Illusion wants to know, has anyone seen the movie Crash yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_25]: I have not, but I want to.
[SPEAKER_25]: I've heard good things about it, because Illusion, you won't shut up when you tell me about the movie and you say it's good.
[SPEAKER_25]: But actually, I think my roommate's family or something went to go see it, and they said it was very good.
[SPEAKER_25]: So I want to see it.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I saw the trailer, and it looked good.
[SPEAKER_28]: I want to see Unleashed.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was actually going to try and go see Crash like two nights ago, but it was too late.
[SPEAKER_25]: Like, all the theaters were closed.
[SPEAKER_25]: Man.
[SPEAKER_25]: Doobs says, were you a jock quarterback giving swirlies to nerds back in high school?
[SPEAKER_25]: Or an energetic cheerleader, as LemonLimeJump said.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was neither.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was a band geek.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was a band geek too.
[SPEAKER_25]: Not only was I a band geek, I was in yearbook and student council.
[SPEAKER_25]: So I guess that kind of makes me a cheerleader.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was on the chess team and on pep squad.
[SPEAKER_25]: You have to remember that my role in...
[SPEAKER_25]: Ranma wants to know, favorite Nintendo character and why?
[SPEAKER_25]: Link, he's just hot.
[SPEAKER_25]: Older Link.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_25]: Melee 2.
[SPEAKER_25]: If they do Melee 2, I'm hoping that's like a surprise announcement at E3.
[SPEAKER_25]: I would just die.
[SPEAKER_25]: Um, now just tell me... LemonLimeJump wants to know, now just tell me, Liege... Is that a mistype?
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_25]: Just tell me, just how do we know the Earth to be banana-shaped?
[SPEAKER_28]: Um, I can illustrate that with sheep bladders.
[SPEAKER_25]: Is that a Hitchhiker's Reference?
[SPEAKER_28]: No, it's Monty Python.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, Monty Python.
[SPEAKER_28]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's it!
[SPEAKER_25]: We have all the, um...
[SPEAKER_25]: We have all the questions we got from our listeners.
[SPEAKER_25]: That wasn't a whole lot tonight.
[SPEAKER_25]: They're kind of quiet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was going to take that.
[SPEAKER_25]: This one poor person has been calling into the Skype line like all night long.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's take it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, I was going to take it, but he's not on now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Person call.
[SPEAKER_25]: You have one minute.
[SPEAKER_25]: Maybe I should just call him.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, go for it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll see if he picks up.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_25]: We're calling you because you've been calling us all night long and we felt bad.
[SPEAKER_25]: Please say something.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hey, you're there.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_15]: RPGKing7.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hello, RPGKing7.
[SPEAKER_25]: Real quick, because we're at the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_25]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I was just wondering what DS games you're looking forward to hear about, sorry, to hear from E3.
[SPEAKER_25]: DS games, Animal Crossing DS, I am all about the Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_25]: If they have anything on Katamari Damacy, I'd be really curious about that too, but Animal Crossing is the one I have to see.
[SPEAKER_25]: And anything that is online enabled with the DS, I would say.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'd have to see that.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm sorry, Animal Crossing Animal Crossing DS will own anything and bless Nintendo because they're the only company that can get away with this crap repackaging the same damn thing and putting a new bow on it and we all eat this shit up and I am so excited about Animal Crossing DS and it's the same damn thing as before with, you know, a few new features damn you Nintendo, damn you how about you, sir?
[SPEAKER_25]: what are you looking forward to?
[SPEAKER_15]: um, I
[SPEAKER_25]: Castlevania DS because it's the first time in a while we've had a real sequel to a Castlevania game I didn't even think of that I haven't picked up a DS yet but if it's good then it'll be what I'll pick up a DS for I didn't even think of Castlevania DS I definitely can't wait for that one The Konami booth is going to be so happening this year Oh my god, you guys don't even know the half of it Trust me, you don't even know the half of it How swinging that Konami booth is going to be this year So I'm excited Anything else?
[SPEAKER_25]: Because it's the end of the show
[SPEAKER_15]: No, just to say hi to you from up here in Canada.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, hello, Canada.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Don't get too cold up there, okay?
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll try not to.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's always so cold up here.
[SPEAKER_25]: I know.
[SPEAKER_25]: I know those stereotypes.
[SPEAKER_25]: Got to love them.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, I'm just going to walk on over to the beach as soon as we're done with the show here and run into some celebrities.
[SPEAKER_25]: I have a date with Cameron Diaz after the show.
[SPEAKER_25]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: See you.
[SPEAKER_25]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_25]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_25]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_25]: And if you've seen our pictures before, because they used to be on the website a long time ago, but if you've seen our pictures before, yeah, we all have blonde hair and blue eyes.
[SPEAKER_25]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good thing I'm not from California.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it automatically happens when you get your driver's license.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, it's this process they make you go through, actually.
[SPEAKER_25]: Jamie, your final thought for tonight.
[SPEAKER_25]: Um... Give me money.
[SPEAKER_25]: Actually, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_25]: I have one thing real quick.
[SPEAKER_25]: What?
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: If you want to send us an email, if you want to send us an email and ask us a question about E3, you have something specific you want us to find at the show, what you have to do is send an email to E3...
[SPEAKER_25]: at OrangeLoungeRadio.com You've got to wait about two minutes.
[SPEAKER_25]: Don't send it just yet because I'm actually creating the account as we speak.
[SPEAKER_25]: Send an email to E3 at OrangeLoungeRadio.com This is the email we're going to be checking at E3 and answering the questions on our podcast.
[SPEAKER_25]: So if you have anything you want to ask in advance or anything, send it over email.
[SPEAKER_25]: Send it in a couple minutes and we will be reading those emails at E3 and getting responses to you via our podcast.
[SPEAKER_25]: So you can kind of live vicariously through us in that sense.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm a mini-disc player and reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know, this whole thing is that happened with the lawsuit and everything.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's all about protecting what is, you know, Konami.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's protecting Konami's patents.
[SPEAKER_25]: And it's all about, you know, what Konami, you know, came up with and everything and people infringing on that.
[SPEAKER_25]: Very interesting, the kinds of things that, you know, were patented in this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_25]: It would be very interesting to see, like, all the different things that Konami's patented.
[SPEAKER_25]: In regards to DDR, of course.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Have a good one, you guys.
[SPEAKER_25]: Final word of the show.
[SPEAKER_25]: I guess since it's just me and you, I'll give it to you because I don't want it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_04]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would say, don't look for all of your happiness in just one place.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I mean, it's okay to ask the big questions in life.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't expect any answers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, yeah, don't take it all too... No, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_00]: You should always think... No, that's wrong.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, actually, I don't think I've learned anything.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that is a lesson in itself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_25]: We've got a podcast to tape, so we're booting you off in the stream.
[SPEAKER_25]: Thank you very much for tuning in to Supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: We do appreciate it, guys.
[SPEAKER_25]: What we're going to do now is we're going to drop you guys from the stream, but just reconnect in like 15 seconds, and you go back to Orange Lounge Radio's Bomani Music