[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of May 9th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once again, welcome to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your home for what you, the gamer, really want to know about.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joining me, as always, my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say hello to DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yo, yo, yo, what up, my homies?
[SPEAKER_03]: What up?
[SPEAKER_02]: Girl, what up?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ceiling, Sky, my cue.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not your voice tonight, you're not perky tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's much better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you're primed and ready for G4 now, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm not on enough drugs, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say hello to Loki as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: How you doing, sir?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm looking for this... I'm trying to find this one game.
[SPEAKER_01]: My friend at work was telling me about this crappy truck game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like this
[SPEAKER_01]: Diesel Truck Racing Game
[SPEAKER_01]: I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've seen it before somewhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to download it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't actually want to buy it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just want to download it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I call that a Walmart game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the reason why I call that a Walmart game is if you've ever been to Walmart, which I'm sure most people have if they have them in your area, if you go into the Walmart arcade, quote unquote, what do they always have?
[SPEAKER_02]: They have the crane game that you can play.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they always have some type of hunting game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Deer Hunter.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then usually they'll have like an 18-wheeler game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the Sega 18-wheeler game was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Walmart doesn't have the Sega 18-wheeler game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Walmart's...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not big on Walmart, but we won't get into those reasons here on this program because we're going to talk about games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranma is my favorite store.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to read more about it, read my blog.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And your games, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: The games that you've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Metal Slug X last night on the MAME with my man.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we beat it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game's freaking hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's kind of cool walking around as a zombie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, your mic was acting up there a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: We got you, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I need to discipline it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get me a ruler.
[SPEAKER_03]: Smack that ass.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wasn't it, mommy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Metal Slug X Metal Slug X
[SPEAKER_03]: and it still has all the Pole Position logos and all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll put pictures on it up on the web.
[SPEAKER_03]: You need to.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we played Metal Slug X last night and I'm hoping to convince them to play through some Space Harrier with me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you put infinite credits in Space Harrier and it's on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because that game lasts forever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or maybe some Blazing Star.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else besides the retro?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, widescreen Pong.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, how about you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Isn't it like scary that
[SPEAKER_01]: 2 out of 3 people in this studio have a MAME cabinet in their... Rub it in a little more, why don't ya?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what we could do for you?
[SPEAKER_03]: We could get you one of those mini Mac things.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know? $500.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get you a cabinet that they're throwing away for $100.
[SPEAKER_03]: We could build you a MAME for under $800.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, I live upstairs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, dudette.
[SPEAKER_02]: I live upstairs.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not hauling a MAME.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can carry a gutted machine upstairs.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not that heavy.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had two pole position machines in my living room.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all about Barcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I want to get the MAME cabinet in here, I'm going to have to get rid of your chair.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, our next project is getting one of those cocktail machines, the table-looking ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that I would have in the house.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would get rid of the kitchen table, even though it's my roommate's, and have the cocktail cabinet.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be rock.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we're planning on doing that as our next meme.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, Loki, your gaming week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I tried Super Monkey Ball Deluxe for the PlayStation 2, and I'm here to say that it sucks ass.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's
[SPEAKER_01]: Super Monkey Ball lends itself to make it look like oh yeah it's a cool kids game people might like it you go and play it and you're like what the fuck this sucks it's hard and it sucks I didn't like it and it was boring and I just didn't like it then I looked at I haven't really opened it up yet Area 51 the brand new game so maybe I'll play that I don't really know it's like all these first person shooters that are coming out nowadays it's really big whoop you know
[SPEAKER_01]: Final Fantasy XI Final Fantasy XI Final Fantasy XI Final Fantasy XI
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I waited for the last thing to die at the end of our chain, and I fake disconnected.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's what I've been doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: That and a lot of Ridge Racer for the PSP and Luminous.
[SPEAKER_01]: Again?
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been playing Ridge... I beat Pac-Man, finally.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I beat... What was it?
[SPEAKER_01]: I still have the...
[SPEAKER_01]: Beat the Angel car a little bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played it a few times and it's still really hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't the Pac-Man car cool though?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not as good as the one from Ridge Racer 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of Pac-Man, I have to get this off my chest before we get much further.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you know your Pac-Pix game came out this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, but that's not the one that I was really interested in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I was listening to a previous podcast and you said something about the Pac-Pix game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want Pac-Pix, but I want the freaking Marble Madness looking one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'll pack and roll.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pack and roll.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, Loki, anything else?
[SPEAKER_01]: So anyways, yeah, just Ridge Racer and Luminous.
[SPEAKER_01]: I unlocked two more skins today.
[SPEAKER_01]: But as you know, really Luminous, it comes down to I don't have enough time to play it, so I can't really get that far in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, I don't know, Ridge Racer, I like it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was actually looking at maybe getting some more games coming out pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, they have, like, I don't really know what the hell it is with the PSP and the games coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, for example, you know, you have Metal Gear Solid and people are like, oh, yeah, Metal Gear Solid, awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, it's a card game, turn-based card game.
[SPEAKER_01]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_02]: Metal Gear Acid.
[SPEAKER_01]: It actually plays more like one of those old-school strategy games.
[SPEAKER_01]: What the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_01]: And then you go, like, oh, Armored Core's coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_01]: Mech Combat, yay!
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I don't get to control them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_01]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, I had games like that, or they actually had games for the PlayStation, you know, come out like that, and they sucked.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, where you had to create the AI for them and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's not fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: You want to play, you know, mech combat against each other.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't want to, like, oh, I'm going to program the coolest mech out there, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, so, before I ramble too much, you know, I was looking... Too late.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, you know, I was looking at Mercury.
[SPEAKER_01]: I might get that, but, you know, I'm waiting for Smart Bomb, which should be coming out pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I actually did play another game.
[SPEAKER_01]: What else?
[SPEAKER_03]: I played the Midway Collection and played Tempest on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tempest isn't in the Midway Collection.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't Tempest... Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Atari one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Atari.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I played Tempest on it which was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Tempest is awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you just go back and forth just like with Trackball?
[SPEAKER_02]: Tempest is awesome, but Tempest 2000 was better.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all about the music in Tempest 2000.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Super Zapper Recharge.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else?
[SPEAKER_02]: What was my gaming week like?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I did one of these interesting things where I bought a game without actually having the console.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if any of you have ever done this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually bought a copy of Luminous this week, even though I personally don't own a PSP yet because I'm poor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: My friend actually went and we were out and about the other night and he decided he wanted to get a PSP but he couldn't really afford because you know when you go to buy a game system, you buy the game system and then you buy the game and the memory card and whatever else comes with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So pretty soon you're making a pretty big investment.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't really get a PSP for $250.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to put in $350 if you want to get everything good with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he decided he was going to buy it all, but he was only going to get one game.
[SPEAKER_02]: He decided to get Darkstalkers.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm like, dude, you can't have a PSP and not have Luminous.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to buy Luminous.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to get a PSP soon enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I bought Luminous like the sucker I am.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so I let him borrow it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if any of you guys have ever done that before, but that's just crazy me, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess I had money to burn, and I don't know why I would buy that and just not buy a PSP, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a moment of weakness.
[SPEAKER_02]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_02]: But at least I have a copy of Luminous now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, this week, I got to go to my very first video game premiere, which was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a party for Red Octane's In the Groove, which is kind of, it's very, very similar to Dance Dance Revolution, and in fact, if you are a member of the
[SPEAKER_02]: Music Gaming Community.
[SPEAKER_02]: You probably have seen these debates going back and forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is In The Groove too much like DDR or what?
[SPEAKER_02]: All those arguments aside, I had a really good time at the show, which took place in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_02]: They really know how to throw a party.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Open bar and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game itself looks very smooth.
[SPEAKER_02]: It made a great transition from the arcade to the home version.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was very impressed with the new dance pads that showed up as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Red Octane's new afterburner pad, awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was pretty happy with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, if you are a fan of In the Groove, you're not going to be disappointed by the home release, what can I say?
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was pretty much my gaming week, not a whole lot else outside of that that I haven't already been playing and talked about on a previous show.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, why don't we get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, since we were talking about the music games, and a lot of people know us because of our music and gaming affiliation that our 24-hour stream has over on Live365, we
[SPEAKER_02]: There actually were some leaks this week that DDR Extreme 2 and Ultramix 3 are confirmed and going to be shown at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's pretty cool because Ultramix 3 has some interesting new modes in it, such as quest mode, where it sounds like you're going to have a story where you go around and meet other DDR characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of a first for a home release.
[SPEAKER_02]: Should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I've been actually asking for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, I think it'd be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean,
[SPEAKER_01]: How bad can it be?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dance, Dance, Dance bad?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even remember Dance, Dance, Dance old.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, Extreme 2, getting a lot of raised eyebrows because the article that was leaked on GamePro confirms that
[SPEAKER_02]: Genie in a Bottle, and Oops I Did It Again are going to be in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a lot of us hardcore music game fans are like, oh god, oh god no, oh god.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we're kind of hoping that those are the only two really, really commercial songs in it to sell the game, and then the rest are going to be like cool new stuff, you know, from not well-known artists, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did they confirm that it was a purple interface?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Inside joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, Red Octane announcing not only are they publishing in the group, but they're going to do a new harmonics game later this year, Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now you can dance at home and you can play the guitar at home.
[SPEAKER_02]: How cool is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can sing at home.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can be a one-man band, dance, sing, and play the guitar, but not all at once.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly?
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless you have multiple systems.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be pretty smart.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, honestly, think about this.
[SPEAKER_01]: That'd be really cool, land-wise, to link these games together for, like, you know, kind of like they did with the arcade with Drum Mania and Guitar Freaks, to be able to land these, like, different games together or whatever and be able to play, like, a song.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, one person sings the lyrics, the other person plays the guitar, the other one, you know, does, you know, whatever, you know, a keyboard or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why don't they do that?
[SPEAKER_01]: This is what they need to be doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wouldn't complain.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's my idea, Pat and Penny.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Video Games Live
[SPEAKER_02]: This is being put together by Tommy Talarco, who you guys might know from the television and other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's done music for games, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, goody.
[SPEAKER_02]: G4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the Clear Channel Music Group are putting this thing together.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be starting off with a July 6th show at the Hollywood Bowl, and it'll go on some other venues announced in Denver and Boston.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll be doing some music, playing Halo, Metal Gear Solid music, and then, interestingly enough, they also mention...
[SPEAKER_02]: Donkey Kong, and Pong Pong didn't have music, did it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no idea what they mean by music from Pong but it's in there, so go figure Also interesting to note, Final Fantasy will have its music played even though Final Fantasy is doing their own concert so I don't know if they had the license or whatever they're doing They're being sneaky
[SPEAKER_02]: But also, they're going to say, not only is it the orchestra playing the music, but choirs and laser shows and footage of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Freaking laser shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, goody, laser shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be like, you ever been to one of those shows where they play Pink Floyd's Dark Side of the Moon to Wizard of Oz?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Freaking lasers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are they ill-tempered video games?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so that should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you guys have any interest in checking this out?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I'm going to the Final Fantasy concert, as is Loki, the more friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does this sound like something we ought to be getting tickets for, too?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm going to the art show, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I'm going clubbing, and then I'm getting some chicken and waffles.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but this is something that's touring the country.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not just E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that being said, is it something... Hypothetically, if this came to San Francisco, would you go?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: If somebody drives me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would not go because Tommy Talarco is attached to it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tommy Talarco for me is like Bobby Flay on the goddamn Food Network.
[SPEAKER_01]: And for anyone that knows me, you know how much I hate Bobby Flay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will actually sit there and watch Bobby Flay's show and scowl at him the entire time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Even though he can't see me through the TV, but I will do it anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I friggin' hate him because he's a little whiny bastard.
[SPEAKER_01]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Tommy Talarco is a little whiny bastard just as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: He is the Bobby Flay
[SPEAKER_01]: MTV Movie Awards
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, you might be thinking, what the heck do movie awards have to do with video games?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know, it's just like, what the heck does music have to do with MTV anymore?
[SPEAKER_02]: Good question.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, MTV Music Awards, I'm sorry, the Movie Awards will be adding a category.
[SPEAKER_02]: Best Video Game Based on a Movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is great.
[SPEAKER_02]: The nominees for Best Video Game Based on a Movie, Spider-Man 2, Chronicles of Riddick, Escape from Butcher Bay,
[SPEAKER_02]: Harry Potter and the Prisoner
[SPEAKER_02]: Geeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolute Harry Potter geeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that that's bad, I'm just saying, they're geeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I only bought one Harry Potter game, and it was awful, but it seemed like it was based more off the book than off the movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was not a fan of the Quidditch game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why isn't Grand Theft Auto nominated?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's best video game based on a movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Vice City was based on Miami Vice, a TV show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it was based on Miami Vice, and it was also based on... Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Al Pacino movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Scarface?
[SPEAKER_01]: Scarface, yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think, unfortunately, it's a little bit of a stretch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, darn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thankfully, they didn't do best movie based on a video game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe they were going to try and do it, but then they realized, gee, what came out this year?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alone in the Dark, Resident Evil Apocalypse.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's the other one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Was there another one?
[SPEAKER_02]: The island one, Alone in the Dark.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alone in the Dark.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they thought, we really want to give an award to one of these crappy games?
[SPEAKER_01]: Please do not.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't want to hear an award winning Alone in the Dark.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that would be horrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we don't need that, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm making any more movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of movies, what do you think about this, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: The PSP UMD format has been cracked.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can now read the files off of the UMD disks for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is, let's see, coming off a story that actually Engadget ran.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, that they did this.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now ISO's popping up all over the internet.
[SPEAKER_01]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, there's three of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's, um, Wipeout, the USA version.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's Ridge Racer, the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then there's some other tower of some... Vampire Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_01]: Vampire Chronicles, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_01]: I already have the ISO for the white belt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but what can you do with it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because the USDs are in those little case things and you can't really burn... It was kind of smart what Sony did there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet they did it just to combat piracy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, here's what you can do with it, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can take the files and try the reverse engineering, which is going to be close to impossible.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can rip some of the, like... I'm sure some of the graphics from it, but that's really useless crap anyways, you know?
[SPEAKER_01]: You can look at... There are individual files in there that... They're basically these files called ELF files or whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're basically like executables or whatever, and you can probably try to create something out of that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, the whole reason I think that they ripped Wipeout is because they're looking for the web browser.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wasn't ELF a band?
[SPEAKER_01]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was ELO, Electric Light Orchestra.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe I'm thinking EMF.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nevermind.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, this is just a step.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, because later on this week, actually, or last week, I should say, right after this story came out, they actually announced that they had run code on the Japanese PSP, the version 1.0, because all the US ones are shipped version 1.5, where the whole is covered.
[SPEAKER_01]: But basically, this guy who actually has one of the...
[SPEAKER_01]: One of the development kits, he created his own Hello World program and it runs off of a memory card.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any other interesting hack stories going on?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've been saying it, and there's actually the joke out there about installing Linux on Dead Badger, but now it's Linux for the DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have successfully...
[SPEAKER_01]: Booted a kernel on there, and for those who don't know, that's like the operating system type thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we're actually running this shell called Sash, and simple text games are on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you know, all those old, like, you know, things, Zork or whatever, you know, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, yeah, there's information on that on themodgods.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have a whole thing on it, and...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't really follow the Linux thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would only be cool if Zork was one of the text games that they ported.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then I might consider... They have Zork as a 404 message.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, but anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it'll be cool just because you can do an actual soft keyboard on there using the touchscreen versus trying to type on the...
[SPEAKER_01]: PSP is just crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only one game cart needed.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there are eight players, they'll actually use both DS screens during the game to kind of spread things out a little bit because it might get kind of crowded with eight people on one screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully it can restore my faith in the DS a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's anywhere near as cool as Super Bomberman 2 was, I'll have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: June 21st is the date we'll find out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's go ahead and let DarkSakura present her advice column because, you know, we here at Orange Lounge Radio, we're not just here to talk about games, but we're also here to better your life because if we talked about video games all the time, we'd have no time to go out and get our hair did.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, DarkSakura, it's your turn to give us your advice column.
[SPEAKER_02]: What are you going to talk to us about tonight, my friend?
[SPEAKER_03]: Today's advice is how to treat a severed limb.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number one, locate any individual bleeding arteries on the stump.
[SPEAKER_03]: Two, pinch off the large arteries.
[SPEAKER_03]: Three, apply a tourniquet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Choose a strip of material at least an inch wide, tie it around the stump as close to the end as possible so it will not fall off when tightened.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tie it moderately tight, tighten just enough to stop most of the bleeding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keep pinching the arteries.
[SPEAKER_03]: Four, tie off the ends of any blood vessels being pinched.
[SPEAKER_03]: Use fishing line, dental floss, or heavy thread and a sewing needle if available to carefully tie off arteries.
5.
[SPEAKER_03]: Clean the stump thoroughly.
6.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loosen the tourniquet.
[SPEAKER_03]: As pressure from the tourniquet decreases, check your ties.
[SPEAKER_03]: If bleeding is just moderate, you can remove the tourniquet.
[SPEAKER_03]: In order to preserve tissue at the stump, do not leave a tourniquet applied for more than 90 minutes.
7.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dress the stump.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tightly cover the end of the stump with clean cloth or gauze.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now my final advice though... Yes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop playing with those branch cutters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Clean the stump thoroughly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, you don't want any, you know, axe shavings on it or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or chainsaw oil.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ew, now I'm thinking about the end of Fargo, and I'm getting all grossed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've never seen that, but, you know, they had on a... Well, I just wrote it for you, but it's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like I'll ever see it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, they had on the Darwin Awards.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was two guys, brothers, and they had this bright idea that one would cut off the other's leg with a chainsaw.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hilarious!
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, of course he died.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if he had heard your advice, maybe he wouldn't have died.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nah, I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_03]: He cut through a major artery in the leg, and that's one of the ones that's like cutting one in your neck.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just trying to promote your column over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, but I still don't like stupid people to breed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really, your column will do no good for stupid people.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is how to preserve the lives of intelligent people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about another big story that was going on in the gaming world.
[SPEAKER_02]: Namco has merged with Bandai.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bandai has bought Japanese developer and publisher Namco.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be named the new company
[SPEAKER_02]: Namco Bandai Holdings and it is official as of September 29th 2005 and I believe this makes them the third largest don't quote me on that third largest gaming company well you know this also means that means that what we get out of this is a new Dragon Ball Z game with the Tekken 5 engine be interesting but I don't know I always thought maybe this is me personally maybe I'm just not
[SPEAKER_02]: Giving enough respect to Bandai, but I always kind of preferred what Namco put out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm a little sad that Bandai bought Namco and not the other way around.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you play imports, though, it's all about Bandai.
[SPEAKER_03]: They put out all the DBZ games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bon Presto put out this game that it's a lot like Guardian Heroes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe that's what it is, because I play some imports, but I don't play a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what this means?
[SPEAKER_01]: That in the next Tekken game, you might have a hidden character that is Hello Kitty.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: You may have Goku in Tekken.
[SPEAKER_03]: If we could have Gon in Tekken 3, just think about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to hold my breath for help.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's Maru in Tekken 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: That
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello Kitty Fighting Game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The concept kind of scares me a little.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: They really need to do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: It would just be cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: I choose Twinkle Twinkle Twinkle Twin Stars.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, what would be great is to do the Hello Kitty Fighting Game and make it as violent as like Tekken 5 or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Twin Stars would be about as effective as the Ice Climbers in Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Melee and everybody hates playing the Ice Climbers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know anybody that enjoys playing the Ice Climbers.
[SPEAKER_02]: No way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dan plays the Ice Climbers and he's awesome with them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, he's a freak of nature or something because nobody's good with the ice climbers.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have ice climbers on our nest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, dude, that game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you guys have any feedback on our show, you want to write us and tell us that you are an ice climbers player, I don't know, send us an email, togo, T-O-G-O, at orangeloungeradio.com, and we might read some of your letters on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now one thing that we have been getting in the mailbox is that we have been getting a lot of response from folks overseas actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes we have.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually as a result now we're going to start covering a little bit more of the UK Europe news for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's start it off.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, you have agreed to kind of head up the UK scene.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what's going on for our friends overseas?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, first and foremost, because I know there's been an issue of debate because for a while there was one thing being said by Sony and Amazon had a different date for the release dates of the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now both of them are completely in sync.
[SPEAKER_03]: The PSP will be available for £179 on 1st of September.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be a value pack that consists of the system, a pouch, 32MB memory stick, duo, a battery pack, headphones with remote control, AC adapter, wrist strap, cloth, and a sampler disc.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can also go to yrpsp.com and order a copy of Spider-Man 2 that will be shipped to you for free.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's an interesting way of doing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Amazon UK is taking pre-orders at £179.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also do have a few release dates for GameCube.
[SPEAKER_03]: This month, coming up on the 20th, we have Fairly OddParents Shadow Showdown, an Animaniacs game with an announced date.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dude, they're still making Animaniacs games?
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_01]: No one watches that anymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is it even on TV anymore?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: It must be big in Britain.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: June 2005 for GameCube, Donkey Konga 2, Hit Song Parade, Medal of Honor, European Assault, Killer7, Batman Begins, and
[SPEAKER_02]: Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six 4 Lockdown Bratz Rock Angels Prince of Persia 3 Closes Window
[SPEAKER_03]: Next up on PC, we have Star Wars Galaxies Episode 3, Asheron's Call 2, that's on the 6th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Coming up, Space Rangers Imperial Glory, Deep Sea Tycoon 2, Bard's Tale on the 27th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Skip it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And next month we've got Roller Coaster Tycoon, blah blah blah, and more blah blah blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And second quarter, ER the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Seven Sins is coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seven Sins is coming out, yes indeed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, but she's reading the British chart right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's coming out there too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seven Sins.
[SPEAKER_01]: This game has a mini-game where you take the woman's nipples and they're actually the analog controls and you can play around with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, next up.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have for the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: The 5th we have Star Wars Episode 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have Yoshi's Touch and Go on the 6th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pack Picks on the 20th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Skip Yoshi's Touch and Go.
[SPEAKER_03]: 27th Need for Speed Underground 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: June 2005, we've got another DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a temporary title.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ultimate Card Games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else coming out good?
[SPEAKER_03]: GoldenEye in July.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bomberman DS on the 1st of July.
[SPEAKER_03]: And August, Puyo Pot Fever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which just came out here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I have to get, because I am a Puyo Puyo fangirl.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, see, this is the nice thing for you folks overseas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, you know, whereas for us in...
[SPEAKER_02]: Here in America, it's kind of interesting to hear the delay of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, sometimes we bitch and complain about how long games take to come over from Japan, but man, you're in Britain, you've got to wait for the PAL translation and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: It takes forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we kind of get to hear about that, but it's kind of interesting if you're on the other side of it and you're in Britain listening to this, we can already tell you which games suck, so just skip them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm telling you, don't buy Polarium.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, just to mention, Castlevania DS will be out third quarter.
[SPEAKER_03]: for the PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just going to pick out the stuff that doesn't look really sucky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ghost of the Shell Standalone Complex on the 6th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tenchu, Fatal Shadows, Seven Sins, which we were just mentioning.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alien Hominid for PS2 coming out on the 27th.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hasn't that game been out here for like two years?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, not even two years.
[SPEAKER_03]: NARC is to be announced.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have June 2005, Destroy All Humans, Batman Begins, Medal of Honor, Yu Yu Hakusho, Dark Tournament.
[SPEAKER_03]: and King of Fighters Maximum Impact, which I'm actually going to be getting very soon because I like King of Fighters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Last two sections to go, Xbox, Star Wars Episode 3, blah, blah, blah, Area 51, Alien Hominid, WrestleMania 21, next month, Capcom Fighting Jam, Destroy All Humans, Cold War, Conquer, Grand Theft Auto San Andreas, and...
[SPEAKER_03]: Later on, there's going to be some worms.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, my fiance really liked worms.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, there's Cricket 2005.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, last but not least, on the Game Boy Advance, we have Kingdom Hearts Chain of Memories coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Finally, you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_03]: Herbie Fully Loaded.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't bother.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is, you know, Herbie Lovebug.
[SPEAKER_03]: Koala Brothers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next month, WarioWare Twisted.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mega Man Battle Network 5, Dragon Ball Z Advanced Adventures, Mario Party Advance, Batman Begins, July we have Fantastic Four, and coming up fourth quarter is Prince of Persia 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and they get the Shaman King eventually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking though of our email, we actually did get some good email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lee wrote in and said that we make his LA drive a lot easier to deal with.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also heard from Tommy.
[SPEAKER_03]: He says he enjoys our podcasts and that we hold his attention.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, hey, if we can distract a gamer from the games just for long enough, that totally is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for writing in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: We appreciate the support.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys are awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: XBOX 360
[SPEAKER_01]: of course that MTV special is this week I probably won't be watching because we're lucky enough to get to go to E3 next week so we'll just check it out then honestly folks honestly they've made the console bigger it looks like a freaking PS2 but white it's white and virginal it is bigger it looks the size of now my Comcast receiver and that sucker
[SPEAKER_01]: is huge.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, that's like, this is like one and a half Xbox size-wise.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's almost, it is almost the size of a PC case.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we'll see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_01]: They came up with a brand new original idea for a webcam.
[SPEAKER_01]: My ad is very ugly.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, um, their brand new controller, um,
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that'd be kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_03]: All this is is another example of parents not doing their damn jobs and expecting the government to do it for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the only reason this is going to pass is because they're lazy asses.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why we have censorship.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why the FCC is as rampant as it is these days.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because they do not want to take responsibility.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're going to breed a child, they need to make you sign a fucking contract that says, I am going to raise my child and have some type of control over what they do.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what being a parent is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not about lobbying the government to do it for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's called being fucking lazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have a, I don't know, I'm like, I totally see that point of it, and I'm not saying this is something that, like, needs to happen, but it's kind of one of those things where it's like, it doesn't totally bug me because, you know, we shouldn't sell violent video games to minors, but why do, it's, yeah, I think you're right where the parents have to really have a more active role in what their minors are buying, really.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think having the rating system is good because then you're giving them a way to understand what type of game it is that they're purchasing for their child.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I find it very interesting that they will pass a law for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, they've never passed a law that says a movie theater must make sure that there is a child 17 or when a child 17 or younger is coming in that there is a guardian with them or they will be arrested because that crap happens all the time where kids get into R-rated movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why are you picking on the video game industry?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe there is a law on the books, but you and I know nobody enforces that law.
[SPEAKER_02]: When we were kids, we got narrated movies all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the thing is, and this actually is directly affecting my life, because my fiance manages a GameStop.
[SPEAKER_03]: What if some kid comes in and one of his employees sells the game and then it gets back to GameStop corporate when their parent raises a big fit on it and they fire him as the manager?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's just... You know, this is just more of a case of people sticking their nose where it doesn't belong.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, if you want to stick your nose somewhere, shove it right back up your ass where it's been for the last 50 years.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a very passionate subject for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll probably get some emails on that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I welcome emails on that, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, just... I want...
[SPEAKER_03]: to hear from your parents.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I will tell them exactly how I feel and why they're being retards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Happy Mother's Day, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, happy Mother's Day.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on to just a couple of last stories here.
[SPEAKER_02]: EverQuest 2 is expanding.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a brand new expansion pack coming out called Desert of Flames.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, 40 new creatures, 12 new zones, and you can advance to level 60.
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: We've talked about import gaming, especially on our live three-hour program that we have Sunday nights over on OrangeLawsRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've talked about places where you should buy import games and places where you should not buy import games because we're into import gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: What types of sites on the Internet would you recommend?
[SPEAKER_02]: And keep in mind we're not being sponsored by anybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is just personal opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: What sites would you recommend?
[SPEAKER_03]: and NCSX, first and foremost, Japan Video Games.
[SPEAKER_03]: PlayAsia's been decent to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do know people who've had problems with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually have had good experience with Lixang, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: But NCSX just sits at the top of them, of all of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Japan Video Games is another pretty good one.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's where I ordered my Beatmania 2, my Drumania.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're the only import company I've bought from, actually, and I don't have any complaints.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, but if you say there was one that you would never recommend to anybody and you would say, forget it, don't ever do this, what would you say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Buy right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And why?
[SPEAKER_03]: They have stolen money from me, not delivered promised product.
[SPEAKER_03]: I ordered, and I specified, Japanese Tekken 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: They sent me the Asian release, and then when I emailed them, it says, we didn't make any such promise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Better Business Bureau and the North Carolina Attorney General's Office have taken action against Buy Right Video Games and they have closed their doors and ceased operations as a result.
[SPEAKER_02]: Woo-hoo!
[SPEAKER_02]: Buy Right Video Games, of course, sold used antique and imported games and they were doing refurbished systems and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's interesting because if you check out the website fatwallet.com, a bunch of people were just complaining about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've been complaining about just what Jamie said there, bad service, misrepresenting themselves, and stealing your money.
[SPEAKER_02]: So one quote said that they ordered a Saturn and it was cracked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Soul Calibur didn't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Better Business Bureau says this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Based on BBB files, this company has an unsatisfactory record due to unanswered complaints concerning delivery problems and product dissatisfaction.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Bureau has processed 414 complaints about this company in the last 36 months.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you one of those?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I actually never got my thing to the Better Business Bureau.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have the letter prepared.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm actually hoping that they are doing a class action lawsuit because I'm going to get in on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, this is interesting, too, is that
[SPEAKER_02]: On April 12th, the North Carolina Attorney General's Office told Buy Right Video Games basically to request that they do not take orders, inform customers of the business status, and they have to provide a telephone number for customers to contact them in case of complaints.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't comply because as of April 26th, they shut them down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we say, good riddance.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to email them and gloat.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's going to do it for another podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any parting words from Loki over there, who's been kind of quiet this last bit of show?
[SPEAKER_01]: What was the thing about the two guys that were making movies?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I ended up skipping that because we were running long, but I'll mention it real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Clive Barker, John Woo, getting together to do this project.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called Demonic.
[SPEAKER_02]: And basically what it is, they're going to be simultaneously doing a next-gen console game and film.
[SPEAKER_02]: Silent Hill Movie
[SPEAKER_01]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Parting words?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's hot in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_02]: And my parting words are visit the website, orangelaunchradio.com, and subscribe to the podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't just listen to it online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check out our website and figure out how to subscribe because in two weeks, E3, we will be providing you podcasts every day we're there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're going to give you the news as we get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: and have a good one you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for tuning in to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio to go edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next update.