[SPEAKER_31]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format
Oh, God.
Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_33]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_33]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_33]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_33]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_29]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_33]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_33]: And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_06]: This is episode number 113 for this, September the 26th of 2004.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're tuned in to the Bee Money Scene's most absent-minded radio station of all things, Bee Money.
[SPEAKER_06]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: Joining me, as always, yes, the whole crew is back here tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: My lovely co-host, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know her better, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: OMG, WTF.
[SPEAKER_07]: BBQ.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also in house tonight, the faithful, lonely man from last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Say hello to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kitchen Man.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now he's Kitchen Man, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was throwing away the nasty fries.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and I'm here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, hello.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you sound a little drained after last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, also joining us, we have a variety of special guests.
[SPEAKER_07]: Say hello to the always
[SPEAKER_07]: A couple guests who are always here, it seems like.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're just kind of the fourth and fifth wheels of the show, respectively.
[SPEAKER_07]: In this RV of mobile home... Never mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: Say hello to Bradley, Arcadian42.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_07]: Howdy.
[SPEAKER_07]: How you doing, Bradley?
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, say hello to Angel.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, you're not going to use me?
[SPEAKER_07]: You're not going to... Sorry, DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, you're just Angel for short now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, damn it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: D-E-R Angel USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's your new name now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, at least you didn't put 2X Angel, Pop Music Angel, whatever else.
[SPEAKER_07]: You got the shitty mic, just to warn you.
[SPEAKER_07]: You gotta hold it at the bottom when you're talking it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Careful.
[SPEAKER_13]: I got the shitty mic right here.
[SPEAKER_07]: You go, girl.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did they even get what I said or no?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, they heard most of it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not going to go there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Stop sending them hurricanes.
[SPEAKER_07]: We had a really big show tonight, and I'm very disappointed.
[SPEAKER_07]: We only have about half our usual listeners tuned in right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shame on you!
[SPEAKER_04]: You're watching football.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was after I did the show last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were all scared off from the Loki experience last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: DDR Xtreme USA Music
[SPEAKER_07]: and a whole lot of other Bomani news.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just been a busy week.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, we might have to actually stay on topic tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're right, but first we're going to do How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day when we get back from this break featuring licensed music from DDR Extreme USA including what I believe would be Jamie's favorite licensed song.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's an old 80s song by a British lady.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's a little wild.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank you for watching.
Thanks for watching!
DarkSakura
DarkSakura.com
Love, love, love, love
[SPEAKER_19]: Simply Be In Love Simply Be In Love Simply Be In Love Simply Be In Love Simply Be In Love Simply Be In Love
[SPEAKER_19]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio, because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are back with Orange Lounge Radio, and of course tonight, big news, lots of news in the video game world this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was a game that came out that we've all finally been looking forward to, and thusly, we're going to dedicate tonight's entire show to this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hooray for Final Fantasy XI Chains of Promethea.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, no bullshit.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's been two.
[SPEAKER_17]: No way.
[SPEAKER_17]: I like both of those.
[SPEAKER_17]: I need The Sims 2.
[SPEAKER_17]: You need to kill them in more original ways and better graphics.
[SPEAKER_17]: A certain former intern of ours has my copies and claims to have lost them.
[SPEAKER_30]: Dope.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: I just thought it was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's great that you can kind of just whisk yourself away into the imaginary world of Sims 2 where you can live out your sexual fantasies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am going to kill the Olsen twins in a pool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_17]: I want to build the house of all pool so I can take all the people I hate and have them drown there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, Sigurd's posting in the chatroom that it was him, so I can say it was Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sigurd sent me all these pictures of him living out his fantasy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, you can, um, what's great is, I, like, saw, did a review on somethingawful.com about it, and apparently there's, like, three different cities you can start in.
[SPEAKER_04]: One's, like, completely medieval, and there's, like, some other strange one, and some other thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what's cool, though, is you can make, like, three and four story tall buildings and stuff in this.
[SPEAKER_17]: Can you push people off?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, but he had really creepy, fuzzy chairs.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he kept all of the dead up in his, like, roof.
[SPEAKER_17]: My question is if the Rosebud Code still works.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, from the old-ass Sims City?
[SPEAKER_05]: Good question.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a question.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know how they had, like, a Sims that came out a while ago?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was like the Sims Herbs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, it was the urban version of the Sims.
[SPEAKER_07]: It came out not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to know if you have drive-bys in that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_17]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's San Andreas.
[SPEAKER_07]: Different game.
[SPEAKER_07]: They need Grand Theft Sims.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what we need.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, yes, we do have to tip our hat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie doesn't have to tip her hat, but Matt and I have to tip our hats to Final Fantasy XI Chains of Promethea because we've been waiting for that game for a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've had the game now for almost 48 hours, or at least 24 hours, and have not been to any of the new areas.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the beautiful part.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've had the game for a day and a half, and it's been installed, and I have yet to see any differences except one new song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Beautiful waste of $30.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what, dear, dear addicts?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm still playing Ragnarok Online for free!
[SPEAKER_04]: Zelda Online, they do have...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so cool!
[SPEAKER_17]: I could go play the Satella view, Zelda, on my computer.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I have to deal with people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, we're getting off subject.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have to go back to our roots, and we have to do what this show is all about in the beginnings of the first chapter.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, not that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not that yet.
[SPEAKER_17]: But, um, we have to do... The Athens game, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_07]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_07]: The greatest game of all time.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_07]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_17]: Last week, not this like very past, but the week before, I was... Sorry, how was your two weeks?
[SPEAKER_17]: I was a wreck.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because the hurricane hit Mobile, Alabama.
[SPEAKER_17]: Guess where I'm from?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll take Mobile for $200.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm not from Kansas.
Anymore.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anymore.
[SPEAKER_17]: As if I ever was.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyway, yeah, I was up that Wednesday night just watching the news.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because they had a live feed from one of the local stations in Mobile.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I was watching...
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, the pressure, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, uh...
[SPEAKER_17]: But luckily, when the north eyewall was going to hit Mobile Bay, and they were expecting it to surge all the water up through the bay and flood all of downtown, you know, hence Water Street.
[SPEAKER_17]: But instead it sucked out all the water, so it's kind of stunk there for a little bit, but there wasn't any extraneous flooding.
[SPEAKER_17]: It blew over a bunch of stuff, knocked down some trees, but there were no casualties in Mobile.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_17]: And there were no serious injuries reported.
[SPEAKER_17]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_17]: However, Tornadoes decided to drop down in the town I was born in, in Dothan, Alabama.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dope.
[SPEAKER_17]: Tore up a bunch of trailer parks.
[SPEAKER_17]: And nearly hit my granny's house.
[SPEAKER_17]: It still dealt like a block from her house.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it missed her?
[SPEAKER_07]: It missed her.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_17]: You have a hit movie gallery.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their headquarters happens to be in Dothan, Alabama, and I fucking hate them.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dude, I used to go to, like, one of the movie galleries out there that were, like, the crappiest place in the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are the crappiest place.
[SPEAKER_04]: They buy out mom-and-pop stores that replace all the employees with retards, and then they just, like, run the business.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you're missing movies, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, well, we've only checked the first box so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, why don't you check the second box?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that's where your movies are.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: On a serious note, before Jamie gets back to her story, just, you know, we hope that all you guys are safe from Ivan, and we hope everything's alright with you guys, our thoughts are with you guys, and if you're in Florida right now, RUN!
[SPEAKER_06]: RUN AWAY!
[SPEAKER_06]: THERE'S A HURRICANE COMING!
[SPEAKER_06]: PICK UP YOUR PLAYSTATION AND RUN!
[SPEAKER_07]: No, seriously, we hope everything's alright with you guys.
[SPEAKER_17]: This has just been sort of, I mean, it hasn't ever happened like this before.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unless your last name is Bush, then by all means, stay.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what, at this point though, after having a whole week filled with seeing the debates between those two particular presidential candidates, and by the way people, more than two people are running for the presidency, hello!
[SPEAKER_17]: There are other parties to choose from.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll never... That's because people are stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's more like jogging, or brisk walking.
[SPEAKER_17]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's like Coke and Pepsi.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can drink other sodas.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_17]: Shasta and Fanta and Bosco.
[SPEAKER_17]: Those are good.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can drink root beer.
[SPEAKER_17]: You don't have to drink Sprite or Coke.
[SPEAKER_17]: But anyway, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I've just decided that neither candidate is worth my precious vote.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I want them both to burn in hell.
[SPEAKER_17]: I vote for Billy Capp.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh hell yeah, I'm voting for Build-A-Cat.
[SPEAKER_17]: Although, something that was in, I've actually put a link up in my live journal a couple days ago.
[SPEAKER_17]: Apparently, there's a couple other candidates, but I'll mention that later.
[SPEAKER_17]: That I would be considered voting for.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: I might vote for the gay penguin.
[SPEAKER_17]: But nah, I'm voting for Build-A-Cat and Opus, Radical Meadow Party.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like I always do, because there's never been anybody worth voting for.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to remember to turn in my registration form.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to mail it back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, shame on me, because I've moved.
[SPEAKER_17]: But I otherwise went to school, yay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Did homework, yay.
[SPEAKER_17]: We got slow at work, finally.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I've been writing fanfiction at work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Productive.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because I'm bored.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know, I've been doing other stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_17]: And today, Dan and I had a very interesting conversation about that supposed draft coming up for vote.
[SPEAKER_17]: First of all, I don't think that anyone needs to worry about it, because how many years have they tried to bring it back and not enacted it?
[SPEAKER_17]: But even so, I mean, where it's not good for the forward-thinking, general, middle-class people, it would be a really good thing, though, for all of the people who are out there, like,
[SPEAKER_17]: I will become gay not to go in the military.
[SPEAKER_17]: I will take one.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's going to be... I'm just saying, if they do bring back the draft, there's going to be a... It's going to be the new fad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Instead of moving to Canada, everybody's going to start sucking dick.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, that's going to be... There's going to be this big, huge inconsistency that's going to have to be addressed at some point.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, I don't think it's going to be... Overall, it's going to be good for...
[SPEAKER_17]: Good for the military itself, you know, to have a bunch of people there who they're not going to have time and resources to train properly and who aren't going to really want to be there.
[SPEAKER_17]: But on the other hand, you know, for, especially for larger cities that are dealing with, you know, high crime, you know, high, I'm trying to, right now I just lost the word I was thinking of.
[SPEAKER_17]: But overall, I think that it could improve things on a social scale, but there's so many drawbacks to it otherwise, I don't know that I'd be able to support anything like it.
[SPEAKER_17]: But my fiancé's all for it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I told him they should have made it 30 so I could go.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'd freaking volunteer, I don't care, except we've got that little issue with me and him right now about it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm working on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything else you want to share?
[SPEAKER_17]: No, except Dark Knight is pretty damn funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: by the doctor to fix my ingrown toenail.
[SPEAKER_17]: Was he the evil doctor?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, he wasn't an evil doctor.
[SPEAKER_04]: It only took a couple minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it hurts like a bitch.
[SPEAKER_17]: He wasn't even moderately evil?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: He talked about... What was he... He was rambling on about something that was like mad cow disease, but it was in deer.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess mad deer disease.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what the hell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, this is something like... Something to keep me focused on something other than, you know, them...
[SPEAKER_04]: Poking my foot with needles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, yeah, so that hurts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been hobbling around for days.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I just, today I ripped the bandage off because I'm supposed to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently I forgot a process of the bandage ripping off where I'm supposed to soak my toe in cold water and a little bit of hydrogen peroxide to loosen the impacted bandages in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I forgot about that, so I just kind of pulled.
[SPEAKER_04]: and with the polling came the yanking and then came the bleeding and that came the hurting so that really sucked and um so then there's that and then earlier this week I got DDR Extreme I did a show people got bored so I stopped the show and then I did a show last Sunday and people got bored and we did a segment called Crank Call Orange on his radio and I hung up on someone and that was funny and then um
[SPEAKER_04]: What else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, and then, let's see, you got Chains of Promethea, didn't really do anything, leveled some characters, and played a lot of Final Fantasy because I couldn't really go out and be active.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and got a book about my device, the Skull Experiment is what the book's called, and read it, and apparently my device may be a little bit harder to get working than I thought, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can still do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and I broke the lamp on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Angel, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_07]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_13]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Worked a lot and, you know, did what I was supposed to do.
[SPEAKER_13]: Went to school.
[SPEAKER_13]: School was okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: School was, well, school.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I actually got some good news from my folks, actually.
[SPEAKER_13]: I called them on, what was it?
[SPEAKER_13]: I had asked them if they had gotten hold of my brother and my sister-in-law and the baby and everything, and well, it turns out they're okay, so that was like a pressure off my shoulders that you wouldn't believe, except for you, Jamie, because, you know, your family and everything.
[SPEAKER_13]: so, uh, yeah, that was just, I was just so thankful that, you know, the kid was okay, and, uh, their family's okay, and, yeah, so, that was, that was just the highlight of the week, pretty much, oh, yeah, and Extreme, and Andrew's command mission, oh, boy, Mega Man, more Mega Man, yay, oh, wait, if he was listening, oh, wait, he's not listening, haha, I'm safe,
[SPEAKER_04]: See, I wanted to see, you know, I was waiting for, you know, a goddamn title match between Mike Tyson versus, you know, Hurricane Ivan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I think that would be really sweet, and they could totally set that kind of stuff up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, and Tyson's not doing anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's just being bankrupt.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, they could do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, and I'm probably going to get Final Fantasy XI this week, I guess.
[SPEAKER_13]: And become the... I don't know, I'll probably be sucked up into it and stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or I'll just go back to there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or Ragnarok, or... God, I could just go anywhere, couldn't I?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, if anybody wants to know about there, go to there.com.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, okay, that's my little spiel.
[SPEAKER_13]: Goodbye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bradley, do you have a mic over there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, goody.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bradley, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_07]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_07]: I do.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, uh, this week was work, of course.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, Wednesday I came over here and did the... played some DDR USA Extreme, or whatever it's called.
[SPEAKER_11]: Extreme USA.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wasn't particularly impressed, but it was alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, then... And actually, I think that was the first time I played DDR in... in months.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, let's see, then...
[SPEAKER_11]: Saturday didn't do very much.
[SPEAKER_11]: Got the thing about the initiatives for the state ballot on November and got to see the two that I had did the temp job with.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because one of my temp jobs during November, March and April was basically checking petitions for the stem cell one and the lawsuits one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'd say, oh, there's what I was working on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_11]: which was interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then Thursday or Friday I had a bunch of old Best Buy gift certificates.
[SPEAKER_11]: I went and got the Aqua Teen Hunger Force DVDs and watched that most of the time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Those are fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Today I didn't do very much.
[SPEAKER_11]: I came here and that's all.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: My week and my day, actually my past two weeks because I wasn't here on Sunday because I was on a business trip.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was in the lovely town of Allentown, Pennsylvania, which is about an hour north of Philly, about an hour west of Jersey.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, just kind of did my thing there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't get to play a whole lot of DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was actually thinking I was going to get to go out and play more DDR, but I was still working a lot this time around and...
[SPEAKER_07]: It was kind of one of those things where when I was done working at the end of the day, I didn't really want to go out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just kind of wanted to go back to my hotel and watch TV and sleep, so I didn't really do a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I did go out one night to a little mall out there in the area, which did have a DDR machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was actually going to Walden Books there in the mall because I wanted to pick up some books.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they happen to have a DDR machine, and you know me, I can't pass it up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, it was a Namco arcade, I believe, because they had Pac-Man stuff all over.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember the name of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Time something?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what the hell it was called.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: and it even impressed this one girl and she just started randomly talking to me and she's like, are you freaked out by strangers talking to you?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, not really.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kind of lonely and sad because I'm by myself in a strange town.
[SPEAKER_07]: But she talked to me a little bit and that was cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't plug the show though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you should listen to my radio show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, bad me.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then, okay, but then maybe I was just being an egotist or something, but I was looking at the scoreboards on the machine, and the Pop 4 difficult scores were kind of...
[SPEAKER_07]: Eh, like I was like, I could get that, you know, like, and so I really wanted to do it, and not, I'm usually not a scoreboard whore, but how cool would it have been to have my name on a machine like thousands of miles away, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: So I had to do it, so I put my coins in, I started to do it, and then the fucking pad, like, wouldn't work, like, it was just totally not registering, like, half my steps, and I fucking failed on, what, Irresistible Mind, like, standard, I failed that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh well, what can you do?
[SPEAKER_07]: So much for that, trying to get my name on the scoreboard at the Lehigh Valley Mall, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just, you know, let that guy have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And over the weekend, I actually got to take a little bit of a tour of the East Coast a little more.
[SPEAKER_07]: My friend came and picked me up, and we drove through New York City a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't really stop to play DDR anymore until we were on the way back.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I knew that there was an In the Groove machine in Jersey, and I thought, well, you know, we talk about it a lot on the show, and we've said a lot of judgments about it, but none of us have actually played it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm like, I better go play it
[SPEAKER_07]: So therefore, I can give a fair review of the game and actually say, well, I've played it so that, you know, you can't say I'm just talking about my ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I will tell you what I thought about that a little later.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it was at this place called Eight on the Break.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which I actually, for some reason, by the sound of it, made me think it was some kind of boardwalk place.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have no idea why I thought that, because it's not even near an ocean at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it was interesting because there was this street fair going on the day we went.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it was so random, because the girl I was with, my friend Amanda and I, had no idea where we were going.
[SPEAKER_07]: We were just walking around trying to find this place.
[SPEAKER_07]: and suddenly here I am, thousands of miles away on a Sunday in the middle of some street fair in little town America.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is really odd.
[SPEAKER_07]: Surreal for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then we found the place and we went in and I was actually surprised.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was quite a lot of Bomani at this place.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not only had they the groove, but they had a 2DX machine and a Parapara machine and DDR and just a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I was pretty impressed.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was kind of surprised they had all that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Granted, not all the machines were in tip-top shape, but you know, hey.
[SPEAKER_07]: It actually ran on quarters, which always impresses me, because I don't like tokens that much, because I always leave with extra tokens.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the machines actually took quarters, so that was good.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there seemed to be some okay crowds.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't really talk to too many people.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was kind of just a loner.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wasn't there to make a show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just kind of went in, played a few games, and left.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that was my weekend, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I've just kind of spent my time here since I got back home, just trying to catch up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because when you leave town for two weeks...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really hard to catch up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to go back to work tomorrow, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, that's pretty much it for me for How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else anybody wants to add?
[SPEAKER_04]: I watched Rad today.
[SPEAKER_04]: And might I add, I've, like, I only remembered, like, one scene of that movie, and that's what got me the bite, is where the guy was riding on the fence.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I actually watched the movie today, and that was for, like, half a second.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, but for some reason in my mind that stood out, that and the backflip in the, um, hell, hell race.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, my God, that movie is so cheesy and awesome, and just, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just pure 80s goodness, and I watched the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Made me happy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_17]: I last saw that movie in, huh?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, I would like to.
[SPEAKER_17]: I last saw that in Albany, Georgia when I was 10, I think.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's the last time I've seen that movie and it's very scary that I remember where I was.
[SPEAKER_17]: I need to see Monster Squad 2.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was at my Uncle Wayne's house.
[SPEAKER_17]: with my cousins and we were watching this movie and then it was over and we watched it again because at the time that was like our favorite movie and my cousin had one of those stunt bikes and was in his backyard trying to do all the stunts and everything it was kind of kind of cool
[SPEAKER_07]: I got asked a question in the chatroom, www.orangelandrea.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sid wanted to know how Jay and Silent Bob's Secret Stash was, because I completely forgot to mention that was one other thing we did while we were in Jersey.
[SPEAKER_07]: We went to Red Bank, New Jersey to go to Jay and Silent Bob's Secret Stash, which was very cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was just your typical kind of comic book store, but it had a lot of memorabilia from the movies, which I thought was really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually bought Loki's birthday present there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bought him a comic book.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I got him a shirt.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the shirt says shit on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I picked up some stickers and stuff too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like I got Jamie a Bear is Driving sticker.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I picked myself up a sticker.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I got a poster.
[SPEAKER_07]: A brand new poster.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which we're going to hang up at some point tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be on the wall that you can see on the camera.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got a new poster from Jay and Silent Bob's Secret Stash.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's the one where Jay and Silent Bob has a whole little monologue on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where Jay and Silent Bob are talking on the...
[SPEAKER_07]: Ain't It Cool News style site.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're talking about the movie and they say, you are the ones who are the ball lickers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have the posters.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it was good times.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was kind of a fun little place to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, hooray.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and Jason says I'm a mean man because at the Phoenix airport on the way home I actually stopped and got to see Jason, our webmaster, for like 10 minutes because I had a layover in Phoenix for like 30 minutes or so.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I got to say hi to our webmaster.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that was very nice of him to come out and see me on his break from work.
[SPEAKER_07]: So thank you, Jason.
[SPEAKER_07]: And your airport rocks.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Phoenix airport is the best place to have a layover.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_17]: The shirt was on the webcam a couple of pictures ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess we're going to go to a break, and then we're going to come back, and we want to definitely talk about DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_07]: A whole lot we want to say about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll get your thoughts, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the Skype line, if you want to know how the Skype line works, you can actually talk to us, just like a phone call, but free.
[SPEAKER_07]: www.orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Click on Interact With Us, and all the information is there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: I missed you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aw, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, how was the show last week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was, uh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: We played a lot of music, and I played a lot more music from, um, the Bomani-style remix contest, which was supposed to be judging, like, three weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this isn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, um, what else did we do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we tried a new game that failed horribly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, um... Um... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some other shit happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was...
[SPEAKER_04]: I know we played the Mary-Kate and Ashley Olsen CD and that was sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, there's your summary of episode 112.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, also, we definitely want to talk about this, the Akira Yamaoka contest.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have an announcement we want to make about the Akira Yamaoka contest, and we'll do that when we get back from this break.
[SPEAKER_07]: And for those of you that haven't heard yet...
[SPEAKER_07]: We're giving away two signed Akira Yamaoka CDs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we have the details when we come back from this break.
[SPEAKER_07]: In this break, Konami original music that's brand new in DDR EX USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to start it off with Maximizer.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of you guys haven't even heard that yet, I don't think, so we're going to play that for you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Funk Boogie, we'll get in there too, and of course, You're Not Here, because Jamie insists that I play You're Not Here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie demands it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So here it is, Maximizer on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoy, we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_27]: Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
We've got two forever, the plane grass blows and the wind is dancing
[SPEAKER_19]: It would be a much better fight with you, with me If you hadn't met me, I'd be fine on my own, baby Never felt so lonely when you came along
Thank you for watching!
And who has time for tears?
Never thought I'd sit around and unravel your love
[SPEAKER_07]: After this song, we'll be having a Let Them Move Marathon.
[SPEAKER_19]: No!
[SPEAKER_07]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Crap-free Bavani Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not only crap free, but playing probably the only internet radio station on the planet to be playing Maximizer and all that fun stuff at this time.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, hope you enjoyed that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it looks like some of you guys maybe missed that, so we'll have to play that after the show is over.
[SPEAKER_07]: Definitely for you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, of course, Maximizer being from DDR Extreme USA, which was the big news this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some very interesting opinions on that game, just kind of all across the spectrum.
[SPEAKER_07]: People love it, people hate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll open it up for some of your opinions as well, but first, what we think of DDR Extreme USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I know some of us have played it a lot, some of us have barely seen it at all, but kind of, what did you guys think of it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll start off with Loki, he had the most exposure to the game, I'm kind of curious.
[SPEAKER_07]: What did you think of it, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: They had, okay, um, decent songs, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing I hate is unlocking old shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I honestly hate unlocking old shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, ooh, Trip Machine!
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never played that one!
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's just stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the things that really lacked in this game, the enosisms, they were just not funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, some songs just did not have them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the Karaoke Revolution cover songs...
[SPEAKER_04]: Bizarre Love Triangle, that was the only one I liked.
[SPEAKER_04]: The rest sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: The singing was just awful and just crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the steps weren't, eh, they're okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: The new Konami Originals, Funk Boogie, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maximizer, not exactly what I was imagining, but eh, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, I don't know how to describe it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's annoying, but addicting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or like, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just, I hate that type of music, but it's a pretty cool song.
[SPEAKER_04]: or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, um, you know, the two transplants, uh, Your Rage, I, um, or Your Rain, the Rage mix, I don't like that song anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just annoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, uh, and You're Not Here, that's a pretty cool song.
[SPEAKER_04]: The steps so suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're all up.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just all up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, um, now the best thing going for it, and I really don't understand why I didn't have this, um, to start off with, why the fuck do you have to unlock mission mode?
[SPEAKER_04]: My god, it was the coolest part of the game, and you have to unlock it, like, after a very long time to finally get mission mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was really stupid, because that's the best part of the game right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then, okay, let's talk about the eye toy.
[SPEAKER_04]: The eye toy games are, eh, they're okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: The things that I don't like, okay, the hands and feet mode, actually, if you have a well-lit room, it works pretty well.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem is, it's not hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's easy and stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: What they really could have used in this game is edit mode and where you can make your own hands and feet steps.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would fucking rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you can do some crazy shit there and it would be a lot more fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then the other thing, some of the other games like the Coconut Panic, that was kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amusing, but dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: And the other modes that they've got, I didn't really play any of the non-iToy party modes, but they're okay from what I've seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're just kind of, I think it'd be more fun if you were drunk.
[SPEAKER_04]: And other than that, Mission Mode, I had a lot going for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of good stuff in Mission Mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish it was longer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish some of the songs, they had some newer songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: The character unlocks, I really don't care anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mission mode will be the only thing that keeps my attention with this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the only thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mission mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's actually the only thing that's challenging in this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I'm going to give you my thoughts.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the game a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the game so much.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's probably my favorite...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's up there with Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd say this and Ultramix are kind of like my two favorite home mixes right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, I think it's very cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really like some of the new stuff they put in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think there's two big mistakes here, though, that they made.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to get this off my chest.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody's saying this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, it's a game-crippling mistake that they made with the game, and that was the removal of the dance play setting, where you can't turn off the buttons on the pads.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: and considering that the whole thing is based on trying to get up there and dance and move, I realize for a lot of beginner people, they're probably not going to have that problem.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I take that back because I was having some friends play it last night, some beginner friends, and they would try to be picking a song and they'd be stepping on my pad, which is a $100 red octane ignition pad, and they're fucking backing out because they're stepping on the wrong steps on the bottom.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're trying to step off the arrows.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, I just, it was, it's just a horrible oversight.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, seriously, I know this sounds insane, but they should fucking recall the game and give us new copies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, that's how bad of a mistake I seriously think this is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, in the bright side, well, okay, no, let's keep raining down the bad stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else bad did I want to say about it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I also do not like the fact that they unlock old songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really just hate the repeat songs, and you shouldn't unlock old stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's really bothersome.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it would be cool, like, if, say...
[SPEAKER_04]: They had an included dropout in every fucking game since in the US mixes, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they had, like, I don't know, like a song, like, say, for instance, I'm in DDR 10th Mix or whatever it is, and look, there's a song from First Mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, I haven't played that since First Mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty cool that they're unlocking old stuff for me to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the only situation where that'd be good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not, oh, look at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was just in that other game I bought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, here's the other mistake I think they made.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this may be kind of... This may be kind of a little bit controversial.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think the other mistake that they made with this game was calling it DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I seriously think that's why you've got so many people that have their expectations on one level when the product that Konami was trying to deliver was something...
[SPEAKER_07]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_07]: Beginner stuff, getting some friends into it, and it was fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, that's what it's all about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Those modes weren't for hardcore players to be challenged, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're just stupid fun stuff, and I think it succeeded.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really like the eye toy stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have a problem with it at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of hope they keep it going.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would like to see hands and feet mode get a little more challenging in the next mid.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's something they could expand on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another thing that they didn't include that really needs to be included, sensitivity settings and adjustments for the eye toy.
[SPEAKER_04]: How the fuck, if I'm in a dim room, I can't set it to dim room mode
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, like you can with iToyPlay or iToyGroove, they don't have any options to set the iToy stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can't calibrate it to make it look nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're fucked if you're in a dark room.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't set it to be more sensitive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or non-sensitive.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it's too sensitive, then you're fucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's the other thing that really sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they should have just, honestly, knowing what we know now about the next Japanese release and seeing as pretty much Konami of Japan made most of this release anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't really blame the US for what's going on on this release.
[SPEAKER_07]: The dance play setting thing, I'm almost positive it's Konami of Japan's fault.
[SPEAKER_07]: We all know the story.
[SPEAKER_07]: We all know the story about the Marvelous Thing and how that was fought by Konami of America to Konami of Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Konami of Japan said, no, they're not changing the Marvelous Thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I would bet money the exact same thing happened with the dance play setting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shame on you, Konami of Japan, for being lazy with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You really upset a lot of us with that, so shame on you for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no way...
[SPEAKER_07]: I really want to purchase DDR Festival knowing that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And especially because, you know, what we'll talk about later, but Festival doesn't really have that great a song list so far.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if that dance play setting isn't going to be in Festival, there's no reason I need to buy it, honestly.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's zero.
[SPEAKER_09]: But...
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess really knowing what we know now about DDR Festival, the next Japanese release, they probably should have just called this mix DDR Festival.
[SPEAKER_07]: The US one, they should have just called this mix DDR Festival.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then people wouldn't have gone in with all these expectations like, Oh, Cartoon Heroes has to be in it, and Sakura has to be in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because honestly, Konami was doing something different with this mix, and I think it was cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I, for one, like the new interface.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's not...
[SPEAKER_07]: The circle thing that was bugging everybody, that people were talking about, like, oh, it looks like third mix and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not what I'm talking about, really.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's just one part of it, but really, the rest of the music in the game, and the way it looks in-game when you're actually playing the game is amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's way better than, like, any other DDR game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks in-game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It takes everything that's great about fourth mix, everything that's great about max, the 60 frames per second and stuff, and combines it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the interface is the best one they've had yet, with the Oni battery bar and everything looks great.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what?
[SPEAKER_07]: The wheel looks a little different.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't really bother me at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the wheel better than... You see it for like two seconds.
[SPEAKER_17]: I like the wheel better than the other way, because you... I don't know, it just... Having started with Second Mix, I think that it makes me think a lot more of the older ones, so I like it better.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the little records would have been cool, but, you know, I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_07]: The interface really doesn't bother me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not something that, like, ruined the game for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It didn't really faze me at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of thought, oh, that's different.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I can see where people who have been kind of stuck on DDR Extreme for several years now, who have really badly, because they can't afford a Japanese PlayStation 2, have wanted something like that for a console for a long time, are a little bit disappointed.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's a new song.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, from that standpoint, if Konami knows damn well there's not going to be any new arcade mixes, which from Konami Japan, it doesn't sound like they're ever planning on really doing one, it would have not been smart to release just a port of DDR Extreme, because then why would you go to the arcades?
[SPEAKER_07]: so I think them making it a lot different was probably smart on their end in the end because you'll still go to the arcades to play Sakura and all that stuff so I don't know just kind of my thought I know but come on come on they know damn well it's here they know damn well extreme is here
[SPEAKER_07]: Haven't we had this talk on the show with somebody from Konami here, and they said that they know it's just one of those things where it's like, and I always said this, nobody has confirmed this, but this has always been my opinion on this, is that it has to do with the music licensing, and that it's way easier to get the music license in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if they put that disclaimer on there that says, don't use this outside Japan, and then, oh, well, gee, imagine that, the machines ended up in the U.S., gee, fancy that, how did that happen?
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't have to go and get sued by the record companies because they have the disclaimer on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the arcade owner's fault.
[SPEAKER_07]: The game's in there when it's not supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_07]: But at the same time, they got all the great music for DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's just my thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know you didn't get to play it a whole lot, Jamie, but what did you think of Extreme?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just kind of looking at it.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: I like the non-stop music when you're picking the non-stop.
[SPEAKER_16]: That music was just pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the mini-music was really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the new mods that they're doing in this mission mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also Air Japan's going to hack those out and put those in the normal game.
[SPEAKER_14]: But feeding time?
[SPEAKER_04]: Feeding time scared me.
[SPEAKER_07]: So stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Angel, I know you got to play a lot of Extreme this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: What were your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to open up the Skype line soon for your thoughts, but I want to get everybody in the studio first.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, well, I didn't get to play too much of it, considering I'd just gotten it... What day was it, release Tuesday?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, the thing that kind of got me down was, um, Unlocking Your Rain, like, the second song I played.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm like, no!
[SPEAKER_13]: I wish that it was, you know, like, the last song.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just because, like, that was the song I was really looking forward to, but... Isn't Your Rain in there by default?
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you just miss it the first game, maybe?
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought it was in there by default.
[SPEAKER_13]: I might have, um...
[SPEAKER_13]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just... Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, that was kind of a downer.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know there's other stuff that I probably have yet to unlock, like the BT song and the, oh, whatever, all the other songs that we've been playing today.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, you know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: That's for the week to come.
[SPEAKER_04]: And how many games, how many games will it take before you make more steps for Max 2 Oni songs?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the Max 1 Oni songs, whatever song.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, Max 2 Oni songs, come on now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, Zegaru Apple Mix, it's been out forever now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make some new fucking steps.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't take that long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, just make new steps.
[SPEAKER_04]: Complete them.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did it in the UK, you know, before the beatmix in Historia 2001.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did it there because they like to be complete.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, you know, we just have to be lazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're only going to have challenge steps because we don't want to make new steps.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So get off your ass and make new steps.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I think this mix will hold me over just fine until Ultramix 2 comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, the bar of expectations is just so high with Ultramix 2 right now with everything I've heard about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just kind of like I'm almost going to feel bad when it comes out because it's probably not going to... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: My bar is so high for Ultramix 2 that that is really the one I'm waiting for at this point.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, Extreme's cool and all, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do recommend if you are a DDR fan and you have a PlayStation 2, you should have this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should have this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you have a Japanese PlayStation 2, then I guess you have a choice.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you have a US one, then you really should just get this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's DDR and it's good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll play more this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, you know, unlock more crap.
[SPEAKER_13]: And maybe I'll like it more.
[SPEAKER_13]: But right now, as soon as I saw you ran, I was like, no!
[SPEAKER_13]: Big disappointment for me, but I'll keep playing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Shane, don't hit me, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bradley, you're a DDR fan.
[SPEAKER_07]: You mentioned at the beginning of the show you were a little bit disappointed with the mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just kind of curious on your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, based on what I saw, I wasn't that impressed with it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was just, nah.
[SPEAKER_11]: It didn't make me excited or anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I probably would, if I got to see Master Mode, or might have had, or whatever that is called.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because we didn't unlock that while I was here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, the Maximizer?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, not Maximizer, the Master Mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Mission Mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I like to do those kind of weird things in owning modes and things like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Instead of just straight up DDR when I'm playing with the home mixes.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, that kind of reminds... I don't have them anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: That reminded me of something.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of people were really upset because there were no 10-foot steps for Maximizer because supposedly Maximizer is supposed to be this new... Well, okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have the Mission Mode thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't have steps in-game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kind of like...
[SPEAKER_07]: Big deal, because for me, honestly, I don't get the desire to have all these insane 10-footers on home, because how in the hell are you going to pass that stuff on a home pad?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I realize people do it, but I've been playing DDR for years, and there's no way in hell I'd be passing half those 10-footers on a home pad.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, you just can't do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not the same as the arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, granted, you may have a metal stage or whatever, but if that's the case, you are in the minority.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's face it, you are not
[SPEAKER_07]: The majority of, uh, you know, the people that are gonna be picking up DDR, you are the minority, and if, you know, Konami's gonna cater to you, you're, like, extra special if you get your ten-footer, so, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just, I just don't see the point in bitching about there not being a lot of new ten-footers, because, especially with the dance play setting not being fucked up.
[SPEAKER_07]: How, now how are you gonna pass ten-footers?
[SPEAKER_07]: Now the dance play setting's there, it's like, ugh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unless you're playing Button Button Revolution, but that's not what DDR's supposed to be for!
[SPEAKER_07]: Then they wouldn't be getting their weight loss news stories and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anybody else?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go to a break, and then I'm going to open up the Skype line, and we'll get your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_07]: And speaking of DDR in the news, we want to get to that story, because DDR was in the news again this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, of course, you know we've got to mention that.
[SPEAKER_07]: This break, we're going to do some of those Karaoke Revolution songs, because there's surprisingly some decent ones.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will not be playing Waiting for Tonight, though, because I fucking hate that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we will play Bizarre Love Triangle and some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_07]: And with the Skype line, open up your thoughts on DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you want to argue with us on some point, go for it.
I love you, DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, yes, this lady's a knife, and the feeling's right Oh, yes, this lady's a knife, oh, what a knife Oh, baby, oh, baby Oh, baby, oh, baby Oh, baby, oh, baby Oh, baby, oh, baby
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh yes, it's late at night, and I'm feeling light Oh yes, it's late at night, oh what a night Oh yes, it's late at night, and I'm feeling bright Oh yes, it's late at night, oh what a night Oh yes, it's late at night, and I'm feeling light Oh yes, it's late at night, oh what a night Oh yes, it's late at night, and I'm feeling bright Oh yes, it's late at night
[SPEAKER_19]: There's no talking to you It's so sad that you're leaving It takes time to believe it But after all that's said and done You're gonna be the lonely one Oh, you'll be leaving like
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_33]: For up to the minute Pomanian gaming news, discussion forums, and for access to the chatroom, visit our website at orangeloungeradio.com We're back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I forgot to even talk about the Karaoke Revolution songs in DDR Extreme, but playing those kind of reminded me of some of the reaction from the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Karaoke Revolution songs, I thought I was going to love it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought it was going to be a great idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: But to be honest, I'm not a big fan of any of the Karaoke Revolution transplants.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, maybe a couple are okay, but at the same time...
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of applaud Konami for trying that because it was a pretty clever idea to get some big dance songs in DDR without having to pay such a high license fee is to put in the covers.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just that the covers aren't that hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think it's a neat idea and maybe they'll do it better next time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, but I can't say I'm a huge fan of any of those songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's me personally.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not really a huge fan of any of those.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't think the original Bizarre Love Triangle is good?
[SPEAKER_17]: No, the original Bizarre Love Triangle was excellent.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm talking about the Cher song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Women's career was over a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I forgot to bring up the... I'm glad the microphone didn't pick that up, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not even gonna... I said, why can't she ski into a tree?
[SPEAKER_17]: If she had skied into the tree, she would have bounced off from all the plastic in her face.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway... On a different note, I want to talk about the Akira Yamaoka CD contest.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: After the show tonight, at some point, probably check for it tomorrow on our website, OrangeLandRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: We will be starting the contest next Monday.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're going to have to listen Monday, Tuesday, and Wednesday night.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you can't listen, get your friend to listen because we've got to be giving out some trivia questions that you're going to have to answer to correctly be put in the drawing to win one of those CDs.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't want to miss it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're going to be starting that next Monday.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course a big thank you to one of our partner sites, DDRspot.com for helping us out with this contest.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're going to be giving away some CDs too.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you don't win with us, go try and win with them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because they're going to be doing their own contest.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what they're doing yet though.
[SPEAKER_07]: They haven't even clued me in.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: So definitely check them out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're going to be relaunching their site.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't want to give too much away though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I already said too much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, as promised, let's open up the Skype line and see what your thoughts are on DDR Extreme USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, I gotta wait, because there's the delay, so I probably should open it up a little sooner, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, what are your thoughts, buddy, on DDR Extreme USA?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, DDR Extreme, so many complaints, so many complaints.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still haven't played the game where all these complaints are directed towards, because I played a very decent game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you must have been playing some completely different game than everybody else, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I fully enjoyed the song list.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, there are a few that I didn't like, but, I mean, out of 70 songs, you're going to have a few that you don't like.
[SPEAKER_07]: I agree, I agree.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's going to be that let them move, or in the case of DDR Max 2, Forever Sunshine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: Forever Sunshine was good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, please, yourself.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, alright, to each his own.
[SPEAKER_07]: Use their own.
[SPEAKER_09]: Agree to disagree.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's just these one-line complaints saying, oh my god, I hate this game, go get Japanese Extreme.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_07]: So basically people saying this mix isn't Japanese enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not Japanese enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ironic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ironic, considering this game was pretty much made by Konami of Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've pretty much found out.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you don't think it's Japanese enough, just play the stupid feeding frenzy mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: The last four American mixes you own DDR Festivals?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, of course, we don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, there could be something unlocked, or there might be some cool features they haven't talked about yet, but... 22 Dunk.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm betting on 22 Dunk.
[SPEAKER_07]: Assumably, it's all the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's gonna be totally like Max 1, the Japanese one, with the whole two unlocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Two unlocks!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_04]: There's gotta be more, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: If I play like 500 times, there'll be more?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or was that Max 2 with 3 unlocks?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, will there be 4?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh wait, no, I thought it was Party Collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm gonna guess that there's gonna be 5 unlocks in this next game.
[SPEAKER_04]: 5 unlocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brand new.
[SPEAKER_07]: So noted.
[SPEAKER_07]: What was your favorite thing about Extreme USA, Mr. Mullet?
[SPEAKER_09]: My favorite thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: Easily the mission mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I didn't think there was gonna be that many missions, and I didn't get a chance to play the game until Thursday, so I had to wade through about a billion complaints on the Freak Forums.
[SPEAKER_20]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_09]: But as soon as I heard someone say something about Mission 75 I was like, hold on, back up the car, 75?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I know, there's a lot of missions in there I think even here in studio we're only through like Mission 53 We just haven't had enough time to play through all the missions Have you checked out Mission 38 yet?
[SPEAKER_07]: That was the one with Absolute It was Absolute and it was all these different speeds Oh, that was fun
[SPEAKER_09]: But then again, wait till you get, there's one in the second half with Firefly Heavy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Same deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, jeez.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speeds up, slows down, and apparently near the very end, like 98 or 99, there's the official fucked up Frozen Ray mission where it's reverse scroll, dark, arrows mixed up with random speed changes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_09]: What mission number is that?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's either 98 or 90.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's in the last five.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did the one, there was a Frozen Ray one, and I had to turn the controller upside down to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it was on, it was like 49 or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mission 50.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mission 50.
[SPEAKER_09]: It took me over 50 tries for that one, and I did it with my pad right side up, and I managed to, I had to memorize the first part without looking at the screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: I could do this mission now without looking at the screen.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll tell you, the one that stuck me for the longest time, and I can't believe this one took me as long as it did, but it's Your Rain on .5 and Dark.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I swear to God, we had to do it like 40 times to beat it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That didn't take me that long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did we ever get the one done where you have to, it was kick the can, where you had to get 20 of each?
[SPEAKER_04]: 20 goods, 20 greats, 20 perfects?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're still stuck on that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's like in the easy bunch.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're still stuck on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We can't do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's too hard to get goods for us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah, like, oh, the 20 great, good, perfect ones.
[SPEAKER_09]: I managed to pass that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It took me a while, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, I mean, there's like some of them that were apparently very hard and that I couldn't pass.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or, like, I could pass.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was, like, really surprising.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's apparently some easy ones that took me forever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess it all depends on what you can do and what you can't.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why don't you plug your site again, because you have this really nifty column over on that site, and people should go look at it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yes, www.insidepulse.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Expect a DDR Extreme review that actually praises the game for what it has rather than what it doesn't have within reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, I don't bash the game because it doesn't have Sakura, for example.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I will point out some of the fatal flaws, as it were.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I mean, to be totally honest, this game has enough material in it to make this the greatest home version ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Until next month when we get Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or November, really.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm telling you, I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Based on the hype alone...
[SPEAKER_07]: Ultramix 2, all the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, anyway, I'll finish my thought if you don't mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like I said, it has enough material to make this the greatest home version ever, but it has enough, it has the critical dance pad error, which really didn't affect me that much, but it has that error and it has a few other errors to bring it right back down.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the good far outweighs the bad, really.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really.
[SPEAKER_07]: I agree, the good outweighs the bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: The dance pad thing is really annoying, but I'll get over it someday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Somehow I'll survive.
[SPEAKER_07]: When are you going to start writing for the wrestling portion of the site?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I'm curious about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Had to ask, had to ask.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get some wrasslin'.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you looking forward to Rumble Roses?
[SPEAKER_07]: All the boys on that site must be looking forward to Rumble Roses.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: You got the Bomani artist, you got the wrasslin'.
[SPEAKER_07]: Boobies, come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I get that game, it'll be to hear Look to the Sky again.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look to the Sky and Boobies, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Look to the Boobies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look to the Boobies, exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's Rumble Road.
[SPEAKER_07]: That should be it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know how when they advertise things, they have that tagline?
[SPEAKER_07]: It should be Rumble Roses.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look to the Boobies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome action gameplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Realistic, rusty moves.
[SPEAKER_17]: Lots of boobies!
[SPEAKER_17]: And mud.
[SPEAKER_17]: Don't forget the mud.
[SPEAKER_17]: The flesh-colored mud.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look to the boobies.
[SPEAKER_07]: True color mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, I'm hanging up on you, Mullet.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got to let some other people call in.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right, bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: But thanks for the input, as always.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, it's always good to talk to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, we'll reopen the Skype line if somebody else wants to call in.
[SPEAKER_07]: And let us know their thoughts on DDR Extreme USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to have to kind of start shifting gears here in a little bit, though, because we definitely want to get to the cage match.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, now we've got to get to our FUs, and I still want to talk about In the Groove at some point, and all that other stuff as well.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wasn't that a Madonna song?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that's Into the Groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's Into the Groove, not In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: In the Groove's a little different.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, another caller.
[SPEAKER_07]: Howdy, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yo, it's Dork.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Dork, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_07]: I love this name.
[SPEAKER_07]: I swear, I'm declaring that our listeners have the coolest handles on the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Between like El Mullet and Dork, come on.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hey, you guys win at the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Captain Canada, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: You guys win at the internet.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hey, Dork, guess who?
[SPEAKER_28]: Anyways, on the subject of... Oh, fine, don't guess who.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're fired.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm sorry, what's up?
[SPEAKER_07]: Angel's taking over.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's up, Dork?
[SPEAKER_07]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's up, Dork?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_28]: Repeat, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, you have to repeat.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was chaos.
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh, wait.
[SPEAKER_28]: What?
[SPEAKER_28]: Angel was talking?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, she was.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, but it's your turn.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's your turn.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, what did she say?
[SPEAKER_07]: She was trying to say hi.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think there's a delay or something and it messed everything up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, what's up?
[SPEAKER_07]: What's your thoughts on Extreme?
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, uh, I got some good thoughts and bad thoughts.
[SPEAKER_28]: I kind of said some good and bad on Wednesday, but eh.
[SPEAKER_28]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: But for the most part, you have to remember, you have to satisfy everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there's always the way the song list could be improved to match our own personal tastes.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you change the song list to what you would like, then somebody else would hate the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I understand, I understand.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could always just have more songs, hey?
[SPEAKER_28]: Maybe so, but... Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: I kind of figure that Oni and Nonstop are a bit too easy, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, maybe.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think some of the non-stops are a little bit too easy, but then again, everything is difficult with that dance play option being gone, so... Yeah, but then again, to negate all that, you have Mission Mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_28]: Which is really awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mission Mode is very awesome.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's one of the coolest things in DDR yet, next to online play.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, by the way, the Frozen Ray on Heavy with the one on Dark, Reverse, and...
[SPEAKER_28]: Mixed Up Arrows, that's Mission 98.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mission 98, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: We haven't gotten there yet, we're a little slow.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: I tried that one up to like 100-something times already.
[SPEAKER_07]: So on a scale of 1 to 5, how would you rate DDR Extreme?
2.
[SPEAKER_07]: 2?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, ouch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, what would you say was your least favorite thing about the whole game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Least favorite.
[SPEAKER_07]: Songless.
[SPEAKER_07]: Songlist, ouch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe next time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, we're going to let you go so we can talk to some other folks.
[SPEAKER_07]: But thanks for the call, Dork.
[SPEAKER_07]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_17]: I can feel the evil vibe building in this room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_17]: Thanks to Loki's device.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh God, Loki's trying to finish his little device over there.
[SPEAKER_07]: The one he's been working on for the past three episodes or something.
[SPEAKER_17]: I feel the evil is close.
[SPEAKER_17]: I feel that Satan's going to come up and just burn up the floor.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, we got another caller.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is going to be the last one for now.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey there, Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm glad to get the last call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it won't be the last call ever, but for this segment.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if we have time at the end of the show, we'll take more extreme thoughts.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is the ultimate call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: But for now, you're the lucky one.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_07]: What's your thoughts on DDR Extreme, Dark Knight?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: There are some little downsides to it, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: What are the downsides?
[SPEAKER_08]: I agree with you with the dance play thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I kind of noticed that when I looked at it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like, something's missing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, uh...
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I can't cut the extra arrows off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the dance play thing was a real bummer.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mission Mode was okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm kind of slow because I'm still stuck on Mission 15.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's hard!
[SPEAKER_08]: But they do have the crazy missions on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: One, it was like all the arrows were bunched up into one big arrow.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you didn't know which way you had to hit it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't seen that one yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like all the arrows get bunched, jammed into one arrow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, I have to... It scrolls like one line.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki played like half a mission mode while I was out of town, but it's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I gotta look at some of these other missions that I missed out on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe I'll just erase the file and start over.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then it was like one mission where you have to deliberately get no goods on all freeze arrows.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, I can't do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: My feet doesn't let me do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know I failed it like six times.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the one where Maximizer can't get a combo higher than four.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, of course, they have the ability to go to challenge or non-stop during, like, while picking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Instead of, like, having to pick it early, you can pick it, like, on the song rotation.
[SPEAKER_08]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, like, when you're looking at it, you see, you're, like, hearing the second song, and then all of a sudden, like, I want to do a challenge step.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you go to challenge, and you go to challenge mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gotcha, gotcha, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, like that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess the odd stuff, Hyper Dash is the only thing I like on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else, I didn't even want to attempt to even try.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just by looking, I'm like, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: All in all, I'll give the REX about at least an 8.
[SPEAKER_07]: An 8 out of 10?
[SPEAKER_08]: An 8 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, thanks for the call, Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got to let you go because we're going to get to break, but thanks for your input.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: We will take more calls a little later on during the show about DDR Extreme USA and your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_07]: We do like hearing what our listeners have to say because, you know, they know more than we do most of the time, which is the sad truth.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are going to go to a break, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: When we come back, my review of In the Groove and the Cage Match when we get back.
[SPEAKER_07]: After this, starting off with some more licensed music from DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know some folks in the chat room wanted to hear this.
[SPEAKER_07]: So here you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some music for you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoy.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: We will leave someday Your hand in my hand We will make our plans We will fight so high Tell all our friends goodbye We will be just like you This is what we'll do
[SPEAKER_19]: Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio, Bomani Music, and more.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are back with Orange Lounge Radio, talking about DDR Extreme USA mostly, but you know, just by coincidence, tonight was probably going to be dominated by DDR Extreme USA chat, but I got a chance to play In The Groove this week, which is the other Bomani-ish game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not really a Bomani game, but you all know the story.
[SPEAKER_07]: You want...
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, DarkSakura was barking orders at Angel.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_17]: I asked very nicely, okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: I said, would you please get me a napkin?
[SPEAKER_07]: But you barked it a little.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll show you bark.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the Groove's been, it's controversial.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's just leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a controversial game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Many folks are like, what the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically, for those that don't know, the folks that did Stepmania, which is the DDR sim, teamed up with some other folks in Seattle, I guess, I don't know what they did before, teamed up with this Rockstore Games thing, to put together a new machine for the US, I'm assuming to make up for a lack of new DDR mixes in the US, although...
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure they would tell you this has nothing to do with DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: They just want to make a brand new music game to kind of give something for the music fans to appreciate.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I got to play the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I went to 8 on the Break where they are beta testing it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: From what I understand, I actually checked one of the big websites, itgfreak.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Funny, itgfreak.
[SPEAKER_07]: I checked this site out and it's apparently still a beta machine, even though the full version is out.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it looked pretty finished to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It played pretty finished, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: but again it's a beta so some things I saw may have been different from the final version but I think for the most part my assessment will be on track and I realize there's people that love Indigroove and I realize there's people that hate it and hate everything it stands for so that being said my review of the game is basically going to be summed up with it's not as bad as people who brag on it would make you think it is it's not that bad but
[SPEAKER_07]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, the mines.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought, now see this is one of those things that I wouldn't have known unless I played the game because I thought mines were a stupid idea to begin with until I actually got to play it and I thought it was actually really fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: The way the step charts were done, the mines were really smartly placed, it's a neat new feature for the game, I like the mines, the mines can stay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, I think as for other step mania maker folks out there,
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: In the Groove scores you on this percentage system, which is basically your score out of 100% of the possible, and this is how you can tell that this game is absolutely slanted towards people that perfect attack, which, when you look at the people that work on it, doesn't surprise me much, but that's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: For a perfect attacker, you know, it's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: The scoring system's pretty smart, and I like the scoring system, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And just as I said, it takes perfect attack to the next level of
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't see a lot of stuff that looked very freestylable to me, however.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I think if you're more of a freestyler, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you may be liking some of the new songs, but it's definitely a perfect attacker's game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's my assessment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also like the fact that they have the Beatmania chart there where it does...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it shows like a little graph that you can actually see where you sucked in the song and where you were good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, again, things cater to perfect attackers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, because now everybody is screaming and hollering in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: As I said, it's a controversial thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody feels very strongly one way or the other.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is just my big fat opinion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take it, leave it, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is something I put in my good column.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not bad for a first mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: Considering this is the very first...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't care how you want to put it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't ignore that these people were obviously influenced by DDR significantly.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not a bad game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought there was more places where you could rank.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just thought the kind of ranking system was kind of cool, like you could rank in all these different spots, and every song had a top ten list, which I thought was kind of fun, so the ranking system was better.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're a mode whore, you're in for a treat, because this thing has about a zillion different modes on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't even read them all.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not a mode whore, I could give a shit, but if you're a mode whore, you're gonna have a blast.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Zodiac by Banzai
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought that song was really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's something I would like to play on the station sometime.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe even do an In The Groove hour of songs or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought some of the cheesy cover songs... Oh, you guys did that last week when I wasn't here?
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: I thought some of the cheesy... You guys, nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki and Bradley.
[SPEAKER_07]: The guys, not girl and guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought some of the cheesy cover songs were really... As a person who appreciates the gay music, I thought the dance covers of Mouth and Torn were really cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I kind of like those songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Missing Heart.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was like three Missing Heart songs in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought that was awesome because I like Missing Hearts.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you have Zodiac.
[SPEAKER_07]: Play a little clip of Zodiac for me because I like this song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty Please.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually thought this song was really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Play a little bit for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a real fun one to dance to.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought this was like the best song in the whole mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: At the same time though, it's probably the song that gets incredibly whored out.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's just my guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, that was a little bit of Zodiac.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like that song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, okay, that's what I have in the good column.
[SPEAKER_07]: You ready for the bad?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm gonna take a lot of shit for this comment, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is how I honestly feel.
[SPEAKER_07]: As somebody who's been a fan of DDR for four years, or, what, three or four years, however long it's been, I realize these guys are taking a lot of shit for it being a blatant, like, for people saying it's too much like DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is too much like DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is a blatant DDR ripoff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, that's how I felt.
[SPEAKER_07]: I felt like I was playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: I realize there's new stuff and they're trying to be different.
[SPEAKER_07]: My only suggestion is that it's not different enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think, now there's this whole argument going on about is it legal, is it not, is it legal, is it not.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know where that stands.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not my issue.
[SPEAKER_07]: What, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: It is DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's only changed from DDR enough to make it not so they can't get sued.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty much what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: They only changed, they would have left it the same if they could have.
[SPEAKER_17]: And also I think that since it's not an actually re-engineered DDR, that it's, you know, ground up, they can't say that they stole the engine.
[SPEAKER_07]: But honestly, I think if Konami wanted to sue, and I don't know where this thing stands legally, but I think Konami does have a step to stand on.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is way too much like DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not different enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: I felt like I was playing DDR, different mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought the interface was smooth.
[SPEAKER_07]: The interface was very smooth, but I thought it was very dry.
[SPEAKER_07]: The backgrounds were boring and the arrows were ugly.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was an ugly game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was not a pretty game to look at.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was an ugly interface, basically.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Compared to Feet of Fury, how did those arrows look?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, compared to Feet of Fury, it looked great.
[SPEAKER_07]: But honestly, part of what attracted me to DDR in the beginning was that very...
[SPEAKER_07]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the thing that bugged me most about the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I realize it bugs a lot of people too as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I have played it, and I did get forced to do this in some songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think hand plants are the stupidest thing in the entire game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the game acknowledges... You think you hand plant?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're forced... That went out like years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can turn them off.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was not able to... There were so many modes, I couldn't even see where to turn it off.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: I understand you can turn them off.
[SPEAKER_07]: My point is, they are retarded in the first place.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are really retarded, and they were not put smart.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I was playing songs, and suddenly these hand plants would come up, and I just kind of sighed.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did not feel like throwing my back out to hit them.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not dancing.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is monkey flailing, is when you do those hand plants.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: And I realize it's borderline dancing at first, but the hand plants were stupid.
[SPEAKER_17]: With everything you've said about in the group so far, even the good stuff, it doesn't sound enough to me to even give a rat's ass about it, honestly.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, I think...
[SPEAKER_07]: I honestly think that everybody who is a fan of Bomani should try it once.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's different.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's worth a look.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, my thing is form your own opinion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Play it, form your own opinion.
[SPEAKER_17]: Of course, if someone wants to play a really ass of dancing games, there was that Jaleco one.
[SPEAKER_16]: What was that one?
[SPEAKER_17]: Stepping Stage.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I think that is Stepping Stage.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stepping Selection.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was that one.
[SPEAKER_17]: No game is as bad as that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I realize it's not really dancing in the first place, but the hand plants, it's what I hate about Pump It Up and it's what I hate about it in the group.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, that's just, I hated it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought, this is going to sound really cold.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought it was kind of stupid that the step chart makers had a credit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not talking about something like it's in the credits of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm talking about when you select a song and you go into the song, it shows in the same font size and type in the bottom corner, song name, song artist, and the step chart artist.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, the effort went into making the step charts.
[SPEAKER_17]: You should have some credit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the credit can be given at the end of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: This was the part that kind of bugged me, is that in most songs that I played, it was the same person every time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did that person put a lot of work in the game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure, I'm not going to debate that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the thing is, I don't think that person deserves as much credit as the person who created the song, for God's sake, the artist and the song you're dancing to.
[SPEAKER_07]: I realize it's a little thing, and I'm probably going to get shit for that comment, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's something that struck me as kind of like, I kind of went, that's kind of dorky.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's totally something, though, I would expect from the Sim scene.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I was a beginner, I wouldn't want to play in the groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has a really nice tutorial mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll give it that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's probably better than anything DDR has for beginners.
[SPEAKER_07]: But kind of looking at it, if I was new and I was walking into the arcade and I was looking at it, I wouldn't want to play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the interface is to hold turn off.
[SPEAKER_07]: When I was playing, the CD skipped, and it caused the whole game to skip, and it caused the arrows to skip.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of like the Ultramix glitch that some of the service packs have.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very similar to that effect.
[SPEAKER_07]: And since this game is so heavily based on Perfect Attack, that is a big no-no.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a big no-no.
[SPEAKER_04]: CD skipped.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why the fuck is it running off of a CD?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got a fucking hard drive in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Run off the hard drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, why the game... The game should not be lagging at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_04]: No lag.
[SPEAKER_07]: My thing is, I don't know if it's a CD skip or what it is, but it was like a CD skip.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it was kind of... bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh... Lastly, I...
[SPEAKER_07]: D.D.R.
[SPEAKER_04]: What I would just say is, FoonMix did it better.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to do the interface, Technolize did it better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, you put FoonMix songs and steps with Technolize's theme.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, you've got a better game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it comes down to.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's one point, but I will agree with you that FoonMix's steps were better.
[SPEAKER_07]: But FoonMix isn't an arcade game either, and I'm not talking about FoonMix right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, alright, there's the bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I gave you good, and I gave you bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: My final assessment is that everybody should try it at least once.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I honestly don't see this taking over DDR because here's my other point.
[SPEAKER_07]: While I was in the arcade, I just kind of observed in the arcade as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: While I was in the arcade, people were playing DDR non-stop.
[SPEAKER_07]: People came up and were playing DDR non-stop.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was one of three people the whole time I was there that played in the groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: I watched in my time there DDR make twice as much money as in the groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: A two-year-old game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the reality as far as I can see.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't debate that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's another thing, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your average DDR mix, and I understand this is brand new hardware that they're adding to the scene and everything like that, your average DDR mix costs about $800 to upgrade.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you were going to take a third mix machine, upgrade it to Extreme, it'd be about $800.
[SPEAKER_04]: This sucker costs over $2,000 to upgrade for an arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: An arcade that's risking, you know, adding this, I mean, cause, you know, DDR Extreme, sure, it may not be pulling in the crowds it was before, but you've already got that game, it's already been paying for it, and it's already, it's still making money.
[SPEAKER_17]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: This still will be good.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just... That's been proven right there at Food Mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know that's not an arcade game, but it's all in-house artists, and the songs are really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it comes down to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Songs are good, steps were innovative, the backgrounds were awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's... They put more effort into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not talking about Food Mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to finish up in the groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't want to leave it on such a sour note, because I did talk about a lot of bad stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, I just want to reiterate, it's the first mix...
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it can only get better.
[SPEAKER_07]: For a first mix, it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: But to me, and this is kind of my final say on it, I left playing this game the same taste in my mouth that I get when I play Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I don't mean physically, but I mean basically the way I kind of react to Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not like, oh, you know, cool, they have a Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe I'll play that for fun once in a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's exactly how I feel about In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_17]: Maybe somebody wants to say something about it, but I'm not going to have it open very long because I want to get to the cage match because we're starting to run late.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, yeah, I do want to allow, you know, if there's somebody that has a counterpoint, I want to give them a chance to speak back.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, www.orangeonstrater.com, click on interact with us if you want to interact with the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: And give us a shout on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_07]: And let's see what you have to say while I set up for the cage match here.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I guess In The Groove has gone gold or whatever and they're shipping to different arcades and what have you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, we're getting a call from our old buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jason!
[SPEAKER_07]: What's up, Jason?
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, it's me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course!
Of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I love hearing from Jason.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's up, Jason?
[SPEAKER_07]: You got something you want to say about In The Groove?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a few things that are always on my mind about this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: One little side note of something you said earlier.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rocksaur Games made, basically they took the number one game that comes with most Linux distributions called Tux Racer.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's basically a little racer with the penguin Tux mascot for Linux and they put it in an arcade game and shipped it out to arcades.
[SPEAKER_03]: We actually have one out here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never knew that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you go to the Rocks or Games Company website, there's two things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tux racer and the groove.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess you'll kind of leave it at that point then.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: The two things that are kind of
[SPEAKER_03]: What's hanging me up about all this is that, first of all, the songs, I still want to hear all the songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still want a soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still want to get all the songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do want to play the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But already the variety is, you know, VR USA, a nice group of songs, but all along it's similar lines.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure there are.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still want to play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: but yeah, the main two things that are on my mind, I don't know how many people I've told this to, maybe two or three people.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are about to tell two more, because that's how many people we have listening right now, two more.
[SPEAKER_03]: The arcade manager, like something to do with the arcade hardware manager for Rockstar, was standing like at the corner of the Konami booth at E3, and I was just kind of watching everybody play Extreme, and we had a nice little discussion.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember that guy, I saw him too.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's
[SPEAKER_03]: The two things that are hanging me up is that they're going to go for a copy of the Bomani series.
[SPEAKER_03]: He said they have eventual plans to start cloning the other games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Starting with Beatmania will most likely be their second.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a nice idea because it gets more games in the US.
[SPEAKER_03]: It finally brings these here legitimately and with a variety.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: At the same time, it's this little company undertaking this whole task of all of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to say they're just going to lose.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, this isn't an easy thing to take
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a difficult situation.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a really difficult situation.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think if Konami has issue with what's going on here, they need to do something about it now before it does get out of control.
[SPEAKER_07]: But maybe they can't do anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe that's the sad part of it, is that maybe they can't do anything.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, Konami US no longer has an arcade division anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: The whole thing about that article was that they don't produce the machines here, but they can still get it through a third-party distributor.
[SPEAKER_03]: and the bookkeeping is done in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do want to play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: If we ever got a machine here, I would play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know I would.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to play it, but I just don't know what to expect from it yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think big arcades with a lot of Bomani games should get in the groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just kind of a fun little alternative.
[SPEAKER_07]: And actually, I can see, because I've heard that this place that I went to has these big Friday night tournaments and stuff, and it does seem like it's a very tournament-friendly game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kind of not surprised by that, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think big arcades that have lots of Babani games should get it just as an alternative, but I wouldn't recommend the whole world jumping on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead of having three, four, or five extreme machines all in a row?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no need for two extreme machines.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get a fourth plus, and then get into the group.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fifth!
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, or fifth.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get a fourth plus or fifth, and then get into the group.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fourth plus, fourth plus.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it for now.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there anything else you want to say, Jason?
[SPEAKER_03]: Console games are going to make this thing very interesting when they finally decide to start working on those.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to be brave and say it doesn't happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously this isn't the authority, but ITG Freak already has locked forums in place for whenever that actually starts.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is on their to-do list.
[SPEAKER_07]: Feel free to prove me wrong, but I'm going to say right now it's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Feel free to prove me wrong, it's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see what goes from here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, now supposedly, supposedly, that they have some sort of encryption thing that they did with this whole game on the hard drive on this thing where you couldn't, you know, say, I don't know, because it is basically Set Mania, you couldn't, I don't know, add songs to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Supposedly they have this, something tells me that they don't, and I think that all you're going to have to do is buy this game and be like, hey, you know what, I don't want to buy your next upgrade for this thing, because they weren't going to do downloadable updates or something like that, that was one of the things I think they were talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so basically you could say, you know, I like this DDR Extreme machine I have here, but what I'm going to do is I'm going to take all the songs from DDR Extreme that are already available for download on the internet, and I'm going to put them in this, you know, in the groove thing, and I'm going to call it In The Groove Plus.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I'm going to sell it for $3,000 on the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what's interesting?
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is something I completely forgot to say about In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think what's going to be interesting about it
[SPEAKER_07]: is that basically, yeah, the irony of the situation is is that everybody's going to pirate it to play on StepMania and then they won't bother within the group.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the irony of the whole thing, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's how, honestly, that's how most people are playing it right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even better, there's people out there bootlegging fucking DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's going to stop them from fucking bootlegging this thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be even easier and they'll be able to make it even better.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's going to hurt the smaller companies, too.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, the less backing a company has, the more it's going to hurt them.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm digging myself deep enough hole as it is here with the In The Groove fans.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll just end this and move along gradually back to the rest of the normal show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds normal.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, thanks Jason for calling.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am offering a cordial invitation to anybody that worked on In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: or anybody that worked on In The Groove or anybody that had something to do with the making of this game, I invite you to come on this show.
[SPEAKER_07]: We will set up a phone interview or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on this show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Talk about your game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would love to know what you guys have to say about this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, come tell me I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell me there's going to be a home mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am perfectly fine with this, but I want to hear it from the official horse's mouth.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, open invite.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll be nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come to California, we'll buy you lunch.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's about all we can afford in our budget.
[SPEAKER_07]: A nice McDonald's lunch for our guests.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, we can open it up to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's take one more call.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey, your friendly neighborhood legend, Izaku.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Izaku, what's up?
[SPEAKER_23]: I already played in the groove.
[SPEAKER_23]: Obviously because I live in the city and Port Authority bus terminals and you were in the groove place.
[SPEAKER_05]: What'd you think?
[SPEAKER_23]: So far, so good.
[SPEAKER_23]: I mean, the songs are unique for the fact that this is probably the only alternative left, our last hope, because, you know, we're hearing word that this might be it.
[SPEAKER_23]: That, you know, DDR and the arcades might be on its last limb.
[SPEAKER_23]: People are going to get sick and tired.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hold on a second.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I think somebody came in the room.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hold on a sec.
[SPEAKER_23]: Clean your room!
[SPEAKER_23]: No, someone's asking for my roommate, but anyways, yeah, DDR, yeah, people have been playing Xtreme for almost two years, they're gonna get cranky and sick and tired.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's the thing, that's the thing, Zaku, is that I was at this place, and people were playing DDR Xtreme more than they were playing in the group.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, I realize it's just one day, and I realize it wasn't a tournament night or anything, but it was a Sunday afternoon, a random Sunday afternoon in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: and there were more people.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it wasn't the same people playing DDR the whole time.
[SPEAKER_07]: There were more people playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not always... It's not always going to be... Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, it's not going to always be tournament night at these other arcades.
[SPEAKER_04]: If this isn't doing good in this arcade, it's not going to do good in another arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_23]: It depends, though.
[SPEAKER_23]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_23]: Is that a princess phone ringing in the background?
[SPEAKER_23]: Is that a princess phone?
[SPEAKER_23]: That's not my phone, that's my roommate's phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_16]: Your roommate has a princess phone?
[SPEAKER_07]: Your roommate has a cute phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just sounds adorable.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_07]: Finish your thought, because we've got to get to Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, he just left his phone right there, but... Finish your thought, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got to go to Cage Match soon.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_23]: I mean, this is the...
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, in other words, let's just put it, to sum it all up, alternative, in the groove equals alternative for those who have been playing DDR Extreme for the longest, ever since it first came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll agree with you there.
[SPEAKER_23]: This is transitional.
[SPEAKER_23]: Period.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a good one, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Later.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's the funny thing, I agree, it's an alternative, not a replacement for DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's the funny thing, is that, you know, I say it at the same time, it's not a replacement for DDR, but yet it's, it is a rip-off of DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, anyway, before I say some more things that get me in trouble You know what, I didn't like Ultramix at first either And it suddenly became my favorite mix Home mix of all So, my opinion could change later on But for right now, that's how I feel Whatever, it's not all about me anyway As much as I like to think it is Hi guys, how are the rest of you guys doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of you guys look like you're falling asleep Sorry, I'll shut up about it in the room now
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to get to the cage match.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh yeah, cage match, that thing's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, let's get into the cage match.
[SPEAKER_16]: I miss the cage match.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, the way the Orange Lounge Radio cage match works, we play three songs for you guys, you guys pick your favorite, and it goes into rotation all week long here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We didn't do a cage match last week, so let's rewind to two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie surprised us all when she beat Echo Image and something Loki had picked to win it with this Ska remix of Lupin the Third.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's more like beach rock.
[SPEAKER_07]: and here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: You only get to hear a clip of it because it was the last winner.
[SPEAKER_07]: So here's a clip of song number one you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember, to participate, you need to be in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: www.orangeautorator.com Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's song number one you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tokyo Paradise Ska Orchestra.
[SPEAKER_07]: Theme from Lumen III.
Let's go!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Song number one in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tokyo Paradise Ska Orchestra with a theme from Lupin the Third.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Lupin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lupin!
[SPEAKER_07]: Lupin the Third.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because it's French.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lupin.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like Lupin.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're gonna watch some Lupin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, my turn, this is my pick for tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm actually being lazy and just picking the song that I was going to play last week, because there was supposed to be a cage match last week, but, you know, things change, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm just going to pick the same song.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I actually had written a little spiel for you guys to read, so I'm just going to go ahead and read that spiel now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see who's at the door.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, hello, Jonas is here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the little thing I was going to have Jamie read last week before the cage match.
[SPEAKER_17]: Except I was dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Since you cunts voted out Echo Image last week, I was going to pick Britney or some shit to torture you with in my absence.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this pretty kick-ass trance song came to my attention, and Jamie, I know how much you love trance.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it kind of sounds like tack in one part of it, so just listen to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, I know Loki has a total hard-on for this artist, so I thought I'd beat him to the punch by putting this in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's also kind of long, so deal with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is song number two, Ono Ken, with Vijore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoy.
Can I ask you a question?
Thank you for watching!
Thank you.
DarkSakura.com
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, song number two in tonight's cage match, Ono Ken with Vigore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie!
[SPEAKER_17]: I really liked it.
[SPEAKER_17]: It wasn't... The trance I am sick of is the cookie cutter repetitive crap trance that people... Feel the beat, feel the beat, feel the beat, feel the beat, feel the beat.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was a lot more, what's the word I'm thinking of, progressive sounding.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was more what I liked.
[SPEAKER_07]: You liked it, and that's an upset.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, yeah, I liked it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a trance that you like.
[SPEAKER_17]: But cage match-wise, it was a little long.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, I would listen to it all the time otherwise.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, that would be one of my songs on repeat.
[SPEAKER_17]: I would have to give it that high of a rating.
[SPEAKER_17]: However, because of Link, for cage match purposes, I would give it an 8, and this would be what I would have originally given it would have been a 9 otherwise.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jonas, who just came in the house a little bit ago, explicit.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's Mike over there for you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know you got to hear a little bit of Ono Ken, so what did you think of Ono Ken?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold the bottom when you talk.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, what's up?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll give it a 9 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well put.
[SPEAKER_07]: Angel, your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_13]: I really liked it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kind of ravey, just my style.
[SPEAKER_13]: Definitely a 10 from me.
[SPEAKER_07]: My thoughts is I really liked it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It could stand to have been a little shorter, but I'm just lazy, so I give it a 9, because it's not the song's fault that I'm lazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've listened to it before, so I actually didn't even listen to the whole song at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I've had this one forever.
[SPEAKER_05]: So on a scale of 1 to 10?
[SPEAKER_04]: I give it a 9, because it's... I wonder if you can do no wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fair enough, and lastly but not, or I'm sorry, lastly but not leastly.
[SPEAKER_07]: I almost said lastly but not lastly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Arcadia.
[SPEAKER_17]: You said last but not loosely.
[SPEAKER_11]: We never knew that you were loosely.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: It reminded me of something out of DDR or 2DX or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: It had that background that was sort of, it was a bit repetitive on the background, but still it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't you kind of get a little bit of a Taku vibe from it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, Still My Words-ish?
[SPEAKER_17]: No, there was another one that was... Like, what are those song tracks?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, like Traces.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, it made me think of Traces.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, let's go on to Loki's pick, and I think he tried to come up with something at the last minute, but I don't think it worked.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's going back to an old favorite.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I wasn't trying to come up with anything in the last minute, I was just seeing if I wanted to do any new shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I had to check.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that also reminds me that fuckin' Diverse Systems hasn't sent me my CD.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I understand that there's a little problem with that they weren't offering it to the US, but I thought I'd try ordering it anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they have my money.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't have a CD.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that makes me mad.
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as they send me a CD.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, anyways, um, so... No, I went ahead and decided that I'm gonna go ahead and try the Echo Image card again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
Music Music Music Music
[SPEAKER_07]: Song number three in tonight's cage match Echo Image with Come Back Jamie, come back and give us your vote
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, did I miss something?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, you did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Echo Image.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_17]: I really liked that song.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was just so... I mean, again, that would be another one that I would just listen to endlessly, but I don't think it was quite cage-matchy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Still, I'm giving it an 8.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bradley.
[SPEAKER_11]: Gotta grab a thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, for me...
[SPEAKER_11]: The background is pretty good, but the lyrics and the way it's sung is kind of blah.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I'll give it a 6.
[SPEAKER_30]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_30]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, duh, Echo Image 10.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know, I've been giving a lot of 10s lately, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: You're the 10 whore.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not a 10 whore.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're DDR Angel USA 10th Mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: No comment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exquisite.
[SPEAKER_01]: 8.5 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, 8.5 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_07]: My thoughts, you know what, it's kind of, this is really hard for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that is like my favorite song at the moment right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_07]: And in most normal circumstances, I would give that song an 11.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the problem is that I kind of feel the way Jamie does where it's not quite the song I would see winning Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is kind of slow and like, I think if that played in the middle of a dance music station, it would be kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm taking my 11 and bringing it down to like a 9.9.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you know what, it's not up to us, it's up to you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Loki's got a vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, duh, I do, don't I?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I give it an 11 because I'm still listening to this in my car over and over again.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know how long I've had this CD for and I still have listened to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Echo Image, CompuPhonic, you must get this CD.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is so good.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all I listened to while I was back east.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was the only CD I had on me.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm still not sick of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enough about what I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get to what you guys think.
[SPEAKER_07]: And your chance to vote on tonight's winner.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here are those three songs one more time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Starting with a theme from Lupin the Third by Tokyo Paradise Ska Orchestra.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, song number two tonight was Onoken with Vijore.
[SPEAKER_07]: And song number three tonight was Echo Image with Come Back.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, place your vote now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Loki just found something on the internet that's very cool that we must find.
[SPEAKER_04]: They sung the NeverEnding Story, or a version of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Echo Image.
[SPEAKER_07]: Echo Image did a version of NeverEnding Story, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I don't know if it's the same song, but it's got the same title, so I'm going to look for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, we'll find out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so anyway, those are the three you get to vote for right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lupin, Vigore, or Comeback.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I'm going to open up the Skype line one more time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any of your thoughts you want to talk to us about DDR Extreme USA, certainly, in the groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll definitely want to hear your thoughts on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or anything you want to bring up right now, fine by me.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we will get into, of course, the cage match.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not the cage match, the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: In a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to give you guys a chance for your votes to come in first, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, in the meantime, while we're waiting for a call, anything going on in the sim world this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: A few things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alpha 24 came out last week, but I'll mention it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing really new, I think, came with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except more bug fixes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, uh, Technolize...
[SPEAKER_04]: Version 2.8 finally got released with new, supposedly another Easter egg thing in that, probably some cool stuff in the background.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they have their unlock, or the unlock mode stuff is in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: They finished all the stuff for that and fixed some of the Alpha 24 problems.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's also a poll going on DDR Maniacs right now, because the guy that did all the character ripping for 5th Mix is pretty much done with it now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now he wants to know what other games you want to rip characters from, and he will go ahead and get on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I went ahead and voted for, I think, Party Collection or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: They wanted to do Ultramix, but I figured there's only two characters in Ultramix, so that's kind of a waste.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're doing that right now, and I think that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not really much going on right now other than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sort of sim-related, they're going to have...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Wave, or the Fura Fura mode, and .5 speed and all that wonderful stuff, and Break, that you can find in the arcade mixes, which is a free download I might add on DDRAmerica.com, a BitTorrent site, and you can actually, if you have a really kind operator at your local arcade, you can give that to them, and I'm sure they'll put it in there for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like ours.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that's pretty much all that's going on at the moment.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: How long ago did you order that Diverse Systems CD that you still haven't gotten?
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple months ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you going to write them?
[SPEAKER_07]: Contact the Better Business Bureau over it?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're Japanese.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can't understand my English.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I'll try.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll ask them, you know, hey... Because I still have the email, so I could email them again with that email later on once...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking that they're just not releasing to the US, so they're not going to send it to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: But later on, when the time comes when they do release it to the US, I'll be like, hey, I paid for this a long time ago, send me my fucking CD.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's pretty much what it's going to come down to.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they'll have to, because I have my receipts still from that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It shows that it was paid for, so there's no disputing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can just say no, and then, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: When you're dealing with international business, they don't necessarily have to send it to you.
[SPEAKER_16]: The business laws overseas are a lot different than they are here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't think it would be a problem.
[SPEAKER_17]: And you can't necessarily report a foreign business to the Better Business Bureau.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I wasn't going to do that anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: But I mean, I'm saying, if they don't ship it to you and you paid for it, there's not really much you're going to be able to do about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_04]: If not, I'm out that 50 bucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that it really matters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell me you didn't get your product.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, anyway, let's talk about Cage Match and the winner of tonight's Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_07]: Two of the songs did alright, but it wasn't enough to beat the third song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tonight's Cage Match winner is... Echo Image!
[SPEAKER_07]: Songs number one and two tied, but it weren't enough to overtake song number three.
[SPEAKER_07]: Song number three got about what one and two did combined.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the power of Shane persuasion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shane's persuasion in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn him for being a DDR celebrity all of a sudden.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, people wouldn't have given a shit what he said previously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just teasing you, Shane.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's do another break.
[SPEAKER_17]: Are you saying that now his words have a laxative effect when it comes to opinions?
[SPEAKER_07]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, actually, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: In all seriousness, I'm glad that song won.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just kind of, you know, I'm still kind of like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But some people, when they voted for it, they actually said, I want to see a slow song on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_17]: You did close the voting awfully early.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, I did.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm just a dick.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: People didn't get theirs in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they need to wake up and get in on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think it would have been enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: We were several, several votes behind Jamie, so I don't think it would have been enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: When it's pretty clear one song's going to win...
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, anyway, let's go to a break.
[SPEAKER_07]: And in this break, I'm going to pick up kind of a lot of those leftover songs we haven't gotten to yet from DDR Extreme USA, including one of my favorites, Diving.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like that song by Four Strings.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like a Virgin and YMCA.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're also going to gay it up a little bit in this break.
[SPEAKER_15]: When we come back... Dude, I saw them perform that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: When we come back, the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know it, you love it, and it's coming up.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_19]: So much that we should have done I was into Cuba Now I'm stuck Driving Knowing it was you I keep on trying
Thanks for watching!
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Young man, there's no need to feel down I said, young man, pick yourself up around I said, young man, cause you're in a new town There's no need to be unhappy Young man, there's a place you can go I said, young man, when you're short on your dough You can stay there, and I'm sure you won't find many ways to
[SPEAKER_19]: YMCA It's fun to stay at the YMCA Be a family with me So you'll need to enjoy You can hang out with all the boys It's fun to stay at the YMCA It's fun to stay at the YMCA
You can do whatever you feel
[SPEAKER_32]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's up with that Village People song?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it just me, or did it sound different?
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't sound like the same YMCA I remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sounded like they re-recorded it or something.
[SPEAKER_17]: You are not putting your nasty foot on the webcam.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki is changing out the bandage on his foot right now, and he wants to put it on the webcam to scare you all with.
[SPEAKER_17]: Look at his Silent Hill, you know, toe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, how was it to play DDR with that foot?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, I see that NeverEnding Story thing on WinMX.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to double-click it, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_07]: That echo image, never-ending story thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope we get that by the end of the show so we can play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is nasty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't believe you're putting that on cam.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so gross.
[SPEAKER_17]: I want to type.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't want to look at your ugly tongue.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, we've been playing a lot of EXUSA songs for you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know a lot of you guys missed Maximizer a little bit earlier.
[SPEAKER_07]: You didn't get a chance to hear Maximizer.
[SPEAKER_07]: and that's all you're going to hear of it now.
[SPEAKER_07]: But don't forget, all these EXUSA songs are in rotation all week long now on Orange Lounge Radio in our 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bomani Music and More program is on and all the Extreme USA songs are in there for your listening pleasure.
[SPEAKER_07]: We always update.
[SPEAKER_07]: We like to stay up to date for you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we'll be putting other new songs in.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't wait for Ultramix 2 to come out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to have field day with that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, on our station on Monday nights, tune in for Diversion
[SPEAKER_07]: Your favorite fan-made and official Bomani remix songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really good.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of industrial-sounding songs in there and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really good remixes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tune in if you haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: 7 o'clock Pacific Time on Monday night.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then Tuesday nights... That would be where I step in.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's Pump Up the Volume on Orange Sound Radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's where I'm basically supposed to play people's requests, except nobody ever requests things anymore.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I just play whatever the hell I feel like.
[SPEAKER_17]: Usually I'll play a whole CD or marathon stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was so completely impromptu last week, I just decided to play Dressed to Kill Again, the Eddie Izzard routine.
[SPEAKER_17]: Pre-show starts at 7 o'clock, or sometimes at a quarter till 7 if I'm bored.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then the show starts at 7.30 to 10.30, and if I'm bored I go longer if I lose track of time or if I forget to go to bed.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I play everything.
[SPEAKER_17]: I play everything from...
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see, what did I play last week?
[SPEAKER_17]: I played the DDR EX V-Rare 3 CD.
[SPEAKER_17]: I played some comedy.
[SPEAKER_17]: I played, you know, some Metallica.
[SPEAKER_17]: I just play everything.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, since I've got a pretty, you know, diverse sense of taste for music.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a good time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, listen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Listen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wednesday nights, 7 o'clock Pacific Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be back this Wednesday after a little bit of a hiatus, but Rice Princess, LankyStyle, and myself, we bring you a little show called Outside the Box, which is a show dedicated to video gaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: The other games, besides that DDR and foot stomping and beat hitting games.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Why is it for 113 weeks in a row now we have to do the FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_17]: Because I'm still full of angst and I can't make it stop.
[SPEAKER_17]: I would like to give a big FU to the majority of the human race.
[SPEAKER_17]: For one very big reason.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's a stupid moron who ran out in front of my car on Madison Avenue while I'm going 60.
[SPEAKER_17]: I would have hit him had he continued.
[SPEAKER_17]: Asshole decides that he's... Oh, there's a Tercel heading to me.
[SPEAKER_17]: And so he jumps out back into the lane.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I'm just like, looking... I managed to slow down enough.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was going about 20 where I got where he would have been.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I'm just looking at this guy like,
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh my god, what planet are you from?
[SPEAKER_17]: Are you from the planet of, like, perpetually flat people, you know, because they all get run over by cars?
[SPEAKER_17]: You stupid fucker.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then there's, like, the guy on the motorcycle who, like, decides that he's going to speed up when I'm trying to change lanes.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I'm halfway into the goddamn lane, and then he blows... Oh, what... I just... Yeah, I was going 60 on Madison.
[SPEAKER_17]: I usually go 60 on Madison.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was in the 50s, and it was only 10 miles over.
[SPEAKER_17]: Don't, oh my god, me?
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, uh, I was, uh, there's also, like, this old lady who was in front of the line, um, at, uh, um, the grocery store, who decided that she was gonna be the slowest person ever.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is in the express lane.
[SPEAKER_17]: They finally get out of the lane, and then they change cashiers and start counting out the door.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm like, what?
[SPEAKER_17]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: and then like a big actually goes to all that Chinese food and all like the carby food I've been eating all weekend because I decided that I was gonna gonna cheat like mad all weekend and I have and now my stomach hurts but I had coconut cream pie this weekend and that makes it all right and I want to go have a beer I had coconut cream pie when I was on the east coast it was very good it was at a little truck stop style diner too I went to the Hofbrau
[SPEAKER_17]: Huffbrow!
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't call it the Huffbrow.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Huffbrow!
[SPEAKER_17]: Huffbrow!
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially in a town where Arnold Schwarzenegger is governor.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the Huffbrow!
[SPEAKER_17]: And F you to the situation where people say, Oh sure, we'll call you when we're ready to eat.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then they go out to eat already.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then...
[SPEAKER_17]: An F you goes toward a friend's parent for saying something, for completely making an assumption about something that my fiance had said and for just going off on them with no reason.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, first of all, when you assume it makes an ass out of you and me, okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: You learn this when you're in middle school, okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: And then another F you goes to all the people who drive like huge luxury sedans and SUVs who park in compact places.
[SPEAKER_17]: Your car is not little.
[SPEAKER_17]: And also learn how to fucking stay in the lines, okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: If you're gonna park your car there, if there's nowhere else to do it, at least keep your car between the lines so that other people can park.
[SPEAKER_17]: I used to go around to people who did that at school and pour honey on their driver's side door.
[SPEAKER_17]: On the handle.
[SPEAKER_17]: In the middle of summer.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're so mature.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I would go back and check the handle when I was leaving, and there would be flies on it, and it would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_17]: This was, you know, when I was first in school.
[SPEAKER_17]: But, it's like, these are the people that I leave notes on their car now.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, the other day, I left a diagram on how to properly park the car on the top of this SUV.
[SPEAKER_17]: Also, another F you goes toward the H, too, for looking stupid.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, what was wrong with the Hummer?
[SPEAKER_17]: Rob, what was wrong with the Hummer?
[SPEAKER_17]: Do you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_17]: They look cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: They were tough.
[SPEAKER_17]: And now they're all like, hi, we're going to look completely suburban.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aren't those those square cars, the Hummers?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, they were awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're square!
[SPEAKER_17]: They're cool!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I want to put a rocket launcher on one and drive it to work.
[SPEAKER_17]: And it's just...
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, I've got the inked scalp.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's really my major B. Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: You sure?
[SPEAKER_17]: I should have ran over that guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I think you should have too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Teach him a lesson.
[SPEAKER_07]: Darwinizen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, let's move on to, uh, Loki!
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to say that I can't be that bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, my first time using those erupt chairs is, um, okay, there we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that was easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, uh, actually, I'm not that mad right now because I just noticed I'm getting a whole lot of new echo images and that makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But my main FU goes to my toe, because it hurts bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it doesn't, it's just, it hurts more with the, like, where they poke the needle in, because it's actually bruised, and if you touch it, it's really tender, and it's like, ugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, my toe looks really nasty, and it burns every now and then, so that's kind of bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, I should just have gone to the doctor earlier, and we wouldn't have this problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's, you know, a rule for everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have a problem, don't wait it out, because you don't know
[SPEAKER_04]: The doctor knows better than you do.
[SPEAKER_04]: So just go to the doctor, take care of... And that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, um... OtherFU goes to Paranoia Eternal on hand-to-feet mode for breaking my lamp.
[SPEAKER_04]: That wasn't my fault, that was purely DDR Extreme's fault for breaking the lamp.
[SPEAKER_04]: And... Finally, um... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty much all I've got.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, um... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you to goddamn...
[SPEAKER_04]: Jack in the Box for being fucking slow because they burned the stupid chicken tenders.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to myself for not taking Monday off of work because after leaving on a two week trip I really should have taken the next couple days off so I could just relax and catch up with everything I missed but F you to being gone so long because I missed everybody and it was sad but I'm back now and everything's better
[SPEAKER_17]: We missed you too, but our aim's improving.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, you're trying.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to the mall where the DDR pad was broken.
[SPEAKER_07]: That kind of pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to the same jack-in-the-box because that was my chicken tenders they burned and I had to go back and do.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they could have, you know, given us an update or something, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to all these video games coming out all at once that I want to buy and I'm not having, like, enough money to buy them all.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, I'll live.
[SPEAKER_07]: And...
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess that's really it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have a whole lot of angst.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm a nice person.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, maybe not, but I'm just... I'm not feeling very creative tonight, so... Oh, I thought of one.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to the fact that my flight got delayed leaving from Phoenix into California, into Sacramento, because...
[SPEAKER_07]: We all get on the plane and we're all sitting there and it's a full flight and it's just all packed.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't like all those people being so close to all those people to begin with.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially when you're sitting next to somebody whose arm is all up in the armrest and it feels like they're invading your personal space and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I don't like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then being told that, oh, we're missing a part.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have to go change a part on the plane.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then we're stuck there for like 20 minutes while they change a part.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sigh.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, let's get to some other FUs in studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's start off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's got a microphone?
[SPEAKER_07]: Somebody's got to have one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here he comes.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jonas with his FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll keep it as fast as possible.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to give an FU to work for not giving me some free time.
[SPEAKER_01]: I need to spend some time with my family.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't keep getting five days a week.
[SPEAKER_01]: First of all, I have school as well.
[SPEAKER_17]: Some of us work and go to school.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know that, but I have to take care of family as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: I gotta move, because I'm moving somewhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm moving to another house.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: F you to... F you to some asshole after buying my car for...
[SPEAKER_01]: some asshole after borrowing a car for without my permission to actually change the fluids of the inside like you don't put fucking engine oil on to where the coolant is supposed to be at that ain't fucking cool my car fucked up there
[SPEAKER_01]: And FU for not being able to play DDR Extreme for the PS2.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm hearing some pretty good reviews towards it.
[SPEAKER_01]: FU for maximize your steps to being sucky as hell.
[SPEAKER_01]: FU to RVGL for not fixing their goddamn pads.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wanted to try that EX2, I wasted a dollar for nothing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not to mention some extra gas money.
[SPEAKER_01]: FU to someone throwing tacks on the road.
[SPEAKER_01]: God dammit.
[SPEAKER_01]: And people, people, people don't know what to do, when to quit.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you think you're gonna throw a bunch of tacks on the road and say, ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_01]: And FU for double parking in the school area.
[SPEAKER_01]: God dammit, we all have to park as well, not just one car hogging two lanes.
[SPEAKER_01]: And thanks to that, I actually failed the damn midterm because of that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I was 30 minutes late with class.
[SPEAKER_01]: And since I have to keep the FU shorts, might as well give it to someone else.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bradley.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bradley, your FU's.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck you to politics as usual.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck you to lazy dumb shits in parking lots who leave their...
[SPEAKER_11]: Grocery stores that leave their fucking grocery carts out in the middle of the spaces.
[SPEAKER_11]: So fucking annoying, you can come up to a space and be like, oh, I can go park here, oh no, the dumb shit put the fucking carts in the middle of the space.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you put it up in one of the meaty little things and it's not in the way, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's still annoying and you're a lazy ass for not taking it to the receptacle or back to the store, but if it's in the way, it's a bitch.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, let's see, what else?
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck you to being lazy after work and not really getting much done.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'll give a fuck you to dial-up for being slow, and that being part of the reason it takes forever to go read LiveJournal and check up on everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: DDR Angel, your FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't really have that many FUs this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was getting all excited about Final Fantasy XI until Andrew just text messaged me and said my video card might not like it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So FU to that.
[SPEAKER_13]: But maybe we'll get that fixed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, that's me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, maybe the benchmark will fix it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, yeah, the benchmark.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, yeah, we have that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I've heeded that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hope to get that fixed tomorrow so I can play with the rest of the group.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's not really that much to... Oh, yeah, and I've heeded my...
[SPEAKER_13]: My computer science teacher for getting our webpage project that was due like Friday.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's like, oh, okay, hold the screen on Monday so you guys can do your presentation.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like, dork, you're the one that said you were going to bring it in on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, let's get to our chatroom FUs.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got to make this quick tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you sent a bunch, they're getting cut, just to warn you.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkLion, FU to myself for giving Sky the song Regulus over the Clouds mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: I told you not to play it while I was in San Francisco two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry!
[SPEAKER_07]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: FU to JTap for being one of the most boring anime conventions I've ever attended.
[SPEAKER_07]: My only complaint is that I didn't get to hang around with friends I haven't seen for a long time, even though I was staffing in the video department.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wish I could have gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something came up and I couldn't go.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was originally planning.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dark Knight says, My FU is one of extraordinary magnitude.
[SPEAKER_07]: FU to the local putt-putt in my hometown for taking away the only 2DX machine in Richmond.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's now the only Beatmania we have now as second mix complete.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn them all to Haiti.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mandarin says, FU to dumb Costco customers who don't know how to put perishable shit back where it belongs, but instead put some frozen hamburger patties on the same aisle as aspirin.
Hahaha.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shade23 says, F you to my headset for being missing so I can't defend in the groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, I said good things about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said bad things about it too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Johnfield said, F you to spilling soda all over myself at dinner.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to not enough hours in the day.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you for not being able to go to Tokyo Game Show and get PSM exclusive footage.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sid says F you to Utah for being a Bomani wasteland.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to my hands for failing get on beat wild style every time that I play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to the samurai of the world for the suppression of the ninja clans.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are they still around?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: And F you to my body for waking me up at 5 a.m.
[SPEAKER_07]: every day when I really need to get up at 7.
[SPEAKER_07]: Siegert says F you to the whiny ass DDR freak people who complain that Extreme US is crappy because it doesn't cater their wants.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get over it.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to those same people who blame Konami of America for EXUS's faults.
[SPEAKER_07]: Try blaming the right company for once.
[SPEAKER_30]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to having Job ADD in Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_07]: And finally, F you to the DS only coming out in the silver-black color.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want some sort of blue.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pokemon Blue.
[SPEAKER_07]: Zaku says, F you to having to spend the better part of Friday cleaning out the shit called spyware, addaware from my computer.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to Fox News Live for basically making DDR Freak Mod Frequency look like a fool when she asked him that she thought she was going to interview a nine-year-old and making DDR look like a fad instead of a serious weight loss tool.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're actually going to get to that.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have like five minutes left in show, but I want to get to that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rychan says, F you to all the American brats acting like Festival was made for them so they have every right to bitch about the preliminary song list.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another thing we didn't even get to.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to our arcade manager for not doing anything to take care of our machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to Konami Style for not making it easier to get a hold of the 2DX8 style limited edition.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, DDArcoholic, uh, F you to my emerging pot belly.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to my old CD burner for deciding it doesn't want to burn discs anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I replaced your stupid head with a new DVD burner.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob, your new icon has a penis in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did not put a penis in the icon.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys are just seeing things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and F you to this insane beeping sound that keeps going off somewhere in my apartment complex every five minutes and has been doing so for several days now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe longer because I only just recently noticed it and now it's fucking annoying because it goes beep, beep, beep every five freaking minutes every day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lastly, Nince says, F you to myself for picking a hard to find topic for my research paper.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to my boss.
[SPEAKER_07]: She has this wonderful idea if someone only works for two or three days a week, no matter how many hours they work in those days,
[SPEAKER_07]: She doesn't pay you that week and rolls it in the next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to school now and can't work that much.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need my damn money now.
[SPEAKER_07]: And F you to the creepy guy that was following my friends and I at the movie theater last night.
[SPEAKER_07]: Later found out from her friend working there that he had been there for hours talking to random people.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he says he should have that Echo Image Neverending Story remix in five minutes.
[SPEAKER_07]: So pass that along to us.
[SPEAKER_07]: We want it too.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're done with the F yous.
[SPEAKER_07]: One more kind of big story this week we've got to get to.
[SPEAKER_07]: DDR made an appearance on Fair and Balanced, ha ha ha, Fox News this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we actually got a picture, not a picture, I'm sorry, the clip of the interview here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually haven't even watched this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I watched it when it was live on air, but I haven't even seen this other little clip of it yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says it's 25 minutes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't be right.
[SPEAKER_07]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's more like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's only about three minutes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's check this out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here is a little interview, and we're going to do, of course, in typical Orange Lounge fashion, we will butt in and make comments whenever we feel like it on the Fox News clip.
[SPEAKER_07]: So here it is, the audio version for those of you guys who didn't get a chance to hear it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow, and the audio level is very shitty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me see what I can do about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me see if I can open it up in another program.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give me a minute, you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is what happens when you try to play something when you haven't really...
[SPEAKER_07]: Explore the file yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: If worse comes to worse, we can always save it for next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see what I can do about turning up the volume here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go into this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's try it this way.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't hear it!
[SPEAKER_07]: The audio sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_07]: It's an MPEG.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, Loki's going to try blasting it for you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's on my desktop.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should be able to share it, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me share the desktop.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, can I copy it over to your network?
[SPEAKER_07]: We're having technical difficulties, everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I'm going to try putting it on Loki's computer.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to try one other thing here.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is what I get for trying to do things on the fly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I'm going to drop it in right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki's got it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to try to
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pause it, pause it, pause it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Obviously they did their research there.
[SPEAKER_26]: The member of the DDR Freaks.
[SPEAKER_26]: Did you know that you're a moderator on DDR Freaks?
[SPEAKER_26]: That woman is a moron.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, start it up again.
[SPEAKER_26]: Jason, first, why don't you explain to me what DDR is?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Dance Dance Revolution is an interactive video game that combines physical activity with energetic dance music.
[SPEAKER_02]: It allows you to actually drop your controllers and get up on a dance floor and actually move to the groove.
[SPEAKER_26]: This is not that much different than Twister without the music, no?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, a lot of people have said it's like karaoke for your feet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pause it, pause it, pause it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know anyone that's ever called it karaoke for your feet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Has anyone ever heard karaoke for your feet?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've heard the twister thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've heard Simon Says.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've heard Spider Stomp.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, maybe I should ask Jason Enos.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: My preschool teacher, her name was Mrs. Enos.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Respect a little bit here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pause it.
[SPEAKER_26]: You are part of the DDR Freaks, and I just have to out you on your age, you're 21 years old, you're not a 6 year old 7 year old.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was like the most belittling comment there, I have to out you on your age, you're not 6 or 7.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cause I can't tell by the fact that this guy has facial hair, he's got a little goatee going on, he looks like he's a pretty well built guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: He does look like, by looks alone here, he does appear to be past puberty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember, the average person is an idiot.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have to explain these things.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm five years older than this guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie's older than this guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Matt's older than this guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bradley's older than this guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think almost everybody in this room, except maybe Jonas.
[SPEAKER_06]: How old are you, Jonas?
[SPEAKER_07]: Then everybody in this room except Jonas is older than this guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: So when she kind of says that to him, I kind of get mad.
[SPEAKER_07]: But of course this is Fox News and they're stupid anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I'm positive.
[SPEAKER_12]: 21, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: You like this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, you know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Pause it, pause it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You like this crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you actually like this.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're so weird!
[SPEAKER_12]: Unposit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who are 14 years old, and I know people who are 40 years old.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're all playing the game, they all love the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: For whatever reason, either it's exercise or even competition.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, so since this story has kind of a serious angle, we're talking about obesity and kids.
[SPEAKER_26]: Tell me about the losing weight part.
[SPEAKER_26]: Does it really make you work up the sweat?
[SPEAKER_07]: Unposit.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to point out at this moment they're showing people dancing on the game wearing these kind of like aerobic looking things.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, let me get this straight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me get this straight, Don.
[SPEAKER_06]: When I move, I'm going to work up a sweat?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that what you're telling me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Unpause it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It makes me work a sweat.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's really, you know, songs can run you, you know, at a very slow pace or can even run you at a very high pace.
[SPEAKER_12]: Songs can run up to 300 BPM and, you know, a regular song on the radio can only go to about maybe 120.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, obviously they did not prep him with the questions there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you know, no offense to that guy, but songs on the radio only go up to 130 BPM.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know so much about that, but anyway...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's obvious that they did not let him know what the questions would be in advance, so, you know, he's probably just... Because if it were to go over that, you know, just sheer chaos would erupt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_04]: Too fast!
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't drive!
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like nuclear bombs that go off, you know, just the world erupt into pure anarchy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, unpause it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Pause it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would like to point out, lady, you can do anything for hours and hours.
[SPEAKER_26]: You could play DDR, you could play EverQuest, you could masturbate for hours and hours if you wanted to.
[SPEAKER_12]: You could, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Plot to murder Fox News reporters for hours and hours.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unpause it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just one more song.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll be right there.
[SPEAKER_12]: It gets your entire body into it.
[SPEAKER_12]: You don't even pay attention to yourself.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pause it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, also they had to show your token Asian playing DDR there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I want to point out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love how she had to compare it to EverQuest.
[SPEAKER_18]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, does this game get you addicted and then you want to murder people like EverQuest does?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think that your friends are orcs?
[SPEAKER_17]: I want to put my score on eBay and sell it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, now wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not such a stretch because we all know that there are certain individuals that put their shoes on eBay and some idiot out there is dumb enough to buy it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know anyone who's done that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I could, well, yeah, we'll, anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: Unpause it.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, losing weight or having fun, you know, playing the game, just, you know, listening to music and... I might add that the terror alert was elevated at the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_26]: Hey, Jason, it sounds like you should be marketing this to adults.
[SPEAKER_26]: How much does this game cost?
[SPEAKER_05]: Pause it.
[SPEAKER_15]: That is the funniest capture of him, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: There are so many places you could go with this statement.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sounds like a game you should be marketing towards adults.
[SPEAKER_07]: And why are we all on the Fox News Channel right now?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I know so many children that watch the station.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you do know any children that watch Fox News Channel, they are being poisoned.
[SPEAKER_07]: Turn them away.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make them watch SpongeBob.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pause it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Totally great.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love the fact that Jason just happened... Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so funny you should ask.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just happen to have the game right here in my hand.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so glad you asked!
[SPEAKER_07]: See, obviously he was prepped on his questions, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pause it.
[SPEAKER_02]: In other words, I'm too cheap to buy one myself!
[SPEAKER_06]: Give me one for free, Jason, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we need to write a letter to them.
[SPEAKER_16]: Please don't report on DDR again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please don't report on anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fox News Channel is a horrible station.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I'll pause it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Thank you so much, Jason, Enos, and Don.
Enos!
[SPEAKER_04]: Enos!
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me talk about pronunciation here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it look like there's an I?
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it look like there's an E?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a fucking O. Enos!
[SPEAKER_04]: It would even be, if you mispronounce it, it would be like, you know, Pot or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be Enos, not Enis.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enos, Enos, not Enis.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might as well just call him Jason the Penis Man.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, that's what you're... You're fucking stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Learn to pronounce shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, thank you, Mr. Enos and the little six-year-old from DDR Freaks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm positive.
[SPEAKER_26]: Don D'Amato, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_26]: Greg?
[SPEAKER_29]: Thank you, Derek.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: That guy has such a porn star name, too.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Don D'Amato.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of a porn star name, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you play the clip one more time?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I really quickly want to read for you guys the Fox Facts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dancing video game can help kids lose weight
[SPEAKER_26]: or DDR.
[SPEAKER_26]: Let's kids get their groove on and lose weight at the same time.
[SPEAKER_26]: With us now, DDR product manager Jason Enos and Don D'Amato, member of a fan club called DDR Freaks.
[SPEAKER_26]: Welcome both of you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Still saying dancing video games can help kids lose weight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, get to the facts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jason Enos, CDR project manager.
[SPEAKER_02]: We all know that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Enos has helped design numerous video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Imagine that.
[SPEAKER_07]: He works for Konami and he has helped design numerous video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never would have thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: 15% of American kids are overweight or obese.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that's a fact.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to add that Mel B was in this video.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would be embarrassed to be on this station, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pause it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another 15% of kids are at risk of becoming overweight.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are one Snickers bar away from doom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Put that kid on Atkins right now!
[SPEAKER_04]: Now the risk of them becoming overweight, is that meaning that they're at risk of the overweight person eating them?
[SPEAKER_04]: So therefore they're becoming part of the overweight person?
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_26]: Anyways, back to it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Pause it, I can't resist.
[SPEAKER_06]: Listen to how she's talking down to him.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Dawn, you're part of the DDR freaks, and you're not nine years old?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, we've got to finish.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unpause it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Let's get the rest of the facts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Over 9 million American kids are overweight or obese.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they've taken that 15%, and now they've just... You know who's to blame for that?
[SPEAKER_17]: Mommy and Daddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_12]: 7-year-old.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm 21, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: You like this.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, you know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: I know people who are 40.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, of course, his name, Don D'Amato, porn star and DDR Freaks member.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it says DDR Freaks member.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Domato has played Dance Dance Revolution for years.
[SPEAKER_07]: For whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_07]: Over 10% of children aged 2 to 5 are overweight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because you so should get your 2-year-old into DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: 2-year-olds aren't... Yeah, those are the people that are fucking putting those stupid kids on the pads.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want my fat bitch to get you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Less fat and less bitchy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Either it's exercise or even competition.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, so since this story has kind of a serious angle, we're talking about obesity and kids, tell me about the losing weight part.
[SPEAKER_26]: Does it really make you work up a sweat?
[SPEAKER_12]: It makes me work a sweat.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's really, you know... Pause it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kids need 60 minutes of activity a day for their health.
[SPEAKER_07]: So kids, start having sex early because you need 60 minutes of it every day.
[SPEAKER_12]: It can run you, you know, at a very slow pace or...
[SPEAKER_06]: approximately one half of kids do vigorous physical activity regularly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I would like to readjust that number to about 99% of teenagers who masturbate frequently.
[SPEAKER_16]: What arcade is that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have no idea what arcade it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does it look familiar to you or something?
[SPEAKER_12]: It could even run you at a very high pace.
[SPEAKER_12]: Songs can run up to 300 BPM and, you know, a regular song on the radio can only go to about maybe 120.
[SPEAKER_12]: So maybe songs can end up being about three times as fast and moving around three times as fast as any, you know, normal buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Approximately one quarter of kids report no vigorous physical activity.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the other...
[SPEAKER_07]: And that quarter would be the liars.
[SPEAKER_26]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be funny because if they muted out that it was about DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this is something you could do for hours and hours.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: A quarter of U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: kids spend four or more hours a day watching TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could part of that four hours be watching TV to, you know, see the arrows that are going up the screen to play the game?
[SPEAKER_17]: I didn't mean that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually watching television programming.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: No shit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Pause it, pause it, pause it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Can you sense it a little bit in his reaction?
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you sense it just a little bit in his reaction?
[SPEAKER_07]: He's just kind of like, no shit, lady.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you think I'm doing on your piece of shit television station?
[SPEAKER_15]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: I see it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to say that's what he meant to say, but I sense it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just brought out our latest... The next time I see him, hopefully at E3 this year, I'm going to ask him, don't you think you should be marketing this game for adults?
[SPEAKER_04]: See if he gets the joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also give you a dollar for that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll double that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dance Dance Revolution Extreme for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, the fast facts went away so that we can see the nice cover of CDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_02]: We also have a version that comes with the dance pad so you can get started right away for $59.99.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm going to have to ask our promo department if we've got... Same one, same tag.
[SPEAKER_26]: That looks kind of good.
[SPEAKER_26]: Thank you so much, Jason Enos and Don DiMato.
[SPEAKER_26]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_29]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_26]: Greg?
[SPEAKER_29]: Thank you, Derek.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's what we're here for.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our longest show ever, thanks to that little clip.
[SPEAKER_17]: I need to go home.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: It needed to be made fun of, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: With all respect to Don and Jason for being good sports with that interview, we just had to... I'll take any chance I can to make fun of Fox News.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, let's move on with our final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got to wrap up this show.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll start off with our guests.
[SPEAKER_01]: Start off with Jonas.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jason Enis.
[SPEAKER_08]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: All I can think about is Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_13]: Please kill me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Addict.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Arcadian42.
[SPEAKER_07]: Last week is a tip.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Finally.
[SPEAKER_07]: My thought is we didn't even get through all of this week's news.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's how crazy of a week it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why is it that the Monty News always is like all of a sudden it's all in one week?
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll just have to carry it over to next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: And tune into our other shows too, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: And in this corner, weighing 250 pounds, the raging fury, Enos the Penis!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_15]: My intestines hurt.
[SPEAKER_15]: Damn carbs.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, and, uh... Oh, I have one more thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: The only person you have to blame is yourself.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're all going to do the final word together today.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to say it once for everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should see this coming.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's tonight's final word.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, I gotta get it queued up so we got the music ready to go here.
[SPEAKER_07]: One, two, three, Enos!
[SPEAKER_32]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_32]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_32]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_00]: So dangerous, so dangerous.
[SPEAKER_00]: He fights the law, but he also fights the crime, but not as much.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dangerousque.
[SPEAKER_00]: With Ronaldo at his side, he'll have Ronaldo at his side, dangerous He's got some Chinese stars, and he keeps them under the bed when they link the pipe, dangerous That guy is dangerous, the mighty oak has fallen
[SPEAKER_00]: Cool glasses, cool glasses Stick it to the man, stick it to the man Cool, cool glasses He works alone, except when he works with Ronaldo, which is all the time dangerous He's a private eye, a crooked cop, secret agent, and a celebrity pharmacist, dangerous That guy is dangerous, dangerous
[SPEAKER_32]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio, the afterbirth, the part after the credits.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, we've already given you an extra bonus ten minutes tonight, so you should be thankful for that.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going home.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, you've got to get home, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jonas is leaving.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have to do my quiz for database management.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our listeners are all leaving too, so it's going to be short.
[SPEAKER_07]: I definitely want to play this for you guys, because I just got it, and we've been talking about it a little bit before earlier, so you know I've got to play this for you guys now that we've got it, thank you Ninst for passing this along, but we did manage to get that echo image, never ending story, what is this?
[SPEAKER_07]: The NeverEnding Story Fantasy Remix, or what is that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Fantasia.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fantasia Mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we don't know if this is the actual NeverEnding Story theme song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, but it has NeverEnding Story and Fantasia.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, that's kind of not really a... And it's Echo Image.
[SPEAKER_07]: How can you go wrong with this, no matter what it is?
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, I'm just a child.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_18]: I knew everything.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_18]: I can't forgive you.
[SPEAKER_18]: I just can't wait.
[SPEAKER_19]: Look at what you see in the face, the mirror of your dreams.
Believe I'm a hero, hidden in the light, written on the pages.
One keep the secret We'll fall behind the clouds They are among the rainbows
[SPEAKER_07]: Echo Image there, who we've all fallen in love with recently with a kick-ass version of Never Ending Story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: As I told Sigurd in private message, we've been having a little bit of a private message chat going back and forth.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to have sex with that song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Downright.
[SPEAKER_04]: That song is everything that I imagined it would be.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was so hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so unbelievably hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is why I had to download... God damn it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why couldn't you have put that in Cage Match?
[SPEAKER_07]: As much as I love Come Back, that would have been a much better song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did download... What did I get earlier?
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to get that off your computer too, that song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did download the Icon of Coil remix of Skull.
[SPEAKER_07]: Play like a little bit of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Icon of Coil?
[SPEAKER_04]: Coil, it's another... Play like a little clip.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go in the middle.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kill our speakers there, why don't you?
[SPEAKER_04]: I forgot I turned it up for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Way to go, genius.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're an industrial band, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, stop it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I swear to God, I'm going to start like an Echo Image fan site on orisonradio.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just, God, they are so good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Note said, and I just noticed this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I don't know about this because I was looking at their discography.
[SPEAKER_04]: They only have one album.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's because people don't know it.
[SPEAKER_07]: One album.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm spreading the word.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't download this shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go buy the album.
[SPEAKER_07]: You won't regret it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I swear you won't.
[SPEAKER_07]: And as soon as I can find a copy of the album, I'm going to buy it legitimately too, I swear.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to order it on Amazon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope to God that what they really need to do, and I'm really saying what they need to do, is they need to gather all these artists on this label here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I forget what it's called now.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways, gather all the artists, throw a concert.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just even like two cities or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it's expensive to throw a concert, but these are artists that no one's ever heard of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe get the label to come and chip in a little bit of money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or even just one concert.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft