All the sweet shit that saves me
and the rest.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not again, not again, not again In this dream I can't awake What is real, what is real, what is real It's getting hard for me to say What I need, what I need, what I need Little things in our life And the white sugar's in the ice
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format
You're listening to Orange Line Radio Live.
This morning's talk radio is so much more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_30]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_30]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_30]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_30]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_29]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we are.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are live.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is episode number 110 for this September the 5th.
[SPEAKER_04]: of 2004.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome to Orange Lounge Radio season number 1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
[SPEAKER_04]: Who... You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought we would have been cancelled by now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about the rest of you guys.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's because we don't have to bow down and kiss the ass of the SEC.
[SPEAKER_04]: We only have to kiss Konami's ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's basically just one company.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a lot smaller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, joining me as always, my name's Sky, Rob Roberts, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_04]: This corner, the happiest money on the farm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello to...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm full of meat and well happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're enjoying your meat.
[SPEAKER_18]: I enjoyed my meat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Miss Jamie Summers loves her meat.
[SPEAKER_18]: The ice cream comes next.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who gave her her meat?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_19]: I paid for my meat.
[SPEAKER_18]: Also joining us... I know where it came from.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also joining us, your other co-host, the tech massa with a humongous internet penis.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello to Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm so disorganized today.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't find my other paper.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also joining us tonight, we have plenty of special guests.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello to the one and only Floatwalk.
[SPEAKER_26]: Bagels, anybody?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you might know him under another name if you've listened to this show long enough or if you've ever watched a freestyle video in your life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also joining us, say hello to DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have pizza.
[SPEAKER_19]: Does anyone want one?
[SPEAKER_19]: Or some?
[SPEAKER_19]: Or... No, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's for the rest of the...
[SPEAKER_19]: Studio.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, um, here, how about like a virtual slice of pizza?
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe, maybe a little bit later we'll, uh, we'll get some, uh... Sure, and I have a special surprise for Loki tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, uh, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also joining us is, say hello to, Sharks Girl!
[SPEAKER_16]: Can I just have one question?
[SPEAKER_16]: Where is Raekwon's Cuties?
[SPEAKER_16]: I miss that movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's somewhere around here.
[SPEAKER_16]: We have to go find Raekwon's Cuties.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's the best movie ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we've got a big show for you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know a lot of you guys have had bagels on your mind all week, and we will be spreading the news about what the latest clue is all about.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not going to... I've got to clarify something, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not blatantly giving you the song.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just giving you a little kick in the ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give me a little kick in the ass to get you charged up and figure out what that song is all about.
[SPEAKER_04]: All this and plenty of Bomani news.
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ask Orange Lounge and all that crap you've loved for the past four seasons.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we come back from this break featuring songs from Poppin' Music 11.
[SPEAKER_04]: In this break we're going to hear a Sana song called Space Dog, Megumi with Frost, and a little bit of Hong Kong magic from Yamato.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be right back.
Can you hear me?
I'm a face door.
The earth is shining blue.
Can you see me?
I'm a face door.
Can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Hikibitome Yoyuwa Akeru made kono Te hanasanaide Make a stage Kazayai de daremo Kitta koto nai Hibitsu no kotoba Gutto Taki yosete Gutto
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching!
and more.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hi, this is Mel B of RTF.
[SPEAKER_23]: And for an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Mel B can join us on all the fun together.
[SPEAKER_26]: But hey, if you're a broke ass like I am, why don't you come to one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_26]: Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gee, that guy sounds awfully familiar.
[SPEAKER_26]: I wonder who that was.
[SPEAKER_04]: He sounds like somebody I've heard from very recently.
[SPEAKER_04]: He sounds very, very familiar to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing, FlowWalk?
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, man, it's been pretty busy lately and I have no idea who the hell you're talking about from that promo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the answer is hazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio www.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_04]: and click on chat and you can interact with the chat room there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Jamie is chatting with our listeners there, having a grand old time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she's having to put the smack down when necessary as well because she don't tolerate no flaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except, you know, gay kind of flaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, like, flaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, no being a poopy head on Jamie's watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, we have the Skype line, which we will certainly open up a little bit later in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: www.orangelandredo.com and click on Interact With Us and you can find out all about the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, we're going to start off tonight's show as we do every week's show, playing a little bit of How was your week?
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_04]: And starting us off, as always, our lovely, our own Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_18]: I worked, and I went to school, and then something that...
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sure Melody will expand on as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: We got interviewed for a magazine.
[SPEAKER_18]: For a Lifetime magazine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Lifetime TV for Women?
[SPEAKER_18]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_18]: For the fitness benefits of DDR.
[SPEAKER_18]: So...
[SPEAKER_13]: Coming up next on Lifetime, Sally Field stars in My Burning Vagina.
[SPEAKER_04]: A story about a woman overcoming her vaginal difficulties in that time of the month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also coming up, Sharks Girl and Dark Sakura interviewed about DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Stop... Hear how DDR helped them overcome their burning vaginas.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I love this show.
[SPEAKER_18]: We jumped the shark like when?
[SPEAKER_18]: Like episode two?
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode two.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I wasn't here.
[SPEAKER_18]: That set the pace.
[SPEAKER_18]: Jamie's going on vacation for two weeks.
[SPEAKER_18]: Like, bye y'all, I'm going to Alabama.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, so my week has been kind of okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: I just hung out, did stuff, went to school, spent a lot of time at school, did homework.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I still have no air conditioning, but that's coming up in the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's really... By the way, as a reminder, Orange Launch Radio is based in the Sacramento Valley, where we get temperatures of 110 degrees in the summertime.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, and if you don't have AC, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_18]: And if you don't have AC in your car, it sucks even more.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I could have just escaped to my car.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dan's like, summer's almost over.
[SPEAKER_18]: We don't have to get AC for your car now.
[SPEAKER_04]: As my mother said, you use the old 2 and 70 trick.
[SPEAKER_04]: You roll down two windows and drive 70 miles an hour.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_18]: That would work if one of my windows would roll down.
[SPEAKER_20]: Use in the ghetto.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dude, no, it's not, I don't know what it is, but after my car got raped, it hasn't been the same.
[SPEAKER_18]: Your car got raped?
[SPEAKER_18]: My car got raped, remember?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did it have a burning vagina afterwards?
[SPEAKER_18]: It got raped in the side.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Remember when they broke it in half?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, it got raped in the ear?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_18]: I guess they didn't think my car, you know, well they did get, they did, you know, get in the rear end too, you know, my truck.
[SPEAKER_04]: The trunk was all empty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your car got it in the rear end.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dude, my car was all fucked up.
[SPEAKER_18]: At least it has the back window now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, I'm laughing at the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I'm playing mommy in the chatroom because there was this stupid fucker in there earlier who was being an asshole to everybody.
[SPEAKER_18]: So now he doesn't get to play with us anymore.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that made me feel good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I feel good when I do my job.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when you were young, did you used to ban children from the playground?
[SPEAKER_18]: No, I just beat them with sticks.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: and played tetherball with them and then aimed the tetherball at them.
[SPEAKER_18]: I play well with others when they're the target.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Angel, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_19]: You better have a mic nearby because you may laugh at this.
[SPEAKER_19]: I found out... I mean, what?
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, I found out that there is a haunted house by my old house that I used to live at that I just moved away from.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is this the fort?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, it's not the fort.
[SPEAKER_19]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: I was going to blame it on Loki's little portal from hell, but I can't because it's not even built yet.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then, after I found out about the house, I found out that two days ago it miraculously burned down...
[SPEAKER_19]: without affecting any of the vegetation around it or the oak tree that was right next to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see burning as a running theme on tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_19]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let the joke die.
[SPEAKER_04]: Step away from the joke.
[SPEAKER_19]: Speaking of joke, should I reveal it now or later?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we need to do Loki's present now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's embarrass him now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to have the mic in my hand and I'm just going to talk the whole time.
[SPEAKER_06]: But my birthday's not until next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're getting your birthday present now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like it when I get presents early because it makes my birthday last longer.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki's going to open the gift.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need some good gift opening music here if I can find something.
[SPEAKER_19]: And you have to promise that I get to take a picture of it afterwards.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_19]: and I will give the picture up to OrangeDanceRadio.com to post it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because there's no lid.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's opening the gift.
[SPEAKER_19]: He is opening the gift.
[SPEAKER_19]: And mind you, this is a joke upon all jokes.
[SPEAKER_19]: I thought it was really cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hopefully he likes it.
[SPEAKER_19]: It must go on the webcam.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my.
[SPEAKER_19]: Other side.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little baby...
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_19]: But what is the baby holding?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did it drop something?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it dropped something.
[SPEAKER_19]: Besides the card.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a little help with the artwork, but... For those listening at home, Loki has been given an Iraqi suicide baby for his birthday.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those who have been listening about 50 episodes ago, you'll get that inside joke.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a bad inside joke.
[SPEAKER_19]: I admit it's a bad inside joke.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's one that, you know, we've burnt to the ground, but hey, I said burnt at Gatsby.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, anyway.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, I thought it was cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: I hope he likes it.
[SPEAKER_19]: It needs to go on the webcam, though, because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, he broke the webcam.
[SPEAKER_11]: Five seconds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Angel, is there anything else you wanted to talk about with your week and your day?
[SPEAKER_19]: Not that I can think of at the moment.
[SPEAKER_19]: I will probably give the mic later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then let's speak to Mr. Floatwalk.
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_26]: The week?
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, anyone who knows what I do, it's just been non-stop work for this whole week with so many things getting ready to ship out for this Christmas season.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard a rumor you work for some game company.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, who'd have thunk it?
[SPEAKER_26]: Let's see, but the cool thing about that, I managed to steal myself some good swag during the week, got some Silent Hill 4 posters.
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't start borrowing without returning.
[SPEAKER_26]: Nah, it was given.
[SPEAKER_26]: I asked and I took.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's a cool thing to go into their boiler room and see all the promo stuff from every game that's ever been made, and posters, boxes, all that.
[SPEAKER_26]: Pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_26]: And I saw about 500 Extreme V-Rares.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I visit Konami and borrow things?
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, you do know me, you know.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, my name does have a lot of clout out there.
[SPEAKER_26]: Just don't turn to a name dropper, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I won't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not like a particular pool ball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, sorry, sorry.
[SPEAKER_26]: But yeah, the other stuff in the week.
[SPEAKER_26]: I actually went to a concert on Friday night.
[SPEAKER_26]: Went to go see Kanye West and Usher in concert.
[SPEAKER_26]: And that was...
[SPEAKER_26]: It was a pretty happening event, but I must say, it was pretty entertaining just to see the crowd.
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of crowd did they have at an Usher concert?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm curious.
[SPEAKER_26]: Everything you expect.
[SPEAKER_26]: Every girl from like 12 to 35, you know, just chicks everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did Usher take his shirt off at some point during the concert?
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, you could tell.
[SPEAKER_26]: You didn't even have to see the stage.
[SPEAKER_26]: You just heard like the loudest screaming you've ever heard.
[SPEAKER_26]: Imagine like...
[SPEAKER_26]: 20,000 Banshees going wild.
[SPEAKER_26]: That was just real.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, it's funny to see just how girls react over just one guy on stage.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, one of the funniest stories about that, I mean, I have like so many stories about that concert alone, but probably the funniest one was, there's one part, like in the middle of the show, where he's doing a ballad.
[SPEAKER_26]: So normally what any singer does, he grabs some lucky woman off the stage and
[SPEAKER_26]: He's going to serenade her.
[SPEAKER_26]: So he looks around and he points out this one gal in the crowd.
[SPEAKER_26]: And when you see this gal, like the spotlight's going on her, she's like totally freaking out.
[SPEAKER_26]: She's, you know, you just look at her face because they put the, you know, camera on the projection screen.
[SPEAKER_26]: And I can say from the time she got picked to the time she got off stage, you did not see her smile once.
[SPEAKER_26]: She was too busy, totally like freaking out, making the sad face like, like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe her vagina was, never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_26]: Seriously, but it's funny because now you see Usher get up on stage and he's like walking slowly, taking his time.
[SPEAKER_26]: He gets up there, you know, he's got like a bouquet of flowers for her.
[SPEAKER_26]: And you can like, when the camera zooms in on her, you can see her face, she's like mouthing I love you to her, you know, to him, which is pretty standard.
[SPEAKER_26]: Any fan would do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know I would.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, and then so finally, like just somewhere around the part where, you know, he's talking about, you know, I'll get down with you and all that kind of stuff, where he's singing that.
[SPEAKER_26]: I swear to God, I'll put $20 on this.
[SPEAKER_26]: You can ask Mike, you can ask Little B who saw this.
[SPEAKER_26]: I swear she mouthed the words, I'll let you fuck me.
[SPEAKER_26]: I was just like, damn.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, there's just some whores in this world, I guess.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, I know if it's an Usher concert and a girl says it to a guy, he's flattered.
[SPEAKER_26]: I know if Beyonce pulled me on stage and I pulled that, I'd be out in cuffs in like three seconds.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, I just found that kind of curious.
[SPEAKER_26]: But overall, it was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_26]: And then, um...
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, today it's just been coming up from the bay up to Sacto and hanging out with you guys.
[SPEAKER_26]: And the fun's only just begun.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We always appreciate it when you come and hang out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's always a good excuse to go have Mongolian barbecue as well.
[SPEAKER_26]: Always.
[SPEAKER_26]: And before I pass the mic, I just want to say what's up to the chat room, especially up to Sigurd and Kyle.
[SPEAKER_26]: Word.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got mad loves for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: And even though my new office mate is still psycho, I still hold a little place in my heart for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I still have a Silent Hill 4 poster if you come back.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I gotta bribe you, I'll bribe you, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's your tip jar doing?
[SPEAKER_26]: We are over $30.
[SPEAKER_26]: Where the hell is all this money coming from?
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, well, I explained it a little earlier in the DDR Freak Boards, but the short of it was essentially... Me and Sigurd, we used to have a bunch of stuff in our cube.
[SPEAKER_26]: Like, if you saw the first montage we ever did, we had, like, red vines, we had, like, granola bars and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_26]: And so our boss came in... The clue?
[SPEAKER_14]: Clue?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: Clues, quote.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I wanted to ask you real fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you want to issue, like, a formal apology to the users of DDR Freak Boards?
[SPEAKER_04]: for what you did.
[SPEAKER_26]: I will say this.
[SPEAKER_26]: You guys totally assumed it was a clue.
[SPEAKER_26]: I only said, which of these would you like to have right about now?
[SPEAKER_26]: I didn't mean to lead you on.
[SPEAKER_26]: You led yourselves.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's your own damn fault.
[SPEAKER_26]: I was going to tell you not to apologize, but... Yeah, that's their own damn fault.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tried to say about the inkblot thing, but nobody listens to Scott.
[SPEAKER_26]: I know, man.
[SPEAKER_26]: You're the third eye of, you know, DDR Freak up in this piece.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_26]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh gosh, where was I at?
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, so the story was we had a bunch of stuff and then our boss came in one day on a Friday afternoon and saw that we had a bunch of granola bars.
[SPEAKER_26]: And so he just kind of walked up to us, not saying a word, grabbed about three granola bars, dropped a dollar on the table and just walked off.
[SPEAKER_26]: We were like, what the hell did he just do?
[SPEAKER_26]: We were just thinking for the rest of the day, wow, that was kind of freaky.
[SPEAKER_26]: And he comes back to us later and tells us, well, he was doing interviews all day for people coming to Konami, and he just didn't have time to go on a lunch break, and so he figured, well, hey, the testers have food.
[SPEAKER_26]: So he just grabbed some from us and dropped the dollar as just payment for, well, I don't want to feel like I'm mooching.
[SPEAKER_26]: And then just people started picking up on it, and then what started out as like $1.82 came into...
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I single-handedly put $2.50 in that jar.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yes, you did, and Sharkskull put in her tip as well, and she don't even work there, so just the fact that people are... What exactly is she tipping?
[SPEAKER_04]: Never mind, never mind.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's not a burning you-know-what.
[SPEAKER_26]: No comment.
[SPEAKER_26]: But yeah, that is a week in the life of moi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sharks, girl.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, long time no see.
[SPEAKER_16]: Since like, what, a couple weeks ago on the great mini-golfing expedition?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that was beautiful.
[SPEAKER_04]: The night we weren't allowed to go to the Konami dinner, we were excommunicated from the dinner, so we had to go miniature golfing at Miggle.
[SPEAKER_16]: Although I have to say, Mel and I went miniature golfing in Santa Cruz last week, and I beat him by one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_16]: Pretty freaking proud of myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I would like to remind you that I did school you at Miggle.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, yeah, yeah, whatever, bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was just letting you win.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, she let me win.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you guys hear that?
[SPEAKER_04]: She let me win.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, them's fighting words, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so what else did you do this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything exciting?
[SPEAKER_16]: I worked, which is more so suited for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: And then I woke up yesterday thinking, I'm going to have a wonderful Saturday, and realized I could not turn my head to the right or the left.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, my neck's been kind of sucked sore, and it still hurts.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's why I let Mel drive up here.
[SPEAKER_16]: And, yeah, I've just been kind of like, hmm, yay, pain.
[SPEAKER_16]: Back medicines are your friend, although they make me sleep.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, I've just been kind of really out of it, even for me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hmm, cry.
[SPEAKER_16]: So...
[SPEAKER_16]: I'll go back to work and I'll have an excuse for being a bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any shoutouts or anything you want to plug while you're here?
[SPEAKER_16]: I am now addicted to Mario vs. Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a game I could not get into for some reason.
[SPEAKER_16]: I just played it for five minutes.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm like, I must buy this game.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know why, it just didn't... Mario vs. Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, she's handing me the Game Boy again.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, except Mel just dropped it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Angel comes prepared.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you want to share?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, I'm boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you're not.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm boring.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, I have to pull the joke now.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I didn't have this show, I would be like the most boring man in the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Angel.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was going to say, okay, I must pull the joke now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Do you realize you have all three Mels on the couch?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's a good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But people don't know your real name.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just gave it away, Angel.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, hey, hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's only the first three letters.
[SPEAKER_19]: They can guess the rest.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, nobody started guessing.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, I'm Mel.
[SPEAKER_26]: No.
[SPEAKER_26]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, he's Float Walk, remember?
[SPEAKER_04]: Float Walk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, see?
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_06]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_06]: My day would have been better if my shit didn't crap out on me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shit crap out on you?
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate it when my shit craps.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm talking very vague.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm talking about the little board that I had for my cabinet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not necessarily a main one because, you know, I didn't play with that today.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got my smaller one that I was using for main before, but it's now being used for everything else.
[SPEAKER_06]: Crapped out, and I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_06]: Might have something to do with my shitty soldering job to fix it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that might have something to do with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I have to get a new one.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at least it'll be nice and brand new.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we did get to play a little bit of DDR today.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had it set up so we could play and it was pretty.
[SPEAKER_06]: And my pads worked really well, but they're loud still, so that sucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then yesterday we went to play QZAR and that rocked because, of course, I kicked ass anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: I kicked ass without even effort.
[SPEAKER_06]: Without effort.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was actually spinning around on my ass in the middle of the arena shooting people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Behind my back, all that kind of cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I rock.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, and then I tried playing DDR on doubles and stuff at the arcade, and I realized I have no more endurance anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just gone.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah, I felt like I was going to die.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, yeah, my feet hurt a lot from all the walking from playing QZR.
[SPEAKER_06]: That kind of sucked, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: And since...
[SPEAKER_06]: The girlfriend and sister aren't here.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing that I thought was haunted is not haunted.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wasted my money.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm an idiot.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all we need to know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that sucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: For those who were listening Wednesday, I bought a haunted doll off the internet, supposedly.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, whatever, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that sucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I hate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woo, food!
[SPEAKER_06]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_06]: No food.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a new guest.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, but anyways, yeah, so that was that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, uh, for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, um, oh, and I made a CD, my CD, for my remixes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, um, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty much all that I did this week, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and a lot of Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Loki will be giving away copies of his CD to some of our in-studio guests tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Won't that be exciting?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: Who else wants to play How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day?
[SPEAKER_04]: Jonas, hello, thank you for joining us.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey, what up, y'all?
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_27]: Ups and downs.
[SPEAKER_27]: The ups was the tournament being okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Give us the candy a good time.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, I completely forgot about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Back to School Bash Back to School Bash
[SPEAKER_04]: Mel wanted to share something about the tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, float.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm just saying, if it was a back-to-school tournament, why weren't they giving away some cool prizes like some Trapper Keepers?
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_20]: DDR Trapper Keepers!
[SPEAKER_16]: If it was a back-to-school tournament, why were they holding it on a school night?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Trapper Keeper is bad news.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, we saw South Park.
[SPEAKER_06]: We know what can happen with Trapper Keepers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they could give away Butterfly Binders.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kill me.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I was actually surprised at the turnout for a Tuesday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really was.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a bunch of people I didn't know, and it was interesting.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, new faces I didn't even know as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So was the money raised from this thing to go towards making their marquee look non-ghetto?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because their marquee is pretty crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: It looked like, you know, I'm gonna glue stuff to a piece of wood, and it'll be our marquee.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, they're using the money to actually build the actual Scandia place, like the paths to be better, the speakers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe they can not spend it on more skee-ball machines.
[SPEAKER_06]: My god, they have like eight skee-ball machines in there in the shooting gallery.
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe they can use it to dismantle the damn shooting gallery.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shooting galleries are fun to annoy people.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dude, the shooting galleries suck.
[SPEAKER_18]: My whole reason for going to Scandia had DVD drive failure.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're sending it to Reno.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's gone.
[SPEAKER_18]: Damn it!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so we had the little tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: I dropped in for about 45 minutes, and I was pissed off because they weren't doing freestyle, and I was going to do an exhibition freestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dr. Dick was going to come out and do Sexy Planet, but I got denied.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I had my hoes and everything, and I had my uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh part all figured out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Denied.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stupid Scandia.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am a total dance attention whore when it comes to freestyle tournaments.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait for Spiggle 3, that's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_27]: They actually gave me some news towards how they're going to do tournaments and stuff for Scandia.
[SPEAKER_27]: They're thinking about doing it every month.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, I know, exactly.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ding, ding, ding, oversaturation's calling.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, anything else interesting happening this week?
[SPEAKER_27]: I got another contact from someone who has organized Madden tournaments and various other video game tournaments.
[SPEAKER_27]: They're thinking about getting to the DDR scene as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, DDR and Madden are so much alike.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm teasing, but that's cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: There's a tournament of Madden and Tuesday and Steve Space Pizza in the marketplace.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's been kind of an over, I mean, I'm sorry, there's been a lack, actually, of really big tournaments lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the past few months, big tournaments, there haven't been a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I kind of fear that this December is looking to be almost a little oversaturated.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard of a lot of different things going on, so just be careful, check out the calendar.
[SPEAKER_04]: We all know everybody has an eye on DDR Freaks Tournament Forum, so just check them out.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, then you've got SVGL3, you've got B3 Part 2, I'm not sure when the hell that's going to turn out.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, okay, or FU2 next year.
[SPEAKER_27]: FU2!
[SPEAKER_27]: FU2, buddy!
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: The Sacktown Smackdown, that's the subtitle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Jesus.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, anything else you wanted to share about your weekday day?
[SPEAKER_27]: Except someone threw a damn beer bottle at my head.
[SPEAKER_27]: For what?
[SPEAKER_27]: I was like, whoo!
[SPEAKER_04]: What'd you do?
[SPEAKER_27]: No, I didn't say anything.
[SPEAKER_27]: They thought I flicked them off.
[SPEAKER_27]: I was like, hello.
[SPEAKER_27]: You were waving at somebody?
[SPEAKER_27]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_04]: And they threw a beer bottle at you?
[SPEAKER_14]: I was like, oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: My god, people can be rude.
[SPEAKER_16]: Wait a second, he was driving and someone threw a beer bottle at him.
[SPEAKER_16]: What's wrong with this picture?
[SPEAKER_27]: I was like, woohoo!
[SPEAKER_27]: But then, oh shit!
[SPEAKER_04]: You lead a very interesting life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Explosive, that's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, somewhat, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: My Week and My Day
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, I had a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I actually played a game of DDR, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played a game of Extreme, and this was my set on DDR Extreme, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: I played I Believe in Miracles and Make It Better from DDR First Mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I played another second mix song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I played Let's Get Down or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I made it an all second mix and first mix night.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I miss my old DDR mixes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: Also tonight, I don't know if you caught a glimpse of me on the webcam earlier, but I'm dressed in all black because I'm going out to a goth club after the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That should be fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: You goth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you know I'm so gothic.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's so wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is pretty much what it's going to sound like at the goth club.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: The lights.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm so tragic.
[SPEAKER_13]: I need another clove of cigarettes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just hoping that somebody I know is listening to that so he'll kick my ass when, you know, I go out later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_18]: I didn't... I... Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know where I'm from.
[SPEAKER_18]: And you know that damn near everybody I hung out with was like uber goth.
[SPEAKER_29]: Right.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I never imagined that there would be like a club.
[SPEAKER_18]: What do you do?
[SPEAKER_18]: Go around and just be depressed?
[SPEAKER_18]: And wave your hands around like you're trying to bat the ghosts away from you?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm so gothic that when the night comes, so do I.
[SPEAKER_06]: They fucking play industrial synth-pop, that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really good stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually like the music at that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went once, and then I got... I was with one of my friends who's in this goth stuff, and this one guy wanted to take me home and have sex, and he was dressed up in some sort of...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, it was just wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: And again, I don't know how many times I've had to apologize for that, Loki.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sorry to do that to you, but... I just don't... If your life is so tragic, why would you dance about it?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: In reality, it's actually a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I didn't enjoy it, I wouldn't pay a whole $4 to get in the door.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I'm looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I actually haven't been in like two years.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's a lot of fun people to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all about the people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on...
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to give you a little bit of help.
[SPEAKER_04]: and Floatwalk has gotten a clue relayed to him from Dancer X, the mysterious Dancer X, but Floatwalk talks to him, so you're special.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so we've gotten some things here, so maybe just these first two bits here we'll give away for right now.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, well, it's pretty obvious so far no one has answered the question correct yet, although I will say I have seen some very close...
[SPEAKER_26]: answers on there.
[SPEAKER_26]: And as I mentioned before, a lot of people are trying to, I guess, sort of think that the song is three steps away from what you literally see.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, it's actually right there.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's a little more literal than you think.
[SPEAKER_26]: But also, if you read Dancer X's post, he said in there that it is a new song.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's something that has never been on DDR before.
[SPEAKER_26]: So that should narrow down some of the ideas that you had.
[SPEAKER_26]: and, uh, hmm, do you think we should go ahead and give them the new clue yet?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, let's wait a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see if that new song thing helps them out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's a brand new song, and you guys, it was actually, in his original post, it was, like, the subject line, and you guys completely missed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But hey, you know, what can you do?
[SPEAKER_04]: We can only hold your hand so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, uh, if you have some guesses, uh, we'll be fielding guesses over private message a little later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't just shout it out in the chat room, because we're not paying attention.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, actually, we are paying attention, but we don't want to miss it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's why we like to field the guesses over private message.
[SPEAKER_04]: So after the break, we'll take some more guesses.
[SPEAKER_26]: And I'll even put it like this.
[SPEAKER_26]: If someone can guess it just from the clues that I've given you, if you somehow pull it out.
[SPEAKER_26]: I will guarantee you some cool Konami swag.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, swag!
[SPEAKER_26]: Speaking of swag.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can I guess?
[SPEAKER_26]: We have a huge announcement on swag coming up for Orange Lounge later.
[SPEAKER_26]: You will not want to miss this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Floatwalk's going to talk to us about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is very exciting news for Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Floatwalk's going to tell us all about it right after the break.
[SPEAKER_04]: And on this break, we're going to have three songs that all have a central theme.
[SPEAKER_04]: You try and figure out what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back.
I'm gonna show you how to burn
and many more.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
I'm burning up for you
[SPEAKER_30]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio, because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are back, Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 110.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we told you before the break that the clue has something to do with a new song, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's your chance to give it another guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you get it right, you get to be the one to announce it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh la la.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you could even do that over the Skype line if you have access to that, our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just go to www.orangeontrader.com, click on interact with us, and get the information about the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're looking for your guesses.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, before we went to the break...
[SPEAKER_04]: Floatwalk and I were teasing a little something that's coming up for Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Floatwalk, why don't you tell us a little more about what's going on?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought we had a third mic somewhere we can get for Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_26]: So what were we just talking about?
[SPEAKER_04]: The giveaway that's coming up.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well...
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, as I've seen in Orange Lounge, I know there are a couple people that we hold in high regard in this realm of Bimani and such.
[SPEAKER_04]: People who we'd like to sleep with is this list we have.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_26]: And atop that list, which I think holds true for quite a bunch of people, you know, figuratively and conceptually, or reality, we do have someone who has decided to donate us some swag, autographed swag no less,
[SPEAKER_26]: and that person would be... Drumroll anyone?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, we got clap on the clapper.
[SPEAKER_26]: But that'll do.
[SPEAKER_26]: And that person is... Akira Yamaoka.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, indeed.
[SPEAKER_26]: DDR Spot did the interview with Akira Yamaoka a couple of weeks ago when we posted it on DDR Spot.
[SPEAKER_26]: He mentioned somewhere in the email that he would be willing to give out some swag to our listeners and to our readers at DDR Spot, and given the business relations between DDR Spot and Orange Lounge, I figured why not share the wealth with everybody, so...
[SPEAKER_26]: We do have a handful of CDs to give away.
[SPEAKER_26]: How we will do that, we are still determining right now, but you will have to listen to not just Orange Lounge Radio on Sunday nights, but I think there's a little more attention you'll have to be paying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we're cooking up a scheme right now on how we're going to give away the CDs, but we are very excited to be working with DDR Spot on this exciting giveaway.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know a lot of people out there want those CDs, so we're going to make it tough.
[SPEAKER_04]: More staff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who'd be sucker enough to help you guys out?
[SPEAKER_26]: People who like something different.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'll say this as far as DDR Spot, one thing I do like to pump up about us is the fact that any kind of Konami news that breaks from the US side of things, no one's going to beat us to the punch.
[SPEAKER_26]: Half the people who are on Spotstaff work there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that difficult, having to have a DDR fan site, yet at the same time you work for Konami?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you wanted to blow the lid on the whole Ultramix 2 song list, the Extreme Unlocks and all that stuff, you could do it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh yeah, we absolutely could.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you could get sued, but you could do it.
[SPEAKER_26]: We could do it, but at the same time, there's movies that you geek up over.
[SPEAKER_26]: You don't want someone to tell you how it ends, word for word, verbatim.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: The boat sank and Darth is Luke's father.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, essentially.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, just working for a while, it's like... And Jesus does die.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the end, they hang Jesus.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, I mean, I think the best way of putting it... Wow, Jesus dies and laughter ensued.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry for the spoiler, guy, but Jesus does die at the end of that recent DVD release.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: But the thing about, I guess, working there, like, the first day, obviously, you're surprised just as anybody to find out, you know, this news.
[SPEAKER_26]: But then, once you start playing something for 40 hours a week, the novelty dies out after the 15th hour.
[SPEAKER_26]: But I think we've gotten to the point where it's something, I mean, it's something we've all done before.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's pretty standard nature to understand the nature of the beast, how people are on boards.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, obviously they're going to pester you for a clue here or there, but now that I work closer with the product managers and all the PR people,
[SPEAKER_26]: I kind of know where my limits are and once those are drawn out, it's easy to hold on to those, stay within those boundaries.
[SPEAKER_04]: So speaking of limits, any other hints about things we could look forward to?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying guys, I'm trying to get something out of them.
[SPEAKER_26]: I will say for Ultramix 2, SP7 will be ready when Ultramix 2 ships.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, we already know what it is and there's new stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, good.
[SPEAKER_26]: So you're not just getting run-of-the-mill things.
[SPEAKER_26]: The Xbox Live is going to be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's going to be more robust this time.
[SPEAKER_26]: You've probably heard, obviously, you can trade edits online.
[SPEAKER_26]: You can download step data.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have they made an official announcement?
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't have to say one way or the other, but have they made an official announcement about being able to play those edits?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know there was a little bit of confusion about being able to play edits.
[SPEAKER_26]: To, like, challenge someone online with the edits?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, with playing edits.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: Quite honestly, I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, there's so many things that go into, you know, like... Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_26]: It just slips me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's cool, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want you to say anything that's going to get you in trouble, so don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_26]: What else are things to expect?
[SPEAKER_26]: A lot of people geeked up over DDR Extreme having a VRare.
[SPEAKER_26]: I will say there is a high chance, not 100% sure, but there's a high chance we'll have a VRare number 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh!
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: You heard that here first.
[SPEAKER_04]: A VRare number 4?
[SPEAKER_26]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_04]: How would that
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I see where this might be going.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll leave it to our listeners to figure that one out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_26]: But other than that, I mean, Ultimix 2 is looking snazzy right now.
[SPEAKER_26]: We're almost ready to send it off to Microsoft and just let them give us the good word.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I don't know if you can repeat any of this, but you were telling me some funny stories about working with Microsoft earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if that's something you've got to keep on the down-low or...
[SPEAKER_26]: No, actually, it's kind of fascinating.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, anyone who works in video games and does stuff with, like, Microsoft or Sony, there's actually standards you have to follow.
[SPEAKER_26]: Like, funny thing is, things on the PlayStation controller, for example, you know those little analog sticks you have on the sides, you know, in the front of the controller?
[SPEAKER_26]: They actually, like, anytime they're referred to in a game, they actually have to be called right analog stick or left analog stick.
[SPEAKER_26]: You can't call them anything else.
[SPEAKER_26]: Or you could call them L3, R3.
[SPEAKER_26]: But if you say, like, yeah, in the instruction book, use the thumb stick, you would actually get zinged for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what exactly is a zing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Does that mean they come out and kick your ass or fine you?
[SPEAKER_26]: They'll say, we're not going to ship your game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_26]: There are some things they'll let slide, but there are some things they're pretty strict about.
[SPEAKER_26]: And, like, just how you name your stuff is actually a big deal.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, not a big deal, but a semi.
[SPEAKER_26]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, I mean, it's... When you work in QA and video games, there are things you have to test, like, you have to make sure your game can run 72 hours without crashing, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_26]: There are things you have to do, like, you have to pull the controller... Driver 3 passed that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, how did Driver 3 get through QA?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, you didn't go through Konami, that's for damn sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's for damn sure.
[SPEAKER_26]: But yeah, it's an interesting beast, just, I mean, a lot of people think when you're in QA you have to play games, you know, you just play it ad nauseum, but...
[SPEAKER_26]: You really, you know, you're supposed to sit there and you're supposed to break what you can.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, so anyone who's trying to get into the game industry, that's... You gotta learn how to break games, not how to play and break them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, that's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Loki's very good at breaking games, I must say.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I broke Ultramix last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, I was telling you this earlier, I actually broke Ultramix, so... Something got through the cracks somehow, I don't know, but... Well, Ultramix was a half-rush job, but I mean...
[SPEAKER_26]: Like any other game in the series, the first will always have flaws, which is why you come out with the sequel to correct.
[SPEAKER_04]: It honestly wasn't a big deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I found it more amusing than anything else.
[SPEAKER_04]: It didn't piss me off or anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Besides, flaws in Microsoft products is nothing new.
[SPEAKER_04]: Service Pack 2, anybody?
[SPEAKER_26]: What else?
[SPEAKER_26]: Most people know that a lot of the step data for new songs has been done by
[SPEAKER_26]: Konami QA, I think people who, there's, you know, usually two people, people who like fun songs and people who like challenging songs, I think they're going to get a good variety of both.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm very excited about Ultramix too.
[SPEAKER_04]: But something we haven't talked a whole lot about, DDR Extreme, it's just about out, it's almost there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta say, because we were talking about this last week, we were kind of like talking about the whole GameStop leaking the song list, some of the song list unlocks early and stuff, we were like, boy, Konami must be really pissed off at what happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was there a little bit of frustration from the clue givers and things like that about the GameStop article?
[SPEAKER_26]: Kind of, sort of, yeah, actually.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, you know, I was talking to Jason... I'm sorry, not GameStop, GamePro, my bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, Jason Needles was actually kind of, I wouldn't say mad, but he was definitely surprised that they would just blow out a whole bunch of screen caps that more or less gave away a lot of the secrets.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't think necessarily it was intentional, it was just kind of like somebody just wasn't thinking, they were just grabbing screenshots and not thinking about, oh, maybe somebody's trying to keep the unlocked stuff a secret.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, well, I mean, I actually saw, like, what a press kit, you know, there's essentially different types of versions you get of a game, like, for example, they got what's called a media version, kind of like when a
[SPEAKER_26]: I don't know anything about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I would think stuff like You're Not Here and Maximizer and stuff, you guys were probably trying to keep under the lid a little bit, and then it just kind of got blown out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, You're Not Here was a little bit spoiled by the Dancing Stage Fever fusion song list, so it was kind of like, you know, there's a good chance that people were kind of thinking, okay, yeah, that probably would be an unlock, but Maximizer, that was
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though you can go back to the whole reading the master song list thing and Maximizer had turned up there before, this is really the concrete confirmation people were looking for.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yes, it's on there.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's basically, to put it, it's America's own version of Max.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know whether to be excited or scared.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_26]: I actually, I mean, a lot of people look at that and they say, oh, it's an 8-footer.
[SPEAKER_26]: Gosh, you know, that's like a big letdown.
[SPEAKER_26]: But I...
[SPEAKER_26]: There was a guy who, you know, Pac-1 Kenobi, who's pretty well known in the DDR community, you know, on DDR Freak, and he was not able to full combo that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to say, I am actually glad it's not a 10-footer, because honestly, I can't play 10-footers at home.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I can barely play them in the arcade as it is, but home versions aren't meant to be 10-footers.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you're playing on those freaking ignition pads, you know?
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_26]: But I will say, Maximizer really sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_26]: I think
[SPEAKER_26]: Gaba, Gaba, Gaba, Gaba, Gaba
[SPEAKER_04]: LankyStyles here with Rice Princess
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I just want to know, Mel B, how do you stay so sexy?
[SPEAKER_26]: I'd say I do about 50 push-ups a day and one pack of pork rinds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess I'll open up the Skype line in a little bit for those folks that may have a question or something about Ultramix 2 or DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_04]: I swear I will hang up on you if it's something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll go to Skype line and see if anybody has anything they want to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I just missed that call.
[SPEAKER_04]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see if anybody calls back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Over on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: We cannot hear you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you turn up your microphone volume or something?
[SPEAKER_25]: Is this better?
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_25]: Is this better now?
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, I missed all the Ultramix 2 thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: Can you fill me in?
[SPEAKER_04]: You missed everything on Ultramix 2?
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, I only managed to pick up the other half, but I got cut.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shame on you for being tardy to the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shame on you.
[SPEAKER_25]: I had to clean up my room.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could clean your room while listening to the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't buy that excuse.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's going to be on a disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ultramix 2, Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Xbox Live portion is going to be bigger.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a clue still involving the bagel out there, and it's for a new song.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Ultramix 2 is going to have a variety of different kinds of music.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Folks that are into DDR are doing the steps.
[SPEAKER_04]: We know that much.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's going to be a mix of challenging versus fun.
[SPEAKER_25]: Who are these people that are actually doing... Are these people well-known?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we give any more information about the people doing the steps?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess not, really.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we give names?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think we can give names.
[SPEAKER_26]: I can't necessarily name, drop, I mean, I'm sure I could, it wouldn't make a hell of a difference, but that said, the people who are in QA are actually... Wait, we can't hear you, Zach, let Mel finish.
[SPEAKER_26]: They are accomplished DDR players, there are people who have won tournaments, there are people who, you know, not only PA'd, there are people who freestyle, so...
[SPEAKER_26]: They take into account, like, you know, for basic steps, for example, you often want steps that are, you know, pretty easy and, like, freestylable, so we take that into account.
[SPEAKER_26]: We take into account that, you know, for maniac steps, there are people who are total difficulty whores, and, you know, we do stuff that is ergonomically, you know, doable.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, we're not going to do something that's, like, we strive for 11 feet, you know, because...
[SPEAKER_26]: There are such things you need to have as game balancing and such.
[SPEAKER_26]: Like I said, we're trying to find moderation, you know, balance.
[SPEAKER_04]: In other words, Zaku, just go pre-order it tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Word.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, one more thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: Have you only focused on one half of the country, or is it all over for these players?
[SPEAKER_04]: Certain players, is it only one part of the country?
[SPEAKER_04]: In other words, are all these players coming from NorCal?
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, let's put it like this.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's based in Redwood City, so it's not like we just sat out there and we had this big audition.
[SPEAKER_26]: Anyone could apply to Konami, but they had to go through the whole interview process.
[SPEAKER_26]: They had to go through people like me who have worked there for a year, and I have to gauge their acumen on how well they play the game, what they think makes the game well.
[SPEAKER_26]: Most of us are based in Northern California, but there are some people who have been imported.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imported from different places, that's all we can tell you, bud.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anything new about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything that we know about the song list is already up on the site.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't have any new info tonight, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: We may have one more song before the night's over.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's up to you guys.
[SPEAKER_25]: Are the song packs going to be better?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are the song packs going to be better?
[SPEAKER_26]: That's an opinion.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, like I mentioned about SP7, there is new stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll answer it, yes.
[SPEAKER_25]: Wait, the new song pack for Ultramix is coming out already?
[SPEAKER_04]: Service Pack 7 will be out the day that Ultramix 2 is out.
[SPEAKER_25]: Do we have the names of the songs yet?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not yet, bud.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll have them soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, thanks for your questions.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was engaging and fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see if anybody else wants to call in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Questions about Ultramix 2 or DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the meantime, let's go over some of these clues.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got some people that guessed some of the songs that were in the game, and now we're going to let you know if anybody was right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had Sigurd put in a guess, but unfortunately he's not allowed to participate because he was right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Woo-hoo!
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will say Sigurd was right on his guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good for him.
[SPEAKER_26]: He better be right, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jazz said the sweetest thing by some band whose name I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking maybe U2.
[SPEAKER_26]: Now he's thinking too abstract.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a decent guess, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was decent.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, I liked it.
[SPEAKER_26]: I think that's the one thing I like about this whole thread thing, is you really get to see how people think.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's like, they'll come up with the strangest word associations, and they'll try to go three steps.
[SPEAKER_26]: Because of this and this and this, I think it's this song.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, it makes for great reading material and sure kills time at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: White Rob has a guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pam Baker and the Blue Plate Special with Bake in the Blues.
[SPEAKER_26]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says, the plate was blue and the bagel was baked.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't get more obvious than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But unfortunately, it's not it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: No dice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bummer.
[SPEAKER_04]: E.B.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sumaru says, John Desire with Hot Limit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe because the bagel's hot?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But... Nah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, bud.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so those are the guesses we got so far, so we'll just have to see if anything else comes in later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mel was talking about a V-Rare that is coming out for DDR Extreme, and that song list was leaked to the internet this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like some retailers are getting their copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a scan of the back cover and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's out there now, so we got to tell you what's on it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, damn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's another one of those things where they beat you to it, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, there's only so much you can do.
[SPEAKER_26]: We held up our end of the bargain, but we can't handle what the retailers do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the retailers leaked it.
[SPEAKER_26]: If people like the VRare list, then, you know, hey, all is good in the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: Track number one is Scorching Moon by Sean the Horny Master, which did not get censored.
[SPEAKER_04]: People thought it would be censored to just the master or... What's to censor?
[SPEAKER_26]: The dude plays horns.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, not anymore, you know.
[SPEAKER_26]: I still have a little sadness in my heart for the fact Shoti's no longer in Konami.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number 2, A by DJ Amuro is the second track on the CD.
[SPEAKER_04]: Track number 3 is Ecstasy by D-Complex.
[SPEAKER_04]: Track number 4 is Your Rain, the Rage Mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Akira Yamoka featuring Mary Elizabeth McGlynn, the track we premiered for you last month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wild Rush, Factor X, is track number five.
[SPEAKER_04]: Track number six is The Departed, Show T with A Stupid Barber.
[SPEAKER_04]: Track seven, Mobile Moga by our favorite, Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Track number eight, Jet World by Muchiko Izumi.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm white.
[SPEAKER_04]: And track nine, 321 Stars by DJ Simon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Track ten, V for Extreme by DJ Taka.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here are the bonus tracks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Eleven is I Need You, the Inside Door 3 mixes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never heard of that one before.
[SPEAKER_26]: Um, actually, that was, uh, yeah, Party Collection VRare also.
[SPEAKER_26]: No, actually, they're one of the VRares that came out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, it's like, it has all three mixes, like, all kind of used together.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_26]: No, it's just the Inside Door 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Supafova does that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Drop the Bomb, the original extended mix by Scotty D. Should be an interesting track.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Party Collection OST?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: 13 is Be For You, Glorious Style.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be the long version from DDR5th Mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys trying to hint at something there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Track 14 is So In Love, the train version by Caramel S and The Master.
[SPEAKER_04]: and track number 15 is I Need You, the true platinum mix by Show-T.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's the V-Rare.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: Actually, while it's still on my mind, one thing I'd like to point out also for anyone who's fans of Konami artists and, like, the B-Mani musicians, one of the games that's coming out this fall, Rumble Roses for PS2, the all-female wrestling game.
[SPEAKER_26]: You know, two of the best things ever made.
[SPEAKER_26]: Hot!
[SPEAKER_26]: A lot of the B-Money musicians did compose music for that, like DJ Taka did a track there.
[SPEAKER_26]: Sota Fujimori did stuff there.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, let's see, who else?
[SPEAKER_26]: The guy who did, freak, I can't remember his name, but the guy who did Jet World, he did something.
[SPEAKER_26]: Dez Rowe did a track on there.
[SPEAKER_26]: So yeah, I mean, it's actually funny enough, they were called at their commission somewhere at the last minute to do music for the game, and from what I've heard, it sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait to see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So definitely, if you're a Bomani music fan, you're going to have to pick up Rumble Roses.
[SPEAKER_04]: But of course, as soon as we can get our hands on a soundtrack, we'll play some tracks for you.
[SPEAKER_26]: How could I forget?
[SPEAKER_26]: Akira Yamaoka did tracks on there as well.
[SPEAKER_26]: Gosh.
[SPEAKER_26]: Thank you, Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: The other night, a bunch of us were at Lions, and it was like Dan's GameStop people.
[SPEAKER_18]: And they were there discussing on how they were looking forward to the...
[SPEAKER_18]: Realistic Physics Engine of Rumble Roses and the Invigorating Mud Effects.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was a funny conversation.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, talking about how they were going to admire the aesthetic qualities of Rumble Roses.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, we did talk about this a couple weeks ago, chat room, but I didn't know about the Desro thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's more artists in there than we originally thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: I knew Akira and I knew some of them, but I didn't know Desro.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's way more people than I thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any chance we might see some Rumble Roses songs on DDR, complete with some new characters?
[SPEAKER_04]: As I do my little bounce thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Question from Explicit, here in the house.
[SPEAKER_04]: How many polygons are in each breast in Rumble Roses?
[SPEAKER_04]: More than a handful.
[SPEAKER_04]: On that note, I think we'll go to a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: and to make up for Floatwalk's grotesque error earlier, we will be playing an entire block of Akira Yamaoka music.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, including some requests.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had some requests.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we will go to this.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want to do that other clue?
[SPEAKER_04]: Should we do the other clue, Floatwalk?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell, Floatwalk, let's give him another chance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Clue, colon, a unique aspect of a type of cells in the body.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, uh, those of you who took physiology in high school...
[SPEAKER_26]: Time to dust off your books and your brains and you just might find something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have fun, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back.
You touched my body once.
It burned.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: Amagi Novoleo Amagi Novoleo Amagi Novoleo
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We put your thing down, flip it, and reverse it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio Season 5 has just started, and in case you missed it, a unique aspect of a type of cells in the body.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's time to guess one more time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send it in over private message to Sky in the chat room if you have a guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, you can't participate tonight because you drove.
[SPEAKER_04]: So... You got a mic right next to you, hon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other side.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, normally I would have, like, one thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to be good today, but sort of not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because if I were going to be bad...
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd be breaking into the pizza and then having a few shots.
[SPEAKER_18]: But because I ate the whole thing of ice cream today.
[SPEAKER_18]: I wanted ice cream so bad all week.
[SPEAKER_18]: I wanted ice cream more than I wanted booze.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what I'm going to do... Imagine if they made ice cream booze.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_18]: I've actually sort of... I had this creme brulee liqueur that was really good.
[SPEAKER_18]: So I've decided how to cheat.
[SPEAKER_18]: I decided that tomorrow was going to be my cheat day.
[SPEAKER_18]: So when it hits midnight, I'm having some Guinness at home.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the spirit.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm going to finish off the Guinness in my fridge and have some Amaretto.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any special plans for Labor Day?
[SPEAKER_18]: Sleeping.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, no, I'm going to do my homework tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm going over to Julie's where there's air conditioning.
[SPEAKER_18]: Air conditioning, wow.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I'm going to do my laundry.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because see, look what I did not bring over tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Laundry.
[SPEAKER_18]: Was my laundry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Impressive.
[SPEAKER_18]: So I'm doing my laundry at Julie's tomorrow and making use of one of her five computers that she built.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_18]: No.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm actually working on right now building my own laptop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, actually, it's not really a laptop.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to be putting it inside of a case of a Dreamcast, and it's going to be a portable PC with its own LCD monitor, which will also double as a car PC with its own navigational and GPS system.
[SPEAKER_06]: and will be an on-road computer for our show.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, you know the Dreamcast uses Windows CE.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm actually gutting it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just using the case.
[SPEAKER_18]: Like the Nintendo PC?
[SPEAKER_06]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to use a Nano ITX motherboard, but they're not available yet, so I'm going to have to use a Micro ITX board.
[SPEAKER_18]: Why not build one out of a PS2?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, because... Because you can find plenty of broken PS2s.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Dreamcast is small.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to use an old PS1 because they sell for $30 on the internet.
[SPEAKER_18]: I could give you one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, a PS1, but the board's too big for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I had a Nano ITX one, it would fit perfect.
[SPEAKER_06]: But as it is, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just pricing it because it's kind of expensive.
[SPEAKER_18]: The Nintendo one was built out of laptop parts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's what I'm going to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Laptop, hard drive, LCD monitor.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm actually going to hack a portable PlayStation 1 LCD screen.
[SPEAKER_18]: They have a Dreamcast mobile monitor, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll have to check that, too.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think one of the ones on Lixang.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lixang, I'll have to check them.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyways, yeah, that's what I'm going to work on.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be kind of cool because I want to, like, I was actually, what I was setting up for was mini-MAME or, like, mini-Bomani stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, like, making a micro turntable Beatmania type setup for, like, that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the only problem is they're not very powerful PCs.
[SPEAKER_06]: They only go up to, like, 1 gigahertz.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because they're just, you know, they're mic, no fan or anything, but it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_18]: They make the, like, they have, like, tiny fans now and heat sinks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, that's the project I'm working on.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: So you've given up on communicating with the dead?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope, have not.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have my eight and a half pounds of magnet wire in my room.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I have my germanium on my desk.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I actually was looking at copper today, but they only have copper-plated circuit boards.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that might be good enough just to stick on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can...
[SPEAKER_18]: Order copper from the science ordering places.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I just need a copper plate, and it's small.
[SPEAKER_18]: Copper plate?
[SPEAKER_18]: I'll talk to you about that later.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think I know where to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, I'm just looking in the parts for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only thing is I figured out that the guy's design is physically impossible because if you were to make something that strong in that small of space, it would literally melt.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would just be gone.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: This dead would take it over and it'd open a portal to hell.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, it wouldn't do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only portal it'd open would be burning down the house.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I just don't... It couldn't...
[SPEAKER_18]: It couldn't maintain the structural integrity it needs to keep the portal to hell open, so it would just burn up from the flames of Hades.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyways, yeah, I'll do that later.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be hotter than a... I was pricing it today at Radio Shack, but I don't like Radio Shack because they're too expensive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to go back to drinking.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes, you learned quickly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, I'm in a sound effects mood today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, let's go see if we got any guesses.
[SPEAKER_04]: We actually only got one more guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like some people, they want more time with this clue.
[SPEAKER_04]: They want more time with the unique aspect of a type of cells in the body clue.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm wondering how it feels to want.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we will give another chance for guesses if there's still... Some people want to Google it, so they're Googling away.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we do have one guess.
[SPEAKER_18]: You should have paid attention in school.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chaos Dimension suggests a song, and I've never heard of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: You Got Beef by Chucky Akins and V-Unit.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mel's saying no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: Isn't it nice to want...
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't it nice to say something Jamie just said?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, I just sort of said that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rent!
[SPEAKER_18]: Pay it!
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seegard got it right on the second guess as well as the first guess, amazingly enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: He sent me another message and he got it right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was so amazed.
[SPEAKER_26]: If you got it right on the second guess, that's kind of like saying he battled himself in a race and he came in third place.
[SPEAKER_01]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_01]: Beautiful people.
[SPEAKER_18]: That means his ass came in last.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, as somebody says in the chat room, as I recall, you got beef is not a unique aspect of a type of self in the body.
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe, well, you know, if you... We got the beef self.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you call yourself maybe a beefy built guy, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where'd Loki go?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did he disappear into the bathroom?
[SPEAKER_15]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to talk to him.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just, like, pay attention in school.
[SPEAKER_15]: See, people don't like to be made to think.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a hard clue.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are hard clues.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is why it's taking you so long to get it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nobody likes to be made to think.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because nobody thinks anymore.
[SPEAKER_18]: Chatroom, prove me wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: See what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys know about the big day of November 18th coming up.
[SPEAKER_04]: 18 November, as some folks have been referring to it, where we get a whole shitload of new releases from Japan, including Poppin' Music 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there is a brand new website open for Poppin' Music 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it doesn't give us a whole lot about the game, but it does show us those cute little Kubricks that are coming with the limited edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: So cute!
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, I need to get that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I need Poppin' Music Kubricks.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some more information in our chat room, if you care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Link to the website that has more information.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, 8th Style is going to be getting a limited edition with it, and apparently the limited edition comes with some kind of, what I thought was cool, not only do you get a little EMUs card, but you also get...
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to add a comment on 8thStyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I got a report from DarkLionXVI this afternoon, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_04]: Siggy, that he was saying that the limited edition was going to be retailed at $130.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I wish Siggy was on Skype right now because I'd call him and make him tell us more information about the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's on Skype.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was going to say something, but no.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you mean, who cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to eat style.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mel's saying, who cares what's in it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's $130.
[SPEAKER_04]: Buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the problem?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just buy it.
[SPEAKER_19]: And how?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ziggy's not on Skype right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll try to call him later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe he can give us more information about what's going on with the... Because I haven't been paying close enough attention.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm getting confused enough at all the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: news going around that I can't keep track of the Japanese news as well, so... Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shall we have ourselves a cage match, boys and girls?
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's do it!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: We's gonna have a cage match!
[SPEAKER_04]: Last week in the Orange Lounge cage match...
[SPEAKER_04]: I need a quiet in the studio, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's too much sidebar conversation going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can't hear ourselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last week in the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match, we had Bond 1, that was Jamie's pick, with a song called Shine.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what was so special about Shine, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_18]: It used some of the same samples from Afronova.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it has a little bit of a DDR tie into it, so we'll hear that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you only get to hear a clip of last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_04]: As a reminder, the way the cage match works, we're going to play three songs for you guys, a clip of last week's winner, and two new songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio, as chosen by your votes in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we will get to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's song number one you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: But please remember, do not vote until I say so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number one, Bond with Shine, the Dub Chakra mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's a clip, enjoy.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, that was last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Bond with Shine, the dub Chakra Mix.
[SPEAKER_18]: That song just makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Will it win for two weeks in a row, or will it succumb to one of our challengers tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's find out.
[SPEAKER_04]: First challenger tonight is one of my picks, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to admit, ever since I heard that Skulk was announced for Ultramix, I've been liking that band Echo Image more and more.
[SPEAKER_04]: and not that Sigurd has anything to do with that by allowing me to borrow the CD for a little while but honestly, the more I listen to it, the more they remind me of Erasure and all these cool synth-bop bands I love and I gotta say, I love this song and I want to put it in tonight's cage match it's a song by Echo Image from their CD and the song is called Standing Alone it's track 2 from their album, I believe it's called Compufonic I'm going off the top of my head there so here it is
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you like Skulk, you might like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Echo Image with Standing Alone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enjoy.
Black rain clouds sealing up the sun The shouting voices in your head Tell me nothing You scream but no one hear you calling You left without your life
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, as typical Orange Lounge fashion dictates, we'll go around and see what everyone thought of Echo Image with Standing Alone.
[SPEAKER_04]: And not standing alone there in the corners, DarkSakura with her impression.
[SPEAKER_18]: It freaking sounds like Depeche Mode, I like it.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, that one gets a 9 for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice solid 9.
[SPEAKER_18]: And it's not trance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mr. Floatwalk
[SPEAKER_26]: It's pretty solid.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's a smooth track.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's what I like.
[SPEAKER_26]: You know, you got all the keys to Cincinnati, but it's not overly, you know, like, it's just not very loud and over-imposing.
[SPEAKER_26]: I just think it's something you can really relax to, and that's why I dig it a lot.
[SPEAKER_26]: I think I'll give it a nine and a half.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, lanky style.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like it, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: So far, the two tracks I've heard from them have been really good, so I gotta listen to that CD sometimes, so I'm gonna give it a nine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shark Scroll.
[SPEAKER_16]: PrettyNine Angel
[SPEAKER_19]: That sounds hot, as well as the rest of the TV.
[SPEAKER_19]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: Fat 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, another Fat 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: Explicit.
[SPEAKER_27]: This song gave me an orgasm.
[SPEAKER_27]: I like this song a lot, though, so I'll give it a 9.5 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, how you doing, Heather?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, who the hell did the mic go to?
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki's sister's here to give her impression of the song.
[SPEAKER_07]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: I want more of these embarrassing Loki stories after Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fire Poker, it was one of those log, like, you know how they have those things to pick up logs?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a log grabber thing, you could move logs in a firebox.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are so sending Loki out of the room after Cage Match, I want more of these stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anybody else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Does Loki's girlfriend want to give a number to that song?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, what song?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, next up is Loki's pick, and Loki has picked something very special for you guys tonight, very special, it's special.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, now, I was gonna go with my remix, which, you know, that's just, you know, standard, because, you know, I make it, and so it's gotta be in there, but no, no, um, you know, my fiance had better plans, so she picked this song, I don't know who it's by, um, it's, uh,
[SPEAKER_06]: Papa Smurf, Lick My Ass
[SPEAKER_10]: The Chocolate Factory
[SPEAKER_04]: A score of negative infinity from Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's hear from Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I tell you, this is my fiance's pick.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did it for her.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it gets a 10.
[SPEAKER_06]: This one's going to be Rob's song.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob was going to use this in another week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So don't be getting pissed off at me.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is all Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all his fault.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's acting all innocent, but it was all him.
[SPEAKER_06]: Besides, the Flash video is much better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Floatwalk.
[SPEAKER_26]: Wow, I didn't even know PapaSwerve was black.
[SPEAKER_26]: That said, yeah, that said, I got two words for it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Solo 2005.
[SPEAKER_26]: On a scale of one to ten?
[SPEAKER_26]: Let's see, well, if we're talking booties, I think an eight kind of looks like a booty, you know, if you tilt it sideways.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, yeah, I'm going to give it an eight.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to put that in the cage match, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Angel, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see, Comedial Factor 6.
[SPEAKER_27]: Explicit.
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh, no fucking comment.
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh, I'll just give it a question mark, because it all depends on what people... Okay, I'll give it an 8, equal sign 3.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, 8 equals 3 from Jonas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, LankyStyle, did you have a vote?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think what I have to say is that Poppa Smurf should watch out because I'm sure she licked all the other Smurfs' asses before she got to him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's a great song and all, but gag factor is basically all.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, comedy, 10.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song is a whole 8.
[SPEAKER_18]: That song reminds me of a fanfic that my, uh,
[SPEAKER_18]: Roommate from college had printed out on that.
[SPEAKER_18]: You remember back in the days when printer paper was all green and white and had the tearing edges on the side?
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, my friend went to the computer lab at my school.
[SPEAKER_18]: This is in 1995, mind you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Printed up the Smuck Fest.
[SPEAKER_18]: Someone had written a Lemon fanfic about the Smurfs getting it on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gross.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was scary.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that's what that song makes me think of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's wrap this up so we can get past this topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got one more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have an online name, Honda, I should refer to you as, or just Loki's sister?
[SPEAKER_04]: Gypsy Wolf.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would you give that, Gypsy Wolf?
[SPEAKER_07]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Having seen the animation for it, I have to say a 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wow, a 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're easy to please.
[SPEAKER_04]: You gave two 10s tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's review so you guys can vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number one, last week's winner, Bond with Shine, the dub Chakra Mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number two is Echo Image with Standing Alone.
[SPEAKER_04]: and song number three is Papa Smurf, Can I Lick Your Ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, place, vote, now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we will tally up those votes very shortly and let you know who won tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me, uh... Oh!
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie already beat me to the place vote now thing, so... Thank you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_18]: Moving on... You are welcome!
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, let's, uh... Loki, why don't you give us a sim update?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's going on in the sim world?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know you've built your own thing, and I know there's food mix news, all sorts of fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well... Uh... Ooh!
[SPEAKER_06]: Done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, anyways, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: No, there's another, I think... I can't remember if this was last week or this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's another update to Techno Fiend.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got some cool stuff in it.
[SPEAKER_13]: What's Techno Fiend?
[SPEAKER_06]: Techno Fiend is a... Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Techno Fiend is a new Step Mania skin that's nice looking.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very... They do a lot of cool stuff to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Plus it has the Ridge Racer and Game Over thing, which is kind of cool too.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: They have, it looks nice, so that's what I have on the cabinet right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, it would have worked better had the cabinet, like, not broken itself, but anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: Other than that, it was just announced this week that Food Mix Plus had hidden content in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now I have on our website how you can get to that hidden content.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically there is a dummy file in one of the directories there and you turn that into a zip file and you get a brand new song, new steps for some of the older songs, and new Oni courses.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then other than that...
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's really not that much else.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, oh, no, no, it should be mentioned, the first pack of ripped characters from DDR5thMix has surfaced online.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can find the link on DDRmaniaX for that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're pretty nice looking.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're ripped directly from the DDR games because the guy that, he built his own software to do that kind of stuff, so that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: and, um, other than that, really, um, not too much else, uh, DDROSC3's going on right now, I think the first pack of songs has been released for that, um, and I know DDR, um, the remix contest on Bumai Style and, um, DDR Maniacs, I think, are up already, they're done, they should be posting those, uh, those songs online for voting soon, and I think that's all, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: You need a mic, because we're not going to hear you.
[SPEAKER_27]: Have they added a comment section on Be My Install already for The Sims?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think you could, that's new.
[SPEAKER_06]: They already have that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, because I just noticed about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, but that's all that's going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: When a radio show calls out,
[SPEAKER_05]: That means you're a shock jock and you're doing stupid bits.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is your refrigerator running?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hey, Siggy, what's up?
[SPEAKER_22]: I thought you were going to scat me after Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the Cage Match is done.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just waiting for the votes.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So tell me what you know about these new 8-style limited editions and stuff because I haven't really been following it because I can barely keep track of what's going on domestically, let alone importly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So share what you know with us, would you?
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, here's what I've known so far about 2DX 8-Style Special Edition.
[SPEAKER_22]: They have, well, along with 8-Style, they have a 2DX Red e-amusement card.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's going to be random, so we'll never know what's inside each art cover for that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, they have a 2DX Visual Emotion DVD.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I can't wait for that DVD.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm reading the translation right now.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, they have the 8-Style V-Rare Soundtrack
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, an 8-style V-Rare, really?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that should be cool, okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then the 8-style special edition, special made box, like a, you know, like a box for stacking your preview styles from, you know, from 5th, 6th, 7th, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, and then, of course, here's still a little bit interesting.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's a BeatMe2DX-style mail magazine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like M-A-I-L or M-A-L-E?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, darn.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And with any other information on what's going to be on that magazine?
[SPEAKER_22]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're losing you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Speak into the mic a little more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_22]: D'oh.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, well, maybe we can get a hookup.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well thanks for sharing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were curious what was going on with that.
[SPEAKER_22]: I checked on the Web Konami website for TJXHL.
[SPEAKER_22]: The price is about 106,000 yen, which is, I think, or actually 10,479 yen, including tax.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds like a lot, but it's not quite that bad.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's approximately $130, according to NTSX.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'll be looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for the update, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_06]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, take care bud.
Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's also known as DarkLionXVI.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some more information on 2DXA style.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just to clear up something from our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey Orange Launch Radio, if I'm not correct, isn't this the first time you've ever called out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually it is not.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, we've called out before.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh yeah, like when people tell you, you know, are you getting cold, are you getting hot, I will say, someone in the room is pretty freaking hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mmm, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know I'm hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not talking about myself either, but.
[SPEAKER_18]: Some of us just can't help it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my, all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to go to a break pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we're just going to do a bunch of random songs in this next break, so we'll probably do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got to find those songs, though, so somebody has to help me fill time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's going to help fill time?
[SPEAKER_18]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've had, how many shots now?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think, well, I'm almost out of this glass, so that would be six shots, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm feeling okay, but a little dizzy.
[SPEAKER_06]: A little slightly dizzy.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not feeling that warm.
[SPEAKER_18]: If it were a cheat night, it would be on.
[SPEAKER_18]: I need to sit down with someone with some either dark rum or tequila and just do shots.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, other than that, let's see, what else can I talk about?
[SPEAKER_18]: I should have brought my amaretto for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, actually, where's Gypsy Wolf?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the chat room is reminding me of something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gypsy Wolf, we need embarrassing Loki stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we give you a couple minutes?
[SPEAKER_04]: I suppose we can give you a couple minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, in the meantime, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll do embarrassing Loki stories after the break.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do have to get into the FUs of the week soon, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you guys want to hear who won tonight's cage match, actually?
[SPEAKER_18]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll get to it in a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will tell you that one song just like obliterated the competition.
[SPEAKER_04]: It totally blew the competition out of the water.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you guess what song it is?
[SPEAKER_04]: Which song would you guys think it is that obliterated the others?
[SPEAKER_04]: Papa Smurf.
[SPEAKER_18]: Papa Smurf.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because our listeners tend to go for the gross potty humor.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, how else did Loki win a cage match by singing I'm Staying In?
[SPEAKER_04]: Here is tonight's winner of the Orange Lounge cage match.
[SPEAKER_18]: Chatroom, you have restored my faith in you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: An upset there by Echo Image winning tonight's cage match with Standing Alone.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm still getting my revenge next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: About twice the votes that Bond got.
[SPEAKER_04]: Papa Smurf
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still trying to prep for the next break because there's songs I'm looking for.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little random mix of songs I want to play for you, certainly.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want to know who that one person was.
[SPEAKER_04]: What one person?
[SPEAKER_18]: The one person who voted.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would share, but I'll let them reveal their identity in the chat room if they want to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, free... Mel says a free Max 2 be rare.
[SPEAKER_04]: A Max 2 or an Extreme?
[SPEAKER_04]: Max 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, he only says Max, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I ain't that stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's it going?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I might have fallen for that, because I would have been all, ooh, V-Rare.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'll just throw a giant papier-mch V at them.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can't take requests this break, because we have songs we really, really want to play for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will be right back with more Orange Launch Radio and the FUs of the week coming up when we get back as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: But please don't send those in yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: And more clues?
[SPEAKER_06]: More clues?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe, but send in those guesses right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: The clues never stop here on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_09]: GF GF
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: I now sway, like they used to do, with a house beat to it, and before I'm through, you might learn a thing or two, you can show your piece, and you can catch me on Soul Train late next week, don't you know I'm all that, and a bucket of wings, I'm on the jabs, when I feel the need to shake my good thing, when you see me coming, sit back, relax, stay
[SPEAKER_20]: Hi-ho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter B, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Logie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hallelujah, it's raining men.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, we are, speaking of things that have been coming over me, private message, we have some more guesses for the song that we've been trying to guess all night long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mel, it starts off with, I'm sorry, Float, it starts off with this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a good one from El Mullet.
[SPEAKER_04]: The guess is Divine Sweet Divide by Tanya Donoli.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is why.
[SPEAKER_04]: The jam on the bagel is sweet and cells divide.
[SPEAKER_26]: Too abstract, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, a little bit too abstract.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a bad guess there.
[SPEAKER_26]: I like the way you're thinking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I like the way you're thinking too.
[SPEAKER_04]: John Fields says, Cytoplasm by WND Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cytoplasm is unique in all cells.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, it holds everything inside a cell.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a cell always has a nucleus, which is round like a donut hole.
[SPEAKER_26]: Sold!
[SPEAKER_26]: Not quite.
[SPEAKER_26]: Although probably right now with these guesses I'm probably relearning everything I forgot in physiology, man.
[SPEAKER_26]: I sucked at biology.
[SPEAKER_26]: Except, you know, when we talked about the reproductive system.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh yeah, I aced that sucker.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's all the guesses so far.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's all?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's it so far.
[SPEAKER_26]: My goodness.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you a little later.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll open it up for more guesses.
[SPEAKER_26]: Like I said, guys, I mentioned before the last music bed, someone in the room is very hot on its trail.
[SPEAKER_04]: After that last batch, somebody else is just, like, smoking, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, just thinking a little too far into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the only problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you honestly clue me into what we're talking about?
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we should do the FUs of the week now.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we don't have to.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, we can just sit here.
[SPEAKER_18]: Damn it, I need to vent.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before we vent, though, where's Gypsy Wolf?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the chat room is begging for more Loki stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, could you please leave the room for a minute?
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nellie, can you take him to the bedroom?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, what's the worst?
[SPEAKER_07]: All he's going to do is object to things.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, all right, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: He won't have a microphone, so it won't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, any funny childhood stories from Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, okay, anybody's familiar with Construx?
[SPEAKER_07]: The building toys that you kind of snap together, they have those little blue things?
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, one thing that, you know, I used to do would be, this was also before I was, no, this was after I was born, but I was too young to remember most of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw pictures my mom showed me, so, anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you would build power suits out of the Construx and run around the house with them.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, shoot the dog, whatever was cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, I don't know, I can't really remember all that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, the one that was the best thing, I love this, this wasn't embarrassing, this was just fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was Mission Control with our dog.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Matt would, Loki would sit there and he would, our dog, our Labrador, would walk around the house and do stuff, eat, drink, etc., her normal thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: and he would say, Houston, we are taking in water and she would drink or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, I would do the ground control at NASA's commentary on everything that my dog was doing as if it were some sort of spaceship or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: It made people crack up like crazy and it was funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was great when she was downloading cargo and taking a dump out back.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jettisoning, fuel, urinating, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: My dog is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Too bad she's dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pets are cool, but, you know, I mean... That is so wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: What else do they used to do?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, we have, like, um... What else was it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember much.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, we did a lot with Marbleworks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did a lot of crap with that, put water down them and shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: We hit Army Men and Mom's Ficus Tree.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I remember now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a water balloon launcher and I used to launch tennis balls at the people on the bike trail over the green belt from us.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was cool because you can hit those people from 200 yards away.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we got lucky one time and we hit a guy and he fell over and that was funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that was that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then there was those little paratrooper guys you could do where you could get army men and strap parachutes to them on really windy days.
[SPEAKER_07]: They'd fly right over the house.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could watch them go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, goodbye!
[SPEAKER_07]: Melted quite a few army men too.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: How many poopy stories?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did he ever shit himself or anything?
[SPEAKER_06]: I ate dog food as a kid.
[SPEAKER_07]: He ate a whole entire bowl of gravy train.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gravy from ear to ear when he was a kid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, it had meat in it, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: If it's good enough for the dog, it's good enough for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give me meat!
[SPEAKER_07]: Dog's like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: Where'd my food go?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well thank you for sharing those with us.
[SPEAKER_04]: We needed some good embarrassing Loki stories, so... They weren't that bad, but they were still funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: I killed a man with a trident through his chest.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's from Anchorman, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Then I think it's... Do you have pictures?
[SPEAKER_06]: They have pictures too.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's in my photo album somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: My baby photo album.
[SPEAKER_18]: Is there a name we can call you, Alpo?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think
[SPEAKER_18]: L3?
[SPEAKER_18]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob, sorry.
[SPEAKER_19]: I just had the worst idea ever, and no, this had nothing to do with Andrew, okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: Next remix for Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: Long chain running, but he has to do something with dogs or something.
[SPEAKER_18]: He probably needs to do a remix of Disco Dog.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, let's get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Jamie, why do we have to do the FUs of the week every single week on this show?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because we're full of to anger.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, this is bad.
[SPEAKER_18]: An F you to John Fields for making me laugh while I have a headache for shiny disco dog balls.
[SPEAKER_18]: My first F you goes to the chat room for not guessing correctly.
[SPEAKER_18]: And not enough of you guessing.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, goddammit, guess.
[SPEAKER_18]: And to...
[SPEAKER_18]: Silent Ben for misspelling the word that you misspelled.
[SPEAKER_18]: There's a site called dictionary.com.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, there's one called hyperdictionary.com.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just use it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Learn how to spell.
[SPEAKER_18]: Please, people.
[SPEAKER_18]: And learn grammar.
[SPEAKER_18]: And by the way, U is not spelled U. That is a letter.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's Y-O-U.
[SPEAKER_18]: Your is spelled Y-O-U apostrophe R-E or Y-O-U-R depending on the context you're using the word.
[SPEAKER_18]: Not you are!
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Now if they put apostrophe U, apostrophe U, then that would be okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: How would it be okay?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because an apostrophe is for if you're shortening a word, so... But there are only certain allowed abbreviations of words that are grammatically correct.
[SPEAKER_18]: that are commonly accepted by people who have been educated.
[SPEAKER_18]: That doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_18]: Up to the third grade.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not educated.
[SPEAKER_06]: We know that.
[SPEAKER_18]: And normally, normally I've gotten a whole, but I've gotten off of my whole Grammar Fiend kick.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got it, but I hit my saturation point sometimes.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, uh... Anyway, uh... Anyway...
[SPEAKER_18]: Another FU goes to the people on the road who are major assholes and don't know how to drive.
[SPEAKER_18]: Amazingly enough, my drive here was without incident.
[SPEAKER_18]: But a lot of my driving lately, especially to and from work, had been full of people who usually drive semis who don't know how to drive.
[SPEAKER_18]: Semis are cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, I hate the ones that are like the trucks full of gravel.
[SPEAKER_15]: The gravel flies all the way out.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have a crack in my windshield now because of the freaking rock truck.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's like, you ass.
[SPEAKER_18]: And it's going to cost like $300 if I wanted to replace my windshield.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, it's so minor that I can live with the look, but it's there and right in the corner of my vision.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's like, it's, there's, look.
[SPEAKER_18]: My car is already raped.
[SPEAKER_18]: And now I've got a crack, not a crack, but like, it's not a crack, it's a chip in the windshield is what it is.
[SPEAKER_18]: And, oh, piss me off.
[SPEAKER_18]: So,
[SPEAKER_18]: So another FU goes to the hot.
[SPEAKER_18]: I really dislike this part of living in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_18]: I love the winter because I like the rain a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I like that when I moved out here, it was raining.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I was like, oh, it's just like Alabama, yay.
[SPEAKER_18]: But anyway, it's just a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, we think this is getting all cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then it's hot.
[SPEAKER_18]: So it's like, what's up with that?
[SPEAKER_18]: Also, an FU goes to my apartment manager for me having told her weekly for the last month to fix my goddamn air conditioning and it's not fixed yet.
[SPEAKER_18]: And again, with it getting into triple digit heat and not having a working air conditioner, that's like a health hazard.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know in Arizona, if your apartment manager doesn't fix your air conditioning in your apartment, you can take them to court for it.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I wouldn't be surprised if you could do it here.
[SPEAKER_18]: This is fucked up.
[SPEAKER_18]: and seriously here, I mean, I honestly would have grounds for negligence because there is a statute that's referred to as duty of utmost care.
[SPEAKER_18]: And see, I know this because I'm taking business law right now, so don't fuck with me.
[SPEAKER_18]: But no, it's especially like for hotels, for people who run facilities, there's a duty of utmost care to provide services to tenants, to guests,
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, that they need to make sure that they provide a place that's going to be safe to live, safe to exist, you know, to operate in.
[SPEAKER_18]: And this is not, you know, safe.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, when it gets up that hot and there's no way to keep cool, then that's dangerous.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's getting bad.
[SPEAKER_18]: Leave my foot alone.
[SPEAKER_11]: Another FU goes toward...
[SPEAKER_18]: American River College and this is why alright for anyone who's been paying attention to my live journal there's been the saga of my student loan check and see I work for my lender so I know where my money is I know when my funds have been dispersed I know how to do your job financial aid department at ARC I could do your job blindfolded so when I'm told that my check is mailed out last Friday
[SPEAKER_18]: and it's, you know, I check the mail every day.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm not meaning last Friday as in two days ago.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm meaning the week before.
[SPEAKER_18]: It does not take seven days to mail a check in town.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, maybe two.
[SPEAKER_18]: But not in Carmichael.
[SPEAKER_18]: When ARC is six minutes from my house and the post office is six minutes from both ARC and my house.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, this is just, it's,
[SPEAKER_18]: So I'm going to call them on Tuesday and say, excuse me, bitches.
[SPEAKER_18]: If my money isn't here within the next two business days... Give me my money!
[SPEAKER_18]: Your asses are getting reported to the Department of Education and you know what they will do to you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bitch better have my money.
[SPEAKER_18]: They will pull your funding.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, I vented.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's like been my rage for the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you forgot it was a three hour show here for a minute.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: I just had a...
[SPEAKER_18]: Big build-up of rage, and now I feel better.
[SPEAKER_18]: You feel better?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I feel better.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you have to say?
[SPEAKER_18]: My foot says, get this thing away from me, bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, he found the third mic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Scary.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, let's go to Loki and Loki's FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm starting to get a little dizzy.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, first FU goes to my stupid cabinet and the goddamn Ipac 2 for not working.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even know why, because it works for like 2 seconds, or like, well, maybe a little longer, 2 seconds, but more like 30 seconds or like half a song in DDR, and then it just stops working for no reason, and I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was conflicting with the Ipac 4 that I had in there, but no, that's not the case, because I unplugged the other one, and it still breaks.
[SPEAKER_06]: So apparently, my shitty solder job that I did on it didn't work, so I need to, I don't know, get a new one, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it's because it shares the name with a crappy Macintosh computer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm sorry, I forgot there's a Mac lever in here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to go run and hide now.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm coming after you, and I'm going to clock you in with my iPod.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck you to the new iMacs, because, well, you can make them look prettier, but they're still going to suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said you can make them look prettier, but they're still going to suck.
[SPEAKER_16]: Dude, what is this?
[SPEAKER_16]: Like, crap on the Mac fan base?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, it's no fair to you because we happen to have a bunch of IBM freaks here.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: If I had $3,000, I'd love to buy an iPad.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell is the i in the iMac and iPod?
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell is i mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: Internet or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know how to use computers, so I buy this piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mac.
[SPEAKER_05]: The opinions expressed on this show by Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, I think Apple computers are for people that don't know how to use computers, but think that pretty computers are good.
[SPEAKER_16]: Loki is very lucky, he's far across the room from me right now, but he's not far enough to miss being hit in the head by a soda bottle or something.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now, now, now, now, now, we have... In defense of Apple, I played on an Apple II computer, and I played a lot of kicks on that in Lode Runner, so okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Without Apple, we would not have had Oregon Trail.
[SPEAKER_26]: Represent.
[SPEAKER_26]: Or the first version of Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego.
[SPEAKER_26]: Or Odell Lake.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I was going to say Odell Lake.
[SPEAKER_18]: My first computer was a Mac.
[SPEAKER_18]: And it came in that little box with the 5-inch screen.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I played a lot of Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego on that thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, and you know, who needs to upgrade my computer or even work on it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I can't get to it because goddammit, the monitor and the computer are the same damn thing!
[SPEAKER_18]: I take that back, my first computer was the Texas Instruments computer.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, and I forgot... I spent five hours programming in BASIC to watch a little ball bounce back and forth across the screen and change color.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I forgot about Mac's contribution to the first-person shooter realm, Marathon, because that game is so much better than Quake and Unreal any day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, those games weren't even out yet when Marathon came out, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can go on for hours about how bad Apple sucks, but I don't think I will.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's talk about Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Microsoft sucks, too, because Service Pack 2's lame.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least he's an equal opportunity offender.
[SPEAKER_06]: They said, yeah, Microsoft Windows is never going to be secure until about, I don't know, 2011, 2015.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, thank you for warning me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm buying your piece of shit now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, wait, no, I'm not buying your piece of shit now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm downloading it for free.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even by then, the hackers will have new, you know, things to break.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't matter, it's just, you know, their software's gonna suck, no matter what.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's all we have, okay, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's what you get when you outsource.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, those people in India, they're just not as sharp as those people in, you know, America.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, wait, I'm wrong, they are sharper than them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, um, no, other than that, um, really not anything else I'm mad at other than, um, well, not anyone being at QZAR last night because there, I don't know where the hell people were in Vacaville.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no, I'm not talking about you, I'm talking about the Vacaville folk that normally are there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, is that normal?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, there's no Skater Cowboy, no anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: No Skater Cowboy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just, no one there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, oh my god, they left Vacaville.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's scary.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the things just keep getting better
[SPEAKER_04]: No, things just keep getting worse.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, actually, it's been an okay week, but I would just first like to say, you know what, if I was going to say F you to Apple, that's because I was a Commodore 64 fan back in the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I've been contemplating buying a Mac laptop.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to listen to Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of want one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, because laptops are different.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think laptops are different.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you can't upgrade even a PC laptop very easily.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not very easily.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can put up like a memory upgrade, and that's the main thing you can do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want one!
[SPEAKER_20]: I want one!
[SPEAKER_20]: Where?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, otherwise, uh, an F you, uh, I don't know, an F you to the fact that I'm leaving again in just over a week, and that makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't want to leave again for two weeks, especially with everything that's kind of going on back home.
[SPEAKER_05]: You get paid a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I could get SARS.
[SPEAKER_05]: You get paid in money and sex.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, on the other hand, at the same time... Shut up, Nelly.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the same time, when I do go, the company pays for all my food, so that'll be extra money that I can spend on video games!
[SPEAKER_06]: No, go ahead and finish the FQs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I completely forgot about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess I'm done since the rest of you are going to take all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: This wasn't about FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is... I won a trip to San Diego in October.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm gonna be staying at the Hotel Del Coronado.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is basically a fucking expensive hotel, which is also haunted.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um... Take your germanium.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, your portal to hell.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, your... Shut up!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll never get past security on the plane.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll think it's a bomb.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe... Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is that bomb you have?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not a bomb.
[SPEAKER_06]: You said bomb!
[SPEAKER_06]: You're a terrorist!
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, that's all I have.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, Hotel Del Coronado.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome place in San Diego.
[SPEAKER_04]: All expenses paid by my work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yummy.
[SPEAKER_04]: OLR stalker fans, now you know where to find them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to Floatwalk with his FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_26]: Lordy.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, didn't go keep this actually pretty short.
[SPEAKER_26]: First FA of the week goes to all the people over in Japan's board to say that the people who are creating steps for Ultramix 2 don't deserve to be doing any of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, like you people do over on the board.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's funny because one of the biggest arguments is, well, I've never seen any of these guys ranked on the sim file community.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm sitting here thinking, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_03]: That should be a credit!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, exactly!
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm sitting here thinking, okay, wonderful, 90% of sim files I've seen are like 1,100, you know, finger steps, you know, patterns.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, okay, you try putting 200 pounds of pressure on those fingers and doing that, then maybe, just maybe, I'll give you a little bit of credit there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And like, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: Meanwhile, you're doing, you know, having a real life and making money doing your job, where these other people who have no jobs are sitting there doing nothing but making steps and putting them on communities and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I know there's a lot of probably a few cool, you know, people there online doing these steps, but seriously, he's got a life he needs to take care of first.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, I mean, you got all that going on, and I'm sitting here thinking, with all the edits you make in sim files, guess what, you're just making, you're basically playing 2DX there, you know, get with the other game, you know, don't waste your time on...
[SPEAKER_26]: Arrow Smashing, you know, just saying we don't know what we're talking about, we're underqualified, but I could go off about how good we are and all that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Have they even played any of the steps yet?
[SPEAKER_26]: They're like, oh, they suck already!
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, I mean, once the game drops, I think people are definitely going to be pleasantly surprised.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: People are still going to hate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same thing I was telling Sigurd when he was here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: No matter what, when the game comes out, people are going to hate the steps.
[SPEAKER_04]: And oh man, the people around the office were ready to throw down with, uh...
[SPEAKER_26]: But you know, it's all good.
[SPEAKER_26]: You know, we're rich.
[SPEAKER_26]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_26]: Scoreboard.
[SPEAKER_26]: Look at the scoreboard.
[SPEAKER_26]: Our scoreboard says we got paychecks.
[SPEAKER_26]: And last FB of the week just goes to work.
[SPEAKER_26]: I know, yeah, you guys are thinking, why should I bitch about working at Konami?
[SPEAKER_26]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_26]: I have to work tomorrow for Labor Day.
[SPEAKER_26]: And not on a fun game at that.
[SPEAKER_26]: But that said, you know, that just ain't right.
[SPEAKER_26]: You know, I got people who want to spend time with me.
[SPEAKER_26]: You know, I got a lady who needs some lovin' in.
[SPEAKER_26]: You know, what happens?
[SPEAKER_26]: I gotta leave her in the morning, man.
[SPEAKER_26]: Like, you know, I'm just the, you know, John that picked her up and, you know, dumped her off, man.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, what's up with that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_26]: But, you know, it ain't really like that.
[SPEAKER_26]: What's the point of having to work in the morning?
[SPEAKER_26]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, yeah, and one last F you.
[SPEAKER_26]: Goes to Order of Chaos, actually.
[SPEAKER_26]: Sure, you know, people say you shouldn't crack on your own.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_26]: Ever since he posted that rubbernecking post of all the car accidents...
[SPEAKER_26]: Every day I've commuted to work, I've had to be stopped because of, like, traffic accidents happening.
[SPEAKER_26]: So he's made my commute, like, half an hour worse every single day ever since he posted that two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_26]: Thanks a whole hell of a lot for nothing.
[SPEAKER_26]: You get no Oreos.
[SPEAKER_26]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_26]: I love you anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, special lady, Shark Skrull, do you have any FUs you'd like to give us tonight?
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, I kind of did, and then...
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm just in pain and kind of mellow now, so this F.U.
[SPEAKER_16]: space for rent, highest bidder.
[SPEAKER_16]: I bid a penny.
[SPEAKER_16]: Give me a dollar, bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Angel, your F.U.s of the week.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, F.U.
[SPEAKER_19]: to SBC for basically giving us the lowdown of having, or we have to pay $150 to get a phone jack in the den to have DSL.
[SPEAKER_19]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't think I want to play that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to shop around a bit, see if... Well, yeah, we can do Cable too, but... We want... This is true, but... I want to... Other people in the house want to exhaust all options first before... Subjecting to Cable, so we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Cable in Sacramento is just better than all the DSL in Sacramento, so... Probably.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might want to research that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's Loki at the internet.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm Al Gore.
[SPEAKER_19]: I created the internet.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, and I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because I can't think of anything at the moment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's go on to Explicit.
[SPEAKER_19]: You're FU's.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: I wanna give an F to Texas Hold'em.
[SPEAKER_27]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_27]: I need some cards that goes at least an 8, 9, 10, Jack, Queen, King at least.
[SPEAKER_27]: All I'm getting is nothing but 2s and 3s.
[SPEAKER_27]: How the hell can you win an actual Texas Hold'em game with just those cards?
[SPEAKER_26]: Someone's cheating.
[SPEAKER_26]: Play 2-7 offsuit, best hand in the game.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, but, fuck, I'm not wasting no fucking 40 bucks, and another F you goes to my family for forcing me to play the damn game.
[SPEAKER_27]: God damn it, I told you I'm not wasting more money.
[SPEAKER_27]: I only play games that I know I'm gonna win money on, like Blackjack.
[SPEAKER_27]: I get 200 on cash for kicking that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Told them, ah, no wins whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_27]: Or should I just say fuck you to the cards and sell for giving me the bad luck?
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: And fuck you to some lady throwing a damn beer bottle in my head.
[SPEAKER_27]: What?
[SPEAKER_27]: I just mentioned this before.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just her way of saying I love you.
[SPEAKER_06]: No!
[SPEAKER_27]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, she wants to share a drink.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing says I love you like a beer in my face.
[SPEAKER_04]: A drink?
[SPEAKER_27]: Kill me with a drink.
[SPEAKER_27]: I got hit in the head right here.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, dude.
[SPEAKER_27]: Got hit in the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should have been like, oh, you want a drink, huh, bitch?
[SPEAKER_05]: Beer tastes good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just waving like this.
[SPEAKER_27]: You didn't have to throw a damn beer bottle at me.
[SPEAKER_26]: Perhaps you were thinking tastes great and she really meant less filling.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, dear.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anything else?
[SPEAKER_27]: F you for some kids kissing on my Toyota Corolla S tire.
[SPEAKER_27]: What?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude.
[SPEAKER_11]: Holy crap!
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, waving is the first step to rape.
[SPEAKER_06]: She was only defending herself.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a reason why there's porta... There's a fucking reason why there's porta potties in bathrooms.
[SPEAKER_27]: You can't piss on tires, they don't clean the tires.
[SPEAKER_27]: F you to the security up at the Rage for breaking up a battle and stuff and for breaking up people freak dancing in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh goody, that's what I'm going tonight.
[SPEAKER_27]: Just because I have a nice boner by accident after some girl's freaking on me does not fucking be how raping her.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember that part about TMI being in the show?
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember that part?
[SPEAKER_27]: Raping is a crime, but freak dancing is not.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, anything else?
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's just say, do be continued.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: As usual.
[SPEAKER_27]: Who else?
[SPEAKER_27]: That's too much.
[SPEAKER_27]: LankyStyle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you really want to go there?
[SPEAKER_04]: You say what you want, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: All I have to say is big F you to people who want to fucking... Miserable people who have made their lives fucking horrible on their own and want to fucking bring everybody else down because they're fucking immature little fucking pricks.
[SPEAKER_05]: You go ahead and do it without us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go ahead, drive your fucking car off the road and kill yourself because no one's going to fucking miss you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't bring us down because you're shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't need to really go into detail, it's kind of a personal thing, but it's been a fucking rocky weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they have to understand, to open a door, it does not require your fist going through the door, but there's a handle there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yes, goddammit, Diet Dr. Pepper does taste like regular Dr. Pepper.
[SPEAKER_07]: No sacrifices here, Ren.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we have a segment or a little subject for a Wednesday show, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gypsy Wolf, do you have any FUs?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's brilliant.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, FU to Sacramento for not having any decent clubs.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't found one yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still have yet to find one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been to a couple.
[SPEAKER_07]: Most of them are either really ghetto or really teeny-bopper.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you been to Pace's?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you can put up with the gaiety, it's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's sexy men there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll take you there sometime.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have not been that far.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't had time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, no, nothing else.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go on to our chat room if you then, unless Nelly had something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is she off playing Harvest Moon still?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's not go there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what's going on with the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Knight says, My super FU is to work as always and financial setbacks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for the record, I have to work on Labor Day as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sigurd says, My first FU goes to Sweet Coden IV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blasphemous for me to say it, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: The FU is for the game being too short.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm almost done over 90 stars and only at 22 hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: An FU to parties not wanting my sexy level 12 thief in Final Fantasy XI to join them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Karma Titan says,
[SPEAKER_04]: He wants to get political.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says, F you, George Bush.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bush lied.
[SPEAKER_04]: People died.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you, I lived through 110 plus all freaking day and it ain't that bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you, all your base are belongs to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: VXJasonXV says, I would like to submit one on behalf of my right-hand.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to Adelphia for breaking cable two days ago and not planning on doing anything about it until Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ninst says, F you to my job and the people I work with.
[SPEAKER_04]: The job is getting to be bullshit and the people are getting more stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ninst also says, F you to my computer, I had to format earlier, and of course, there were problems during the format.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Nemesis says, F you to Floatwalk and Dancer X for giving clues that are too fucking hard.
[SPEAKER_15]: It would be really easy clues if you had paid attention in school.
[SPEAKER_26]: I don't know, the more you scream, the harder it gets.
[SPEAKER_26]: Ooh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_16]: Wait a second, isn't that what you told me last night?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just gonna... Damn it, you stole... I was just gonna say it's like sex.
[SPEAKER_03]: The more you relax, the easier it'll get.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: BlackDevilRx says, You know Loki is really a good guy, so F you to the guy who threw a beer bottle at him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except that was explicit.
[SPEAKER_04]: The beer bottle.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he says... He also says F you to Service Pack 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Misty says, F you to the little kids that like to scream their lungs off when I'm at work, the arcade, and already have a headache.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shade23 says, F you to California for having such better arcades than us on the East Coast, bastards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, come to Sacramento sometime.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll feel right at home.
[SPEAKER_04]: If by better you mean broken, then yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Luke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lunarius says, F you to DJ Potato for all of his music, especially for killing 511 with his remix 344, and also F you to Hurricane Francis.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to Wicco for not sending me my white poppin' buttons and delaying me building my poppin' ASC.
[SPEAKER_04]: I happen to like DJ Potato, he's a cool guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanie.
[SPEAKER_27]: F you to BlackDevilRx for not caring about me, dammit!
[SPEAKER_04]: SilentBen says, F you to Sakura for singling me out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think he meant DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's different than the song in DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please don't boot me.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, you need to realize something about me.
[SPEAKER_18]: I only single people out out of love.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's singling you out for a hug.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aw, hugs!
[SPEAKER_04]: Legend of Zaku says F you to the fact that summer is over F you to having to spend 3 hours shopping for a new backpack today F you to Sam Goody for selling $18.99 CDs for songs that have been out almost over 9 years F you to having nothing to do this Labor Day weekend and F you to myself for having to exchange a belt I bought at Hot Topic today for a larger size thinking that the first one was going to fit me F you to Microsoft for shitting on XP users with piss poor fixes such as Service Pack 2
[SPEAKER_04]: Pixie Dust says, my FU goes to carpal tunnel syndrome.
[SPEAKER_04]: The hospital doctor that saw me was such a cunt and happened to tell me that he hates Bel Air so much, so fuck him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Typing one hand sucks monkey balls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other than that, FU goes to pain, FU goes to boredom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same says, FU to GameStop for looking at me like I was a dumbass for asking for the US Extreme VRare.
[SPEAKER_04]: And FU to Floatwalk for dissing my edit site.
[SPEAKER_04]: I dissed it some more, but I didn't see a damn thing on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkKnight says, OhSky, a bonus FU to the major reign we had in Virginia recently.
[SPEAKER_04]: Almost made Richmond look like the new Atlantis.
[SPEAKER_04]: Totally underwater.
[SPEAKER_04]: Flaronay says, FU to Scandia for still not fixing the DDR pad.
[SPEAKER_04]: KarmaTitan says, FU to Altoids Tangerine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sours are sour.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Misty has the last word.
[SPEAKER_04]: FU to the Arcade for bringing the EX to three songs for credit.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was four.
[SPEAKER_04]: And taking off the unlocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'll give John Fields one.
[SPEAKER_04]: FU to construction on highways that should have been finished years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No more FUs.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're done with the segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's done.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Complete.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finished.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God, that was a long FU segment tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we need to talk about some, like, actual Bimani news at this point.
[SPEAKER_18]: Is there anything else we could... You mean there's Bimani news?
[SPEAKER_18]: What's that Bimani crap?
[SPEAKER_18]: I forgot what that was, because we haven't talked about it in a long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's not really Bomani news, but it's Dance Mania news, and as we all know, the Japanese folks always get a lot of their songs from the Dance Mania CDs.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a CD called Trans Paradise that was recently released in Japan for 1,995 yen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trans Paradise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tracklist isn't here yet, but we'll post it to our website soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: and in not really related to Bomani per se, but those of you guys that play a lot of video games, if you were listening to Wednesday's show, you heard about Acclaim, the video game publisher for such games as Turok.
[SPEAKER_04]: They went bankrupt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Acclaim is gone.
[SPEAKER_18]: I remember back in the days when Acclaim was cool, back in the days when we had NBA Jam.
[SPEAKER_18]: I say a moment of silence for Acclaim.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you say a moment of silence for acclaim?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I have a problem with the volume of my voice.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I can't do that because I'd be too obvious.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like the NBA Jam.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I would always kick ass on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: It was really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish that game was still around, though, because I think they got rid of it, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, let's give the folks in the chat room another chance to guess at that news.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope someone gets it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to play this song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't let Dancer X have another victory, you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to get it.
[SPEAKER_26]: I will say this.
[SPEAKER_26]: As I was scrolling back through the text of everyone in the chat room, someone...
[SPEAKER_26]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki has a song he would like to play for all you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I have to yell at everyone a little bit because we've been trying to get you guys to participate by naming this remix in our forums.
[SPEAKER_04]: To hell with you people.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we've gotten maybe like two guesses or two suggestions that weren't that great.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of you guys said, though, you were like, we need to hear it one more time before we can give it a name.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your last chance to hear this mix and give it a name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fair enough?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I already have a name if you don't pick one.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Loki with a remix of Radical Faith, as yet unnamed.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, go to our forums, www.orangetownsradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look for the thread in Bimani Discussion and guess and give it a title.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Sigurd Rocks, as cute as that was, is not a good remix title.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be for, like, an Echo Image remix or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you want to say about this remix of Radical Faith, Loki, that you did?
[SPEAKER_04]: Brand new?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nah, not really.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: And again, we're open for guesses, and I've gotten one guess so far from Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he's guessing, is it Love Love Shine?
[SPEAKER_04]: And no, this song is not Love Love Shine.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you can't guess, you dumbass!
[SPEAKER_04]: You should have guessed the same thing you guessed the first two times, because you were right the first two times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here it is, Loki's brand new remix of Radical Faith.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want some... no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Name this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just going to shut up now because I'll just give it away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, www.orange.radio.com, forums, name it.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Very sexy from Loki, Radical Faith.
[SPEAKER_04]: An unnamed remix.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I gave you guys the URL to post to on our forum.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a little loud.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, quit yelling.
[SPEAKER_18]: Jamie still has a raging headache right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Explicit as a raging boner.
[SPEAKER_18]: And you noticed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, no, he was saying earlier in a story that freak dancing is not illegal.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like... Raging boner.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's like, I don't know, remember realultimatepower.net?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, sorry.
[SPEAKER_18]: This script is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, as a reminder, please don't send me your guesses or your suggestions.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should say, over private message, you want to go to the forums and post those.
[SPEAKER_04]: That link I posted in the chat room that says...
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't talk condescendingly to your listeners Don't patronize them Way to go, Loki!
[SPEAKER_05]: Way to go, Loki!
[SPEAKER_05]: Scare off our listeners, Loki!
[SPEAKER_05]: Scare off our listeners!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, cry over it Yeah, that's right, Loki, your music sucks
[SPEAKER_18]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_18]: This vacuum sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you going to do maple syrup shots over there, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Syrup?
[SPEAKER_04]: He has a thing of Mrs. Butterworth going, Rob, as if I find Mrs. Butterworth hot or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Monday night, Diversion, Bomani Remixes, 7 o'clock, tune in, love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's happening on Tuesday night, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_18]: You need to be mixing some Malibu with that shit.
[SPEAKER_18]: That happens on Tuesday night?
[SPEAKER_18]: No.
[SPEAKER_18]: Tuesday night, pump up the volume.
[SPEAKER_18]: Starring me, the awesome and...
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, I went to GameCrazy, and the guy there gave me my official nickname.
[SPEAKER_18]: He was asking me what my name was, because they were putting in something for some order.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I was like, my name is Jamie the Great and Terrible.
[SPEAKER_18]: And he was like, how about Jamie the Truly Awesome and Never Nice?
[SPEAKER_18]: So that's my new official title.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Never Nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: And Never Nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: I am officially Completely Awesome and Never Nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, my show...
[SPEAKER_18]: is on Tuesday, and it's called Pump Up the Volume.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I have a pre-show that starts at 7, although when I'm really bored it starts earlier than that.
[SPEAKER_18]: And the show starts at 7.30, but because I now have to get my ass up at 5 a.m.
[SPEAKER_18]: every morning, my show is usually over right at 10.30, unless I'm really bored and I'll keep it going.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I was supposed to do my show last Tuesday, and I had to do an emergency announcement because I had to get my homework done.
[SPEAKER_18]: So blame my apartment manager for not turning on my AC, so I couldn't concentrate to do my homework on Monday, so I had to do it on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_18]: But as promised, I'm going to be doing Overclocked remixes, and I'm thinking about marathoning another CD.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know, maybe Sim & Flow, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe Echo Image.
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe Echo Image.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know, I just...
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we were going to go to break, but it's only ten minutes left in the show, so I thought actually we'd just go ahead and just kind of skip the break and come back to what we were going to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, one more show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: One more show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I'm sorry, Wednesday nights.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mikey Style, tell us about Wednesday nights.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wednesday nights is the night, you know, you're probably like, hey, it's Wednesday night, it's hump night, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Starting to feel good about the work week, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: So why don't you come on over and tune in at 7 o'clock at Orange Lounge Radio on Live 365 and listen to Outside the Box.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because like the name says, it's quite outside the box.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though we talk a lot about boxes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the main reason why you should listen to the show is because I co-host it with Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, so it's not just Rob all the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because Rob's the queen that always takes over the show, you know, runs it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, please, listen.
[SPEAKER_05]: 7 o'clock, Wednesday nights.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have another guest on the song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and I definitely want to share this one because we're almost out of show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really want someone to get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's an open forum for the rest of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send in your guesses for the rest of the show and hopefully someone gets it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's what Jazz guessed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, don't even.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to get somebody in trouble.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have a guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Flow walk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get a flow walk on mic.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, lay it on me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jazz is guessing nucleus with something smooth.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a cell in the body that does not have a nucleus, and the jelly and cream cheese on the bagel are both smooth.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give you something smooth.
[SPEAKER_26]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_26]: You know, when I said people were onto something, I was not kidding.
[SPEAKER_26]: He is onto it.
[SPEAKER_26]: However, he is only half right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, well, you got ten minutes to figure it out, or else you're going to go another week without knowing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob, I think we should just keep playing Gem and Marble.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nah, just don't even go there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just don't even go there, because you're going to get somebody in trouble.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you're not allowed to talk the rest of the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Give me!
[SPEAKER_08]: Ducky, ducky, ducky, ducky, ducky!
[SPEAKER_18]: Give to Radical.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's do some Ask Orange Lounge, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_04]: What will we find out tonight on Ask Orange Lounge?
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to make a jam and then we're going to get it on and hopefully someone will get that clue right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you say jam?
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_18]: This show's on something after all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Skyblind's open as well, but please don't call if you've already been on this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want other people to have a chance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, I'm just saying that, you know, don't, you know, spread the love.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wonder how jam shots would be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: People are never going to come back to this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to take some questions from our chat room, but I don't see any questions.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ask your question now.
[SPEAKER_18]: Shut up, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear to God I'm going to clock you with this microphone.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, don't clock him.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zachu has a question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Legend of Zachu has a question.
[SPEAKER_04]: How did you spend your summer vacation?
[SPEAKER_18]: At work, answering 40 plus calls in queue from people trying to get student loans to go to school.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's how I spent my summer vacation.
[SPEAKER_18]: Next!
[SPEAKER_06]: At work, supposedly answering calls, but... Eh, supposedly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, um... I added it!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's my own word now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was supposed to be answering calls, but I was browsing the internet instead.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yay, internet!
[SPEAKER_04]: Like many of you, I spent my summer not getting laid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Luckily, summer's over.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm not included in that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was talking to our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, FloWalk, how did you spend your summer vacation?
[SPEAKER_26]: In a room right underneath an air conditioning vent, making step data for...
[SPEAKER_26]: Someone figured it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally, we have a winner.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank God, we get to play the damn song before the night's over.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't say.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, what's the guess, Rob?
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, who got it, first of all?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the winner is White Rob, is the person who got it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not me, I'm a White Rob as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ho, ho, ho.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's very obvious, given your outfit, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm giving him permission to tell our chat room what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, the next thing White Rob says to you guys will be the name of the new song.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, it's about time.
[SPEAKER_04]: So WhiteRob, it's on you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: He does not have Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's on 56k, so he can't Skype him.
[SPEAKER_04]: But WhiteRob figured it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So he just gets to post it in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_26]: By the way, I really like this song.
[SPEAKER_17]: Watch him get booted.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to cue it up so you guys can hear some of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, but he misspelled it.
[SPEAKER_04]: He misspelled it, but he still got it right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Close enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nucleus.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what is it, guys?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's tell the people who are not in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is the song?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody want to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Slow Walk, you should say.
[SPEAKER_26]: The song is by a group called Nucleus back from the mid-80s, and the joint is called Jam On It.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is a very unique song for DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: All I can say is this song is a little bit special for DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only mix of the song I have is 8 minutes in length, so I'm going to only play you guys a clip, because 8 minutes is a long time.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, I'm sure the first, like, minute and a half, two minutes should be good enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm just going to kind of start in the middle here and see what we get.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_25]: If you don't know how, get ready to learn, cause Cosmo's taking his turn to burn Take a seat, and know when to see, then you add M-O-N-E-R-E-E-D-E-D-E-D-E-D-E-D-E-D-E-D-E-D-E-D-E-D-E-D-E-D-E-D-E-D-E-D-E
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't get down, let me rock you to the rhythm of the funky sound From hill to hill above sea to sea And when jam on's rocking everybody scream Jam on it, jam on it, on it, on it, on it While we're feeling like we want to dance on that thing Go on ahead and float it Cause jamming on is what we do best It's what separates us from the rest And if you don't think who's there for real Let me tell you what happened to the man who did it
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that should give you a good idea of what that song sounds like.
[SPEAKER_04]: How many of you guys remember that Blast From The Past song there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully, Dancer X isn't too upset that, you know, somebody got it figured out, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: That is the longest clue that ever went without being figured out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So for that, we give Dancer a big
[SPEAKER_03]: F you, buddy, for making our lives hell.
[SPEAKER_06]: F you, buddy!
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't believe they didn't get it after we played Jam and Marmalade on the jazz in It's Raining Men.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought that would be like... I thought that was completely obvious, too, but I guess people just... People don't think we can have any fun with it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Like I said, you guys did not have to think very abstract.
[SPEAKER_26]: There was a bagel, there was jam on it.
[SPEAKER_26]: and the bagel kind of looked like a nucleus or something.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, don't blame me.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's probably DancerX's lame idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't explain the method to your guys' madness, you know, or to his madness.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our madness is, we give you clues, you suffer.
[SPEAKER_26]: Rinse, repeat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hope you guys enjoyed, and congratulations, WhiteRob, for figuring that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You all owe him sex.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or her.
[SPEAKER_04]: I imagine it's a him, though, because his name's Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: You all owe him sex for getting that right before the end of the show, just under the wire.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'll send him some chocolate instead.
[SPEAKER_18]: Same difference.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'll buy him one of those blow-up pillows from JList.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to say, I'm excited to play that song.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's booty as it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it brings back Solo, everything that was great about Solo.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, I think this is just showing up, like, for Ultramix 2, how eclectic the music really is.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, you heard everything from, like, you know, just sort of, like, you heard trance, you've heard house.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, obviously now you're hearing, like, old school rap, so we're trying to touch as many, yeah, you know, break it.
[SPEAKER_26]: We're just trying to hit as many bases as we can.
[SPEAKER_04]: More to come.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any fun ideas for clues in the future?
[SPEAKER_26]: I don't know, we're still working on what to do next.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, you know what guys, it's time to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate to say it, but the show's about over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for those of you guys that didn't get your Ask Orange Lounge questions in, stay tuned to Afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll get those answered.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, let's start with LankyStyle, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's go to... Oh, I've been drinking a little bit and I feel pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to, I guess, Floatwalk.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get a mic.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_26]: Message over to you, same in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_26]: I got three letters for you, L-O-L.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Sharkscroll, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm feeling very Jerry Springer here.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Angel, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_19]: I got a present from Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the CD?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, the CD.
[SPEAKER_04]: Explicit, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_27]: Can you come back to me on that one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I what?
[SPEAKER_27]: Come back.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn you!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I shake my head, I get dizzy.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's getting drunk, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gypsy Wolf, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whoever's throwing beer bottles at people for waving, keep doing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of entertaining.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought is...
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen to our station a lot and whore up our hours and win an Akira Yamaoka CD.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_18]: My final thought is I want to go on leave and travel, but I want to be paid for it.
[SPEAKER_18]: So pay me to travel.
[SPEAKER_18]: Send me to... What the fuck are you doing with that CD?
[SPEAKER_18]: My final thought is... I want air conditioning!
[SPEAKER_18]: And money.
[SPEAKER_18]: And sex.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to give... Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: In that order?
[SPEAKER_18]: In that order, because air conditioning is more important.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: The final word of tonight's show, I'm going to give it to somebody who didn't say a whole lot tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shark Skrull, you've got to give us one word that sums everything up.
[SPEAKER_04]: The final word of the show.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, my friend Donna will understand this.
[SPEAKER_16]: Beans!
[SPEAKER_28]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_28]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_28]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_28]: And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh my god, Becky, look at her butt.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is so big.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like big butts and I cannot buy.
[SPEAKER_14]: You other brothers can't deny that when a girl walks in with an itty bitty waist and a round thing in your face, you get sprung.
[SPEAKER_14]: But that butt you got makes me so horny Cause I'm long and I'm strong And I'm down to get the friction on So fellas, fellas Has your girlfriend got the butt?
[SPEAKER_14]: Tell her to shake it, shake it Shake that healthy butt Baby got back Baby got back
[SPEAKER_14]: Baby got bad, baby got bad
[SPEAKER_14]: Then turn around, stick it out Even white boys gotta shout Baby got back Baby got back Baby got back Baby got back Little in the middle but you got much back Little in the middle but you got much back
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here's the afterbirth, the part of the show after the credits have faded to black.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta make this quick tonight because I'm going out tonight, but I wanted to get the rest of these Ask Orange Lounge questions in because there were some good ones in here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't think anyone was going to get the jam on it thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I seriously didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two minutes left in the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was my drunkenness and saying I should do jam shots that clued them in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sigurd was going to ask, Dear Ask Orange Lounge, why can't the chat room figure out this easy clue?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you got owned, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Knight says, I got one out of all the drunk shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the record for most drinks in an episode?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe DarkSakura wants to share.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, what are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_18]: The time I had, like, what, ten beverages within an hour?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, you think?
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, the last drunk show that we did, I had four double shots of tequila.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's cheap-ass stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_18]: I had half a bottle of the mudslide mix, the TGR Friday's mudslide.
[SPEAKER_18]: I finished off the rest about that much of a bottle, about maybe three inches worth of a bottle of the Long Island Iced Tea.
[SPEAKER_18]: What else did I have?
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh yeah, and I kept making these screwdrivers out of Malibu.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I kept drinking those too.
[SPEAKER_18]: So I was very drunk, and the thing is, is that where I have really good tolerance,
[SPEAKER_18]: That much alcohol in the span of an hour.
[SPEAKER_18]: I ended up passing out on Rob's bed and eating like half of Matt's box of waffles.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Which I probably still owe you the waffles.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'll get you some waffles.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tonight I had, what was it, five screwdrivers.
[SPEAKER_06]: All of them with two shots of vodka in them.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I guess that'd be ten shots of vodka over the course of three hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right now, really, I don't feel that drunk.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I'm a little dizzy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Over the course of three hours is a lot better than over the course of an hour.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I didn't want to kill myself, but, you know, um, no, right now I just feel very full because that's like a whole thing of orange juice right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that's a lot of orange juice.
[SPEAKER_05]: What I'm worried about, though, Loki, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: What I'm worried about, though, Loki, is you haven't, like, I haven't seen you go to the bathroom in these three hour spans.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're a time bomb waiting to go off, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: You drink that much alcohol and orange juice, something's going to explode, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: My stomach, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, all over the... No, I've never thrown up from alcohol.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not throwing up, I'm talking about something else.
[SPEAKER_05]: You haven't thrown up from the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, what's bathroom really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not into water sports, so take care of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll wake up in the middle of the night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why am I all wet?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got to hurry up through the rest of these questions, you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zaku, will you be playing drunk DDR and or any Bomani tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think most people are going home, and I'm going to the club.
[SPEAKER_04]: Karma Titan says, question number 108.
[SPEAKER_04]: Booga, booga, booga.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay or nay?
[SPEAKER_18]: If you're referring to Booga, Booga...
[SPEAKER_18]: No, I'm not playing any game where I stick a finger up someone's ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it was just Booga Booga Booga.
[SPEAKER_04]: I say yay to Booga Booga Booga.
[SPEAKER_18]: Booga Booga Booga is cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: Booga Booga is not.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is Booga Booga Booga?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shay23, last question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any idea when the 8th style limited edition can be bought?
[SPEAKER_06]: Taking pre-orders on Konami style already.