[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki Tonight, May 27th, 2012, a new Star Wars game is set to be unveiled After weeks of speculation, 38 studios shuts its doors And a major game publisher is sued for fraud
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours to talk about video games, gaming culture, the gamer lifestyle with my co-host here in studio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome back tonight, the one and only DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Boy, you missed a fun show last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I didn't because I was eating a bucket of meat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that is a little better, but we'll talk more about that in a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I was very sad though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I sent you my support from afar as I was eating barbecue chicken.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now for those that don't know what Bucket of Meat is, dot dot dot.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is the Big Thunder Barbecue restaurant at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where it's like 30 bucks a head and you get all you can eat meat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like beef ribs, sausages, chicken, cornbread, coleslaw, beans.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they all come in these big shiny, well not kind of shiny, but big iron buckets.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which a couple people ran off with one Are you a fan of finding big sausages at Disneyland?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yes, oh yes Rob Alright, also say hello joining us tonight to Tech Master Loki That sounds like a southern Brazilian barbecue
[SPEAKER_06]: It kind of does a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Brazilian barbecue is amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cornbread could make it better.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they did have cornbread.
[SPEAKER_08]: But also, the people there on the stage performing did You Got a Friend in Me, all kind of bluegrassy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, how fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to go around and talk about how our weeks were in video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: But first, I want to start off tonight talking about what happened last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the podcasters are sitting here going, wait a minute, Dark Sakura was on the last show.
[SPEAKER_06]: There wasn't a show on the feed last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I also have to say one thing for Geovidea.
[SPEAKER_08]: That place did have vegetarian options.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had a skewer with peppers and vegetables and tofu.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was delicious.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, anyhow, off food, on show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just saying, it's cool that they have vegetarian options, but I mean, it's bucket of meat.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it was bucket of salad, I wouldn't be touching the place.
[SPEAKER_05]: Same if I was a vegetarian and I went to a place that's called bucket of meat, probably wouldn't be my thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, look, last week's show.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, live, we were here last week live, and no, this is not a case of me being lazy and not updating the podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's what happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were live, we were doing a show, and while we were in the middle of the classic Game of the Week segment, which as you know is always at the end of the first half, the power went out.
[SPEAKER_06]: The power shut off in the apartment.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't just my place.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was the whole unit.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was the whole stretch.
[SPEAKER_06]: We still don't know to this tonight what caused the issue.
[SPEAKER_06]: But unfortunately, what happened is that it caused the live listeners got to hear at least half a show.
[SPEAKER_06]: But because we were unable to retrieve the MP3 from backup, which, you know, if you want to get technical, it's not really an MP3.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a raw Adobe Audition file.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it was all wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was too much to be able to fix.
[SPEAKER_06]: And props to Travis from Understation Live.
[SPEAKER_06]: He tried to fix it.
[SPEAKER_06]: He tried to go in and move the little packets that were out of order.
[SPEAKER_06]: But he said after about 10 minutes worth of show, he gave up.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't blame him.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have the patience for that either.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's like trying to knit something.
[SPEAKER_06]: So unfortunately, last week's show is gone.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we want to catch you up a little bit on what you missed last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So last week we were joined here in studio by Flaco Jones, who you might know if you listen to Horde House.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's the number one fan of Horde House, my Warcraft show.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't think he'd been on OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: He certainly had never been on as a host before.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think he'd even been on as a guest in a very long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: He talked a lot about his days working at Konami and some of the stuff he got to beta test.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was a league tester on the Winx games, which I'm really sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the part of the show you guys... Do you still have that raw file?
[SPEAKER_06]: I do, and it's like, that's the part of the show I might have to string together and put on Twitter so you guys can hear it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, you should just send it to me and maybe I'll... Yeah, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's, oh man, that's the part of the show you really have to hear, if anything else.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there's a couple important revelations that came up last week, too, that for the OLR continuity, because believe it or not, this show has a storyline over the past 10 years.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very important you understand one of the discussions we had last week, so we're going to re-have it a little bit here tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I play a lot of Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm very sad when I see you signing on and you're not playing Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I'm playing Mass Effect 3 multiplayer usually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: But here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: As you guys know, a few months ago on the show, we talked about, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: We tried Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: For those of you that are into Minecraft, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: But for us, we don't understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: All hell broke loose when the 360 version came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because for me, it was about, oh, there's a tutorial mode that is explaining the point.
[SPEAKER_06]: This game now has a point.
[SPEAKER_06]: And once I kind of was able to get the basic parts down, and plus it's important to note that the 360 version really simplifies crafting and da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_06]: Once I understood all that, I was like, okay, I'm into this.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Loki, I'm imagining it's a similar thing for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went through part of the tutorial, not even the whole tutorial, just the very basic stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And once I figured out, okay, this is iCraft stuff, this is how you do this, this is what this is for, okay, I'm just going to start my own world and did that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Tacos.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, DarkSakura has yet to try Minecraft on the 360 and she has not been turned yet, but we're working on her.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: If I have to pay for it, probably not.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, here's another important comparison I brought up last week that the podcasty folks didn't get to hear because we realize there's been a lot of slamming on the 360 by the PC fans because it's not as advanced.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's based on an earlier version of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the other big, big, big one I hear is the finite size of the map is only, what, 1024 by 1024, which for me is big enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got enough to work with, but I understand where the PC fans, especially if you're playing a bunch of people on one of those servers, really...
[SPEAKER_06]: Civilization 4, Civilization 5
[SPEAKER_06]: Really quick when you don't have hours and hours and hours to play Civ 5 because Civ 5 can go for hours and hours and hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Civ Rev is a really good way to kind of get a quick fix.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I enjoyed both games and I think that's where I'm at with Minecraft now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because of me getting into the 360 version, Alan has been obsessed with the PC version lately.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, well, I see just like kind of getting ideas.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the first things I did after I built a few things was...
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, what are cool things I could build on the 360 version?
[SPEAKER_05]: So I did a bunch of internet searches on YouTube, well, just YouTube searches and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I just kind of bookmarked a bunch of things that I wanted to make.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so I did that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's a lot of cool mods like Industry Craft and stuff like that that you could build machines that will do mining for you and ridiculous stuff like power drills and batteries and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Piping, and all sorts of crazy stuff But, I mean, it's really cool And I hope they implement
[SPEAKER_06]: within the next week I want to go back and give another game a try that I originally kind of I didn't really diss it on the show but I just kind of gave it a review of I don't get it lol and that's the game Terraria because supposedly that's the 2D Minecraft so now that I get Minecraft I'm going to try Terraria again and I'll let you guys know next week how that goes because that's something else I want to explore oh by the way since we did bring it up Civ 5 is on sale on Steam today for $7.49
[SPEAKER_06]: My friend's been playing it on Xbox.
[SPEAKER_06]: Becky's husband.
[SPEAKER_06]: there is no Civ 5 on Xbox you must be thinking Civilization Revolution which is the game I mentioned a minute ago but I've been watching that and it actually is pretty cool except you know that's totally not my thing just like Minecraft 360 it's a good way to get your feet wet with the series other things you might have missed last week we had an exclusive story but we're going to repeat that at the top of tonight's show so we'll come back to that in a minute
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys missed a lot last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there was also the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just for housekeeping purposes, we decided because Jim was not able to finish his Classic Game of the Week, we're not going to have that officially be the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are going to invite him back on the show whenever he wants to come back as a fourth host even and let him finish what he started.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie said she would kindly give over the Classic Game of the Week segment whatever week he comes back so he can finish what he started that night.
[SPEAKER_06]: So just, and if you didn't, if you don't know what the classic game is, well, I have to leave some suspense.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you'll just have to figure it out in a later week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that was about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that was all the stuff that came up last week that was important and worth mentioning.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's get into how is your gaming, oh, VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say really quickly about VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: Friday night, 7 o'clock Pacific, 10 o'clock Eastern.
[SPEAKER_06]: The next phase of VOG will be revealed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I'm teasing a teaser, but I think if you guys are really interested in what we're up to and what the full vision is here, and I know there's a lot of people out there who still have questions like, why did you leave where you were at before just to do yet another radio network?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's more to it than a radio network, and some of that is going to be unveiled soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: on Friday.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm really excited about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So again, Friday, 7 Pacific, 10 Eastern, right here at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're supposed to have an interview at 6.30 tonight, and I teased that on the Twitter a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Her name is Susan.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's with the website hackedonexbox.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we're going to talk a little bit about what... She's basically the Nancy Drew of the gaming industry this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I say that with love.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Nancy Drew.
[SPEAKER_06]: but she really got down to the bottom of what is really going on on Xbox 360 with what they're not calling Xbox hackings but Xbox jackings and we'll talk a little bit about the difference and why that is hopefully we get her on the show here in 10 minutes unfortunately just we don't see her it's kind of like that interview we had two weeks ago where the dude disappeared for a little bit
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't heard from her on Twitter or Skype today these things happen especially because her piece got picked up by a lot of the big gaming blogs she might just be very popular and in demand right now so we're gonna see if we can't get her on if we can't we'll just roll it over to a later week when she can come on but we'll check in with you guys in 10 minutes
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, you've been out for a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: How was your gaming weeks?
[SPEAKER_08]: I've actually played stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Played lots of things.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although I still haven't played Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm very sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played a lot of Portal 2 while I was out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been playing Words with Friends because I figure since I already paid for it, Zynga already got my damn money.
[SPEAKER_08]: And honestly, while I'm at work, it's kind of something I can keep up with Dan.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I've been keeping up with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did try to play Draw Something, but I'm using the free version just because I want to see what all the fuss is about.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I started playing a lot more Fractal.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, if you look on my Facebook fan page for Jamie Summers, hint, hint,
[SPEAKER_08]: I posted a screencap of what Fractal looks like.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm going to be actually showcasing a different game on Steam that I'm playing.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that everyone can see what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to be starting Fallout New Vegas again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just starting over from scratch.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm playing Droplets.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got Droplets on iPhone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which is kind of weird and not as fun as playing it on Steam.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I played some WoW.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I've really been playing Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played a crap ton of it last night.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I was like you know what this is like playing Ragnarok online without people this is great so I've really been getting into Diablo and because it was free because I signed over the blood pact it was free with a big footnote yeah well as you saw what you know when I told my friend on Facebook that it was free he said great how Dan said she signed her life away for a year for a year
[SPEAKER_08]: Which, you know, is what?
[SPEAKER_08]: A third over?
[SPEAKER_08]: So, it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, I think everyone's playing Diablo because I'll log on to WoW and say, Hey, where's all my peeps at?
[SPEAKER_08]: And they're all on Diablo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I've been playing some more Puzzle Bobble again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bust a Move.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I really love that game and it's really great to play when...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what it is, but when I'm sick, and I'm over my cold, guys, I just sound like I'm on the tail of it, but I slept for two days.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was glorious.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was really sick two weeks ago, you might remember, and I'm still coughing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm still having coughing fits.
[SPEAKER_08]: People at my work.
[SPEAKER_08]: And see, I had that sinus attack, and then I had it bad at Disneyland, and then I came back to a full-blown cold.
[SPEAKER_08]: I ran a fever.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I just remembered?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have coffee brewing in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, you do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, so when I'm sick, it's like I don't really have this mental focus.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, I think when my brain shuts down, I become really fantastic at puzzle games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that was like clearing out levels on Fractal that I had never been able to pass before.
[SPEAKER_08]: And for anyone, it's not an easy game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It really is not very easy because you've got so much to keep in mind with the direction of how your little things move.
[SPEAKER_08]: I still tell everyone, get Fractal.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is worth the money.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is such a fun game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, it's called Fractal.
[SPEAKER_08]: Make blooms, not war.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I hope that they pay me for my sponsorship because I am doing that for free.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I'm also supposed to be sitting down because our friend loaned us the Street Fighter Cross Tekken.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm kind of afraid to try it because I do not want to play against the Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, meh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you play anything other than Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_05]: I play Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: He built the Deep Run Tran.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, he did.
[SPEAKER_06]: So when we are talking that Loki started playing Minecraft, we're not fucking around.
[SPEAKER_06]: He is really into Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what's great is when I go into Loki's world, I can hear Nelly laughing in the background whenever something stupid happens.
[SPEAKER_06]: So she's got to be into this a little bit too, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: She's not into it at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: She keeps asking me, aren't you sick of this game yet?
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the point of this game?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm just like, there is no point.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just like Legos.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Legos for men!
[SPEAKER_05]: And girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have been playing Minecraft more than Call of Duty this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did play Call of Duty, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: We finally got to check out the new... Well, they're maps technically for the new game type face-off.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, you can use them for anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we've been playing on them for just our deathmatch maps since we only have like two to four people usually playing at a time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, three to four people, but
[SPEAKER_05]: It's perfect for what we use it for, so we've been actually enjoying those quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, one of the new maps, Ground, it's quite apparent that the spawn points in there aren't that random.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was one time I literally killed somebody and they spawned again right in front of me, so I knifed them to death and then they spawned again right in the next room.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, wow, that's pretty close.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see other things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let's go back to Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the first thing I did in Minecraft this week is I explored the whole map or as much of the map as I could because I was looking for a spot to dig with dynamite.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's what I did because I duped a bunch of dynamite and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: We also made a portal to the nether and went there and I got my glowstone and I don't remember what it's called.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the dirt that's all in the ender that you can set on fire and that will burn forever.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: and there's some other like sand soul sand or something that makes people walk slow I don't really know what the point would that be for um
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: and I'm slowly hollowing it out for I don't know what purpose.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just doing it right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should fill it with candy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have candy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't fill it with candy yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why Minecraft isn't a 10.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's only about a 9.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should fill it with whatever those things that try to kill you are.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no coffee and there's no candy.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there are... Well, see, you're Jewish.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fill it with sheep.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say there are pork chops, which is pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yes, there is cake.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fill it with cake.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fill it with cake and sheep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, throw sheep down the hole.
[SPEAKER_05]: You apparently can.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, I don't know if you've noticed, if you pick up an egg... Have you tried throwing an egg?
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll create a chicken.
[SPEAKER_06]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, are you talking about an automated death machine for chickens?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I've actually thought of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing is safe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I've thought of that for the pigs, and I actually built a trap to catch the pigs, but it doesn't seem to work too well because when you sleep or whatever, the animals respawn and they don't stay in the pen that I made, which is kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: and then I tried putting a glass top ceiling in one of the caves under the ocean and I kept drowning myself when I did that so I said, eh, fuck that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not doing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, at least.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's what I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also played the Pocket Edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pocket Edition's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: More Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: My Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't play a lot of new stuff, mostly because I've been content playing Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mass Effect 3 has got a big multiplayer thing going on this weekend, and I don't know what made me think I would even remotely possibly hit that goal of promoting three people during the weekend, but, you know, I've
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought an iPad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I bought one of the new iPads and, you know, I wanted one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm really not going to give you any better reason than that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm in a slightly different position at work now where I might be doing some more travel-oriented things again and I thought the iPad would come in very handy for that because my laptop is kind of getting a little bit old and there is some stuff you can do with an iPad and some of that does include remote taping and broadcasting a podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've thought of that too.
[SPEAKER_06]: But in the meantime, before I get to all that busy, busy work stuff, I'm doing fun stuff on the iPad, like playing games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And one of the games that I got addicted to is Temple Run.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's one of those games that's really stupidly simple in design.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like the game itself could have been on the Atari 2600 for all I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like you swipe up to jump, you swipe down to slide, left and right to go left and right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the whole kitsch of the game is you're running fast to escape these monkeys that if they catch you, they're going to eat you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I guess you took their treasure or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's so, so, so simple and so stupid, yet it is so addicting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't stop playing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, Temple Run is what I've been playing a lot on my iPad.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's like the iPad go-to game right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the screen's really pretty, you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were watching Archer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, it's pretty for a cartoon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't shake your head at me.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's you judging me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can hear you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that was pretty much my week.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: So a little bit of housekeeping and then we're going to get into some news and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to mention...
[SPEAKER_06]: Dark Tetsuya Ready Player One
[SPEAKER_06]: and he ran this whole virtual contest where people had to like play and joust and find the hidden easter egg screen and adventure and just you know cute fun stuff you know there's there was no point no seriousness just let's have fun on the internet and that's really what it was and it has a winner so I want to congratulate Orange Right won the hunt this week so yay Orange Right you win
[SPEAKER_06]: Something.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to send Orange Wright something from OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will find a... Get his address later.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lock of my hair.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know he... Do you mean that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I'll go... All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to send Orange Wright a lock of DarkSakura's hair and something else actually useful from OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I know what we can send him.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some cat litter.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're not sending him cat litter.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's useful.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can use cat litter for a whole bunch of stuff, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know if you spill oil, if oil drips from your car, you can put cat litter on it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we have posters over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, just stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, we could send him a post.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, posters are kind of a bitch to mail.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was thinking we have a bunch of these little guys here, so I'll send him one of these.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, I know he's a Bomani fan, and in the other room I have literally stacks and stacks of promo CDs we were going to give away at live events we never did.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm just going to put a bunch of those in a box and be all like, LOL, have fun, and I think he'll get a kick out of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Second place, you get nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tough life lesson learned.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: The other housekeeping thing I wanted to mention was that we will not be here live next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am going to be at Bucket of Meat or Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I have to make the most out of my past because the prices just went up and there's no way I'm renewing at the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_06]: so I am going this next week so there will be no live show we are going to try to pre-tape a show earlier in the week we just have to find something that blends with all of our schedules so I'm sorry live listeners you won't have anything here but think of it as fair because last week you got a show that the podcasters never heard so next week you're going to have to get the podcast show just like a lot of other people do so that's next week's show
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's it I have for housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, the other thing I have for housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were supposed to be having an interview right now with Susan from hackedonexbox.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, she's not online.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is almost exactly what happened with MegaRan a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is it about our show?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are we scary?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I was looking at her personal Twitter, and it said something about, I got two hours of sleep last night.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was yesterday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was today.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to use this interview to talk about something that's been going on in the news this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, hopefully you can talk about it instead since Susan's not here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: But apparently there was some stuff going on with the whole we think we know how some accounts are getting stolen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so basically Susan had actually put together an article on her website talking about how she kind of figured out how some of this is going now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now I'm not sure how she came about the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm assuming just web searches because doing the same similar type of web search was able to pull up the same information.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkDeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: and it doesn't matter what sort of safe you know any sort of passwords questions whatever it doesn't matter because they find a way to get that information from Microsoft or the third party companies representing Microsoft customer service or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, they basically, there was this, it was on, I'm trying to remember which website it was now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I know Kotaku picked it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then it was originally hacked on Xbox.com and then Kotaku picked it up, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's where it really kind of blew up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: But basically, the one of the websites, I can't remember what the original website that had this step-by-step information was.
[SPEAKER_05]: GameTagJackers
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: So basically, they talk about the strategy to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: First, you go to Xbox.com, you click support, and basically at the bottom of the page, there's a contact us stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: On that page, you click the email us link, and then Xbox Live, and then you basically, at that point, they impersonate an employee of Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they put, you know, an email address at Microsoft.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: They put the agent's name, somebody that they, I guess, talk to.
[SPEAKER_05]: They could, you know, call up customer service and, hi, blah, blah, blah, my name is blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: They write it down, you know, and they go through this web form.
[SPEAKER_05]: You put the customer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, you fill out a little note to them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Customer, and you put the name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Verify the 16-digit credit card number.
[SPEAKER_05]: He has made an inquiry about how he has forgotten his account's information.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since I am a Tier 1 agent, I am unable to view the customer's gamer tag.
[SPEAKER_05]: He has requested to have an answer changed to... And then you put some realistic answer, I guess, for the question.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Xbox Live Gamertag is... And you put the Gamertag down.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the person's name is supposedly contacting them that you're spoofing.
[SPEAKER_06]: So basically, they're working it by... Because Microsoft is so big...
[SPEAKER_06]: and there's so many departments that don't talk to each other essentially they're impersonating department to department they're impersonating the many branches of Microsoft in order to get your gamer tag and there ain't shit you can do about it except don't put a credit card on Xbox
[SPEAKER_05]: There's really nothing you can do about it because they're literally going and finding the answers to the questions that you put down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even if you put down which city were you born in and you put down Abraham Lincoln or something like that, they can still get the answer to it and they're basically changing it to whatever they want.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, now, unfortunately, you know, one of the things I wanted to ask Susan tonight from hackedonexbox.com, and I gotta hand it to the chatters at, uh, vognetwork.com, ssh100matt says, even the best show hosts get cancelled on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Carson Letterman have been cancelled on, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: And WhatUpG says, when the interview comes on, it should be good even late.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I agree.
[SPEAKER_06]: And hopefully, maybe she forgot it was Memorial Day weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, uh, we'll hopefully get her on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, there's always another time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, one thing I want to ask her about was that apparently Microsoft responded via Kotaku to her report.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you see that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I did see that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where they basically said, well, you can't do this anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really see... They're basically, you know... Well, they're trying... I thought it was irritating because they really tried to poo-poo her story.
[SPEAKER_06]: and it it kind of pissed me off because it's kind of like well you never Microsoft you never acknowledged that this was happening and now you're trying to poo-poo it like well you can't do it anymore and I understand that Microsoft certainly to save their image doesn't want to admit that they had a problem but at the same time being that they are I mean they are on the stock market yes they're a publicly traded company right yeah isn't there some sort of responsibility that they should be reporting this shit's happening
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and they basically said, hey, here's what their Microsoft or Kotaku asked for a comment from them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Their response was, there are several different methods malicious users employ to gain unauthorized access to accounts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Social engineering is one of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are aware of vulnerabilities that social engineering pose and continue to address these through tools and training to help our members keep our members safe and secure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, right there, that sounds like tools and training.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're members.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sounds like us.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're teaching us how to not be social engineered, which...
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool, but that doesn't really seem to apply to us because we're not the ones being contacted by these people.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's your customer service reps.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's another thing I really wanted to get into.
[SPEAKER_06]: As much as I respect what Susan's done this week and what she's been able to find out and put out what needed to be out there on the internet, she put out what people needed to hear this week, and I so respect her for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it is the sole reason this stuff is happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I'm having a hard time remembering when I was hacked.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it was about six months ago at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: I seem to recall my password was never changed, which would tell me that this didn't happen to me because they're resetting your password in this, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: and then obviously they're not going to get a response because they're not at that email.
[SPEAKER_05]: You call up Xbox 30 minutes later and after the answer you say that you got disconnected from a Tier 2 agent and asked to be transferred back.
[SPEAKER_05]: After they transfer you to a Tier 2 agent, you give them the number, the one that you wrote, the one that I guess your customer... Once they pull it up, say...
[SPEAKER_05]: they'll say it'll take a little while to change it call back say you forgot your email but you know what the security question or the secret question answer is and they will ask for your gamertag and answer them and they will give you the email so now so I guess let's see here
[SPEAKER_05]: so basically now you have their email and I guess their security question I'm not really sure how I guess I don't know if that allows you to change it immediately I thought they would send you a
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I just want to deny, deny, deny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just like I want to deny that I couldn't have been phished either.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'm just being a little hard-headed, but I kind of think, why would someone want my account?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, granted, maybe, although I don't think I have much of a public face, I have a public face thanks to this podcast nonetheless, so maybe some a-hole out there wanted it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why they used it to play FIFA 13
[SPEAKER_06]: which I don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think I have a name people want.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so it's not necessarily that or sometimes accounts get hacked because you're a member of live for X number of years.
[SPEAKER_06]: That could be.
[SPEAKER_05]: That I would agree.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why someone would want to account for that but
[SPEAKER_06]: I have friends who were hacked that hadn't touched their Xbox in years.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not clicking for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: They could just probably find random people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe just try it on one or another.
[SPEAKER_08]: Perhaps it's given the amount of time it's gone since it's been used, it makes it an easy target because it's someone less likely to check.
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel like this story has blown a hole in it, but it hasn't still yet shown us everything that's going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me quickly go to the chatroom because there's some good comments here from the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Morpheus from Understation Live Saturday nights here on VOG says, Has anyone considered the possibility if there is inside help within the Xbox call centers for the Jackers?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a scary thought, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not unheard of.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is not unheard of.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, here's an example.
[SPEAKER_08]: When I worked for the mortgage servicer I used to work for, one of our clients had a bunch of information stolen by one of their employees stealing a laptop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it had something like, I want to say, 3,000 bank account information.
[SPEAKER_08]: New bank accounts.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: It happens within companies.
[SPEAKER_06]: It does, it does.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I work in the insurance industry and there's laws set in place to prosecute people who use the information that they find in malicious ways.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, imagine if you could access a celebrity's medical records, the things that might happen there, you know, but there's laws in place to protect everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like with my job now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I run into the same thing, you know, with inspections.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me read this comment from Actdeft in our chatroom as well because I like this too at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft says, let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_06]: PlayStation Network handled their hacking issue horribly, but they handled it nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_06]: Steam handled their forums being hacked really well and kept the users informed and users of what was happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: Microsoft handling the Xbox livejackings is non-existent which is worse of what Sony did and DJ Morpheus added to that remember this is Microsoft they never admit issues until necessary look at Vista and how it was a disaster and Actdeft said yeah pretty much what I'm saying Microsoft denying the whole issue is worse than what Sony did and we're talking that Sony didn't handle the problem that well to begin with
[SPEAKER_06]: and I've said this for months now as much as we give Sony shit and yes they do deserve quite a bit of shit over what happened and you know kind of how they made themselves a target and everything although we give them shit at least they said what was going on and they did take their network down when it was a problem and you know most of all they never had money actually stolen
[SPEAKER_06]: yet here we are on Xbox this much later and we're still hearing stories about how it's done.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you go to that website, hackedonexbox.com, it is still happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have not changed your password on Xbox Live in the past six months, you are a fool to not do it now.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you do not change your password on Xbox Live, if you have sat through all of these stories and have still not changed your Xbox Live password, you are a fool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I wish you the best of luck Now that I've berated everybody Hopefully that wasn't anybody actually listening Oh gee, I should go change my password right now I forgive you if it's the first time you've ever heard me ranting Maybe you didn't think to change it before But if you've been sitting here for the past six months And you still haven't changed it You're just asking for it I've done mine twice since then Because I routinely change my passwords every three months
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's the weird thing, too, and this actually just came up in the past week and a half.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got an email, or I tried to log in to Xbox.com or something, and it made me change my password, but it wasn't a reset or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was some type of, somebody's been trying to log into your account too many times, you better change your password.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so that made me, you know, the first thing I went to, my bank account, to make sure no more money had been stolen or any of that crap is going on, but I looked in the game history, have they been in there, been able to play anything?
[SPEAKER_06]: Thankfully, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: No one actually got in there, but it made me go, they're still fucking trying.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, it was hackforums.net is where this stuff originated from.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have the whole Priv 7, how to jack any Xbox account.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's where all that information was from on her website.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm hoping we can get her on here to tell us more about the story about how she found it and kind of her opinions really having heard so many of these stories on what Microsoft should do.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we'll have to get that in a later week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Death Rising 3 Death Rising 3
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, hey, so by the way, man, tell your friend who liked this post that I'm the new face of Dead Rising 3, lol.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw he works for video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: The trailer should be coming out soon in the next month or two.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: They sent me to this place called MOVA in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_05]: Insane technology.
[SPEAKER_05]: They did Benjamin Button.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looks so real.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll post it on here when they give it to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just real quick, are you sure the name's not Jorge?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, it's Jorge.
[SPEAKER_05]: Auto Mechanic, LA, Illegal Immigrant, Aliens, Controversy
[SPEAKER_06]: Dead Rising 3
[SPEAKER_05]: For sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll probably be one of, like, Xbox or PlayStation's things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: No Frank West or the other guy?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, of course not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Until DLC.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, Frank West, you know, the whole Dead Rising 2 off the record bombed, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, because I think a lot of people kind of saw it as a... I think a lot of people saw it for what it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a cheap attempt to try and get Dead Rising 2 more popularity when it just should have been there to begin with.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think people are starting to call Capcom out on a lot of this shit, and it's kind of fun to watch.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like watching a soap opera.
[SPEAKER_05]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, hey, just like, you know, all the on-disc DLC for Street Fighter X, Tekken, and Dragon Dog, Dragon's Dogma.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's talk Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet Loki will be excited about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet you never thought this would be something happening on OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Minecraft segment.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, we used to talk about Minecraft updates all the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have you now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, this is some serious Minecraft news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Xbox Live Arcade, what game is being played the most online?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's still Modern Warfare 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Minecraft has now edged out Call of Duty Black Ops for the number two spot.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I guess the next update for Minecraft is going to be 1.7.3, which will add pistons into the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the next thing that Xbox is slated to get.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at some point, 1.8, which was the adventure update on the PC, that will be coming to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: The quote from 4J Studios, they're the ones who ported the game for Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game isn't Minecraft on the Xbox, it's Minecraft Xbox 360 Edition, so it isn't really a direct port of the PC game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of them trying to weave these tangled words of, we didn't promise you everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I imagine there'll still be a casual mode that won't have that element in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Minecraft, sales figures, 6 million sold on the PC, 9 million across all platforms when you factor in Xbox, Android, and iOS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe 9.2 million.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's according to Daniel Kaplan with Mojang.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a lot, especially considering I don't think the iOS and... I can't imagine those sold a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I don't think in the millions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe a million a pop.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the Xbox One's probably sold at least a million and a half at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: So... Well, they said they were profitable within 10 hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is... This is the type of thing they're going to look back on in 10 years and be all like, hey, remember in the 2010s when people played Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just like we kind of look back and go...
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, remember the pet rock?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I think it'll be that whole thing where it's still... I just have a feeling that Lego is just kicking themselves going, Damn it, we could have done something like this.
[SPEAKER_05]: We could have so done something like this.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to see this on VH1 in 10 years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Michael Ian Black commenting on VH1's I Love the 10s.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do we even do that anymore?
[SPEAKER_06]: I Love the 10s.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember when we used to have this show?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do countdowns of decades and stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: And it just stopped.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what's going on in Minecraft world.
[SPEAKER_06]: So DarkSakura, if you want to talk about a different game, now would be a good chance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I said if people want me to play the damn game, they need to buy it for me on PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: You think you live in a world where that will happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that means I don't have to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't even try to get out of it like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can download the classic version completely free on their website.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I tried to tell her.
[SPEAKER_08]: Star Wars Star Wars
[SPEAKER_08]: There's going to be a new Star Wars franchise unveiled next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's a bold vision.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we don't know what the crap it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's going to be on GTTV.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, good.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_08]: What it was said, though, is that it actually had a pretty high caliber team on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's going to be very bold.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very bold.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I mean, hopefully it's going to be better than the MMO because the MMO was losing people and it really wasn't all that great that I saw.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not impressed by it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Except I do kind of like the alignment change thing, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's really about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be a new Battlefront series, and that sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: You think?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be worth it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just going to call it something different.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about a return to the Super Nintendo-style side-scroller games?
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be rad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that would be cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, a lot of times when I think about LucasArts, I think about the point-and-click adventure games from back in the day, like Loom and Indiana Jones and shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: So how about a fucking, like, you know, hey, Telltale's kind of made that industry cool again with the whole Walking Dead's doing very well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since they're already stealing from Blizzard, why don't they just keep doing it and do like a Diablo style?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, point like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since they're already, I'm sorry, borrowing from Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am with Dark Tetsuya in our chatroom at VOGnetwork.com as long as it's not Han Solo's dance party for the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what Han Solo's dance party would be?
[SPEAKER_08]: Him shooting people.
[SPEAKER_08]: The end.
[SPEAKER_05]: God, I just hope they don't make a sequel to that game because it was terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: It probably sold okay, but man, it was a terrible game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of terrible, there's been some terrible things going on at 38 Studios and Big Huge Games.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've laid off their entire staff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wasn't there a tweet that something like they had sold 1.2 million or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or was that like shipped versus sold in that whole clever math that we see in the gaming industry?
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, I don't know when that update was, but it sold well under 3 million units, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that stuff takes time, but not enough time to repay their debts.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's just there was a whole bunch of just...
[SPEAKER_05]: Terrible stuff going on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was reading things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, 1.22 million units in the first 90 days is what they said.
[SPEAKER_05]: But also, like, I heard stuff where some of the employees that were relocated to work for this company.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, by the way, you know that house that we bought for you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we never paid for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We took a second mortgage out on your home just so you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have another mortgage now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that kind of stuff can really fuck your credit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that's the really sad thing about this, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hooray to the gaming industry for at least trying to... Because usually you think of the gaming industry and you think of the people on Xbox Live, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also, I mean, considering that there was almost...
[SPEAKER_05]: 380 employees at 38 studios so they you know people on Twitter have been kind of rallying to you know with 38 the hashtag 38 jobs also Facebook group 38 jobs and they've got you know people including like Alex Rubens you know game journalist and he's been you know collecting like stuff into a Google Doc with all these different studios with openings and stuff and
[SPEAKER_06]: and there's also job fairs going on in their area and they're kind of letting these people know he might be a listener of the show because him and I have followed each other on Twitter for a while and so I actually kind of saw his tweets about that when he was putting it together his whole Google Docs thing and I thought that was a really cool idea so props to him I'm glad you're getting your especially because I know he's an aspiring game journalist this is a good thing you know good begets good you know what I mean so good for him
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a clever retort Okay, what is your retort, young lady?
[SPEAKER_08]: The douches keep girl bits clean, so how is that bad?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, look, whatever he is, he's apparently not the best businessman in the world.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can certainly say that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, what about the repercussions that are being felt for the fact that his name basically got a state to believe in his company enough to give them this huge loan that now they're going to have to eat?
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_06]: DungeonBuster in our chatroom says, Amalur wasn't that bad of a game, but the timing for its release couldn't get out from Skyrim Shadow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which, I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of people had already burned through Skyrim by the time it had come out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't blame Skyrim, because it was a few months after Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would blame Mass Effect 3, because it came out literally like three weeks before Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not even that, but maybe it's just me and the fact that I don't watch a lot of TV or when I do, I watch it without commercials.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hadn't really heard a lot about this game, which, you know, considering I do this show, you'd think... To be honest, it's the first I've ever heard of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe that's a problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it is a problem considering it's EA the one publishing it and they usually pimp the shit out of their games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I heard about it and stuff and I saw, you know, they had a demo and...
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't really see any TV advertisement for it, but then again, I don't watch a lot of TV, so it's possible that they had stuff for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's not like Madden or something, they'd spend a lot of money on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Phantasm, our chatroom says, Reckoning had a bad release window with Skyrim and Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it possible that the game just released at a bad time?
[SPEAKER_05]: Once again, I'm not going to blame Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_05]: Skyrim was two months before it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It could contribute, but I think there might be other factors.
[SPEAKER_06]: What about just the fact that maybe the month it released usually isn't a big month for games, especially maybe they should have held it off until summer because those first few weeks really do make or break your game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I'm going to blame?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to blame the fucking online pass because it was a game that had an online pass.
[SPEAKER_05]: They literally called it an online pass for a game that had no online component.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had no online component, but the online pass, they literally called it an online pass, was just bonus DLC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that didn't help.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: Just call it bonus DLC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then if you don't buy it at launch, you don't get the bonus DLC.
[SPEAKER_05]: And all you can do is go, well, damn, I should have bought the game at launch.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I don't see how that's a bad thing at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Instead, you're calling an online pass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you've got to pay this extra money to get...
[SPEAKER_06]: Get online and download this extra DLC I don't really know what the spin was on that Alright, well continuing with things that might drive the gaming industry further into a hole You've got to hear about this patent that was discovered this week Sony Computer Entertainment America, or SCEA
[SPEAKER_06]: Filed for this patent in 2011.
[SPEAKER_06]: It usually takes a little time for these patents to be found.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yes, it's an older patent, but it's just being found now.
[SPEAKER_06]: The patent was for an advertising system where a game will be suspended during play for an advertisement to come up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then the game will continue.
[SPEAKER_06]: Think of it like how TV commercials interrupt your show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hulu.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or Hulu.
[SPEAKER_06]: Adds would be preceded by a warning and a slowdown of gameplay, with another warning displayed when gameplay is about to resume.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's kind of like, ad incoming, everything slowed down.
[SPEAKER_06]: Movie sign!
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye, Pepsi!
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, let's get back into the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, seriously, that reminds me of Mr. Sensei with the movie sign.
[SPEAKER_06]: um now just because they filed the patent doesn't mean it will be implemented it's just you know again patents are to kind of protect ideas or what have you which is weird because i thought i i thought ios games did this shit already doesn't word with friends kind of do something like this where you play and then you get mad if you have the um free version yeah if you i i i have the paid version of words with friends that never does that crap to me
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, would this be terrible if it was to support free full console games?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, for example, ad-supported stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: Say I want to get LittleBigPlanet 2 and I get an ad-supported version that stops gameplay once in a while to pimp me Pepsi or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: I would probably, I'd probably just want to buy the regular game, which is what they want you to do in the first place, but they can make more ad revenue.
[SPEAKER_05]: If this shit pops up in a fucking retail game, I'm not fucking buying that.
[SPEAKER_06]: This was in Wipeout as well, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorta?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it didn't really pause gameplay, but it was in like the loading screens.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's one thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: If they have it as something that's not going to be obtrusive.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it's not going to interrupt your gameplay, I don't so much have a problem with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm cool with the billboards in racing games.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think that if they're doing this as a way to bring in more revenue, they need to decrease the price of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, Brad from PodCulture is in our chat room and says, don't effing get me started on patents.
[SPEAKER_06]: Had my phone delayed in customs a week or so ago because of a BS Apple patent.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, a lot of folks are saying the patent industry in this country is really screwed up right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's a lot of just offensive and defensive maneuvers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember when Twitter came out and said, we have all of these patents.
[SPEAKER_06]: They actually put out a press release that said, we have acquired all these patents and we only plan to use them defensively.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like it's a fucking game of chess.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what the patent industry in this country has become.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, maybe Sony is not even going to do anything with this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just we just want to defend ourselves against when somebody tries to call us on it or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: And to throw my political two cents into it, this is what happens when you allow certain businesses to go deregulated.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Morpheus is in our chat room and gives us an example of what could come to a PlayStation game near you.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll return you to your blood carnage marathon game after this message from some feminine yeast infection product.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be freaking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, that I could support just for the comic value alone because I'd want to see reaction videos to that on the interwebs.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'd be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, maybe this is related news, but Sony Online Entertainment, or SOE, has announced a free-to-play game called Bullet Run.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a revamped game from Acony Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Head1 or Headin was the game with a new title?
[SPEAKER_06]: H-E-D-O-N-E.
[SPEAKER_06]: Head1?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I had one.
[SPEAKER_06]: known for such games as APB and Battleforge meaning they haven't had a lot of luck so far but maybe this will be it and maybe this will make Sony money because oh I'm about to score a headshot on my opponent and have you tried Summer's Eve speaking of douches it'd be funnier it's just relative to the conversation yes it'd be funnier if it was in Max Payne 3 bullet time advertisement
[SPEAKER_05]: Bullet time over Advertisement gone
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw in our chatroom says, You know those ads that appear in billboards in games and such?
[SPEAKER_06]: They actually find ways to block those ads from loading in games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know that ad that pops up on the Xbox Live dashboard?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a little tweak you can make that blocks it so it doesn't load.
[SPEAKER_06]: I seem to remember reading something about that once where it's like on your router, you block a certain domain or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: You never have to see that shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, you redirect certain IPs to your local domain so that it doesn't load those things up.
[SPEAKER_05]: um but yeah i mean you could do that it would it depends but you'd all you would be you'd be interrupted with a blank screen instead you know what my favorite way of getting rid of ads is i'm not giving a fuck ignore it how about that don't give a fuck
[SPEAKER_05]: or just don't, I mean, this is the age of the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're gonna know when there's gonna be some sort of software out there that has ads in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's gonna be on fucking blogs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, can you imagine this next God of War game has fucking ads for like, you know, Subway in the middle of the damn game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you out of fucks to give?
[SPEAKER_06]: Try new Folgers Instant Coffee.
[SPEAKER_06]: It will perk you right back up.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll have plenty of fucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is my thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it's free or a very inexpensive service, I don't really care if there's ads.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it keeps the cost low or free, fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then offer a paid option if you don't want to see the ads.
[SPEAKER_08]: That, I think, is fair.
[SPEAKER_08]: But when you've already paid the money for the game, and then you have your game interrupted, that's a little too far.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's that and the microtransaction stuff, the Facebook-style game in your $60 game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That shit pisses me the fuck off.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to keep doing it because they can charge $60 for a game and someone's going to pay for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they charge $20 for the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why there's going to be another video game industry crash.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: If they paid, now if they charged $20 for a game and then had, I refuse to use the word, had individual transactions within the game, that I could understand a little bit more because then you're paying for the cost of development, you're paying for the cost of advertising, and you're paying for the shipping.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you're a supporter of Ridge Racer for the Vita, which was basically a $30 game that came with nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was basically a six, six, no, I'm sorry, six cars, three tracks.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game can ask my D.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I paid two bucks for Best Move, and I paid for all the maps, all the puzzles.
[SPEAKER_08]: I ended up spending six bucks on that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but two versus 30 is a huge difference.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm saying as an example.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, going to a couple more comments from chat and then we'll move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: ShadowNextGen in our chatroom at VOGnetwork.com says, Too much effort for something that really doesn't mean anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I believe that's in regards to blocking the ads.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sepwin says, I don't have a problem with ads when they fit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like ads in a sports game that look like the ads you see at a real game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, believe it or not, I don't...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't give a shit about those at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: It kind of adds to the experience, really.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes it more realistic.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it really does.
[SPEAKER_06]: YouTube ads, however.
[SPEAKER_06]: Infanel says, stupid ads like on Xbox Dashboard make me want to avoid that product or service.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's what you do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if I go that far with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's what you do, ad people.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is pure ad genius right here.
[SPEAKER_05]: You make a fighting game a la Smash Brothers or Sony mascot Battle Royale, whatever they're calling it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, and you just make it with the mascots from those advertisements.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's one big ad that actually fits within the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: But there were whole games around, um, mascots.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember, like, the Yo!
[SPEAKER_05]: Noid and Cool Spot and... Exactly, and I'm saying... Oh, yeah, Mick Kids.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Those Burger King games were one of the best things I've seen, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, although the games were stupid, I mean, just the fact that they even made them is quite astounding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, quickly, I want to read this comment from chat, and then we need to move on for time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blender in our chatroom says, I bought a Subway sandwich for the Uncharted 3 freebies.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta say, that was a really good promotion, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I bought a Subway sandwich for those Uncharted 3 freebies as well, and they didn't give up to me!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but that's your individual Subway's fault.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been, like, multiple Subways for the, I've been getting, like, the large, you know, they're all, yeah, buy a large drink and you get code for some Battleship thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have yet to get a fucking code in, like, five different Subways.
[SPEAKER_05]: A Battleship thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's, like, for money.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's tying in with the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is a fail.
[SPEAKER_05]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because they're sub-sandwiches.
[SPEAKER_05]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_05]: You figured it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw the best article on Oh No They Didn't, which is one of my favorite websites on the entire internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was an article that was just, here is the complete bits of dialogue that Rihanna had in the movie Battleship.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, it was just, it was great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Video game news.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about something that's actually cool?
[SPEAKER_06]: Less Battleship, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about some Kojima news?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's been some artwork revealed for a particular game that I know a lot of people are super excited about.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what that is?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: A new zone of the Enders.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Enders project is in an experimental phase and he's trying to develop the game using the Fox engine.
[SPEAKER_08]: so hopefully we can see this out before too long right now though it's supposed to be a fully fledged sequel to Zone of the Enders the second runner and so hopefully we can see that out before too long and there's also been plenty of artwork tweeted by people who were at the press event I'd like to see a new Zone of the Enders game that would be fun
[SPEAKER_08]: And this event actually was specific for the Ender's HD Collection.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's up with all these HD Collections?
[SPEAKER_06]: People are buying them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what's up with them.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's travel around the world and look at some games that are going to be coming out a whole lot sooner, as in this week, as we travel the world with release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, US.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's not a whole lot coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, some re-releases, I guess, or I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got Batman Arkham City Game of the Year Edition, which is coming out this week on PS3 and Xbox 360 with that wonderful Harley Quinn's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_05]: DLC and crap thrown in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I like how they talk about... I know people genuinely excited about that and it sounds pretty robust.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Robust, like Catwoman.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's robust bust.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, other fun things this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Deer Drive, Legends on the 3DS, get your deer hunting on in 3D.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otlier Maruru, The Apprentice of Arland on PlayStation 3 this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Resistance, Burning Skies on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_05]: Might have to check that out, that looks pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's not a whole lot this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of it getting cancelled.
[SPEAKER_05]: Max Payne 3, special edition and the regular edition on PC coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's travel to Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Check out the games that are coming out over there in Japan on the Nintendo 3DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, I don't think there's a Disney game this week, but for some reason a bunch of character cases are coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you've ever wanted to stitch character case, import one from Japan because there's a bunch of those coming out there from Hori.
[SPEAKER_06]: It must tie into Dream Drop Distance somehow, it must.
[SPEAKER_06]: uh but what is coming out on the 3ds this is kind of a big deal Dragon Quest Monsters Terry No Wonderland 3d so it's not in the main series of Dragon Quest games but still it carries the name it is from Square Enix so it'll be a little bit of a deal there
[SPEAKER_06]: Guild 01 from level 5 comes out as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all again on the Nintendo 3DS this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Taking a look at the other handheld real quick, the Vita.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: The next big game is Mobile Suit Gundam Seed Battle Destiny on June the 7th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Taking a look at the consoles real quick on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Atlier Meru, Alchemist of Arlen 3 gets a price drop into the best collection.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's also Atlier Rorona gets that same price drop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Coming out from Sega this week, Jisen Pachislot, Hishihoho, Hokuto, Noken, F, Sekimatsu, Kaishu Seisu, Densetsu.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's basically another Pacino game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pachinko.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pachinko game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not like Al Pacino.
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard Legend in there somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's a Sega Pachinko game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what you get.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tiger Woods PGA Tour 13 but that is in English but it's getting a Japanese release and hey Portal 2 gets a price reduction so if you want to hear what GLaDOS sounds like in Japanese there you go lastly on the Xbox 360 in Japan this week Portal 2 gets that same price reduction and that's really it
[SPEAKER_06]: How about the UK, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_06]: Three things.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mad Riders for Xbox 360 and Resistance Burning Skies for Vita on the 30th.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we have on June 1st Max Payne 3 for PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, just a couple more news stories for you guys and then the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: But first, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's talk a little bit about... This is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Connect.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have new technology now.
[SPEAKER_05]: New technology where they can detect you sitting down.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Connect Software Development Kit Update 1.5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now features the ability to connect with you sitting on the couch.
[SPEAKER_06]: and now it can't tell if I'm wearing pants or not right because you know I have this legit fear about the Kinect that if I you know it's my house I'll do what I want and if I'm sitting in front of the Xbox 360 not wearing pants and playing Minecraft I don't want that image broadcast to the internet and I have this fear in the back of my mind I put a little box in front of the Kinect when I don't want to be seen by the internet um yeah they don't have that ability in here it's not one of the listed features but um
[SPEAKER_05]: Other fun stuff, they've got a development kit for face tracking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, some human interface guidelines and other improvements.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, they're saying that...
[SPEAKER_05]: They have full seated skeletal tracking mode, which is to track people sitting down.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they said also that, I think this is more, obviously this is only on PC, but I think a little bit, since most people on PC are probably sitting down to interface with stuff, I would hate to have to stand up to read an email or something like that with Kinect.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it'll be nice, too, that now you can play Kinect without actually having to move.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of the nice, you know, antithesis.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm pretty sure, I mean, the Kinect does detect you sitting down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, for some things, like, you can browse menus and stuff like that in the Xbox Kinect, just...
[SPEAKER_05]: I think sitting down.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think you have to stand up to browse video menus and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then again, I'm not stupid enough to hook up Kinect to do that when I could go, Huh, controller is faster.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, why would I need... I never understood why I need to browse those menus with my arm when I can just put the controller in my hand and just do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's faster.
[SPEAKER_05]: It really is faster.
[SPEAKER_05]: Voice searches, that's kind of cool, but moving my hand around to select things, that is slower.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we will see what this brings into games later on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, couldn't you play Joyride sitting down?
[SPEAKER_06]: Was it supposed to be able to see your hands driving the car?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, I didn't play that long.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it's because it was only looking at your hands.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't looking at the rest of your body.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there's somewhat of an in-joke amongst the community of Konami fans that have been following them for some time, and it's called Konami Will Sue.
[SPEAKER_06]: But maybe this week the joke should be changed to Konami Will Be Sued.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because Konami was sued this week, and, uh...
[SPEAKER_06]: You'd be pretty impressed what it's for.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: City National Bank is the one that's filed the suit against Konami and Autumn Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's over fraud.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the reason why is because the bank hasn't received any return on a $15 million line of credit that it approved to both Konami and Autumn Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the court documents claim that the financial state of Autumn and Konami were false.
[SPEAKER_06]: at the time that they were made and that defendants never had any intention of repaying the loan as promised.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all a quote from the court documents and so is this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rather than paying game-related proceeds directly to CNB or City National Bank as agreed, defendants have kept all game-related proceeds for themselves and have refused to remit any such proceeds to City National Bank.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's what I think the problem is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that they think that those games or, you know, Def Jam Rapstar was going to be successful and they're like, where's our percentage of, you know, of the profits?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why are we only getting like $10?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that is your percentage, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't divide by zero, stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, that's how much, that's how many copies we sold.
[SPEAKER_05]: You get a big fat check for $20.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: But there were no lawsuits.
[SPEAKER_06]: There were no laws.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, right.
[SPEAKER_06]: There were no laws in this game, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think this is a perfect day.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was lawless land.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to travel back in time and visit the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week, DarkSakura dives into the vault and pulls out a classic game that she thinks, hey, you ungrateful little brat, your new fangled crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go back and play something old school like this.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Diablo 2 Diablo 3
[SPEAKER_08]: This is Ragnarok Online, which was my crack.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I have, from time to time, been known to go back on a free server.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am also one of the people who basically has a permanent account on IRO, the International Ragnarok Online, because I played in the beta.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played in the Korean beta, I played in the Japanese beta, and I played in the US beta.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I've played a lot of Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_06]: And my last, I think... Fuck, even I remember this music.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, it's made by Gravity.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is based off of the Mantua, which is called Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there was a Ragnarok 3 animation based off of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was actually a pretty good little anime.
[SPEAKER_08]: It really captured the game very well.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've got different types of gameplay that are in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have PvE, you have Guild vs. Guild, and PvP.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can initiate PvP anywhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guild vs. Guild, I really, really, really liked that function.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it was a big capture the flag kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think that's something that... Now while I'm not a PvP fan, that is kind of the only reason why I like Battlegrounds at all in WoW.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's because it kind of reminds me of this, even though I didn't do it that often.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, honestly, I was a PvE person.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm always a PvE person.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's sprite-based.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is with different 3D environments.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you basically travel all over this little world in the game getting different creatures.
[SPEAKER_08]: And for as long as I played this damn game, Rob, I have not been everywhere in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is big.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, yeah, I've been to everything on the main map, but there's all the little caves and the dungeons and the special areas, and I haven't been everywhere in the game, although I have been to certain areas of the games many times, like the freaking Toy Factory.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or Prontera.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pronterra.
[SPEAKER_08]: Warp to prompt, please.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm glad that they took out that warping thing because that was such a pain.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, priests could teleport and they could open warp portals and they did something because that's not there anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: It really was based heavily off of Norse mythology.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have different classes.
[SPEAKER_08]: They also offered transcendent classes that keep going forward.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, with the different versions you have your jobs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everyone starts off as a novice.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then you actually can become a super novice where you get different aspects of other classes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then you have a swordman who can become a knight or a crusader.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then rebirth classes where you start over and rebuild them with more goodies.
[SPEAKER_08]: So basically your first job class is swordsman, mage, archer, merchant, thief, acolyte.
[SPEAKER_08]: and then you can expand to guns you also have expanded classes such as Gunslinger Ninja or Taekwon which playing a Taekwon is actually really fun
[SPEAKER_06]: The chat room was getting upset with the music because it's the only music you ever heard in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I switched it because there was more than one song in Ragnarok Online.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I love that music.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's Juno, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: That music is so pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love that area.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought you might approve.
[SPEAKER_08]: After the 2-1, you can actually become a Night Wizard, Hunter, Blacksmith, Assassin, or Priest.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played a Blacksmith for a while named Tony Stark.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mecha, Crusader, Sage, Bard, Dancer, Alchemist, Rogue, Monk Lord Knight, High Wizard, Sniper, Master Smith, Assassin, Cross, High Priest Paladin, Scholar, Minstrel, Gypsy, Biochemist, Stalker, Champion
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually have to say that minstrels are pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: For female ones, you had a dancer who basically looks like a harem chick.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a soundtrack come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's all kinds of stuff for this.
[SPEAKER_08]: There are pay-to-play servers, and then there's tons of freemium stuff that goes on with it, too, like the Caffra shop.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can buy different stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: With free-to-play servers, basically, you can play for free, but to support...
[SPEAKER_08]: The servers, they usually have special freebie goods or special goods that you can pay for.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like for one server I played on, there used to be these little dolls you could get that sit on top of your head.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were selling doll hats.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had a sprite artist who would make doll hats.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you paid like 20 bucks and you got a doll hat.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it was good because it kept the server paid for.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it does cost money to keep these going off.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's also Ragnarok Mobile that you can use to focus on your characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then there was the Ragnarok RPG that I've been playing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's a version on Game Boy that I... You got me the Japanese version of it, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played the crap out of that because I could read Prontera and I knew where I was on the damn map and I think an English version of that since came out too but it is really fun I would say that if you're looking for just like a little freebie RPG to get into Ragnarok Online is really fun and like my favorite class still to this day is Assassin because it's like pow pow pow pow it's just all speed it was awesome so yeah my game is Ragnarok Online
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, there it is, your classic game of the week, Ragnarok Online for the PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: And various spin-offs on other devices that DarkSakura named.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: A game I haven't played in about ten years.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have, I've been playing the one on the iPhone lately, and it's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I might have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you play a total... On my shiny new iPad.
[SPEAKER_08]: You play a total asshole, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's so fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, there it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to take a break here live as we are taping our episode number 458B here live on May the 27th of 2012.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to take a quick break here, but don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got plenty more show to come.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got some rapid-fire news.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have the Mailbag FUs of the Week and your calls at 1-877-GAME-OLR or Orange Lounge Radio on Skype are all coming up in a little while.
[SPEAKER_06]: So stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are live on this Memorial Day weekend May the 27th of 2012 with episode number 458B of our podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why is it episode 458B?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well go back and listen to the first part of the show if you want to know why it is 458B.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, we're going to get back in with some rapid-fire news here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, I just want to really plug the VOG conference on Friday at 7 Pacific, 10 Eastern, live at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm getting some people that are just sending me their ideas for VOG stuff, and I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I know Bobby wants to hear it.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura would like to hear it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shit, anybody you can talk to that's one of the hosts on VOG somewhere...
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, Travis, whoever you know we love hearing the ideas and I'm talking to somebody about one idea right now I'm like well that is a good idea actually yes we should do that and so I love it because it's you know just like Orange Lounge Radio where every gamer has a voice was never really just about us VOG Network isn't really just about us either so it's about me it's about everybody no it's about me and my fabulousness stop hating Rob stop hating she's being a parody alright stop hating let's move on
[SPEAKER_06]: It's about the gaming news now.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to travel around and check out some quick stories in a segment we call Rapid Fire News.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's talk a little bit about some upcoming games.
[SPEAKER_05]: XCOM Enemy Unknown actually has been announced to be coming out on October 9th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I thought when I first saw this that this means, ah, damn, I guess we're not going to have any Grand Theft Auto V game announcement for October.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not so sure if that's going to be the case anymore because actually there was an announcement for... Was it Take-Two put out their estimates for their fiscal years?
[SPEAKER_05]: And for 2013, which would cover up through now through... Was it March of... March 31st, 2013.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then we'll play some awesome music.
[SPEAKER_05]: they have about 700 million dollars or you know unaccounted revenue in there and even if like some of these games do really well I don't think they're gonna hit that spot so people are thinking uh maybe that's Grand Theft Auto 5 in there somewhere which honestly if it were to come out in October it would um it probably would compete very well
[SPEAKER_05]: They wouldn't cannibalize stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: God, I hope it's October.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, so yes, XCOM Enemy Unknown, October 9th, and I guess 13th internationally as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, of course, there's rumors, spoiler, I don't know, that EA's next Need for Speed game is actually going to be Need for Speed Most Wanted.
[SPEAKER_05]: and perhaps a reboot of that franchise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, they already had a Most Wanted.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, they did.
[SPEAKER_05]: They also had a Need for Speed Hot Pursuit, but that didn't stop them from having that last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: So perhaps Most Wanted could be, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like Apple's methodology.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the new most wanted.
[SPEAKER_06]: More wanted-er.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe most wanted-to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, there's a schedule going around showing the game's going to be shown on...
[SPEAKER_05]: EA's booth, and also apparently there was a Twitch TV feed or something like that for E3 that also has that listed on there as well, amongst some other TBA titles from Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, we'll probably see something from EA for Need for Speed Most Wanted, whether it be... I hope it's not the same damn title, because that's going to be confusing, because it didn't come out that long ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was only like five years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not that long in game time.
[SPEAKER_05]: And last but not least, Carmageddon Reincarnation has hit their goal with 10 days left to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course, I guess that means we're going to be getting a remade Carmageddon game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, they're saying that they're going to be adding some DLC to it now and probably going to be setting some different stretch goals for that as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: And funding will be done in a few more days.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's move on with some other news.
[SPEAKER_06]: You ever been to a website where you have to punch in CAPTCHA?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, like if you want to like download something or if you want to register for an account, you have to put in CAPTCHA.
[SPEAKER_06]: And sometimes the words are very like nonsense.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love this mock-up where somebody put kill me in the CAPTCHA.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I love this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, there is... I had destroyed enemies once.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, I guess there's a new Detroit-based startup company and they're called Are You a Human?
[SPEAKER_06]: And what they aim to do, they want to replace the Captcha box that people use with mini-games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: It accomplishes the same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You wouldn't be able to beat the game if you weren't actually a human.
[SPEAKER_06]: The tool they're developing is called Playthrough and it's going to allow a website owner to fight bots and spammers by using simple mini-games.
[SPEAKER_06]: for example there could be a level where you put tools in a toolbox or you put toppings on a pizza some websites that are already using this Quicken Loans and Fathead I don't know what Fathead does but Fathead makes giant posters on the wall of sports figures oh
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I had no idea who they were.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't own any of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do have a sweet Tron poster.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't own any of those either, but the reason I know they do that is because they also have that option for your Xbox Live avatar.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, why the fuck would I want a six foot tall picture of my avatar on the wall?
[SPEAKER_08]: I really have a big problem with your Tron poster.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just because it looks like all those little teleporting effects are just really bad use of the blur tool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of Tron, I did happen to see that that episode of Tron Uprising was on Disney last night.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was like, ooh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're only a couple weeks away from actual new episodes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know what I found out is that, funny enough, a week from tonight, they are going to be doing some type of kickoff event at Downtown Disney.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guess where I'm gonna be, yo?
[SPEAKER_06]: So I plan to bring you a VOG.
[SPEAKER_08]: You better bring me Tron stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: You better have a neon blue carpet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am so going.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there will be a full report on VOG for sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not expecting much though.
[SPEAKER_06]: For all I know, they're just going to have a giant screen out in the middle of downtown Disney that's playing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're going to get kidnapped by a recognizer.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'd be awesome if Paul Rubens was there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my gosh, it'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll see, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to hold my breath.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you know who was at Disneyland, by the way, last weekend when we were there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, don't ask me how I know that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rumors about a new Castlevania game on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently the name has leaked out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Castlevania Mirror of Faith.
[SPEAKER_06]: Supposedly this is a game that's going to be shown at E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Makes sense to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's about time there's a new Castlevania game out on a handheld.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have no reason to disbelieve this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially because it's funny because this particular site is a site Nintendo Netherlands or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might remember OLR blew the story on that about six years ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the DS games we had the exclusive on.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I have no reason to doubt them.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're sloppy.
[SPEAKER_06]: The names get out.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, they're claiming it's directly from Ubisoft Milan and Ubisoft would know some of this shit because they are doing some of the launch games which include, for Ubisoft Rayman Legends, The Avengers, Assassin's Creed 3 and Just Dance 4 a game called Killer Freaks from Outer Space supposed to arrive a few weeks after launch those are some pretty specific, I mean, granted about three of those are a duh but Killer Freaks from Outer Space, you can't guess that that was announced at E3 last year oh was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember that one yeah, they even had a video of it
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so maybe it's just somebody using logic, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like a cross between the Rabbids and Critters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, the Rabbids were like evil alien things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wii U does DirectX 11.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's already running Unreal Engine 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: 2 gigs of RAM, 560 megs of that dedicated to the OS.
[SPEAKER_06]: November 23rd, the launch date, but remember that's coming out of Milan, so could be a little bit around there for other regions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Launch price hasn't yet been decided, but they're saying $350 to $450, which tells me $399.
[SPEAKER_06]: Multiple versions of the console out there with developers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Graphics being powered by a Radeon HD 6770 chipset.
[SPEAKER_06]: Assassin's Creed 3 is 60 frames a second at 1080p.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is only running 720p on the other consoles right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: November 23rd would be a Friday.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if they launch it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But again, that's Milan.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not America.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there sometimes is some shift with the days.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know the other thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Those Italians.
[SPEAKER_08]: Italians.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here's a problem I have with Ubisoft, this information coming from Ubisoft Milan, because Ubisoft Milan would be a, it's basically a portion of the company that does development for certain games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So which game are they working on that they would be privy to this information?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, Ubisoft Milan, let's see, let's... I'm sorry, I can't hear Ubisoft Milan without hearing in the back of my head RuPaul saying, London, Paris, Milan.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Most interesting about this, Valve working on a digital distribution platform and portal ports.
[SPEAKER_06]: That could be very interesting if Valve is involved with the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to bring a heck of a lot of core gamer quote-unquote oomph to the Wii U. That would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: One other thing I'll say here, the new button supposedly has some link to the Wii Vitality Sensor.
[SPEAKER_06]: So maybe a new form of it or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I figured it would be a biometric button.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so that's it for the Wii U rumors, so let's move on with some more rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, Rob, well, how about some stuff having to do with touchscreen graffiti controls for Jet Set Radio?
[SPEAKER_08]: This is for the Vita release.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, well, and there's still not a date on it yet, but they're saying that they're bringing in touchscreen controls and camera integration so that I guess you can, for customizing your tags in the game, so that should be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: and then this is the thing that I lusted over yesterday and oh my god I want this so bad it like seriously makes me moist um girl the Street Fighter um
[SPEAKER_08]: 25th Anniversary Collector Set that comes in a big black box has a review figure 15 discs that includes on it Super Street Fighter 2 Turbo HD Remix, Street Fighter 3 Third Strike Online Edition, Super Street Fighter 4 Arcade Edition and the DLC and Street Fighter X Tekken and the DLC with a documentary, 2 anime movies, the full Street Fighter animated series and 11 discs of music
[SPEAKER_08]: and it has a light up Ryu statue and Ryu's belt.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is too much Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_08]: For $150.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I want it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course you do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you are a consumer whore.
[SPEAKER_08]: And how.
[SPEAKER_08]: But really, I don't care because I freaking love Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking at this set and oh my dear God, it just, I'm literally moist right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't help it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, how about Harry Potter stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: How about it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently there's going to be a Harry Potter for Kinect and there's a trailer out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got a really creepy face capture thing on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It does, but it actually looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks good in the trailer.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then I'm like, the games are never really like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just make the damn MMO already.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Screw Harry Potter because fucking Ryu.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, he's underage.
[SPEAKER_08]: Statue, not anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: Statues, statue of Ryu that lights up.
[SPEAKER_08]: with... It even has a certificate of authenticity.
[SPEAKER_08]: How can you pass that up?
[SPEAKER_06]: So you know it's authenticity.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll go on my wall and I will stare at Ryu for hours because that was my first video game crush was Ryu when I was a little kid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aw, that's kind of adorable.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm spent.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm really spent.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are going to go to the Fugle question of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Google Question of the Week is a segment of our show where we ask a question on Facebook and Google+, and we read some of our favorite answers here on the program.
[SPEAKER_06]: We didn't ask one tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of you might have said, hey, I didn't see a new question on Facebook or Google this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's because we never got to read last week's answers because of the crash, and it was a pretty timely question.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I want to go through some of those right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to start on our Google Plus page.
Shit.
Google Plus.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just dropped that brand new iPad of mine.
[SPEAKER_06]: How convenient.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I have a case on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's the weird thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't access Facebook right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you access Facebook, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I access Facebook?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, there it went.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just went.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I was getting worried that I was going to miss the questions here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_06]: The question of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: More and more games are incorporating multiplayer into their games.
[SPEAKER_06]: For example, Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some in the industry have been quoted as saying that multiplayer is essential in this day and age to having a successful game.
[SPEAKER_06]: How important do you feel that multiplayer is to the games you purchase?
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you ever been swayed on a game purchase because of the fact that it did or did not have multiplayer?
[SPEAKER_06]: Redertainment answers the question and says multiplayer is irrelevant to me due to my ISP being fucking incompetent PSN being incompetent and me cancelling Xbox Live Gold as part of my effort to buy a house so in other words the world is out to get him
[SPEAKER_06]: Vlogus responds and says, these are all from Google Plus again, Uncharted, Gears, Halo, etc.
[SPEAKER_06]: All have some form of competitive multiplayer that I've never tried.
[SPEAKER_06]: I only buy games for the single player component due to the rampant negativity on the online services.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do love co-op multiplayer with my family or friends.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell Jamie I apologize for my bad grammar and punctuation.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's okay, I'm not reading it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You apologized to the wrong person.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm mad.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: You actually didn't do a bad job.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have pretty bad grammar myself, so I'm usually pretty forgiving.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And lastly, Jim, he was supposed to be here last week to answer this in person, but he decided to go on Google Plus and answer instead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Flaco Jones I don't care much for multiplayer modes in games because I'm all about the story and it doesn't make much sense story wise when there are seven Nathan Drakes running around shooting other players at the same time plus I rent or buy used so I don't even get to play multiplayer thanks to online passes
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to the Facebook community now that Facebook is working for me at Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio and read some of the answers that you guys sent us over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we're going to start off with a reply from DDR Dollar Bill who says, Never, as in, has you ever been swayed?
[SPEAKER_06]: Never.
[SPEAKER_06]: Multiplayer never made or break a purchase for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was nice, but it wasn't life or death either.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it wouldn't change a game grade by one point if it was included nor excluded.
[SPEAKER_06]: JVmon says I almost never play multiplayer online and if I do it's only with friends who usually don't buy the same games as me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even then cross game chat fixes that problem and we can hang out while playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: So would it sway me?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we have a lot of people that are like, no, no, no, never, never, never.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to an answer from RedTheHaze.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've no problems with added multiplayer as long as it's good, builds on the single player game, and adds to the experience, but has no negative consequences to the single player.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just like when I bought Mass Effect 3 when it was on sale for $30 just for multiplayer, even though I haven't played Mass Effect 2, but I plan to play 3 once I get to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Panaxium responded and said...
[SPEAKER_06]: However, Prime Hunters was a lot more fun, except for the cramping and trolls, but I digress.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the end, I would rather have an amazing single experience than half-baked multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mike B responded saying, I think it's great as long as it has a co-op story mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is fun playing through the story with friends.
[SPEAKER_06]: I kind of like that whole co-op versus versus too because I think the type of multiplayer can really change a lot too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's really important to state too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think a game like LittleBigPlanet
[SPEAKER_06]: Really is enhanced by the multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's one game I didn't really see get brought up here.
[SPEAKER_06]: But a game like LittleBigPlanet really gets enhanced because it's more of a co-op.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, I'm into Mass Effect 3 right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a lot of that is because it's co-op.
[SPEAKER_06]: It isn't necessary, especially for established single-player franchises, but sometimes it can be a welcome addition that doesn't take away from its campaign.
[SPEAKER_06]: Portal 2, Dead Space 2, and Mass Effect 3 are just a few examples.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are all really good examples.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me read one more from John K. Oh, excuse me, I didn't read the name.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Critical Myth, my bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: So again, those are all answers from our Facebook account, facebook.com slash orange lounge radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come thumbs up us over there and you can answer a question in a future week.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about you guys here in studio?
[SPEAKER_06]: How important is multiplayer to you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't really give a crap about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You really go out of your way to avoid it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yet you play an MMO.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but you notice, what do I do most of the time?
[SPEAKER_08]: I quest.
[SPEAKER_08]: I play by myself and just chat with people.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the having to play with other people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I like raiding, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm with my guildmates.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm with people that I pretty much know.
[SPEAKER_08]: PVP I hate I mean I don't really mind doing like the most fun that I have in dungeons is when basically I've just tagged along with you know with the ones that you've done for like what was that one that was really fun that you drug me around in your motorcycle for
[SPEAKER_06]: The Isle of Conquest?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Isle of Conquest.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was fun because I was playing with you and Alan.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I just have this thing about the random stranger thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: All appearances to the contrary, I am a bit of an introvert.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've taught myself how to be outwardly extroverted, but really I kind of like to do my own thing and stick with the folks I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: I lost my train of thought that's alright I'll go ahead and just say I really agree with the answer that said it's best when it more enhances a single player game that's already there especially the examples of Portal 2 and Mass Effect 3 I think are two great examples of where multiplayer really just sweetened the pot for a game that would have already been worth the asking price
[SPEAKER_08]: Portal 2 Multiplayer Portal 2 Strangers
[SPEAKER_06]: You're so mature.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, before I get to Loki's answer, let me get to our chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some folks talking about Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, obviously Skyrim gets brought up as a game that didn't need multiplayer to be successful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jim Sally says, Skyrim is awesome, but it would be twice as good if a co-op mode was added.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a lot of people have been asking for something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But ShadowNextGen says, I don't know if Skyrim would be good with co-op.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game is really all about your personal choices.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't necessarily need multiplayer for Final Fantasy or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blender brings up a great point in our chat room what about Journey Orange Lounge Radio and he's not talking about the one from the 80s about the band he's talking about that new one on PlayStation Network and I gotta say no one's bought it for me yet well I have it and I've played through it and I gotta say Journey is like on a whole nother level with the multiplayer it's like a new type of multiplayer experience you can't even really define you don't have to talk to them do you
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you never do.
[SPEAKER_06]: which it's it's so crazy like the simplicity of the game and kind of what it's done for multiplayer games Journey again if you haven't played it on PlayStation 3 and you own a PlayStation 3 you really gotta check it out it just it's amazing it was better when people didn't tell you there was a multiplayer component and I did not even know there was going to be multiplayer in it and I was just blown away amazing
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, that's going to do it for the Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you to everybody who responded.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had a ton of answers on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm so sorry I didn't have time to read all of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: But answer us in a future week, and we'll try to get some in.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can always get your thoughts through to our mailbag, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: and we'll read those in a future week.
[SPEAKER_08]: For now... We don't have any.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, sadly we didn't get any mail this week so we don't have anything to read but maybe in a future week.
[SPEAKER_06]: For now though, let's get to some news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's talk a little bit about...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's for a project called Destiny and also they're talking about some of the expected bonuses and stuff based on performance and also saying that they're going to have a version of the game that's going to come out on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, in the fall of 2013, there's going to be follow-ups in multiple years, and it's supposed to be a four-game deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, at the end of that, they're going to have the option to fund a new marathon game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that's definitely a lot of...
[SPEAKER_05]: corporate mumbo jumbo at least in the leaked document but it'll be cool to see what this new Destiny game is supposed to be like.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll probably be like Halo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm thinking it will be.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was hoping it would be Pimps at Sea but you know unfortunately we can dream but that's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Diablo 3 Diablo 3 Diablo 3 Diablo 3
[SPEAKER_06]: have no part of this whole authenticator and ways to protect their account.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Blizzard's coming in and saying, well, people need to be more careful with their account information, but apparently it has come through in recent days that there are a small number of accounts that are being hacked with authenticators on them, but it's coming through malware on the user system.
[SPEAKER_06]: and the blue posts that are on the forums are very adamant that, yeah, we're looking at the MSInfo files of people that are saying they're getting hacked with an authenticator and they've got all sorts of malware on the system and that's where it's coming from.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this whole single player always connected experience is really starting to rub people the wrong way and this is just the latest feather in that hat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, really?
[SPEAKER_06]: I did not want to fucking deal with this and now people are getting hacked and all this shit because they don't have an authenticator on their account?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, Diablo 3 had amazing sales in their first week, but what is the long-term damage this shit is causing?
[SPEAKER_06]: We talked a little more about this on Horde House this week at www.hordehouse.com, my World of Warcraft themed spinoff show, but to kind of ask here a little bit, Loki, I think you're a good one to ask because you're not as sucked into this Warcraft phenomenon as DarkSakura and I are.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are your thoughts about Diablo 3 being always connected and have they screwed PC games
[SPEAKER_06]: that might want to explore this in the future with this consistent botched thing after another.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I never like any always connected games there, especially if it's not required.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it's not an MMO, then what's the point of me having to be always required a connection for this to happen?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, say, if I want a game on my laptop, it doesn't mean I'm going to have Wi-Fi everywhere I go.
[SPEAKER_05]: And...
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, that kind of sucks if I can't play my game that I purchased because I don't have an internet connection at the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's another reason why I wouldn't get the game, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other than, you know, just don't really want to buy the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Burn, our chatroom, asks, so it's malware?
[SPEAKER_06]: The rumor was it was joining public games that opened you up to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, Blizzard is passionately denying those claims.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: As we've learned, though, throughout other parts of the game industry, that doesn't necessarily always mean anything, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would like to think that they've tested that and it's true, but... And just because you have malware, I mean, because there's a lot of malware out there, but, I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying, oh, well, we can see that you have malware on your system.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it the same malware for each thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, what exactly does this malware do?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because there's malware that just, I go search something on Google and all of a sudden I get transferred to another page that has nothing to do with what I just searched for.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like another search engine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or is it something that's like, I'm specifically putting this malware on your system to steal your information?
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, why can't Blizzard, just to give extra protection to the accounts, very similar to what Star Wars, the Old Republic did, you have these personal questions that only you would know the answer to, and whenever Star Wars suspects that you're making a major change or you're doing something weird where it might not really be you, it asks you to answer three of those questions at random.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, why couldn't they?
[SPEAKER_06]: Gee, you usually play Diablo 3 in Sacramento, California.
[SPEAKER_06]: All of a sudden, you're trying to log in from China.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I should ask you a private question that only you would know the answer to because the odds that you were playing in California and now you're suddenly playing in China are very, very low.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or here's a thought, since we've gotten these little readouts of what processes you have running and stuff, and we've noticed that there's specific malware programs or whatever running.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's because probably none of that has any information.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like saying, oh, well, you know, you've got some sort of virus on your computer, so that must be how they're hacking your system.
[SPEAKER_08]: And seriously, most malware that you'll find are usually like site trackers.
[SPEAKER_08]: That type of thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing that's really going to have anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's for advertising.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's hope Blizzard can patch this shit up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I seriously think they're doing some long-term damage here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did find a new patch applied last night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I didn't see what it was for, but they did patch my game last night.
[SPEAKER_06]: We ain't found shit!
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess some people in chat are saying they emailed within the past hour or so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, check it again.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want to check it again?
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll do the FUs of the week first.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is usually the time we do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Loki wants to jump in.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I was just going to jump in with some random stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I figured I'd... Already logged in.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was doing Google searches for information regarding this Xbox jacking stuff there's actually a whole bunch of information about doxing which is finding out the information on people like their name, city, state all the personal information based on some of this other stuff and that's how they steal accounts it's by knowing all your personal information tons of ebooks on it too be careful who you add on your social networks that's for sure so we have one
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, yay, we do have an email after all.
[SPEAKER_06]: From Munma.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: Question for the staff.
[SPEAKER_08]: What has to be the single most expensive gaming accessory you have purchased for your gaming console?
[SPEAKER_08]: And to read the disclaimer, this email was brought to you by Anime Jam Session, the podcast about anime, cosplay, convention, roasting, pop culture, and everything in between.
[SPEAKER_08]: Podcast guaranteed to derail in 10 minutes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your money back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Check us out at www.animejamsession.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the cheapest fucking plug I have ever seen in the history of this show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to ask a really generic question and then plug the shit out of my show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Micro Machines.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's alright, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because we love Anime Jam Session John Machida was great We're gonna allow it I did buy my husband Steel Battalion Oh yeah?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: So, um, but keep in mind, if you look at my BitMoney collection, I've got a poppin' music controller, I have four 2DX controllers now, I have two Guitar Freaks controllers, I have a keyboard for Keyboard Mania, I have a drum controller for Drum Mania, and then we have all this crap we have for Guitar Hero, so it's really hard to say when you look at the whole thing, but I think the single most expensive has to be the Steel Battalion controller, because that was 300 bucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would say the most expensive... I know this probably doesn't count for the original question, but I fucking bought a Japanese PlayStation 2 just so I could play all those Bomani games back in the day, so I think I get that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially, you know, I bought the controller, I bought the DDR mats, all to work with the Japanese setup.
[SPEAKER_08]: We bought a JPS2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, keyboard... I bought fucking keyboard mania, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I think that qualifies.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can tell you what our most expensive game was.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Was probably Dracula X. Oh, yeah, yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought an arcade cabinet to put DDR in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never really gone around to putting DDR in it, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: But looking at accessories on their own, what is the most...
[SPEAKER_05]: Just all my Rockman stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I have, you know, $100 guitar here and drum set and another bass guitar that I got specially that's collecting dust under my desk at work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now what was your most expensive system?
[SPEAKER_08]: What is the most you've ever paid for a single video game system?
[SPEAKER_05]: My first Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you dumb bastard.
[SPEAKER_06]: You did pay a lot for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it your PS2?
[SPEAKER_06]: Most I paid for a system?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Might be my PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think a PS3 was more expensive than importing the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will second that because keep in mind when we bought ours, we still have our first model PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: And thanks to Discover, we got $100 knocked off of it because we got a reward on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we paid $600 for our first model PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, the one and only Bobby Blackwolf in our chatroom at vognetwork.com said, I own a very expensive set of Roland V-Drums, and I just put it on TwitPick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it does work with... That does.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's not really necessarily an accessory.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so then moving forward to... Because I really like elaborating on this one.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's the most you've ever paid for a game?
[SPEAKER_06]: The most I've ever paid for a game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, Japanese importing...
[SPEAKER_06]: and probably Beatmania 2DX6 style.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say it was probably the most expensive one I got because I got that when it was brand, brand new.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have actually paid more than $100 for a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think I've ever paid more than that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I paid $120 for the Sailor Moon Super S fighting game on Super Famicom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Add up all the months of World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm saying for the game itself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Alan's joining us and I think wants to say something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi Alan So we're talking about most spent on a game Yes sir When I was, there was a year or two where I was importing Japanese games And I only got four or five of them But I want to say Tobel number two The sequel to the Square Fighting game I think I spent close to like 90, 95 bucks all told to get that game It also had the demo on it though for Final Fantasy 7, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah I think so Yeah Alan, remember when we had disposable income?
[SPEAKER_06]: What about you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: My iPad says hi.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: What's the most you've ever paid for a game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Standalone didn't come with anything else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Motorstorm Apocalypse because it was a beta or it was a barely yeah you bought that on eBay or something didn't you yeah yeah so I would what about people who bought that Capcom mech game that was like 200 bucks because they have the whole controller oh Steel Battalion I've got no check this now I have two copies and two controllers you're sick but I mean that would love
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is the rarest system that you own?
[SPEAKER_06]: I love SSJ100, Matt.
[SPEAKER_06]: The most I've ever spent on a game was Yaris for zero points.
[SPEAKER_06]: Paid way too much for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, the most we ever spent on a what?
[SPEAKER_06]: A system?
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think is your most valuable system that you own?
[SPEAKER_08]: In terms of personal value and then in terms of financial value.
[SPEAKER_06]: My still working Super Nintendo in terms of personal value.
[SPEAKER_06]: In terms of actual... I don't really have a lot of rare systems.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really have any old shit that still works.
[SPEAKER_06]: The HD DVD player on my Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: My arcade system for most valuable and for personal value.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Xbox of fame.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think our most valuable one is our Neo Geo.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's talk about how much money we've spent on this sick obsession here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Burr in the chat room is trying to call me out saying, Sky had disposable income that could have gone to improving the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Talking about that stinking power device.
[SPEAKER_07]: He did put a lot of money into the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, this iPad.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just did the Facebook questions for the Fugle Question of the Week off the iPad.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it did go to improving the show, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: by the way I'd like to answer a niche or is it niche or niche whatever I think it's Nietzsche Nietzsche that's not how the philosopher's name is spelled oh well whatever there should be a T and a Z in there we did not buy a 3DO because there is all of crap for 3DO we did almost buy a CDI
[SPEAKER_06]: if you want me to go through the list of what we own we'll need a whole other show for that alright that's it for the mailbag now we will do the FUs of the week angst, anger um
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm angry at being sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I feel tons better now.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is what's funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: I slept all day yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, literally almost all day yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I slept most of this morning, had weird ass freaking fever dreams.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I go out on my bicycle feeling like crap because I needed to go get NyQuil from the Kmart around the corner from my house.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I mean, it's about a mile.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I rode my bike a mile there, got all my stuff, rode it back with a backpack full of stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I was so hot and feverish and shaky when I got home.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think my fever broke from my bike ride because now, like, my lungs feel better.
[SPEAKER_08]: I still have, you know, the stupid sinus headache, but I feel, like, infinitely better than I have in weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, F you to having to go through all of that just to feel better.
[SPEAKER_08]: And F you to bread.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm having to go back on raw food again.
[SPEAKER_08]: And hey, don't knock Kmart because I got a Sonic the Hedgehog shirt there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to my cult and F you to power not being available during our show sometimes.
[SPEAKER_06]: F you to the music stopping.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, F you to Burr in our chatroom for saying the Fugo questions just had to be read from a retina display to protect Skye's precious eyes.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, F you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, and then my other F you of the week goes to this cough that will not leave.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I've had this cough for like two weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: You remember when I was sick on the show a couple weeks ago?
[SPEAKER_06]: I still have the cough.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I may.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just hiding it well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura's medical advice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which I'm not a doctor, disclaimer, disclaimer Are you taking any Guafenicin?
[SPEAKER_06]: Excuse you, what is that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Mucinex This is the former, what's that store?
[SPEAKER_08]: GC, whatever that you used to work at I used to work at GMC Yeah, that's a GMC Well, you can go to the dollar store, Rob And get plain old Guafenicin And take two doses of it And it is the pharmacy dose And I guarantee you, it will clear up your cough
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, what else will it do to me?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the same stuff the doctor gives you a prescription.
[SPEAKER_06]: No!
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, I like my big gay life, dammit.
[SPEAKER_08]: All it does is a mucus thinner.
[SPEAKER_08]: It helps you produce it so that you don't have it causing the cough anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's how mine has gotten better.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: That and lots of NyQuil.
[SPEAKER_06]: A couple more stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you guys on the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's talk once again about more Activision drama.
[SPEAKER_05]: This kind of ties in with the whole lawsuit between, you know, Wes and Zempela versus Activision.
[SPEAKER_05]: and just some of the dirty stuff that went on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously the first part of the lawsuit's been settled, but there's still the whole lawsuit against those people.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was this thing that came out called Project Icebreaker.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently it was an initiative designed by Activision to secretly scour the computers of those two individuals
[SPEAKER_05]: for evidence that would support a firing.
[SPEAKER_05]: This involved them attempting to hack into their accounts or their systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, the possibility of faking a fire drill to get them to leave the building so that someone could go and hack into their computers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just dirty shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously, I can't believe that they would even... Well, no, I can believe that they could do that because it's Activision.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: also um you know of course some of the stuff you know during that's been released is spreadsheets um talking about the top 20 um Infinity Ward employees and their salaries and of course Wes and Zempella have made quite a bit of money um apparently they've each uh
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: I was reading some of that crazy shit on the internet, those Activision emails and so forth, and it's a scary inside look to how some of this shit operates.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's, man, it's almost evil.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is evil.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not almost evil, we know how evil they are.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you're asking a lawyer to do something illegal, they're like, I don't know if I'm comfortable doing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's move from something evil to just kind of shady.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has to do with THQ, and I guess they're going to be having a June 29 stockholders meeting where they're going to do what's called a reverse stock split to avoid a delisting from NASDAQ.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that's really not shady, it's just business, but I guess it's sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a tricky way of doing things.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It totally is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a little bit like the shell game.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are going to have some pissed off investors.
[SPEAKER_06]: So anyhow, apparently what's going to happen is that they have to do the stock split to maintain $1 per share minimum that NASDAQ requires.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently there are going to be three options in the process, one of three, one of five, and one of ten, reverse stock split ratios.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any of these options, it means there are fewer outstanding shares with an increased apparent value per share.
[SPEAKER_06]: So for example, if they do a one to three reverse stock split, each stockholder will own one stock for every three that they had prior to the split, even though the total value of the company doesn't change.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that 61 cents that they're currently trading at, they do a one of 10.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now it's, oh, it's $6.10 a share, but hopefully you only have one share instead of 10.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they can do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: What happens if you have two shares?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot of people that get novelty stock.
[SPEAKER_06]: They just buy one share.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then again, how many people just buy one share of THQ?
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've got more people that do that shit with Facebook or Disney or Coca-Cola or Pepsi, big companies.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's...
[SPEAKER_06]: There's actually a company out there, some website, and I hate that I'm giving them free advertising, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like buyoneshare.com or oneshare.com, and they actually do this whole little shtick where they'll print out a certificate, and you can frame it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like a gift-giving thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of a neat idea for a gift.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they did a report on some website the other day, and it was like, if you had bought one share of Apple in 1982, it would be worth $1,000 now.
[SPEAKER_05]: My mom, who actually worked for Intel for a while, part of their thing was that each employee got a certain amount of stock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this was way back in the 70s and 80s and stuff, and she still has it.
[SPEAKER_05]: She found the certificate in the attic the other day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's funny, as we looked into it, and that split so many times since that one share of stock, I only think it was one share, it was like a few shares of stock, it was like,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: I do not have the Twitter topics up yet so maybe Loki I know there might be some last minute stories tonight because there was a lot of stuff we had to cut from tonight's show and it's just it's picking up as we move towards E3 I'm sure we've got some stuff here of course I'm not ready as usual
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm still looking at that hacking stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't believe all the information that they have out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically telling you to use those white pages or reverse searches and stuff like that to find out people's personal information that your phone company and stuff collects so you can hack someone's Xbox Live account.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can talk about Silicon Knights.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Silicon Knights had this lawsuit against Epic because they're saying, Your engine was too hard to use.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why our games suck balls.
[SPEAKER_05]: And apparently they failed to provide evidence of damages or whatever for their lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so the judge assigned them their own value of a dollar.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if they win their claim, they get a dollar.
[SPEAKER_06]: A whole dollar?
[SPEAKER_05]: A whole dollar.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could buy a candy bar with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, we got a call coming in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the one person that actually sent an email into the mailbag, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what's funny is that the chatters were like, no, Ranma doesn't get through tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ranma does not get to call in because he sent an email.
[SPEAKER_04]: But when nobody else calls, you guys... I can't help it that I have the fastest internet in America to beat everybody else 99% of the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're just that awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind tonight, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, what's on my mind is a bit of a hardware review, which is in conjunction with the email that I sent earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: When I was at PAX East playing at the Square Enix booth, they had these nice headphones that I was playing a theater rhythm with, and I was like, the music quality is just phenomenal, where did you get it?
[SPEAKER_04]: They told me they had it at the Astro Gaming booth, and I checked out their equipment, and after thinking about it for all of five seconds, I decided to buy them.
[SPEAKER_04]: But not right away, I decided to save my money and get them for my birthday, and which I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now I own a pair of Astro A30 gaming headsets with a powered mix amp, which is perfect for Xbox 360, PC, television, and cell phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I have to say, audio quality is quite phenomenal compared to what I was used to listening to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, I'm yelling with the chatters because apparently we had a drop, but I'm showing that we didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Usually if we drop, we show that our sent information drops way down, but I don't see that, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they're just saying it because I'm on the phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're just like, drop the stream so I get off the phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haters gonna hate.
[SPEAKER_06]: The timer reset to 1 minute 30 seconds so maybe there was a hiccup, but that's weird because usually that number resets.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, podcast listeners don't care about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, the hardware.
[SPEAKER_06]: So how expensive is this thing supposed to be?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, the headset itself is $129.
[SPEAKER_04]: The mix amp is $99, but you can get it as a bundle for $199.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it worth it?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're an audiophile, I say yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you're looking to change your normal headphones for your cell phone or MP3 player, if you're looking for a bit of a change for mobile gaming, I would definitely go with the headset standalone.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Mixamp, like I said, gives better audio quality.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the songs I actually tested to see how well the clarity of the music is was Loki's Verbalicious remix, which is one of my personal favorites.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are those surround sound headphones or are they just standard headphones?
[SPEAKER_04]: The headphones itself are standard.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get the surround sound 7.1 with the mix amp.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have those kind of headsets.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like the headset with the surround sound built in.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I've got a pair at home, but I paid a lot less than $200 for them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they weren't Turtle Beach.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember what the hell I got.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're Tritons, the ones I have.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually tried on a pair of Tritons, and they were phenomenal while I was playing them with Bioshock 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, Ranma, I'm going to let you go so we can get some more calls, but anything else you want to plug here on the show real quick before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Luke Chan already plugged it for me, so I'm going to run high back under my rock for the next seven days.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see you in seven days.
[SPEAKER_06]: Got it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry I was a little distracted during that call, but those things happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, there it goes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Phone's ringing right off the hook.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, this is Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Actdeft, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to talk about the email Ranma sent you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little tangent about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have any accessories or a very expensive video game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the most expensive one I have paid for is Bitmania 12, Happy Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I have spent tons and tons of money on
[SPEAKER_02]: on Pokemon plushies, Pokeballs.
[SPEAKER_06]: And why is that?
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, I was thinking that this call was going to go in the direction of because you live in Mexico and not every company releases their products officially in Mexico, sometimes you have to pay these crazy-ass import fees.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it kind of along the same lines for Pokemon?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, most of the time, since a friend helped me get most of the stuff I get from the United States, so I import, so I pretty much pay what you would pay for something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's still a pretty expensive little hobby, if you want to call it like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I live pretty much 10 minutes to the border.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I live pretty close.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay, shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: So how often do you just drive up into the States to pick up what you want?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, unfortunately, I can't right now because I don't have a passport or a visa.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, dope.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I cannot cross the border, but I used to, and...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it depends on how much traffic is there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It usually, it can take up to an hour to cross the border and pretty much go to the next town.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a GameStop, there's a mall too, and there's a Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's pretty much, well, very renowned stores to go and buy stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's not that difficult.
[SPEAKER_06]: And please tell me you live in one of those parts of Mexico I'm not seeing on the news, like you live in one of the safer parts, I hope?
[SPEAKER_06]: More or less.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care of yourself, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't like some of the stuff I see on the news.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes me very sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is safe around where I live, but we live pretty close to some of the other parts that you do see on TV, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's not that bad right now, but it's not that good either.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm sending happier thoughts your guys' way, because I always, you know, when I see that stuff on the news, believe it or not, I do think about, I know people in Mexico, and I hope this is not something they're having to deal with, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: But Mexico's a big place, so I know there's a lot of parts you see on TV and parts that are just fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, didn't mean to steer the conversation in a totally different direction, but that'll happen sometimes on OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any recent games you've been playing you want to talk about?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not many, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did play The Walking Dead on Steam.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got it for free on the Tall Tale Twitter account.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay, very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty thoughtful of them to give me one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's a pretty cool game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that much action, but story and the decisions you take, it's pretty much, well, compelling.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sucks you in.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hear it's a great game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've really got to check it out at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know nothing about the books or the TV show, but that doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: It can still be a great game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still need to play the Jurassic Park game, which even though I know that game got kind of razzed, I like the movies well enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to try it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now I have Weird Al in my head.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jurassic Park is frightening in the dark.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aw, Donna Summer.
[SPEAKER_08]: All the dinosaurs are running wild.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember another song, but I don't sing that well.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, Actdeft, I'm going to let you go, buddy, so we can try and get another call.
[SPEAKER_06]: But take care, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: You too.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I mean that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Donna Summer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was trying to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was at work.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was legitimately verklempt by that news.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was so sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, granted, I know there was... Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was a death I was more saddened by.
[SPEAKER_06]: Robin Gibb?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: No!
[SPEAKER_08]: Bee Gees!
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: By Adam Yalch, MCA.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that was... Because... He was young, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's not just, you know, that he was famous.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was all the good stuff he was doing and just how absolutely brilliant of a person he was.
[SPEAKER_08]: That big Kurosawa fan.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: And is it just me or did she stay gorgeous?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, she did.
[SPEAKER_06]: She sure did.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, we have a call coming in right now, so let's go to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Chugga-chugga-chugga-choo-choo You sexy people, it's Jim Sally Hey, your train's behind schedule You're usually on the Bobby Blackwolf show But you're delayed three hours tonight I got delayed, I went on the wrong side of the tracks today Well, you know, we've been saying for a few weeks now That, you know, we made a left turn at Albuquerque And other folks we used to work with made a right So I was thinking maybe you just made the wrong turn at Albuquerque
[SPEAKER_00]: Listen, you can't do anything right when you're doing it in Albuquerque.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what's up, Jim?
[SPEAKER_00]: Listen, we were talking earlier about putting multiplayer in things in different games.
[SPEAKER_00]: It needs to be in Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm playing this stupid game a lot lately.
[SPEAKER_00]: I wish there was like every now and again I'd roll up to somebody like me that was uber powerful and could kill everything and had way too much money.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think about the whole Elder Scrolls Online?
[SPEAKER_06]: We were talking about that either last week or the week before.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that's trying to appease some of these people who want their multiplayer Elder Scrolls.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that enough for you?
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it would be great if it was just little missions like go out and hunt a criminal.
[SPEAKER_00]: If I do a lot of bad stuff in the town, maybe that town can just pay another player to come chase me.
[SPEAKER_00]: and good luck because you ain't gonna kill Jim Sally in this game I'm stupid powerful do you find when you're playing these games like I'm an accountant so I'm very good with numbers and maximizing productivity I find I just overpower everything in the game it's it's pretty insane right now I I wonder if um there'll be some type of how do you play Skyrim on the PC or do you play on console um I play it on the console because consoles are better yeah and and um
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm better, so that's why I play it on the console.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Oblivion needs to do it, sorry, Bethesda needs to do it right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I kind of think Skyrim is going to stay single player and they're going to really try to push you to pay that monthly fee if you want to take it multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Listen, it's about time that they just let Obsidian do it for them.
[SPEAKER_00]: If they make the best sequels to games, perfectly solid and stable, they should just let Obsidian make it.
[SPEAKER_00]: They've done it with Fallout.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let them do it with Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I hope they're listening to your suggestion, but sadly they probably aren't.
[SPEAKER_06]: You got that right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well Jim, anything else you want to share with us tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, I play way too much of that Walking Dead game that the last caller just called about.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, people are loving it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what, brother?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to tell you this right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: The hardest part about the zombie apocalypse?
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll be pretending I'm not excited.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kim Sally's getting ready.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm getting ready.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I will pass the word along to my friend at Telltale because they're very proud of that game and they should be.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know, before we were talking about Minecraft's, you know, record-breaking figures, Walking Dead was doing very well for itself on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think that's some really good news, you know, because there's a lot of people that think adventure games are like a niche thing, you know, and yeah, Telltale's filling that niche very well, but Walking Dead's really kind of broken it mainstream for them and I'm happy for them and for adventure game fans everywhere, really.
[SPEAKER_00]: You got that right.
[SPEAKER_00]: But anyway, brother, I got to take off.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just want to say, everybody, that if you go to bed and you don't think about zombies coming, then maybe you're not scared enough or too scared.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something to ponder in bed tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Jim hung up.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like it when he calls us.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like it when he calls Bobby too, but it's okay if he misses that train and calls us once in a while too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do a little alternating.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys who tried to call.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry if you didn't get through, but please send us an email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com In the meantime, any other last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to get to these Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a few of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: My brain is broken, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: It requires Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_06]: We might be able to manage that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me quickly do some Twitter topics here from Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of indie games on sale until June 1st for the PC, Steam, and iOS, Android.
[SPEAKER_06]: Support indie devs.
[SPEAKER_06]: BecauseWeMay.com That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We didn't even bring that up during the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shame on us.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's a great thing to support.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least look into it, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: BecauseWeMay.com Actdeft also wants to share that you can get the Awesome Knots theme song for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you haven't played Awesome Knots yet...
[SPEAKER_06]: It has an awesome theme song and you should definitely check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll do a few more tweets here, but let me ask Loki first.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I was going to talk about Shootmania, which was part of this Mania Planet series.
[SPEAKER_05]: You may remember them from Trackmania.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shootmania is their FPS editor, and it also is a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shootmania Storm is the first thing they have right now that's in beta, and they actually have the registration open for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: But...
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks pretty cool, and you can basically create your own FPS game with this, and they've got all the tools to make, I think it's an online FPS maker.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, it should be noted that they're supposed to have Quest Mania at some point, so that means a really cool RPG maker, so I'm kind of interested in that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sign up for the beta, so we'll see when that happens.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was checking that out, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Binding of Isaac is one of the games, and they're two bucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, yeah, I was actually going to pick that up this weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for reminding me.
[SPEAKER_06]: A couple more tweets here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ionotropic tweets us on Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ragnarok Odyssey for Vita.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it going to be awesome or not?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's hard to say when the game's not in front of me, but did you even know that that was coming to the Vita?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even know anything about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have a Vita, so I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can borrow mine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now that you've got your iPad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't hate me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going to a couple tweets from Tiger Claw.
[SPEAKER_06]: Death spank the bacon-ing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Indie game The Movie will be Steam's first full-length film release.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had no idea Steam was looking into doing this, but apparently Steam is going to start giving out movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, the 1080p video will be DRM'd as much as any other Steam product or game for those of you that were worried about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you will have to have the Steam client in order to watch it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you can pre-order the movie on Steam for $8.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: That includes a 10% discount until June 12th when the movie's coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this is a new area for Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now they're going to take on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, by the way, you know what else is on that sale on Steam since you mentioned it?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Psychonauts.
[SPEAKER_08]: Five bucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Guess who's buying it and not buying Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Psychonauts is a good choice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even the most hardcore of Minecraft fan would be hard to argue with you there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to load up this other story from Tigerclaw, but our internet's being a little wonky, but it's titled A Video Game Designed to Help Doctors to Recognize Drug Abuse.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell would that game be?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's using the same technology used to train FBI agents in interrogation tactics, a combination of self-disclosure and nonverbal cues.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game uses an actor's voice to stimulate a hypothetical conversation with a patient seeking, for example, pain relievers.
[SPEAKER_06]: The program generates responses based on the doctor's questions and the doctor must identify indicators of possible addiction or abuse based on the simulated patient appearing on screen before them.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this is something where you're the doctor, you're trying to recognize a patient that's asking for a drug who might be addicted to them.
[SPEAKER_06]: This sounds like L.A.
[SPEAKER_06]: Noire.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're looking for those hidden cues to let you know if there's a problem or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of weird in a way, but neat, I guess, that video games are being used out there in the real world.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to do it for Twitter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any other last-minute stories tonight, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, then that brings us to the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're ending a little bit early tonight, but that's because we unfortunately didn't have that interview happen, but hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Things happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really hope you guys out there enjoy the rest of your Memorial Day weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought before we wrap it up for tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Freaking steam and stuff on sale.
[SPEAKER_06]: taking all your money.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought tonight is be sure to check out Girls Gone Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: We love them.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're a great show and I was their guest this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I need to make sure that I plug that appearance at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: GirlsGoneWow.net Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Time for more Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys so much for downloading our show or listening live, however you are tuning in, and for supporting independent radio and independent broadcasting.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what we say, if you like what you hear, tell a friend or two or five about the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, Blender was telling me he brought in some friends of his from PlayStation Home to listen to the network tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's exactly the types of stuff we're looking for, so thank you to Blender, and thank you to everybody who is helping to spread the word.
[SPEAKER_05]: And no thank you to PlayStation Home for not upping the caps limit of their club.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we want to have everybody in our clubhouse, but we can only have 25 people, and it was maxed out a year ago, so I'm sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: But maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe things will change someday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're out of here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a wonderful week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will not be here live next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very important.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby will.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will not.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will see you live in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will be on the podcast feed next week, however, with a pre-tape show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hardcore, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a great week, everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Be safe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't be a dick.
[SPEAKER_06]: And good night.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_01]: To join us for a live show, tune in to vognetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_01]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next week!