[SPEAKER_08]: Tonight, May 6, 2012, Call of Duty Black Ops 2 is revealed, The Elder Scrolls Online is a reality, and we talk to video game hip-hop artist MegaRan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, my friends out there on the internet, and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are live with episode number 456.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's 456 of our show on this May the 6th.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's 5-6, 2012.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of you numerology skeptic people have a lot to look forward to in tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you to talk about numbers and video games and gaming culture and all that good stuff with my co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say hello first off to the one and only DarkSakura or Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_10]: To quote Eddie Izzard from Mystery Men, to paraphrase I should say, but money isn't dead, but money is life!
[SPEAKER_02]: Eddie Izzard was in Mystery Men?
[SPEAKER_10]: He was the leader of the Disco Boys?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was Eddie Izzard?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna be honest, I know this isn't the popular opinion, I didn't really care for that movie when I saw it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That movie was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was okay, but I saw it so long ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: Avengers, Avengers, Avengers.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other cynic voice you hear over there is the one and only Techmaster Loki!
[SPEAKER_03]: I have also not seen the Avengers.
[SPEAKER_02]: You both are lame.
[SPEAKER_02]: Snake360Dude
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we did have YYRs, who you're thinking of, and he was on the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I wasn't taking the interview because he did, you know, was he plugging the new game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he's kind of a listener of the show anyway, so it's weird to call that an interview.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of which, where is the new game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Where is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: He said it's being worked on, but I think he had some other stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Beggars can't be choosers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let him take his time.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, but anyway, tonight, we posted to Twitter earlier in the week, and we were like, hey, guys, who do you want us to interview on the show?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, within reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, we're not going to be able to get Reggie Fils-Aimé, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not, you know, a television network or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not going to get, you know, those folks.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so we kind of fielded some of the responses, and one idea that I really liked was getting
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a chick, I thought I was in love before, but I
[SPEAKER_02]: That song is called Splash Woman, and you can hear it in the background, like that riff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then he has some verses that he's laying down about Splash Woman, or his Splash Woman.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's brilliant.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I can't play the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't give that away because you got to go to his website if you want the whole thing there or iTunes or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's one of his bigger well-known songs, Splash Woman.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Capcom loved it, grabbed him, said, you got to do more.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he's got like a Mega Man 9.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's got a Mega Man 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're going to ask him about some of his other projects.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's not just a Capcom guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's got Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to talk to him a little later on in the show, 6.30 to be exact.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're a Mega Man fan who saw the shout-out on Twitter and all that, who's waiting for him to come on the show...
[SPEAKER_02]: 6.30 Pacific, 9.30 Eastern is when he's going to be here.
[SPEAKER_02]: But join our chat room because we are a live show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Random was awesome enough to agree to do a live interview.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so you can actually ask your questions live in our chat room, vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't ask them yet because I'll lose them before the interview starts.
[SPEAKER_02]: But when we get going, when we get random on the phone, you can ask those questions.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, anyhow, we do tape live every Sunday night at the Voice of Geeks or VOG Network right after the Bobby Blackwolf Show, 6 Pacific, 9 Eastern.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hope you'll join us live sometime, even if you missed our action-packed show tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Before we get into our gaming weeks, the type of video games we've been playing, we usually like to kind of have a kickoff topic, and we kind of got into it a little bit already, but everybody's talking about, everybody, everybody in the geek world is talking about the Avengers.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, I know you were there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you went and saw the Avengers movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a comic fan.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a Marvel fan.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Joss.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: And Joss Whedon.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a Joss Whedon fan.
[SPEAKER_02]: How was the Avengers movie?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was beautiful.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm sorry everybody if I sound kind of like a 12-year-old boy today.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've had allergies.
[SPEAKER_10]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: But, I mean, Jeremy Renner's ass.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, please.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wanted to reach out and touch it, but Dan was next to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: In full 3D.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, I have to tell you about what was running through my head the entire movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a new ship.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am totally sailing on the Hawkeye Black Widow ship because oh my god aren't there I know I know a lot of you don't read gossip websites but I think I read something about because you know I read all that trash I think I read something something about Jeremy Renner and Scarlett Johansson they've been flirty like there's pictures of them on the red carpet flirty so hmm
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're pretty.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet there's a lot of men out there that would like a shot at Scarlett Johansson, so you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's all because of him is the whole reason I went to see that Mission Impossible movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Him and Simon Pegg, because hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, I can say, first of all, because it's a Joss production, there is the Joss death.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will not tell you who.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Dan's like, it's going to be Hawkeye.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not spoiling, but it did make me go, damn you man!
[SPEAKER_10]: Like I did with Wash.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And stay during the credits.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was that meme you showed me earlier?
[SPEAKER_02]: One does not simply go to a Marvel movie and not stay through the credits.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly, because now keep in mind, I'm not just meaning the, because you know there's that lovely designed bit of credits where they give you the big stuff and the main guys who was in it, who were in it, sorry, and then they give you a preview for whatever the next one is, which I'm not going to spoil, but if nobody gets it, please ask me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will be more than happy to explain to you what it is and why you should pee your pants.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then... By the very end of the movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: And really listen very carefully to the dialogue right before the credits.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's all I'm having to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: TigerClaw in our chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chatters, don't spoil.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you spoil, you're getting kicked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take your spoiling to the private messages.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just double-click on somebody's name and you can private message them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can talk... Double-click on DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will gush to you while you're in the show, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Talk to her.
[SPEAKER_10]: But...
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to tell you, everybody in that movie was cast perfectly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to the chat room real quick at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tiger Claw says you're going to see a lot more of Jeremy Renner.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's taken over the Bourne movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Matt Damon Bourne Conspiracy, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those Bourne movies are pretty awesome, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm excited about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad you think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's better than Matt Damon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Matt Damon.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just didn't care about the Bourne movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Matt says, I give it to Joss Whedon.
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't mess it up because I had my doubts.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think there were a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you hear this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Over the weekend, not only the biggest opening weekend ever, which nobody thought Harry Potter, you know, part two or part eight or whatever could ever be topped, but 200 million plus for the Avengers this weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-mm.
[SPEAKER_02]: and this is the other real telling thing I thought Hunger Games beat that no, no, Hunger Games didn't beat it either I mean Hunger Games was huge but didn't beat it A plus CinemaScore and CinemaScore, those are the pollsters that go out and talk to the people right after the movie I actually polled for them once they were out in Roseville one time and I don't even remember what the movie was but they polled me on it
[SPEAKER_02]: and they actually take, you know, they grade it A plus rating from CinemaScore.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's huge because that means word of mouth is going to get out there that, hey, this movie doesn't suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go see it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And going to some other chats, Panaxium, I hope I pronounced that right, in the VOG Network chat room said, Avengers did something amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It combined multiple heroes in a single movie without breaking it.
[SPEAKER_10]: because hello, who else could do that but the Joss?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I have to say, I have to say, I have to say, everybody was characterized perfectly.
[SPEAKER_10]: The interaction was perfect.
[SPEAKER_10]: And for those of you who read Ultimates, yeah, it does take a little bit from the first, it really does seem like it's based a bit more off of Ultimates with a good splash of 616 Universe in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, it's really good.
[SPEAKER_10]: And no, the Hulk doesn't smash Jar Jar Binks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I'd pay to see that, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would pay for that Star Wars slash Avengers movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to tell everybody what my favorite line in the movie is, and it's not a spoiler, because they did the first half of it in the trailer.
[SPEAKER_10]: is this whole scene where Iron Man's flying back and the huge thing is flying behind him and he says, guys, I'm bringing the party to you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, the next scene is Black Widow standing there with this completely confused look on her face saying, I don't see how this is a party.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the best line in the whole movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let me go to a couple more comments from chat and then we'll move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a video game show, but look, we're all geeks at the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there was an Avengers video game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, actually, I was going to ask, where is the video game?
[SPEAKER_02]: It is coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Strike while the iron is hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, well, I guess the Avengers is something that's kind of always... Rush the game out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, that's perfect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's have a sub-party.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if you'd planned better, it would have been out for the movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want them to do something like Ultimate Alliance, honestly, because that was both...
[SPEAKER_10]: The second one did the whole Civil War thing and it was kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the first one, I love the gameplay in both of the games.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were just fantastic.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would totally dig an Avengers movie done in Ultimate Alliance style.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, so going to our chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a hater.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do have a hater in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, every big fandom is going to have its haters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ranma's in the chat room saying, Fuck Joss Whedon.
[SPEAKER_02]: James Cameron will come back strong with Avatar 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, because he came out strong with Avatar 1.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was some cheesy piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, look, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, because everybody bought into, oh my god, I have to see this in 3D, my eyes will be blown out of my head.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just such a terrible story.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one of those movies people don't want to admit they like, just like Titanic.
[SPEAKER_10]: Guys, may I please?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't worry about rip-offs and who's going to come out on top.
[SPEAKER_10]: There hasn't been a real original idea since the 60s maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're all going to take your money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's be real.
[SPEAKER_10]: One day we hit the day where all of the ideas have been used up and everything is derivative.
[SPEAKER_10]: Deal the fuck with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to make Titanic more 3D.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Deal with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Falling sunglasses.
[SPEAKER_02]: Technus in our chatroom says, this does mean that if they ever do an Avengers sequel or another Marvel movie without Joss Whedon, it will never be as good.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_10]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_10]: And honestly, given the big preview of the next movie, Joss has to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's nobody who can handle that except maybe, and please forgive me for saying this, Chris Claremont.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please tell me it's Buffy and the Avengers.
[SPEAKER_02]: No!
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll just have Treyarch do it, and then they'll add zombies.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, the only other person who I've seen handle characters like that, and yeah, he did kind of fuck up most of the modern Marvel stuff, but back in the day, Chris Claremont was the man.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's the one who gave us Dark Phoenix.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's the one who took X-Men from being, you know, just the crap of the bottom of the Marvel bin and made it the top A player it is now, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't mean to start a nerd war, but there are two movies I am looking forward to a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Avengers, I was like, okay, I don't really read a lot of Marvel, but I'm into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the Iron Man movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was good, and all the movies were good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll go see it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't want to see it opening weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: I knew the crowds were going to be insane.
[SPEAKER_10]: One thing Tiger Claw also did say, and let's not forget, Joss Whedon also wrote comics.
[SPEAKER_10]: He did write Astonishing X-Men when it came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: but there are two movies coming out that I'm really looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of them I'm going to get smack talked for and I don't even care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to see the Dark Shadows movie next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to see it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know people are like, it looks stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: The original soap opera was stupid and so was the 90s revival.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's what made it awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a little worried because I hated that Alice in Wonderland reboot but if they did it right, it's going to be a fun time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm looking forward to that cautiously.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Michelle Pfeiffer is a flaw-free goddess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Michelle Pfeiffer is a flaw-free goddess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Helena Bonham Carter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also a flaw-free goddess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go see Stardust to know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: With Michelle Pfeiffer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll see anything with her in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have that on HD DVD.
[SPEAKER_02]: I sat through an Oprah Book of the Month turned into a movie for Michelle Pfeiffer because I love her that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: and hello the best the only Catwoman which leads me to I am still excited a lot about this Batman movie really really excited about the third Batman movie you know I'm kind of two thoughts about that one but you know what preview I saw that I will be there to see because I love the original so much Frank and Weenie
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_10]: That looks adorable.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I freaking love Frank and Weenie, so shut up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't judge.
[SPEAKER_10]: I see you judging.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm judging a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stop judging me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Video games, as much as we love to talk movies and all that It's all about the Tron series starting in June Tron!
[SPEAKER_02]: We can all agree on that, Tron is king, yes Disney XD, I am there Finally, OLR Avengers assemble, Tron OLRians assemble Thank god we agree on something As long as I get to be Hawkeye There's no Hawkeye in Tron, you fool
[SPEAKER_02]: This should be Hawkeye and Tron.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I have to say, I have to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hurry up, we gotta get to games.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know why there were all these Disney trailers before?
[SPEAKER_10]: There were a bunch of Disney trailers before the Avengers movie because Disney bought Marvel.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they also did a whole series of superhero comic book covers, Duntron style.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I saw that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, they were epic.
[SPEAKER_10]: I loved them as Marvel.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyway, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, we are the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Join us in our chat, vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the Spider-Man trailer was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, games, games, games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Games hat.
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: What kinds of games did you play this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: I played Portal 2 because that's the only thing I could get to run because my internet has been crap all week.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's the last week before finals.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've also had a crap ton of design work to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: So Mass Effect came out of the box.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_10]: It didn't get played, but it got opened.
[SPEAKER_02]: You tease.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yes, Frankenweenie, really.
[SPEAKER_10]: Frankenweenie's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Zombie dogs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually did play through some Portal 2, and I played a little bit of WoW, but like, okay, this is what was so stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: I get in queue, and I'm sorry for going off on WoW stuff, but this just made me
[SPEAKER_10]: Fart, angry farts.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was trying to play WoW, and I was in queue.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I didn't realize how close I was to a level, so I did a cooking daily.
[SPEAKER_10]: Level, got kicked out of queue.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, shoot.
[SPEAKER_10]: At 13 minutes of waiting in queue, so I get kicked out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: So anyway, yeah, it did take me 13 minutes to do a cooking daily.
[SPEAKER_10]: um so then I get back in another queue and we all get in everything's happy we're in there yay queue and then oh I'm gonna leave log off fine offline what everybody leaves the party as soon as I get my quest I'm like all of you suck and I just logged off for the day dying 100 fires
[SPEAKER_10]: Make the fleas of a thousand camels nest in your genitals.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you didn't even get... Here I was waiting for you to talk about Warcraft and your anger rant about Children's Week.
[SPEAKER_10]: And speaking of things... I'm saving that for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I cannot get my Drake this year because of Children's Week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whores.
[SPEAKER_02]: She just wanted her virtual pony.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this like bring your child to your virtual world day?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it's bring your orphans into bloody battlegrounds and slay things in front of them and have a little five-year-old wander behind you while you're in the firelands.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's exactly like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like I was telling... That seems very unsafe.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was telling Becky, and Becky doesn't, she's not really into WoW, she doesn't play it, nothing of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was telling her about Children's Week and her reply was, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_10]: that's fucked up and it's the best place to when you have to do the five dailies thing the fastest place to get it done is Firelands if you're 85 so just run them through oh this thing is setting you on fire oh you're stabbing fire dogs in the face and little kids wandering behind you going this is cool
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you eat ice cream in front of them for an achievement.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, you do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Called bad example.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then you give them a gun and a kite.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never really thought about how messed up Blizzard is with this holiday, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of disturbing.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then you give all of the children toy swords and say, go back to the matron.
[SPEAKER_10]: She has to deal with you now.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're not my problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm not really understanding why this is a problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it because you have to make sure that they're safe?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or is it just like...
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Zeba in our chat room makes a great suggestion for DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just stop playing WoW then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Picaruna wants me to be on Horde House, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can arrange that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should come back on Horde House.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: HordeHouse.com is the spinoff show all about Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other games, Loki, I know you got something else to talk about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't play a while, so I play Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3, and honestly, that's all I really played this week because I only played it at work, and the rest of the time I've been working on my Portal 2 papercraft thing, which I'm almost completely, about 99% done with the body of the portal turret.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you see that amazing Portal cake that was out there on the internet with like a cake falling through a portal?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was on my Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You gotta see it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll find it and link my Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everyone should be looking at my Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Kuro Tsubasa.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, kind of a running theme throughout tonight with the, you know, our guest Omega Ran and the Fugo question we're gonna get into is, you know, creating art inspired by video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is it about, and you're basically making art based on Portal 2, granted it might be on a template that's already out there or whatever with your own flair,
[SPEAKER_02]: What is it about this game that makes you want to have a piece of it in the real world?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they're funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're funny little things.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if they sold those, I'd probably buy some.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't count the stuffed ones because they look stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm talking about like an actual, you know, if NECA, for example, made a full-size portal turret that talked in like, you know, shot airsoft BBs or something like that, I would probably buy two or three.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just kind of wanted to put it together just to try it because it was a cheap project.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, although now that I'm looking at, you know, okay, I want to look a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_03]: So now I have to use Bondo and Plex, or not Plex, uh, fiberglass, which sounds like a load of fun, except it's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, so I, I don't know if I'm going to do that or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, um, yeah, that's just fun right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did a Portal Tour in Maya as one of my final projects.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I remember seeing that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, that's what I did.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been looking at getting Portal 2 for... Redeeming my copy of Portal 2 on Steam that I have for my PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still have to do that or look at it or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if it doesn't work, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's so cheap now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure I can get it for a few bucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then I also want to get Skyrim on PC now too because of all the cool mods that they have.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I regret buying Skyrim on PlayStation 3 just because I'm missing out on all these darn mods.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought Sony said they were... Maybe I was just hallucinating but I thought Sony said they were going to bring some of the best ones to PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, what did they ever do with the Steam stuff for Portal 2?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I may do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess I played a little bit of the Perfect Strangers advergame thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I played it a few times because I liked reading the dream board that had a lot of references to having sex with very large women and stuff of that nature.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's pretty much all I played.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did want to play some Skyrim this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to go back, but I'm afraid if I dive back in, that's going to be another three months of my life.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's going to be more than three months, because by the time I get to about three months, they'll release the expansion.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Just over from there.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why I was like, oh, no, Skyrim Online.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or not Skyrim Online.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Elder Scrolls Online.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, ah, crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to have to play this, aren't I?
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I started reading up on it, and I was like, well, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: My Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a lot of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I played a lot of Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get that out of the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mass Effect 3, I'm playing more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of side missions, working on the main missions.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to a really awesome part in the story that I don't want to spoil for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll just say something involving the Citadel happened, and it was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the thing that gets me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am really into multiplayer in this game which you guys have to understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really play a lot of Xbox Live games online especially things that are kind of like shooters although I don't know if I'd call Mass Effect a shooter but it's a shooter.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a shooter RPG hybrid.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's more of a third person shooter now than it is an RPG.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess, but my point is, I can't think of a lot of games on Xbox Live outside of arcade games and music games, like Rock Band, that I've played online that I truly enjoyed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, one of the last ones is like Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: You wanna go back that far.
[SPEAKER_02]: with your pink guy but I love Mass Effect 3 online and I think a big part of that and the community is great sometimes I hear random people yelling at people across the room in their own house but you don't hear the same stuff like FU and the racial slurs and the sexuality slurs and things like that that typically are associated with Xbox Live I don't hear it in Mass Effect 3
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, yeah, the fact that it's co-op, I think really leads to a different kind of community for the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, I'm sure it's not perfect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every community has their, you know, dumbasses.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this game's pretty awesome so far from my experience.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm motivated to continue to play it online.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm still not motivated to spend money on those boxes, but I have been saving up credits and doing all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, Mass Effect, good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Mass Effect 3 gets a big endorsement from me I haven't gotten to that ending yet I still am not spoiled on the ending yet I've heard, you know, obviously all the complaints about it But let me tell you what I've been on this Mass Effect bandwagon I just started back in February And I sunk like 30 hours of Mass Effect 1 40 hours of Mass Effect 2 Maybe like 45 or 50 after all the DLC And so far I'm up to about 21 hours of Mass Effect 3 That doesn't even count the hours of multiplayer I played
[SPEAKER_02]: The endings could be monkeys flinging poo at each other, and that's not going to rob what was a great experience.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I might kind of go, wow, they really screwed that up, or kind of say, that was shitty, or compare it to the ending of The Sopranos, which wasn't that great either, but I'm not going to suddenly think, oh, I need to go return my copy of Mass Effect 3, it's so terrible, and the ending just ruined it for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to our chatroom at chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Excuse me, I almost said the old one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going to vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: TigerClaw says, Rob, I believe you have a crush on Kaden.
[SPEAKER_02]: Technus says, Mass Effect 2 was a completely different departure from the first Mass Effect game, but the more I played it, I like how more faster paced it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, I'm thinking about finding a way to cheat so I don't have to do the stupid mining on the side.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, here's the great news without spoiling Mass Effect 3 All that crap, out of the way All that crap, out of the way So, alright, one other game MegaRan's coming on in just a minute, we gotta call him But I do want to mention quickly another game I played this week A new game, Fez, on Xbox Live Arcade Because everybody's telling me Rob, this is like an 8-bit looking game with great music It's a puzzler, it is right up your fucking alley Go play this game
[SPEAKER_09]: You play Fez now?
[SPEAKER_09]: Fez is cool?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fez is cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, Doctor Who reference.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Doctor Who reference or not, it's a pretty fun game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quickly, the concept, it's the 2D world that you're in getting turned into a 3D world.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you basically rotate the screen like it's a cube and everything you thought was a 2D scroller is suddenly like has four different sides because you don't really go up or down.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's just like the four sides of a cube.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: How to unlock an antecube is in one of the achievements.
[SPEAKER_02]: Minor spoiler, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a gamer tip.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So a lot of depth to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I thought I saw Picaruno.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody in our chat said, yeah, I'm a little late to the show tonight because I was trying to get one of those freaking cubes in Fez to unlock.
[SPEAKER_02]: So apparently it's like Castlevania Symphony of the Night where there's a pretty easy game in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then just when you thought you beat it,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Video game, hip-hop artist.
[SPEAKER_02]: He goes by Random as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like Mega Ran because, you know, Mega Man and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And obviously, that was a lot of what he became famous for.
[SPEAKER_09]: But Airman can't be beaten.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, you know, we played a clip from Splash Woman earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to play another song of his a little later here after the interview.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a talented guy, really into the art.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he, you know, he's made it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Bobby joked on his show earlier, he got on SportsCenter with a rap about Jeremy Lin.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's not just restricted music.
[SPEAKER_02]: to video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, and I understand, even better, this guy is a teacher during the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's a teacher IRL, as we say, and he's this video game remixer on the side.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I want to talk to him about his art, and I want to open it up to you guys for your questions on vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's get random on the show right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've punched in his number, and we're giving him a call.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is live radio, folks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything can happen, just like the phone getting forwarded to an automatic voicemail.
[SPEAKER_02]: let's try it one more time maybe he was on the line and we're going to try that again real quick it is live and anything can happen on live radio and sometimes it might go to a voicemail let's try it one more time here
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he might be on the other line or something right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: These things happen in live radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll try him again in about three minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, if you're a friend of Mega's listening, you might want to tell him we're trying to get through.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Meanwhile, let's go to our first news story tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, I may cut you off if we can get through to Mega, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I just mentioned the Elder Scrolls Online.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's being developed by ZeniMax Online, not necessarily Bethesda, but it's owned by the same company.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it will be an MMO based on the Elder Scrolls series.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to take place on the entire land of Tamriel with some of the places being locked out initially because they're going to add them in expansions later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, um, you know, definitely a lot of worlds including, you know, Skyrim, um, and, uh, elsewhere and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, it's interesting though because actually this was from an article coming out of, like, the latest issue of Game Informer and they had kind of shown off a little bit, um, of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least some of the screenshots, uh...
[SPEAKER_03]: One thing I don't really care for about it is that it's a third-person perspective.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I know that's an option in the Elder Scrolls games to play as a third-person perspective, but I really like the first-person aspect of it, and I understand that the reason that they wanted to go that route is because it'd be less of a learning curve for people that are from other MMOs.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the problem is, though, they've made the game very similar to World of Warcraft, and that's kind of...
[SPEAKER_02]: Star Wars The Old Republic
[SPEAKER_02]: Elder Scrolls because of the Elder Scrolls engine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's try to go to Mega again, since it is 35 after right now, and it is live radio, and he could be anywhere right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: He could be in the basement writing his next hit, and the cell signal might not be catching.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's see if maybe he's come to the surface.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to try to get through again real quick here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh boy, that's really not good.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk more about Elder Scrolls Online while we try to fix that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, and then, let's see, they also, you know, they're showing off some of the different kind of artwork for the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of it's still very early, but, I don't know, it looks like a pretty cool game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just a little disappointed with the, you know, third person perspective thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then again, I guess I got used to it with Final Fantasy XI and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then some other stuff not necessarily related to the Elder Scrolls Online but Skyrim one of the rumored DLCs for it was supposed to be called Dawnguard well that's been officially announced now that Dawnguard will be the first expansion to Skyrim and it will be coming out this summer and of course being talked about during E3 and the rumors of course that it's going to feature
[SPEAKER_03]: and some other types of characters and races and stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Might even be cool if they have some of the... Because remember when they had this kind of a developer thing with Bethesda where it's like, okay, we're giving you a week to come up with this really cool shit for Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go!
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they had spear throwing and I want to say that the kill cameras for magic and stuff like that came out of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm pretty sure Crossbows probably will come out of that as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it would be neat to see some more of that stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they seem pretty creative, so I'm looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, also, we talked about this, I think, a little bit last week, but the Kinect update finally came out now for the Xbox 360, and they have 200 voice commands added.
[SPEAKER_03]: added in there as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ironically enough, not on the PC, even though there is Kinect on PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: That won't stop people from hooking up their microphones and streaming Fus Ro Dah!
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently there's already mods available.
[SPEAKER_03]: And here's the other weird thing, too, is you have to have Kinect in order for those voice mods to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't just use a headset, which is a little strange.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's how they did it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I'm going to try again here, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's cross our fingers and our toes that he's out of the bunker, wherever he's at right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my gosh, this is embarrassing, but these things happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it's live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything can happen live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: He's got a big project right.
[SPEAKER_02]: He just did some Kickstarter thing that made a ton of money.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw something on his Twitter about getting a voice actor to do some voices for his project right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I guess he's just a little busy right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we will keep trying here.
[SPEAKER_02]: in just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, Loki, you mentioned you're not too interested in this Elder Scrolls MMO.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just because, you know, I imagined, you know, okay, it's basically going to be like Skyrim, but instead of just being in the world of Skyrim, you're going to have, you know, a lot of players running around, and it's going to be all the time in real life.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of what I envisioned as, like, the MMO for the Elder Scrolls being like.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then it was like, okay, it's going to be a third-person perspective, and
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's going to have the hot bar, just like all the other MMOs.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: So basically you're copycatting everything that other MMOs are doing because you want to draw more people to it so that they're not afraid of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead of taking a risk and actually doing some stuff that would get the people that play your games normally...
[SPEAKER_03]: to try the MMO, which I think that would be smarter since there's a lot of people that buy the Elder Scrolls games, and I think that a lot of people that play World of Warcraft and stuff would be fine with, oh, it's first-person perspective.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a little bit fresh.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a little different of an idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead of like, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, oh, dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, go, next game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Click, click, click, click, click, click, click, dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I mean, it just sounds really boring.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why I don't play MMOs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, it's hard to say without seeing the game in action, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's an important part of it, is that without really being able to see the game in action, it's hard to judge it, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, we are judging this off a few screenshots and what we do know about the engine, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I guess, but I'm very unlikely to probably play this game now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I guess let's try Mega again.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been 10 minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, it's deducting money from the Skype thing every time I try.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't afford too many more tries, but I promised you guys an interview, so I'm going to do everything I can.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to feel real bad if you MegaRan fans tuned in and we got to reschedule it, but let's try it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to try one more time to get through here.
[SPEAKER_02]: After all, it is live radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it's been forwarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is the phone even on?
[SPEAKER_02]: Mega's phone may just not be on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe he was trying to nap.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's just so tired that the darn phone isn't even on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I'm going to send a tweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually already did.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I tweeted him.
[SPEAKER_02]: So hopefully he's going to see that and say, whoops.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's this one place in my house I can't stand or I'll lose cell signal.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was standing in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we do have more stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do have some more stories we can go over.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think we'll go ahead and get to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, why don't you read one for us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: How about Irrational and their desire for a Bioshock movie?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, they wanted to do a Bioshock movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: They had somebody lined up.
[SPEAKER_10]: They had one Carlos Fresnadillo, and he walked out saying that the video game company and the studio had to reach an agreement about the budget and the rating.
[SPEAKER_10]: So now we have Gore Verbinski behind it, who wants to make it really scary, but the studio doesn't want to pay for it, really.
[SPEAKER_10]: He wants to do a rated R version.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not at all interested in PG-13 or anything less.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, basically the quote was, the little sisters and injections and the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just wanted to really, really make it a movie where four days later, you're still shivering and going, Jesus Christ.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say though, is Hollywood really ready for something like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because let's be real, some of the themes in Bioshock and especially with the little girls and the killer robots might be a bit much for some people.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I realize there's a lot of sick films out there, but this might be pushing it for some people.
[SPEAKER_10]: We can have some kids out there killing each other with bows and arrows, but I guess it's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I would see it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I watched Dan play through Bioshock because he was busy playing it and I couldn't play it while he was playing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, of course, I don't mind stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's not the human centipede, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, my friend is so excited about the third one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh God, they're making a third one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of movies that have no redeeming... 150 people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Movies with no redeeming qualities whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_10]: She and her grandmother love the human centipede.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's like the grandmas watching the Kim Kardashian sex tape.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've met my friend Carly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's her.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think that they're casting anybody from over here.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's gonna be CG, you know that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think it will be.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyway, I would see this.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't have the budget for CG.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would see a Bioshock movie tying it back in before I would see any of the human centipede movies.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, seriously, how long is it going to be before we get the porn version where it's just a hundred person train?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's been done.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, isn't that what inspired the dude to make the movie anyway?
[SPEAKER_10]: Was watching bad porn with, you know, a chain?
[SPEAKER_02]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's what I'm going to do, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Since it's 6.45 and it's 15 minutes after the time we scheduled MegaRan, I'm going to give it one more try.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this will be the sixth try.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if we don't get through this time, I don't know what to tell you guys because that's six times in 15 minutes and we're still not getting through.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's all cross our fingers and think happy thoughts about MegaRan and maybe he'll get through this time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's go ahead and give it one more go here on the network.
[SPEAKER_02]: I better, you know, I... Oh, that's killer.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's killer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just gonna... I'm gonna do that whole, like, panicking thing, like, am I calling the right number?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did I put the right number into Skype?
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's da-da-da, da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, it's the same number, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the number.
[SPEAKER_02]: Perhaps you should leave him a message.
[SPEAKER_02]: You see...
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's leave a message.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will go do that on my regular cell phone because the number will go out if I do it here.
[SPEAKER_02]: So why don't I go grab my cell phone I'm going to give MegaRan a call and I'm going to give him the OLR number and I'm going to say call it whenever you're ready.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: That way you MegaRan fans hopefully don't have to leave home disappointed tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm going to go do that right now and I realize I owe you guys a story but maybe Loki will cover it for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will forgive him if he's watching Avengers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, maybe you could cover the story for me, and I'm going to go give MegaRan a call on my personal line.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you know how they have layaway and stuff like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Microsoft kind of wants to do something similar to that for their Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is a rumor now that there's going to be some sort of contract subsidized Kinect bundle available starting next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: and what this is basically going to be is it's going to be like going in and buying like a cell phone or a cell phone plan.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get the cell phone at a very big discount and then of course you are locked into a contract for two years and you have to pay your monthly fees and that's how you're able to get like an iPhone for $200 or one that normally costs about $600 or $700.
[SPEAKER_03]: XBOX Live Gold Service
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it would be a way to kind of get people in the door to buying a system and being able to play with it for a couple years without having to drop $400 right away.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, you will be paying a little bit more for the system than you would normally if you bought it outright, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's more of a convenience.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you kind of figure that you're going to have service fees and stuff like that for a cell phone.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it kind of makes sense that it's going to be slightly more.
[SPEAKER_03]: About $460 after the end of the service agreement.
[SPEAKER_03]: The good thing is that at least it's the slim systems now and not the old systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because some of those old systems might not last two years.
[SPEAKER_03]: But...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it's an interesting idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: It could work, especially if you get people to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just going to, I don't know, it'll be interesting to see how that works out.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, people paying $15 a month.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I guess that's not too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, $15 is like a lunch, two lunches.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you can spare a couple lunches a month, I mean, you can be playing Xbox games for a couple years.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's an idea, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'm back from making that phone call.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'll let you guys know what happens.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really apologize to the MegaRan fans.
[SPEAKER_02]: These things happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's live radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: He legit could be somewhere with no cell service right now, just unplanned.
[SPEAKER_02]: Haven't you ever been with your phone somewhere and you thought, oh, I'll be able to make a call or whatever, wherever I'm at, and then suddenly, oh, no cell signal?
[SPEAKER_02]: That could be happening with MegaRan.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could have a cell phone like mine that just for some reason, you have to reboot it every once in a while because...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and so maybe he'll just pop up during the show so we'll see so we'll let you know all right anyhow back to the Xbox story and the $99 Xbox so I just want to point something out with this
[SPEAKER_02]: When the Diablo World of Warcraft annual pass went live in October of last year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you forgot what that's all about because you're not a WoW player, you sign up for a 12-month agreement of World of Warcraft and you get Diablo 3 for free.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you get a mount and you get into the beta and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: One little thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Finals week is not the best week to launch this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, back when that happened, I said, hey, you know, it's just a matter of time before other folks in gaming jump in on this bandwagon of tying you to these cell phone contract style agreements.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, granted, I didn't think about the system element.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had thought, oh, well, sign up for two years of Xbox Live Gold and get free Halo maps or a free game or something like that, a giveaway and all this.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here we are.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're seeing the first kind of cell phone deal arrangement type thing now coming to consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me take it a step further.
[SPEAKER_02]: This might be some people's nightmares here, but let me take it a step further.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're about a year away from a whole nother round of consoles coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not just the Wii U, but the Xbox, whatever they call it, and the PlayStation 4, whatever they end up calling that.
[SPEAKER_02]: These systems will have cutting edge technology are probably going to be expensive as hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, a lot of people balked at the $599 price that was set for the PlayStation 3 when it first rolled out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what if PlayStation now has a way that they could lower that price?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they could come out at E3 and they could say, we're releasing the PlayStation 4 for $199 with a two-year PlayStation Plus agreement.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: The thing is, say if I didn't have a system and I was looking at doing this, this is not a bad deal because I'm already buying, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: XBOX Live Gold
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you own an iPhone, and I'm one of them, I'm just as much of a sucker as anyone else.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you own an iPhone, then you're paying like a $10 a month premium on your bill that's basically the iPhone tax.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care because my phone is sexy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's a hell of a phone.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I have to say, for everyone who's saying Diablo 3 and WoW, to quote Voginator, kiss outside in any sense of social life goodbye, just saying, been playing WoW and Diablo 3 beta and the WoW beta and I work full time and I go to school and I do design work on the side and guess what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I still go out for pink berry and get laid.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's possible.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm going to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a great way to cap it all off, by the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's possible.
[SPEAKER_10]: Time management.
[SPEAKER_10]: Learn those skills.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you have this show.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I have this show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_10]: And potentially another little project with the lovely Sylve.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't bite off more than you can chew, but I do love me some still.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, going to our chatroom at vognetwork.com That's right, Panaxium.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am a time management pro.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shadow Next Gen says the PlayStation 4 will not be $699.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just throwing it out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is an iPhone?
[SPEAKER_02]: A little iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: What does the iPhone cost, unsubsidized?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you get an iPhone direct through AT&T, how much does this sucker cost?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll tell you, because in California and one other state, you have to pay the tax on the unsubsidized amount because that's the way our laws are set up.
$699.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just bought a new Android phone to replace my crappy Android phone, and it's basically the equivalent of the iPhone 4S, but an Android.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a Samsung Galaxy 2...
[SPEAKER_03]: or Samsung Galaxy S2 or something like that and luckily I bought mine used so I got it for about $300 but I mean it's still fucking expensive
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I'm looking through some more comments in our chatroom at vognetwork.com Let's see, RossDLUT says, of course the PlayStation 4 won't be $699.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony learned that mistake.
[SPEAKER_02]: Think about what I'm saying though, RossDLUT.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's a way for them not to make that mistake, yet still charge that price.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would all depend though, because if they're trying to recoup that cost in two years, that's a little bit more than recouping $200 or $300.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's recouping double that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're talking $50 a month payments.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's still a little bit much.
[SPEAKER_02]: WhatUpG in our chatroom at VOGnetwork.com says, Then again, they kept the Vita price at $249, but that sounded good until Nintendo dropped the 3DS price.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a good point.
[SPEAKER_02]: They released the Vita cheaper than a lot of people thought they would, and it sounded great.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, no, the DS is now cheaper.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It still wasn't that bad because they couldn't drop the price of the system anymore, but they added value to it by including a gig memory card.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Vita's still a sexy piece of hardware.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, 3DS is too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not knocking it, but the 3DS doesn't do Skype.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Vita does the web a little better.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some things that the Vita does have on the 3DS right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I will say 3DS has some pretty must-have games right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I own them both.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ross Steel UT in chat says, Sky, will the rent-to-own crowd be big enough?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, I'm going to point to the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: iPhone's the biggest phone out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whether you hate Apple or love Apple, you can't deny iPhone is a huge deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I bet Sony would be very happy to have as many PlayStation 4s sold as iPhones.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what are iPhones?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're subsidized by contract.
[SPEAKER_02]: hmm it could happen all right anyhow moving on let's travel around the world and check out some release dates and what is coming out to a gaming store near you
[SPEAKER_02]: Starhawk
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, that's a pretty quick week.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's the next big, big title coming out?
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be the week after Max Payne 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Herp Derp Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, you mean Max Payne 3, The Rise of Bruce Willis?
[SPEAKER_02]: I always forget because with the whole annual pass thing, I don't have to actually save the money to buy Diablo 3, which is kind of nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, then, you know, beyond that... There's another $15 a month thing I pay for.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, also, the Game of Thrones game is going to be coming out next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the week after next as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: One does not simply pre-order the Game of Thrones games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It should be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's by the guy that did, you know, the actual books.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, at least he wrote the story for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's got characters that aren't... It's kind of like the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Enter the Matrix of the Game of Thrones series.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's two characters that aren't really in there, but then they're probably going to cross into the series.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, I'm trying to load up the Japanese release dates, but like a lot of things on this show tonight, it just doesn't want to work, so maybe we can go to Europe real fast.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, maybe we can, although it's only a few, so you better hope it loads quickly.
[SPEAKER_10]: On May 9th in the UK, we have Datura, which, I'm sorry, looking at that name, it makes me think of all of the times I read Clan of the Cave Bear, because that's what they called, like, this one herb in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: On the 11th, we have Starhawk and Street Fighter X Tekken for PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then that's it for this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, there's some pretty decent stuff coming out, but that's about, you know, that's really it for this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got Japanese release dates for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: But remember that whole golden week we were talking about last week?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's over.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, nothing this week unless you're into Starhawk, which some of you are.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get a chance to check that out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it for Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a few more stories for you guys, then we'll get to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk a little bit about Call of Duty Black Ops.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, we talked about the rumors and the leaked dates and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently they were correct.
[SPEAKER_03]: I honestly thought it was called Eclipse.
[SPEAKER_03]: And actually it is technically called Eclipse.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was the internal name for the game, as I found out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's a little truth to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: but yes, Black Ops 2 will be coming out this year on November 13th and of course on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, PC confirmed I'm guessing there's probably going to be a Vita and maybe a Wii U version or something like that but of course all that stuff will be announced later on
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Unmanned Warfare
[SPEAKER_03]: and so very interesting looking thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of the new stuff that they're going to be adding to the actual campaign of the game including some branching missions and these new type of missions called like
[SPEAKER_03]: Strikeforce where it's almost like a little bit open world I kind of imagine a little bit like the crisis stuff where you kind of have a point A point B but there's kind of all these different ways you can approach things so that sounds kind of interesting and then of course they're going to be adding the standard multiplayer stuff and there's supposed to be some other branching storyline stuff as well
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, I'm pretty excited about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: After seeing the trailer for it, it looks pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: So definitely this is something I'm going to pick up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And actually, it kind of makes me want to go back and play the first Black Ops, so I'm probably going to end up doing that as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you think that there's actually going to be money to make off of sales of the old copy then, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably, because the storyline does tie into the first game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, it should be mentioned that Black Ops 2 Day 1 pre-orders were actually higher than Black Ops and Modern Warfare 3 pre-orders.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, it's off to a good start.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, guess what, guys?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have some great news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guess who just called me?
[SPEAKER_02]: Random, awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he said he apologizes.
[SPEAKER_02]: This has happened to you, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: The phone died.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he had to go plug in.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we're going to get him on now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you guys for being patient.
[SPEAKER_02]: And those of you that left, well, tough cookies.
[SPEAKER_02]: For those of you loyal OLR listeners, look, it's ringing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to hear Random or MegaRan right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, is this MegaRan?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: What is up?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Rob from Orange Lounge Radio here with DarkSakura and Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: How's it going?
[SPEAKER_02]: The artist Random, also MegaRan, joining us live.
[SPEAKER_06]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, I'm good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had an adventurous day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry I'm late.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is A-OK, because that's how you know you're a real celebrity is when you're showing up fashionably late.
[SPEAKER_02]: These things happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't even worry about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just happy that you're here on the air.
[SPEAKER_02]: And hey, if you guys have a question for Ranma, join our chatroom at vognetwork.com and you can ask that question in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But while you guys get those questions out there, I got some questions for Ranma that I want to ask.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, Ranma, some of our listeners here at Orange Launch Radio, they might be gamers, but they might not know about you.
[SPEAKER_02]: So how do you describe yourself to the uninitiated?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm pretty much a gamer, teacher, and musician who makes hip-hop that combines all of those things together.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, just my love for games and my love for music and culture and history.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I put it all together and make, I think, what I believe to be some pretty cool music.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of it is video game based.
[SPEAKER_06]: What I do is I like to use the traditional...
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds from video games, some of my favorites like Mega Man or Final Fantasy or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then create all new creations and add lyrics on top of them, usually about the game, sometimes about my own life and interesting stories and anecdotes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I put it all together and wrap it up and put a nice little bow on it, and that is Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you want to check out the music, of course, you can visit Random or Megaran's website, www.megaran.com, where some of his tunes are available for download.
[SPEAKER_02]: And some of them are free, like the one we're going to play here in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So free is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for providing that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a question.
[SPEAKER_02]: Free is always good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you teach?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I taught middle school.
[SPEAKER_06]: I taught language arts, so basically reading, writing.
[SPEAKER_06]: and history, social studies, stuff like that to middle school kids.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've actually picked like two of my favorite subjects ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm a big history nerd and a grammar fiend.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my, totally.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I've done that for probably the past like seven years or so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Up until this past year when I finally decided to take the leap of faith and make music full time and here I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: So far I feel good.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's really inspiring to be able to do that and do what you love because Ranma, I got to tell you, I'm a teacher too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a different type of teacher.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a corporate trainer.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I teach people in my company and that's my day job.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I've had this podcast with my buddies for 10 years and I'd love to be able to quit.
[SPEAKER_02]: As much as I love my day job, I'd love to be able to quit and do this gig full time.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you're doing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're living the dream and that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and I mean, I think I try to always apply a lot of the stuff that I learn and that I do in teaching as well in music.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there's always lessons and things.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love history, I love poetry, so I try to combine a lot of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of my favorite books I will talk about and rap about them.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's important to try to use, because I love teaching as well, so I don't want to make it like I didn't love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was already doing what I loved.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just a matter of something else that I loved, kind of taking precedence, that's all.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I gotta say, and this is something no one probably knows, the game that
[SPEAKER_06]: I first decided, or the music that moved me to try to create my own music was actually Goonies 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game was great.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a good game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It had a really cool soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I had a Casio keyboard.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that was the first theme music that I used to try to replay on my keyboard.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still remember it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I used to try to recreate that on my keyboard.
[SPEAKER_06]: and so not knowing when I'm 10, 11, 12 years old that I was actually making what is now considered to be fan art but it was just me playing it by ear and having that music stuck in my head and making me want to create.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't necessarily do anything with that but that was the first time that I ever experienced video game music that actually touched me enough to make me want to try to create my own version of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, I really love that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huge, plenty of hours of fun on that game
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Final Fantasy VII was a huge game for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was pretty much out of gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: When it came out, I was in college, and I was totally concentrating on school.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't have time for games anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't have a system until I watched one of my friends or suitemates play it, and I was completely hooked.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw some of the summons and just watched about an hour of the gameplay, and it completely redefined
[SPEAKER_06]: roleplaying games to me because, you know, the 3D aspect and just the character development was just so awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I wound up, you know, getting the PlayStation, almost flunking out of school playing this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's just something that completely enveloped me.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's a huge part of my childhood, you know, so that's what made me go back because the music, the story, the gameplay, everything is just so memorable to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: that it changed the game to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, that was my introduction, well, kind of reintroduction to gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so that was the game that got me back into console gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I feel like I owe a lot to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I decided to do a little homage to it called Black Materia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Luckily, a lot of people liked it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It came out last year and kind of took off a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: That might be part of the reason why I wound up quitting my job and doing music is because the demand for it and for performances after that
[SPEAKER_06]: Just became too much to handle with a full-time job.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it was just my way of giving back to something that was a big part of my childhood.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, I think a big part of why that took off for you is you probably aren't the only one out there that has some memories tied to that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that was a huge game for me in college.
[SPEAKER_02]: I probably failed a class or two because Final Fantasy VII, but it was so worth it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which maybe I shouldn't be telling the teacher.
Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_10]: Final Fantasy 7 came out when I was super broke and couldn't afford a PlayStation my roommate had one and I bought the game not owning a PlayStation I had a SNES I was still playing Chrono Trigger but I played the stew out of that and did time that Knights of the Round did with Quadra Magic and the repeater thing did go long enough for me to make a sandwich
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, you're not the only one to be inspired by Journey either, but the way you've translated this into hip-hop is something else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell me more about the process of creating Journey, a hip-hop excursion.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh man, that was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, as you said, a lot of people were really touched and moved by the Journey video game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was told and emailed constantly about playing the game, but I just didn't have enough time and people were like, you gotta play it, you gotta play it, you're gonna love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's all I need is another game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have games here that are unopened that I haven't been able to get to yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're like, no, that's the best thing about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an hour-long experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just sit down, you play it, and you'll love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played it, and I was instantly inspired.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's a great game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so cool how they just created the entire scenario.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, there's no dialogue whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're basically creating your own story and synopsis.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's just such an experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even know any other way to describe it except an experience because it just kind of immerses you.
[SPEAKER_06]: So when I wound up playing the game through, I think, twice, then I went and bought the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I had a whole day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I was just trying to raise funds for Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we had gotten to a really certain level.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it was maybe $10,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: and usually when I get to the round numbers, I try to give some sort of a surprise gift for the support.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, as I was playing the Journey soundtrack, I said, well, why not work on making some hip-hop beats?
[SPEAKER_06]: So, the entire day, I sat down, I used a program called Reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, what I do is just pick the sounds, record them into the program, try to modulate them a little bit, stretch them out, slow them down, filter them, add some drums, take out some things, you know, bring them back in later.
[SPEAKER_06]: and wound up creating some really cool beats with a very ambient kind of contemplative kind of feel.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that was really what I wanted to create.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it came out pretty well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still listen to it a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you got props from the original musician who did the music for Journey, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw that tweet on your website.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Austin Winstery actually listened to it and told me he liked it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Told me it was a great job.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you gotta love Twitter for that reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just that everything is so accessible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody's one click away.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I guess it just got to the point where so many people were talking about my Journey remixes that they contacted him about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, hey Austin, have you heard this?
[SPEAKER_06]: And so that's kind of what made him respond.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so that was really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, props from the man himself.
[SPEAKER_06]: You really can't beat that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I gotta say, don't we know that about the Twitter thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because this whole interview tonight is being brought to you by Twitter.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, we say we are the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we went to Twitter and we said, hey, tweets, who do you want to see on the show?
[SPEAKER_02]: And Wilco, gotta give him props, tweeted us and said, get Mega Ran on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here we are.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here we are.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta thank Wilco, he made this whole thing happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell me a little bit about what this Kickstarter was all about, and you made it.
[SPEAKER_02]: How did the community help you achieve your goals with language arts?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the community was just humongous.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't... Well, we've done a Kickstarter in the past, like I said.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've done one for... Actually, two.
[SPEAKER_06]: We did one to create vinyl for Forever Famicom album, which is our Nintendo tribute album.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then...
[SPEAKER_06]: We did another later to play a show in London at the London Anime Con.
[SPEAKER_06]: And both of those went decent.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got our goals.
[SPEAKER_06]: We didn't get necessarily way over the goal, but we did pretty well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I decided to go back and try it again.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was one of those things where Kickstarter's kind of becoming pretty trendy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody's doing it these days.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like you said, it's a big buzzword in the industry right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Video game companies are making thousands, hundreds of thousands of dollars on it right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so I always told myself I wouldn't go back to Kickstarter unless I had a really great project idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: So instead of it just being an album, which I've been working on for the past two years, almost three years now, I wanted to make it a full experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: So instead of just an album, it would be an album, a video game, and a comic book.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, of course, I can't do all that on my own without
[SPEAKER_06]: having artists and developers help me out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I want to be able to compensate those guys for helping out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that then came Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I decided to try to raise $3,000, which actually would have been nowhere near the amount that I really wanted to gain to get this.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I said, we'll start small.
[SPEAKER_06]: And lo and behold, the campaign just ended Friday at $15,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: So
[SPEAKER_06]: A 516% completion rate.
[SPEAKER_06]: And just from the response has been overwhelming.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, from Facebook, Twitter, to just the guys on my email list.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went out to PAX East and performed.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was probably right before the Kickstarter really got underway.
[SPEAKER_06]: I told a lot of people about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And people were like, hey, I'm going to support.
[SPEAKER_06]: And sure enough, they did.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had over 300 backers.
[SPEAKER_06]: who are really excited to hear the music as well as to play the game and to read the comics.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think I want to take what I do and just take it to a new level and that's what hopefully this Kickstarter has allowed us to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I want to do this in a whole new way and this could be the album that kind of defines me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've done a lot of Final Fantasy stuff, I've done a lot of Mega Man stuff with other people's intellectual property but I really want to
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's an amazing and really lofty goal and just kind of cool to have like this comic book and video game and album that all tie together yet it's not like it's not some movie franchise being turned into this or some you know it's you it's your story that's awesome that's awesome right that's what's cool about it I wanted to make it based on my story now granted the the
[SPEAKER_06]: Game and the comic, they get a little unrealistic, but it's basically based on my story, and they are interweaving a bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: The album's much more, I guess, realistic.
[SPEAKER_06]: I kind of take that hero and liken him to kind of more of a daredevil, Matt Murdock, where he's just a regular guy with just, you know, some cool abilities, but
[SPEAKER_06]: for the most part a regular guy, he's not flying around shooting beams out of his eyes.
[SPEAKER_06]: But in the game, of course, you know, to make things a lot more interesting, there's a lot more powers that come into it and the comic as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's taking my story and my own original story and original characters that myself and the guys at J1 Studios created and creating a universe around it, you know, like almost a franchise, you know, so it's
[SPEAKER_02]: That is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looking forward to seeing that in the coming months at Megaran.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll have more information on that when it's out, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Random, I know we're a little past our time here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully I'm not keeping you from anything, but we are the show where every gamer has a voice, and we wanted to open it up to our listeners to ask Random some questions tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Random, you have a minute for just a couple questions here from our listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, VOGnetwork.com if you want to ask some questions in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me get to an email question we got earlier in the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is from Will O. Sent us an email that says, and he mentioned in his email that Ranma has a style that just seems effortless and his sincerity bleeds through each track.
[SPEAKER_02]: He honestly seems to love what he's doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I just wanted to throw that out there that that's coming across.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the question, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think it would be possible to be doing what you're doing before the age of social media?
[SPEAKER_02]: How have tools such as Twitter and Kickstarter changed the way you work on projects and create music or tour?
[SPEAKER_02]: So I know you've touched on the Kickstarter a little bit, but back to the question, could you do what you're doing without social media?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I really don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole MegaRam story started because of social media.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was contacted on Myspace in 2007 by Capcom.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if not for social media, I don't know if I'd be here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do owe a lot to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm hugely, hugely grateful to the advent of social media.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it would make it to me a little more fun going out and doing the old school method because I do that a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's kind of what sets me apart and has enabled a lot of success is that I'm not only all over social media, but I perform live probably at least one or two times a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm out at live events, I'm out passing out flyers, I'm out shaking hands, I'm out meeting people.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's not just social media, but I feel like social media is a huge part of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But like I said, I think my leg up comes from the fact that I'm out and about in the community physically making appearances as well as taking full advantage of social media.
[SPEAKER_02]: MC Lars, I've learned so much from a guy, MC Lars, that he's always told me that you gotta get out and play, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to get out and play.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody's got the internet at this point, so you gotta have something that sets you apart, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: getting out and playing as much as possible is a huge, huge part of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let me get to some questions from our chat room at the VOG, or excuse me, vognetwork.com and I'm going to go to a question from Actdeft first and I think this is a good question.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll take this question to the next level.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who is MegaRan's favorite video game music composer?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta say, I'm going to go back a little bit and
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to say my favorite is Yuzo Koshiro.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's done from Streets of Rage to the Actraiser stuff to Super Adventure Island.
[SPEAKER_06]: and a lot of those great 16-bit titles, Yuzo Koshiro is my favorite.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're officially my hero.
[SPEAKER_02]: He is the bomb.
[SPEAKER_02]: We know Yuzo very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wangan Midnight Maximum Tune is amazing music.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, Actraiser.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Maximum Tune 2 soundtrack is my chosen soundtrack for all trips to LA, just saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my God, it's amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I'm going to go listen to that tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Excellent, excellent.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to another question from Breakman, you know, because you're very well known for the Mega Man stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Breakman wants to know, I want to know what is Mega Ran's favorite Mega Man theme?
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I could go with the easy choice.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a couple that, you know, everybody loves.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Mega Man 2, WALL-E, Stage 1, everybody loves that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love it too, but it's not necessarily one of my favorites.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Woodman's theme, honestly, from Mega Man 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another one that tends to come up a lot in my subconscious that I wind up humming is Bomb Man from Mega Man 1.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what else?
[SPEAKER_06]: Crashman.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Crashman.
[SPEAKER_06]: Crashman is great.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's so many, and as you notice, the majority of those that are my favorites, I've never used them, or I've never intended to remake them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Crashman, I just think it's so awesome that I wouldn't want to touch it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, WALL-E, Stage 1, same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mega Man 3, title screen, same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just so great as is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Proto Man's theme, another one I love.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, there's so many great ones, but I would try not to
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Random, I gotta say, I think you'd do him justice based on the Mega Ran 9 album, but I totally understand and respect where you're coming from.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me get one more question from chat that I got, and I know where this guy's going with this name, but the name is iFarTed.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a great name in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: He wants to know...
[SPEAKER_02]: Is there any game that MegaRan hasn't tackled yet that he more or less has an eye on?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm afraid of questions like that because I don't want to answer it and then a couple things can happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: One, someone just takes it and does it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or two, I could never get to it and people are like, hey, what happened to that thing you mentioned?
[SPEAKER_06]: But I will say I have two that my eyes are on.
[SPEAKER_06]: the Metal Gear Solid series and Legend of Zelda particularly A Link to the Past so those are what my eyes are on right now but the next plan though for next year is myself and K Murdock we're doing an all Sega album called Sega State or Sagacity and it's going to be all Sega so from Master System to Genesis to Saturn to Dreamcast
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be all Sega all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'll be our next one.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Metal Gear Solid is one that I really want to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: But story-wise, that's just such a thick story that I don't really know if I could do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it would still be something I'd have to really go knee-deep into, like Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_06]: which is something that took like a year to make.
[SPEAKER_02]: You got some people in chat that are supporting you on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you have a day of screaming, yes, Metal Gear, do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, we're way over time here and I want to get to Mega Ran's song here but quickly, one last question from DarkSakura here in the studio.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had a question if you would ever take a request for Down the Line.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've taken requests before.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, the official game of Orange Lounge Radio is The Guardian Legend.
Oh,
[SPEAKER_10]: So could we hope to have you tackle that someday?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I really, you know what, I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did a Guardian Legend track.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, you guys gotta, you gotta look for, what is the song?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, there's a song called Contact, C-O-N-T-A-C-T, and it's all about con etiquette, and it uses the Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all about rules and regulations for when you go to cons, what you should and shouldn't do.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Guardian Legend, I have to say, is my favorite game of all time, only followed by Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so Oh my god, those are some great games, like, I love Guardian Legends So you were on the top of my hero list now Well, look, we got random way past time here And, you know, we got off to a late start tonight But random, you know, I want to really thank you for taking the time out To come on Orange Lounge Radio tonight and talk about your music Again, if people want to know more about your music They can check you out at Megaran.com And you can also get the music at MegaranMusic.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Random, is there anything else you want to plug here on the show before we get to the song?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything I want to plug?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Follow me on Twitter, at MegaRam.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's MegaRamMusic on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for the support.
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep listening.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Language Arts album will be out for everybody May 22nd, so mark that on your calendar.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'll see you out in the funny papers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, take care buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, we're going to close out here with a track from Mega Ran and this is actually a really special deal here.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is actually a duet that he did with MC Frontalot, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can check this out at MegaRanMusic.com It's Random and MC Frontalot with Wake Up here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check this out.
... ...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Wake up, don't tell me it's time to wake up, snoring like a bulldozer, going like the brick
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: That is Random or MegaRan with Wake Up here on Orange Launch Radio and that song features MC Frontalot.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a great song and it's a great message too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, you know, get up or you ain't gonna eat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an inspirational song and that was a great interview.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even if it started a little late, it was worth the wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, you should get up because you might not shower.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to get up from playing games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some people shower before bed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'll have that con funk that he talks about in the Guardian Legends song.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, he's already said hi on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not Facebook, on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Totally follow him on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to know, why did he tweet Anime Jam Session?
[SPEAKER_02]: He wasn't on Anime Jam.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's all good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ranma was helping me screen the questions, actually, so he does get props and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Listen to Anime Jam Session.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a good show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I don't know how I missed the Guardian Legend one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's got a lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is going to be on my iPhone soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if you want that song on your iPhone or wherever it is that you listen to music, that particular song we just played there, Wake Up, that's free.
[SPEAKER_02]: Megaranmusic.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And thanks again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Write on from Wilco on Twitter for suggesting it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Write on to the management for setting that up and for Random for appearing on our show tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: And since I decided I was going to back the MegaRan language arts video game and comic project Kickstarter, we will also be probably later on giving out a physical signed copy of Language Arts Volume 1 on CD as well as a signed comic to a lucky listener.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Giving.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm looking at the whole album on iTunes, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of giveaways, I was going to wait a little while, but for those of you that are sticking around, because I knew some people would just be here to listen to Megaran and then hit the road, which I understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_02]: But for those of you loyal folks that stick around, I might have a little present for you coming up in Part B. So just stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll get into that in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not as good as what Loki just talked about, but it's still pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got to get back into some news.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're running late now, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was worth the wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: It is going to be what they call the first tablet to offer an attachable console-quality gamepad controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's pictures of this on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just imagine the most giant, stretched Xbox controller you ever saw in your life where you slammed an iPad in the middle.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what this thing looks like.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, it looks a lot better than the one that Razer was looking at making.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, apparently, Wikipad isn't super popular yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: They showed it at Consumer Electronics Show, but they've already gone through some changes with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got a 10.1-inch screen and a quad-core processor now, optional 3G for mobile.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the other thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It ain't out yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's one of those things that is coming soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gaikai is out there, though, if you want to check that out, and it will be interesting to see what happens when these worlds collide with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty big for a portable system, but I'd say, eh, if you can take a laptop somewhere, you can take that somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and then people carry tablets, too, and it's also streaming gaming, so if you think about it, you'll be able to play console-type games, because the same stuff that OnLive is doing, like Saints Row III or something of that quality,
[SPEAKER_03]: through this pad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, and the controls look pretty similar to, you know, a current-gen console, so I wouldn't see why you wouldn't be able to do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd rather have an IK than an iPad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, isn't IK a device for an iPad?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd rather have that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm fine with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or MAME on an Android.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, what's the difference, really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Look, let's go to a time when gaming was a whole lot simpler.
[SPEAKER_02]: We didn't have streaming video games in our laptop bags.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we had streaming video games as part of cartridges hooked up to either a modem or your cable.
[SPEAKER_02]: A portable console was getting a mini television hooked up to a cigarette light adapter and plugging your Nintendo into it, which some guy we knew had in his car, a PlayStation in the car.
[SPEAKER_10]: We did that in middle school with a camp TV that ran on D-cells.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to go to a classic time when things were a lot simpler and take a look at the classic game of the week where DarkSakura is going to dip into the video game vault and find a game that she thinks, hey!
[SPEAKER_02]: You kids ought to be playing this video game.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one's moldy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Random got the jump on you, though, with the Goonies 2 nostalgia.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this one's pretty good, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_10]: A game inspired by my recently seen Avengers, and I'm not going to spoil why.
[SPEAKER_10]: Galaga!
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, Galaga, also known in Japan as Gyaraga.
[SPEAKER_10]: which is the game of pew pew is what it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, it was developed and published by Namco in Japan and published by Midway in North America in 1981.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was the sequel to Galaxian from 1979.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why I didn't do Galaxian?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wanted to do Galaga, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: In any way, your player is fixed to the bottom of the screen.
[SPEAKER_10]: You go back and forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't get to go up or fly around or anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a simple, fixed shooter.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the enemies fly at you in formation, and you have to pew-pew them all before they pew-pew you.
[SPEAKER_10]: And once they're all vanquished, then you move on to the next stage.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yahoo!
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Galaga was pretty, pretty popular, as I'm sure you all know.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we have many different sequels to Galaga and many versions of Galaga.
[SPEAKER_10]: At any rate, Galaga, for me, was just the coolest because you could get your ship get taken up by the little dude who put out the tractor beam thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then if you shot him, you got your ship back and had double ship mode, which was always...
[SPEAKER_10]: Super cool!
[SPEAKER_10]: It also had a few features that improved over Galaxium, like the ability to fire more than one bullet at a time, your hit-miss ratio, and the challenging stage.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you destroyed every enemy in the challenging stage, you got a 10,000 point bonus.
[SPEAKER_10]: And like I said, you also could get captured.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a boss Galaga that would just absorb you up.
[SPEAKER_10]: You could shoot it and get it down.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then there are actually full-on strategies that are based around getting your dude captured.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's how a lot of people play.
[SPEAKER_10]: It also had a bug that was called... Actually, the bug would make your attacker stop firing bullets.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was actually a coding error.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to say the double the whole two ships tied together thing that's like the only way I can do decent at this game I have to get that in the first stage and then go as far as I can like that's the only way to play this game in my opinion
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, a lot of people based their strategy around it, like I said.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's also a split-screen bug that was like in Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not quite the same thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's similar to the split-screen bug in Pac-Man, where your game will roll over from level 255 to level 0.
[SPEAKER_10]: And depending on the difficulty setting in the machine, it could cause the game to stall, and it means it has to be either reset or power-cycled so that you can start a new game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So in the series of Galaxian, and I'm going to start with Galaxian.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had Galaxian in 1979, Galaga in 1981, Gaplus or Galaga 3 in 1984, Galaga 88 in 1987, go fig, Galaga Legions in 2008, Galaga Legions DX in 2011, and Galaga 3D Impact in 2011.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you remember, Rob, at the Dave & Buster's in Milpitas, they used to have the Galaxian, I think it was the Galaxian 3 set, which was a full room that you would play Galaxian in, with the three screens, and that was like some...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: As far as other versions of Galaga that's come out, there's been the Atari 7800, the Famicom version, Game Boy, and also it was bundled with Galaxian.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a GameTap, MSX.
[SPEAKER_10]: The MSX version is actually really good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, NES, because we had a Famicom version.
[SPEAKER_10]: the Sega SG-1000, the Tandy TRS-80 Color Computer, which I played Galagon on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a clone called Galagon, and I played Stu out of this, because my friend had one of these things.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been put out on the Virtual Console, the NES version, Xbox Live Arcade, iOS is the Galaga Remix, which had the original on it, Nintendo 3DS, which was part of Pac-Man and Galaga Dimensions, and Roku.
[SPEAKER_10]: There has also been several versions of the Namco Museum, which are really way too many.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, like, we have 64DS, PS2, Xbox, Nintendo GameCube, Game Boy Advance, and Windows.
[SPEAKER_10]: There were two versions of each.
[SPEAKER_10]: PSP, PlayStation, Dreamcast, Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, and the Wii, which I have most of those.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't forget though, the Namco collection on the PlayStation 3 is the game with the OLR cameo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which makes it double awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is the double awesome version.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course I had to... Jeez, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: You gotta get that one out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jeez, Rob!
[SPEAKER_10]: There was also, it was a side game in the PlayStation version of Tekken in 1995.
[SPEAKER_10]: You could play it as it loaded.
[SPEAKER_10]: In Point Blake 2, there were Galaga Challenge stages.
[SPEAKER_10]: In the 20-year reunion class of 1981 arcade unit that had Ms.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pac-Man and Galaga, there was that.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Pac-Man's arcade party, it actually was part of that too.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was even available on Palm devices and Pocket PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: So Galaga really has an amazing legacy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, my allergies are flaring up, everybody.
[SPEAKER_10]: You all right over there?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why I sound like a 12-year-old boy.
[SPEAKER_10]: At any rate, there were remakes.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was Galaga Arrangement, which was part of Namco Museum compilation.
[SPEAKER_10]: Galaga Destination Earth came out in 98 for Windows, PlayStation, and the Game Boy Color.
[SPEAKER_10]: Galaga Remix came out in 2007 for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you use your Wii remote as a gun.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you have to protect Pac-Man as he rolled through space.
[SPEAKER_02]: The video ran out, so we have to hear that opening theme one more time.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't sing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not with my voice like this.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was actually Galaga, Galaxian, Galplus, sorry, Galpus.
[SPEAKER_10]: Galaga 88 were redesigned and modernized for an iPhone app called Galaga 30th Anniversary that was done by Namco Bandai.
[SPEAKER_10]: And basically the app had Galaxian as a free game and then the main three actually had to pay for the complete set for $8.00.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it had Galaga points, so you could unlock power-ups and special arcade cabinet designs, including the original art.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're a world record for Galaga.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now keep in mind, this is Twin Galaxy stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was set in June 1989 by Steven Krugman of Boca Raton, Florida.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the rapid fire setting... And they say nothing awesome happens in Florida.
[SPEAKER_10]: was used, and it was also in Ms.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pat Mangala, Class of 81, Fast Shot, World Records, and they were both by John Klinkel of Battle Creek, Michigan.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so, I mean, and I remember actually seeing some of the people that had the earlier ones in King of Kong, because they had people just playing, you know, the high score people gathered back together when What's-His-Face was trying to beat Billy Mitchell's score.
[SPEAKER_10]: Galaga, actually there was a Galaga machine that was sent to Matthew Broderick by MGM for him to practice for war games Lost had a submarine called Galaga in honor of the game and basically the writers of the series would play Galaga in between writing sessions
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a Christmas tree ornament shaped like a Galaga arcade machine that had sound clips from the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have the Pac-Man one of those.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: And because the place I'm reading is not updated since, Galaga made an appearance in The Avengers.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you'll say no more.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'll say no more.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because that guy over there is playing Galaga.
[SPEAKER_10]: He didn't think I'd notice, but I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, is that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the quote.
[SPEAKER_02]: Classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Galaga.
[SPEAKER_02]: Available everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: But most notably in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because shield helicarriers have joysticks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: We would prefer that you play the arcade version or the PlayStation Network version that has the OLR cameo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Send us your screen captures on Twitter and we'll send you a no prize.
[SPEAKER_02]: A no prize.
[SPEAKER_02]: My favorite kind of prize.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're running way long for part A. I wonder why.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm not allergic to Sky and Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm allergic to California.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was worth it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to take a quick break, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will be back in just a little bit with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got more coming up in part B.
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio, live on the VOG Network, Voice of Geeks Network, on this May the 6th of 2012.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are live with the 456th episode of our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys missed a fun part A. A little worried there at the beginning.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little worried there when...
[SPEAKER_02]: I want the Sega album I got sonic boobs today, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: We didn't talk a lot about this shirt at the beginning of the show, but you're wearing this shirt.
[SPEAKER_02]: I paid $10 for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a Sonic shirt, and it's so funny because your boobies are right where Sonic's head is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Sonic's got a big head because of big boobies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can't help it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Triple D, hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pixar didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: I put pics up.
[SPEAKER_02]: On OrangeLunchRadio.com?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the other can of Vimto that I drank.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've never had Vimto before.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which our European listeners should know of.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've never had Vimto before, but I'm having a Vimto Light, and it's really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've never had Vimto Light before.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like the regular soda.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not made with high fructose corn syrup, the regular one.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just with sugar.
[SPEAKER_02]: It tastes a little bit like Hanson's Black Cherry.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Black Current, Raspberry Soda
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: I drink that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's good stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Babylon Market.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, we do have somebody staying up late listening to us all the way from the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: Peker Uno is with us saying, I don't like Vimto.
[SPEAKER_02]: I prefer Rubina.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rubina?
[SPEAKER_02]: Rubina is not bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I tried, it's this, I like Tizer, I think is what it's called.
[SPEAKER_10]: T-I-Z-E-R.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just had that really recently and it's pretty darn good, like a grapefruit soda.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_02]: You said you got that shirt at Kmart.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to get that out too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right next to the Master System games that are still in stock because it's Kmart.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the Genesis ad, it's coming.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, Genesis does what Nintendo don't.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the reason why I go to that particular Kmart is because it is literally right around the corner from my neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Shermie needed stuff to pee on.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I got Shermie stuff to pee on.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I needed Sudafed.
[SPEAKER_10]: As you can all tell by my 12-year-old boy puberty voice.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, just saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: So K-More had that many copies of In the Groove there, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: They had a Mario shirt that I wanted.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: But when I saw Sonic, had to get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Sega fangirl and you had a squeed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's move on with some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_02]: A few quick news stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, Saints Row the Third, of course they had this, you know, April Fool's joke, testing the waters bit, I guess they were doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where it was Saints Row the Third, enter the dominatrix, and everyone's like, wow, that would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so they're like, ah, we fooled you, because it's real, and it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what they're doing is they're kind of going the whole, I don't know, copycat of...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently the whole premise of Enter the Dominatrix, which is other than being a complete ripoff of The Matrix, because, you know, that's current.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so basically the saint's leader is kidnapped by an alien warlord named Zinyak and his benevolent race.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently they're trying to grab up all of Earth's resources or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, I guess there's some character named Paul.
[SPEAKER_03]: who's supposed to play some role in there yay Paul you rock Paul stay awesome Paul it's all for you I'm a huge Paul fan I live for Paul in Saints Row the 3rd who the fuck is Paul I don't know who the fuck Paul is honestly that was a movie
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I know Paul is a movie, and that was probably funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's just this whole Saints Row, the dominatrix thing, it's neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the whole thing, they say it's supposed to be like this virtual reality thing, so it's going to be similar to kind of like the Deckers missions almost.
[SPEAKER_03]: But at the same time, I'm like, dude, your DLC sucked so fucking bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do I really want to play this $30...
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I just...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: That was enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Adidas MyCoach was something that was supposed to be coming out from THQ.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, maybe a reason why they're putting out this expansion of the Saints Row, because they're in a little financial trouble.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, apparently this whole deal fell through because they didn't make it out in time.
[SPEAKER_03]: So now MyCoach 24-7 is supposed to be coming out from 505 Games.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have taken over the publishing rights for it, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be launching this summer, apparently.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'll have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure you have it on pre-order.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know me and exercise.
[SPEAKER_03]: And last but not least, a game that actually took up a lot of my time this week, Perfect Strangers.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was an adver... It was an adver game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it says right on the bottom, the guy that's responsible for this actually does adver games for a bunch of different things.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he's done some pretty good stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a well-fucking-done adver game, so props.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was excellent.
[SPEAKER_03]: and um I mean it's a very short game but you definitely should check it out um and of course it's advertising the uh release I guess of the episodes on iTunes which hey it worked I was unaware that the episodes were even out there I was unaware I forgot about that show period to be honest until I played the game oh I never forget that show
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever happened to Bronson Pinchot?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I watched some clips of him the other day when I was asking myself the same question.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know he was in Langoliers and he got mauled at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_03]: The last thing I probably saw him was Beverly Hills Cop 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Mark Lynn Baker.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever else did he do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Other than being like a dead-on ringer for the critic, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's just bask in the awesomeness for a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel inspired.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Mustang.
[SPEAKER_10]: I forgot he drove a Mustang.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We just gave these guys a free commercial.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was a pretty fucking awesome show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did see Second Sight, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: That movie was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because he was addicted to goobers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let me get some stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: But first, a PSA from our chatroom at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pete Garuto is telling us all, you don't know Jack on Facebook is now open to all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know what I'm doing after the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shane, I gotta cancel Mass Effect Multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't know Jack is on Facebook now?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know if he's listening.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's get to some other quick news here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Family Guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if they've done a lot of games for Family Guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't remember if there's been any others.
[SPEAKER_02]: One, and it was not good.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, that was the year they had Adam West at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't good, and they did an iOS game, and it wasn't very good either.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, maybe this will redeem it, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: September 25th, Family Guy, back to the multiverse.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 3 and 360, according to some Amazon stuff that leaked earlier today.
[SPEAKER_03]: And even earlier on our Twitter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wink wink.
[SPEAKER_02]: Activision is involved.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet this will be an E3 showing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually have to look it up because I haven't watched Family Guy in a few years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mainly because I do this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: It happens to be on at the same time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also because it stopped being funny after a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'll give it a chance again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't remind the listeners that Family Guy is on.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's true, it's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Family Guy is a browser-based online adventure.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could say it's for kids, but you know there's going to be some adults that check this out too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's coming from WB Games Montreal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cartoon universe.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is kid-friendly.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Looney Tunes and Scooby-Doo.
[SPEAKER_02]: You make your own Toon avatar.
[SPEAKER_02]: You play puzzles and mini-games, meet new friends, and experience the joy of exploring a place that doesn't actually exist.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's supposed to be popular characters from both the franchises in there, but no playable version of this yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess there's a beta.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a beta version, I guess, that's out there, but I think it's really bugged from what the early reports are saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it is a beta, but you can check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: CartoonUniverse.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_02]: N-A for North America.
[SPEAKER_02]: CartoonUniverse.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pink textures, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pink textures.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks cute, but if I'm going to play a free-to-play MMO, I'm going to play Star Trek or DC Universe or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lastly, for those of you guys that aren't cool enough to go to E3 anymore, like, you know, us, at least you can feel like you're there by sitting on the couch with your bonbons and your popcorn, which you can't even have if you actually go to the real thing, because they don't allow that stuff in these, uh...
[SPEAKER_02]: conference centers and watch the E3 presser on Xbox Live or Spike TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Microsoft press conference will be live on Xbox Live and Spike TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will be spending my time doing what I normally do during these press conferences which is kicking back in the conference room at work and eating a bowl of popcorn while watching this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, I have E3 week off anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm at the point where I've been at my job 10 years and I get so much time off a year for being there that long that I just take E3 week off to have it off.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: I should do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I may actually this year have to move.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our studio may be moving, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I may be moving that week, so I may miss out on some of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: But regardless, for the rest of you guys, you can watch that live as it unfolds.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't imagine it's going to be any different for Sony and Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, you know, maybe they'll be on G4 or PlayStation Home or, you know, they'll be available as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, Xbox used to be on G4, so it's like now Spike has more gaming cred than G4, which, yeah, I can see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Funny how that works.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, a few more stories for you guys in the Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, me, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, there is going to be Cave Story Plus on the 3DS eShop soon, but it's not going to be the Cave Story 3D.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a separate one.
[SPEAKER_10]: All it is is an update for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, Tyrone Rodriguez, the CEO of Nicholas, said that he really wanted it just to be the update, so neither game would interfere with the other if you happened to delete one.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a little weird, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: That you would make a second remake of your game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Cave Story 3D is a separate game from Cave Story Plus.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're two different games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yo, dog, I heard you like Cave Story, so we put some Cave Story in your Cave Story.
[SPEAKER_10]: and for our listeners in the UK, the UK Pride Xbox Connect Bundle will be available in May and I kind of want it, but not really.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be £249.99, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's also going to be a...
[SPEAKER_10]: A skin available, Jealous Skins is going to make a pattern for $30.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they also, though, do have a Stars and Stripes bundle for the American audiences or anyone who happens to want an American flag on their game or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or the Confederate flag.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure they have the Confederate flag, too, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, shush.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then Ratchet & Clank HD Trilogy has been pushed back in Europe.
[SPEAKER_10]: It will be pushed from the 16th of May until early June, Insomniac has announced.
[SPEAKER_10]: The end.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to the Fugle question of the week, except I'm failing, and I did this last week too, didn't I?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's something about the network change.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have the music up for this segment, but every week we go to our Facebook at facebook.com slash orange lounge radio or our Google Plus.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, we're on Google Plus with all the Google employees that are still there.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are some very loyal Google Plus listeners, though, and I get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Man, Facebook does some real dumb shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you hear about now what they're doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I get why people want to run off to Google Plus.
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole Messenger thing will now have this actual Facebook Messenger app that's coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: And look this up on the Internet if you don't believe me.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Facebook Messenger app on the iPhone will now send your location with the messages that you send
[SPEAKER_02]: You can turn that off.
[SPEAKER_02]: So to be fair, you can't turn that off.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know it'll be on by default because nobody at Facebook knows what opt-in is all about.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the other thing with this is that return receipts, you can now request a return receipt for when somebody's read your message.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't turn that off.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you don't want someone to know you read their message, too bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be great for the stalkers that Facebook message you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm sure you could use a third-party app for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know the specifics of how it worked, but when I read that, I was like, grr.
[SPEAKER_03]: More importantly, though, Ranma in chat has informed us that Bronson Pinchot actually has a reality show on DIY.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was unaware of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure it's not.
[SPEAKER_10]: And by the way, Rob, I don't use the messenger anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: I always have it linked me as offline.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just saying, I don't know the specifics, but I look at this and I raise my eyebrow and I go, do not want.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, let's go on to happier topics.
[SPEAKER_10]: I make everyone get AIM.
[SPEAKER_02]: FUGLE QUESTION OF THE WEEK
[SPEAKER_02]: Has a video game ever inspired you to create something artistic in the real world?
[SPEAKER_02]: For example, art, music, a website, anything creative.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did you create and why did the game inspire you to do this?
[SPEAKER_02]: So Shane from Horde House started us off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I'm too busy writing my Mail Shepherd Caden fanfic to answer this question.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've written fanfiction.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: For what game?
[SPEAKER_10]: For a number of games, I mean, just stuff I played.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did Metroid back in the day.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just old stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, the last thing that I did was actually for Digimon, of all things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I used to put together, well, I still put together Mad Mods for Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: And remember, I was inspired to try to figure out what the song from DJ Hero 2 would sound like, the mashup between piano and shout, so I did that.
[SPEAKER_10]: and I've done fan art.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember I did my portal turret for my final project in 3D class.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's get some more of the answers over on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have an answer from Johnny B. Johnny Cage's ball bust a move inspired me to create an athletic cup attached with nails and screws.
[SPEAKER_02]: I advertise this tool of protection for men, women and everyone in between.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, I have a tip for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob on Public Access
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I've seen some of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you saw, I don't even know where the tapes are.
[SPEAKER_02]: I honestly don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, who uses VHS tapes?
[SPEAKER_03]: It is fantastic, I have to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, I'm being serious here.
[SPEAKER_03]: If shit like Tim and Eric's awesome show Great Job can do as well as it does, that Public Access show could have been a hit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you know, it's a shame.
[SPEAKER_02]: I lost touch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we're Facebook friends, but my friend Shannon, who was like my bestie in high school, and I did a comedy show on public access.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kids in high school are such...
[SPEAKER_02]: Cockhead bastard fucks Like, you know, we used to get Like the guys before us did this very, you know, conservative slanted show Because they learned that from their parents Called, I'm gonna name names Because I'm 33 and I don't give a fuck anymore It was a show called Open Debate
[SPEAKER_02]: and these guys would just sit there they fucking would razz our show that was coming up like live on their show and the callers would call in and like talk about what a fag I was on public access TV I got bullied on television you guys but it gets better don't worry all I'm saying is you need to put a clause in your will or something like that that stuff gets released when you die unlike Whitney Houston and the episodes of Being Bobby Brown which unfortunately probably died with her as well I mean
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to belittle janitors Because janitors do an important job
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Porkchop answered our question on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not so much create, but adapted.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Final Fantasy soundtracks inspired me to adapt some of their songs on guitar, such as Eternity Lightwaves and Aerith's Theme.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game's music always impressed me and was very memorable, which made me want to learn these songs for myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: As a result of this, Nobuo Uematsu is also my favorite composer.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you think about it, that's almost the same story that Random told about Goonies 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to say, Koji Kondo inspired me to start off as a music major.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I met him, remember?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love this answer from Stan H on Facebook says, playing Journey as I type this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to knit the scarf and be crazy long.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a Journey joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lastly, from Paul W. Is it weird that when you first said, oh yeah, he did a remix thing based on Journey that I thought of Journey the arcade game?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was worried people would think that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look, one more answer here from Facebook, and then I got one on Google.
[SPEAKER_02]: Paul W. says, Back when I was in second or third grade during the NES and Sega Master System days, I would create my own illustrations of enemies' bosses when instruction manuals for game were more than just a sheet of paper or non-existent.
[SPEAKER_02]: These were new creations I had imagined for sequels to games such as Fantasy Zone or Altered Beast.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think a lot of us did that kind of crap as a kid, Paul, because I can tell you, you must have done this too, and everybody that grew up in a certain time I'm sure did this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did the RPG on the notepad where you drew the dungeon and you'd make your friends go through the dungeon and it was like you wrote your own video game on paper?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I used to have a tablet of that stuff and I'm so sad that I lost it.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is why we're friends, because I knew you were that kid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't even have to ask.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, it started off because I used to like, okay, basically I was inspired by Contra.
[SPEAKER_03]: I used to love drawing mazes, and so that's what I'd do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd create mazes, and then they were mazes with cannons in them, and then mazes with spikes and cannons and alien monsters and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it was kind of like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was like bullet hell, but on paper.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's get to the one answer here on Google+.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jim H. You go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jim's the loyal Google user.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sort of embarrassing to admit this, but in my documentary class in film school, I made a one-minute doclet about my holy priest character in Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually got an A on the project and had to answer questions from my instructor like, have you ever let another player die on purpose?
[SPEAKER_02]: Great story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure the answer is yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it for the Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get back into some news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Warp, Shank, Shank 2, Gatling Gears, Deathspank, and Deathspank the Thong of Virtue
[SPEAKER_03]: and ironically enough it's actually being released on Steam as part of Steam Play and they're also having some other indies that are available as well I guess Death's Bank titles are currently $7.50 individually and then EA's rest of their indie titles are $5 each and those are PC only whereas the Death's Bank titles are PC and Mac um
[SPEAKER_03]: And, uh, interesting enough, though, uh, you know, they've also gotten some, um, hate from, you know, just, just this guy that put out a game called Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, that's right, Notch, uh, basically saying- What's a Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, what's a Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, basically said, EA's releasing- How do you mine fish?
[SPEAKER_03]: So EA's releasing an indie bundle.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not sure how that works, EA.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop attempting to ruin everything, you bunch of cynical bastards.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, tweet drama.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going down on Twitter, y'all.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: It did strike me as really funny that the EA indie bundle was on Steam and not on Origin.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: What would you like to see us approve on Origin?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, kind of almost admitting that it hasn't been that great.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what would you guys like to see us do, you know, to fix it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Close it down and put the games on Steam?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not going to do that Although, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Competition is healthy for the industry So, you know, I don't want Steam to be the one and only But, you know, I don't know if EA should really be giving their own store But I will say this You know, despite the cynical bastard I am in all this I will say something nice about Origin this week
[SPEAKER_02]: I did play, and I didn't talk about this in my gaming week, but I did play that Mass Effect 3 datapad game that helps you with your galactic readiness.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember that whole thing where we were getting really angry last week because I said that you have to play multiplayer?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I downloaded that thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it does turn out, and I do stand corrected, thank you chat room, that's the perk of doing a live show, that you can download this Mass Effect datapad and raise your galactic readiness rating in a...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to call it a Farmville type game but it's very much one of those like Facebooky type of games that you know you send your ship out and wait three hours and you can check on it what have you and it helps raise your galactic readiness and I gotta say the way that all ties together and how you do that on your iPhone yet it impacts what happens on the Xbox and you can check your multiplayer unlocks on the PC that kind of synergy is neat it is neat
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's done well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I will tip my hat slightly to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know this is being done just because it's cash grabs left and right wherever they can get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But as far as the free stuff that's there, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I will say that nice thing about Origin.
[SPEAKER_02]: But as far as the EA Indie Bundle on Steam...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure it was some marketing dude that thought it would be a clever thing and probably didn't go through all the necessary checks and now they're paying for it in the media just like everything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guess what else EA paid for in the media this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: A big snafu in their Rock Band iOS game.
[SPEAKER_02]: A big pop-up showed up when logging into Rock Band on the iPhone or the iPad this week that said, on May 31st, Rock Band will no longer be playable on your device.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for rocking out with us.
[SPEAKER_02]: And everybody was like, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: The fuck?
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought this game and I bought the DLC, it's on my phone, and EA's just gonna fucking shut it off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yank, pull the plug, pull it from my phone, can't play it anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not to mention that while that little pop-up's going on, it's still being currently sold on iOS's App Store.
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, came out later in the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: EA came out and said, that prompt was made an error, and we will give you more information soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said, quote, we apologize for the confusion this caused.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're working to clarify the issue that caused the error, and we'll share additional information as soon as possible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Clarify the issue, fire the employee, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because... Ah, they didn't like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: How did this happen?
[SPEAKER_02]: The cat did not sneak in in the middle of the night and type Dear Rockers on May 31st.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was an intentional message.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially the thanks for rocking out with us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for paying this money, but your game is no longer going to work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now here's my thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a random ass theory, and this ties back into Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know they announced this Mass Effect free DLC that's coming out in the summer, but they put an expiration date on it saying you can get it free until 2013 or 2014, something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Bioware said, note, we don't plan to ever not make it free, but EA's policies require us to set an expiration date.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you know as long as they don't have to honor it and also speaking of Mass Effect when I bought Mass Effect 2 brand new mind you I had a coupon in the box for an online pass expires February 1st 2012 and it was like mid February by the time I was ready to play it it's still redeemed but that expiration date was there and I was about ready to go through the fucking roof because I bought that new just so I don't have to buy the damn online pass I almost went through the roof it did work but
[SPEAKER_02]: This makes me wonder, EA has this crackhead policy of having expiration dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do they have expiration dates?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a great fucking question that I would like EA to answer.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, I don't understand why they have expiration dates.
[SPEAKER_03]: I understand they'll do that on certain things, like, for example, Ultraviolet.
[SPEAKER_03]: You may notice with a lot of the DVDs and Blu-rays that are out there now, come with a free Ultraviolet digital copy that you can redeem by a certain date.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm wondering if it's just because they don't want to keep those copies up on their servers forever.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, forever or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't even make any sense because once you've streamed it or you have it in your collection, you can always stream it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I just don't understand why on a paid app it can expire like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that right there is a perfect example of why going digital only is a bad fucking idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because what's going to stop EA or any company from going, Yeah, we just want this game to work anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: and that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have no recourse.
[SPEAKER_02]: And really, Rock Band is on your phone and you don't need... I mean, I understand if they're shutting down the online music store or they're shutting down the multiplayer or whatever, but how can they...
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop the entire app, including single player, from working.
[SPEAKER_02]: How very dare you, EA.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or if it's a free app, I can see, okay, maybe this is going to expire and a new one's going to come out.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a Disneytron app that did that, but it was free.
[SPEAKER_03]: But here's the thing, though, and this is kind of pointed out as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did something similar with Tetris.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tetris, for example, it expired and stopped working.
[SPEAKER_03]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, they sold a new version of Tetris.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can buy it again.
[SPEAKER_03]: What makes you think that they might not try this again?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yet PopCap, who is now owned by EA, PopCap did it a little better because they turned Bejeweled 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: They spun off Bejeweled Blitz into its own game, but they made it free.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Bejeweled 2 didn't really stop working.
[SPEAKER_02]: You still got that, even though they have Bejeweled 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: They kind of pushed people to go get Bejeweled 3, but they didn't make Bejeweled 2 stop working.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I joined it.
[SPEAKER_02]: When the full VOG Network launches soon, I can't tell you when, but it'll be sooner than you think, we'll have a link to that a little more directly.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yes, I am still able to play Bejeweled 2 on my phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's the music.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't surprise me that they would be the ones behind this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we're going to go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura left the room.
[SPEAKER_02]: She'll be back in a minute here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope, here she comes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every week you guys send us emails.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm allergic to mail.
[SPEAKER_02]: M-A-L-E or M-A-I-L?
[SPEAKER_11]: Both.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, mailbag at orangeloungetrader.com is the place to send us your emails.
[SPEAKER_02]: And DarkSakura might read them.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, hopefully you have some emails for us tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Speaking of, I know that content downloading from the store on PSP, if interrupted, will have to start completely over, which seems unfortunate for a portable, even considering its age.
[SPEAKER_10]: Does the Vita have this issue, or can software be loaded a little at a time?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey Vita people, will it work?
[SPEAKER_03]: Will it work?
[SPEAKER_02]: Will it blend?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you even listening?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was kind of tuning out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: He wants to know if you can download incrementally on the Vita or will you have to start over like on the PSP?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you can download incrementally.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're in download or whatever, or if you happen to turn your system off or something like that, it will restart where it's at.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and the Vita really encourages you to put it to sleep, not to turn it off.
[SPEAKER_02]: You sleep it, and while it's sleeping, it'll download your shit, which is good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, in fact, I keep forgetting that I have mine in sleep mode, like in my bag for like a... And then the battery's dead three days later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why I was like, oh, shit, I better charge this again.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a bummer they didn't include a dock for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure someone sells one, but... They sell one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, do they?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, of course they do.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I love that 3DS dock.
[SPEAKER_02]: It makes it so great to remember to charge it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's just a cheap piece of plastic, but it works so well.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, I almost skipped this email because it said oral advertising, but I saw who sent it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dearest members of the online video game radio cast Pundidocracy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You thought it was some French spam for a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: We get inundated with French spam.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_10]: This week I caught wind of the Metal Gear Solid HD collection being released on Vita.
[SPEAKER_10]: The very possibility of a collection of games such as this being released on the Vita brought the following questions to my mind.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who do I have to blow to get Metal Gear Acid 3?
[SPEAKER_10]: Stay care, bettertainment.
[SPEAKER_10]: This message has been brought to you by oral advertising sent from my iPad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you don't even get all three games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You only get two of the three.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Metal Gear Acid 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who are you going to have to blow to get that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably... Kojima.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Kojima, I think.
[SPEAKER_10]: And from what I understand, he's not too into the blow.
[SPEAKER_10]: You'd have to get his ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would see Acid 3 more on the 3DS than... Because remember they had the whole...
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember that really weird, like, binoculars garbage that you had to put on there?
[SPEAKER_02]: There also is a Metal Gear something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't remember if it came out or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it's out yet, but they were demoing one a long time ago, a Metal Gear something on 3DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that came out already.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was the Metal Gear Solid 3D Snake Eater.
[SPEAKER_10]: Snake Eater.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, yes?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey guys, this is Honey Badger, aka Blade 3 Okay, I have to stop and apologize Because Honey Badger messaged me on Steam last night While I was drunk off cheap sangria Off my ghetto sangria made from Manischewitz So I'm sorry, I was a little drunk
[SPEAKER_10]: I just wanted to say the listeners will support you no matter what changes you make.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, I have a question for you all, but I think Loki may have the most input.
[SPEAKER_10]: How close are we to having essentially gaming computers and fancy cases that are just locked down by Microsoft or Sony?
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, where does the line between high-end console and gaming PCs start?
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty much that's what they are now anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's just gaming PCs, but it's proprietary boards and whatnot, and specialized chips that are made specifically for these systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish it was a little bit more like gaming PCs, but I understand why they have limitations.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it would be kind of cool if, for example, you could have an Xbox 360 and be able to upgrade the RAM in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, say, okay, all the games have to run with this amount of RAM,
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you want the games to run a little bit smoother, you can add extra RAM.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind of like how you can increase the hard drive space.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd be worried, though, about those minimum system requirements slowly bumping up.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it's the one thing that makes people a little leery of PC gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: But RAM's so cheap nowadays.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, but, you know, then it's the video card.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then it's, you know, the operating system that your thing's running.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then it's the space on your hard drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: If any one thing is another.
[SPEAKER_09]: So next email.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted to say real quick, though, since that was from Honey Badger.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that name, by the way, because it always makes me think it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Watch it run in slow motion.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty badass.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look, it runs all over the place.
[SPEAKER_10]: We should get Randall to do a bumper for us.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_10]: Listen to Orange Dolls Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't fuck your shit up.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're not, you're a bitch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey guys, it's Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do I have to do the choo-choo noise?
[SPEAKER_10]: I live in Canada, sorry, and work as a party train conductor.
[SPEAKER_10]: Recently, me and my wife started shopping for Robot Butler, but we can't decide what features we want.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: He really is a train conductor?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he's full of shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or is that a... No, I mean like... Let me finish the email.
[SPEAKER_03]: My dad... A party train conductor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Party train.
[SPEAKER_02]: Legit, legit.
[SPEAKER_02]: My dad, for many years, he recently retired, but for about...
[SPEAKER_02]: 45 years he worked for the railroad and he was a train conductor.
[SPEAKER_02]: So when I hear that, I perk up.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: I empathize with the train people.
[SPEAKER_10]: She loves data from Star Trek, but I'm more of an R2-D2 kind of guy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which fictional robot would you like to have in your real life?
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, I'm off to go look for hobo stealing rides on the Sally Express.
[SPEAKER_10]: Love you and good night, Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_02]: E.D.
[SPEAKER_02]: cause she's hot Mass Effect reference that's all I have on the brain recently I think you know maybe the the gigalobot from Artificial Intelligence
[SPEAKER_02]: Does a Cylon count as a robot?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are they cybernetic?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to spoil, but there's a certain Cylon that's really hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are they full-on robots or are they cybernetic?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I can say Angelica Houston from Captain EO.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a great choice.
[SPEAKER_10]: But she's cybernetic.
[SPEAKER_10]: So are the Borgs.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll answer the questions the way we damn well please.
[SPEAKER_02]: And your answer is Angelica Houston from Captain EO.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I want Angelica Houston to service me.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I want a certain unsaid very hot Cylon that was revealed in the third season finale.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll just leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what about you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want a portal turret.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's technically a robot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then I'm going to change mine to GLaDOS.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to be her when I grow up and die.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, the last email.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to be in a potato?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll french fry you, bitch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bitch, I will come back and julienne you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will take you to In-N-Out and watch them put you in the blender thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw, I'm getting applause.
[SPEAKER_10]: Getting the slow clap.
[SPEAKER_10]: Howdy, OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wanted to call in, but something came up as usual.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that why they're calling it these days?
[SPEAKER_10]: Therefore, I'm writing you folks instead.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was having a discussion with... We're getting the manual work, I see.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you mean you want them to be Sega?
[SPEAKER_02]: They want them to go first to third.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a great thing for the fanboys to fantasize about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ain't gonna happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ain't gonna happen, not for a long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that will happen over Miyamoto's dead body, literally.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know, it's a Japanese company, and there's a lot of... I don't want to sound rude or mean, but just look at the history.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of stubbornness that comes with that, that they know what the people want, and that's not the way they want to go down.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you wanted to look for another example of what I'm talking about, the history of this show, we talked a lot about Konami.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Konami, and I had this conversation with a friend just the other day, Konami...
[SPEAKER_02]: Screw, Konami should have had the music, Konami had every right to be the kings of music games in America as well as Japan, but they fucked it up by not taking the risks.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did for a little while when there was a guy in America influencing a lot, but then that guy wasn't around anymore and music games at Konami fell the fuck apart.
[SPEAKER_02]: Case in point, Rock Revolution.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Nintendo will
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Off topic here, I wanted to mention something since I was browsing through the PlayStation Store.
[SPEAKER_03]: I find it a bit ironic that the full game of Ridge Racer happens to be under the demo section.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that a little funny?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta pull that down right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you sure?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: The one you have to pay $25 for, but it's filed under demo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I thought you meant it's free.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, they screwed up again?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Meaning it's filed under demo because there's no content to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that it for email?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are we done?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com if you want to send us emails for a future week.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the meantime, it's time to get renty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Fuse of the Week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck Children's Week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck all the Zorphans.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck their candy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck their kites.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck the Violet Proto-Drake.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had the three holidays left.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's three.
[SPEAKER_10]: Children's Week has fucked it for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Burn in hell.
[SPEAKER_10]: And your matron?
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck her too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Effie to my ceiling fan in my living room for breaking.
[SPEAKER_03]: My wife decided to turn the fan on high to dry the floors that she had recently mopped and the switch broke.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we couldn't shut it off.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I had to flip the breaker in the house and take apart the fan to shut it off manually.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it gets hot in there now.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to the fact that I'm not going to be able to go to Disneyland in a couple weeks because I kind of wanted to go and my friend's graduating and I'll get to miss it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And F you to Jamie because she'll be, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, you get to clean up Shermie's poop for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to poop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless it was a really good meal.
[SPEAKER_10]: She has been a little drippy lately.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're disgusting.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, just a few more stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we're going to open up the Skype line just for a little bit tonight, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're running a little late because of the interview earlier, but I think it was worth it, don't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a few more stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wait, quickly, quickly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to say this because some folks in our chat room were talking about the whole Nintendo, and some folks brought up the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I must say...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I could see something like that happening long before the Sony and Xbox thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was something that was brought up in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Legend of Zaku said iPhone enough said and it had me kind of thinking about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyway, now we can get to some stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's talk about the dark side of Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there was this Kickstarter for a game titled Mythic the Story of Gods and Men, which is an RPG from this company called Little Monster Productions.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was, of course...
[SPEAKER_03]: This already sounds a little bit outlandish, but it said, to rival World of Warcraft and Skyrim, built together by a team of former Activision Blizzard developers.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the project was asking for $80,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: It raised $5,000 up until a couple days ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically what happened was they actually canceled the funding altogether.
[SPEAKER_03]: and that's because apparently all their assets that they were showing on the site were stolen apparently all the artwork for the game that was supposedly being made was stolen off of different people's deviant art sites also some of the I guess pretty much all of the rewards were stolen from another Kickstarter page the Banner Saga
[SPEAKER_03]: and of course it made it to Reddit and people were warning them online and of course Little Monster Productions responded to the scam saying it seems we've been subjected to false claims of ownership rights to our concepts.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game itself is well in progress and it's not a scam of any kind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for understanding.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you have any further questions feel free to ask.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then of course since then the Kickstarter account's been deleted and they've kind of disappeared and vanished away.
[SPEAKER_03]: With all that money.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well no, technically not because they have to hit their funding goal of $80,000 in order to keep that money so the $5,000 that was contributed or put down actually didn't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: It went back to the people that or actually never left the people that put it down.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still think it's a wake-up call.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, Kickstarter has really taken off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody wants a piece of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, I mean, for some people, it's like an ATM machine right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's a tricky thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I still can't wrap my head around how I really feel about Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there's some things like, you know, what Random was talking about earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm like, you know, cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I saw a great piece on the internet this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: An awesome piece about...
[SPEAKER_02]: Amanda Palmer's Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_02]: And why... And basically the gist of the article is this is why Amanda Palmer gets to do a Kickstarter and you don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I thought it was kind of a really neat article.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just...
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're going to get into the Kickstarter thing, that's cool, but play smart.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this story is a great example of why.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it really seems like there's some people out there who are just donating to everything and anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, hey, it's your money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spend it on what you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: It can be dangerous, and this is why.
[SPEAKER_03]: Educate yourself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make sure that you're aware of who you're donating to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also really think...
[SPEAKER_02]: This would make me feel a lot better about Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kickstarter needs to allow the person, and maybe they do, and to be fair, maybe they already do this and I just never see people do it, and maybe people should be encouraged to do it more, to set a limit.
[SPEAKER_02]: on how much money is going to be raised.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because when I see certain Kickstarters that ask for $30,000 and I can't even put my head around what you do with $30,000 and get $120,000, it's like... Well, they keep changing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're allowed to, I guess, change their goals, I guess, on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But where... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: As a consumer, I want to know where every dollar is going.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm an investor.
[SPEAKER_02]: And when you invest in a company, there's these things called investor and shareholder meetings where you talk about the company and the progress and where the money is going.
[SPEAKER_03]: But really, all that you are guaranteed out of that is basically what slot you fit into as far as the rewards go.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all you're guaranteed.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's my problem with Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, then don't donate the stuff that you're unaware of.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I will admit, you know, there are some Kickstarters I take interest in, like the Star Control thing we talked about last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to admit, I kind of want that cartridge.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounded pretty fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, I hear about people like, you know, Random, and certainly the Pink Elephant in the Room.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's other Kickstarters that, you know, obviously we're well aware of, you know, and I wish success for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's just...
[SPEAKER_02]: There's just something about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I just feel like the other shoe is going to drop on Kickstarter any day now.
[SPEAKER_02]: The bubble's going to burst.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know if I want to be there when it does.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe I'm just being Debbie Downer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, well, I mean, not everything gets we still love you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not everything gets, you know, funded.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, there was the Kickstarter for it was a sequel to God, I remember now what it's called is a PSP game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't very popular, but they were trying to get a sequel for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that fell through.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there is some interesting things on there, and this is another one of those.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a MMO on there, if you can even call it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called Class Realm.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's being developed by some people, I want to say they're in the education system.
[SPEAKER_03]: to basically motivate their students to read more and participate in discussions more and study more as well as learn.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's called Class Realm.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: He says, my kids are the best promoters.
[SPEAKER_03]: He says, they're going around telling other students how great it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: And in my classroom, the other kids come in from other classes for math and science.
[SPEAKER_03]: and they see the classroom stuff on my wall and they want to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And other teachers also have been hugely supportive.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically what he's trying to do is he's creating this classroom thing that's both free and paid as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can do the free sharing the tools with the other teachers and then the paid one you get additional things.
[SPEAKER_10]: We covered this a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually launched now and he's taking donations.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can pledge towards it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let's move on to another story here.
[SPEAKER_02]: We talked about Harmonix earlier in the show, and I want to talk about them again because everybody's kind of wondering, what are they going to do next?
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, they have the Xbox Live and PlayStation Network thing that's coming, but you know that can't be the only thing they've been working on for the past few years.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some rumors are leaking out about what we might see very soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: According to some different job listings that were spotted, Harmonix is looking for a narrative content and level designers and one software engineer.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to be doing a project that's called, quote, a unique motion gaming IP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Harmonix seeks an accomplished narrative designer to incorporate creative storylines into gameplay on a unique motion gaming IP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could it be Dance Central 3?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or is this something brand, brand new?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know, Dance Central 2 kind of tried to do the story thing, but it was a little silly.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you don't expect much out of a music game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could Harmonix be doing something?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, maybe it's Dance Central 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's something totally different.
[SPEAKER_09]: You said unique.
[SPEAKER_02]: they did say unique so I like Harmonix Harmonix does a pretty darn good job even vid rhythm may not have taken off like crazy but it was really an interesting little tool I'm really curious to see what they bring with this I hope E3 is when we get to hear more about it but we'll see
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, how about some other news?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's basically, it's called the Toilet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Toilet.
[SPEAKER_10]: and it gives men incentive to pee in the urinal and to play the mini games instead of on the floor and it makes cleaner restrooms.
[SPEAKER_02]: We live in a day and age where you have to give incentive for grown men.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please don't go pee-pee on the floor.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they've had good feedback from customers.
[SPEAKER_10]: It says toilet cleanliness has improved.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now get the price on this one, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's 130 units out there at 150,000 yen a pop.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's almost $2,000.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, just to be clear, we have heard about this system before because there was the whole, like, toilet jokes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've watched an informative video on this before.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what Jamie's talking about is that now Sega's putting it out there where it's really accessible where anybody can get this.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can get this for your personal bathroom if you're, like, into water sports or something weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, to clarify, and there's been a trickle of information about this, the hardware itself is $140,000, which is about $1,700.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: The minigames are 10,000 yen a piece, which is $125.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you can get a 10 yen coin box that's 25,000 so that you can pay to pee, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: 312 bucks, pretty much, for the box.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a terrible idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pay to pee.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they have home options.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be on Spirit Airlines next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: and now they have home version options where you can pay $2,000 to pay to pee in your own house.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you can... Well, Giovedea, who is a lady, is in our chat room at vognetwork.com saying it's needed in American households badly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, and in college restrooms.
[SPEAKER_10]: But this, honestly, what do ladies have?
[SPEAKER_10]: We can pee.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe not directionally pee like men because, you know, it's really hard to aim when, you know, it's close to the hoo-ha.
[SPEAKER_02]: But why take the fun out of trying?
[SPEAKER_10]: We should have, like, poop pressure games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ew!
Ew!
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, ew about the pee, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least pee is sterile.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really don't want to talk about this story anymore but I really need to You're the one who gave it to me The show where every gamer has a voice Blackwolf in our chatroom at VOGnetwork.com says Sign in the men's bathroom of the LAN center I did Friday Night Gaming at You claim to have good aim Now's your chance to prove it
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, when I was at the University of South Alabama in the humanities building on the second floor in the ladies bathroom, there was a little poem written on the wall in the stall that I would usually use.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you must pee upon the seat, wipe it off and keep it neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was also, now get this, a toilet seat cover that I saw.
[SPEAKER_10]: On the top it says, we aim to please.
[SPEAKER_10]: You lift it up, you aim too, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to understand why women get the better bathrooms.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to talk about this for a minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because we don't pee all over everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was at a gas station driving to LA and I was at the gas station at 3.30 in the morning because, you know, nature called and I had to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the men's restroom was closed.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there was not a soul in this place.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I said to my friend, I said, Victoria, I want you to stand outside this door and if a woman comes, don't let them in.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went in the woman's restroom and, you know, I opened the door and I'm like, suddenly I'm like, there's like flowers and shit in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Check who owns the gas station.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have been in some pretty shithole gas station bathrooms for women, so do not even go there.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Chevron on the way back from Pensacola that's right when you get back into Mobile off the causeway, never go there.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to move on to some other stories quite quickly, but I do want to point out, because everybody in chat was like, how many listeners did you lose during that segment?
[SPEAKER_02]: We gained one, suckas!
[SPEAKER_02]: You got told!
[SPEAKER_02]: When in doubt, potty jokes!
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: We should talk more about that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk about Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Coming soon to the VOG Network, Poop Poop Pee Pee Show!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Microsoft has patented some sort of arm band that has EMG sensors as well as other electrodes in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, what it does is it monitors your muscle movements.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, for example, they would have it programmed to where if you made a fist or something like that, that your character would make a fist.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind of like an extension to the motion tracking and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I guess it could be applied to other parts of your body like your leg or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it is kind of interesting that they're potentially going to have some sort of device that allows you to track yourself a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just worried about how far those things are going to evolve.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a device that you wrap around an appendage, so the TTP for that, how soon?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you don't know what that is, just move right along.
[SPEAKER_02]: A moment of silence, please, because when I heard this news this week, I almost wanted to call the hotline and send some help over to one of our authors at OrangeLawnTrader.com's house to make sure he was okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: La Mulana in North America and Europe has been cancelled on WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Dark Tetsuya, bless his heart, was really excited about that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, really excited about that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was in development, and in development, and in development, and finally they just said...
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck it, we're not releasing it on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now there is some good news, it is coming out on the PC, so maybe it'll be on Steam or something like that, but it was cancelled.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought that was already on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this is like a plus version or like an enhanced version of the game that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, we were waiting on it for two years, and basically at the end of the day they just came out and said, WiiWare ain't profitable anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what everyone's been saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's something they need to fix.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a lot of that is Nintendo's shitty guidelines where it's like you have to sell so many units before you even get like a check.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keep that up and you won't have anybody but yourselves publishing on that service.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, just a moment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rest in peace, La Mulana.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, at least it'll be coming out on the play.
[SPEAKER_02]: It did look like a cute game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was interested in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why can't they put that on, like, you know, Xbox Indie games?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a great effing question.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, Xbox Live Arcade or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe we need to get them on the show to talk about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it seems like they don't like to talk much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Legend of Zaku in our chat says goes to show why Nintendo fails at digital distribution SJ100 Matt says but then again it was Nintendo's fault really so it seems like people are not placing the blame on the makers of La Mulana but they are placing the blame squarely at Nintendo's feet which I can't say I disagree with Shall we open up the Skype line?
[SPEAKER_02]: We shall.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call Ranma just announced that he's a classy whore
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for that on our program.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, 1-877-GAME-OLR or again our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give our show a call and talk about any news stories we may have missed or your opinion on what have you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sadly, Random is long gone now.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's off to work on something else.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can't let you ask him a question but we can talk about what he talked about.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the meantime, do we have any last-minute stories here in studio?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to fire up the Twitter and see if anyone sent us anything to talk about on twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: But first... Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: A call's coming in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Saved from last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's that classy whore Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I. Hey ho, what's up?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_14]: I do have a couple things I want to cover before I get out of here and start off my hellish work week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_14]: First things first, as per orders of the great and mighty powerful Rob, I went to Chinatown Fair.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm curious to hear what you thought about Chinatown Fair because what I read on Twitter was interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sums it up right there.
[SPEAKER_14]: I wasn't expecting this.
[SPEAKER_14]: I really wasn't.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'm posting a link to the complete total of eight photos I took there because all I needed was eight photos.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm scared.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not even trying to be a Dave & Buster's wannabe.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like the kid brother little bastard of Dave & Buster's that nobody talks to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chuck E. Cheese?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not even!
[SPEAKER_14]: Not even.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some skee-ball and the spinny wheel for tickets and a basketball thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Terminator Salvation's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guitar Hero Arcade some people like.
[SPEAKER_14]: and if you notice over in the corner I only got one, it's a picture but right next to that one big screen TV there's another big screen TV that's not even on and they don't even have HDMI cables hooked up for the console
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, they got a Plinko game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know they made those for the prices, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Rob, you and Plinko.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at all... I mean, it looks like a lot of... The ditter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, it looks like a lot of the shit you guys remember got replaced with ticket spitters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome to every other arcade in America.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's sad, but that's what's happened.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know, but I wasn't expecting something like this, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_14]: When I spoke to one of the guys who told me about this, he flat out said the new owner has no clue as to what he's doing.
[SPEAKER_14]: And he's trying to convince the owner to get in some actual good games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well that, you know, and it is a new arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's give, I mean, yes, it's an old arcade, but it's new owners or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's give them a chance.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's what everybody was saying, because at first we're all outside, sitting on the stoop, bad-mouthing and cursing up a storm about this.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then we're like, you know, we'll give them about 30 days.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, go back in a month and see what changes, if anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if nothing changes, well then, shit, they didn't learn anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, give it a chance.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're trying, and we're walking around like...
[SPEAKER_14]: The first thing we started raising with the fact that it is a pump-it-up machine because nobody plays pump-it-up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's funny, in the picture, that's the only machine I see a crowd around.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the sad part.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's probably the only machine that doesn't spit tickets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there was a Terminator Salvation machine I saw there too, and a couple others.
[SPEAKER_14]: and Superbikes2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, you know what Chinatown Fair looks like right now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Roseville Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome to my world.
[SPEAKER_14]: The funny thing is that's the first thing that came to mind.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm like, maybe, I think this is it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe we were on the same wavelength at that time for that five seconds, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so glad that the East Coast now has a place where video games go to die.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, we'll take that with a badge of honor.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ranma, anything else you want to share with the listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I'm just still in disgust from Chinatown Fair.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to pretend I never saw that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, go take a shower.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's not enough bleach in the world, damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, bye, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of Ranma, he passed along a little giveaway we're going to have in just a little bit here on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm waiting until the very end because that's how I roll.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going to some of our tweets that we have tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tigerclaw, of course, sent us a few tweets here.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of them is about Miyamoto's DS patent that will offer upgraded tourist hunting techniques.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hadn't heard about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently...
[SPEAKER_02]: If this is a real deal, there could be some type of advancement in GPS technology in tourist-heavy areas like museums and haunted house type places, and I'm imagining things like Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_02]: This patent would have a system where an overhead grid of infrared positional information transmitters reads a user's DS to light up floor patterns and potential walkways.
[SPEAKER_02]: The user can pick which route they'd like to take, reading tourist facts along the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Technically, there's iPhone apps and stuff that do all that, but this is a different way of implementing that technology that you know would be pretty stable.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, sounds very interesting to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to the phones and take another call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Science Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Zaku, what's up, buddy?
[SPEAKER_00]: Nothing much, just trying to reiterate what Ranma has said about CF.
[SPEAKER_00]: I heard it from my sources a couple of days before it opened that it was going to be radically different.
[SPEAKER_00]: It wasn't going to be anything near what the old CF was.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I guess, in a way, I've got to give them the benefit of the doubt that, sure, they may have a rocky and uneven open just for the fact that it's out of place for what people would normally refer to as CF.
[SPEAKER_00]: But then again, if the owner doesn't make a change quickly, then he's going to lose these folks for quite a while because they're going to go to Brooklyn to Next Level Arcade where the remnants of CF who used to run the place are pretty much alive and thriving there, especially the fighting game community.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me play devil's advocate for a minute here because this is a question I should have asked on the last call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they might lose the fans that used to go, but is it possible that they'll gain fans?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, arcades do this for a reason, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, but it might be a demographic that doesn't bode well for that area.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, the way I describe a CFer is someone who's basically male, about 20-ish, into video games, very competitive.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that type of demographic pretty much held that place together for...
[SPEAKER_00]: for the last years of its old existence.
[SPEAKER_00]: because it was mostly fighting games and to an extent our community, the DDR community.
[SPEAKER_00]: So to have something that barely resembles that and something where the old guard of CF are pretty much at their own place right now that caters to that demographic, it's not going to do any justice right away if that old location has nothing more than just a mini DMV.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, that's pretty much what I'm getting at.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have so much space that they crammed with arcade machines left and right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, just about every place, wall to wall, just literally, just covered in arcades.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now they're just like, there's not that many at the moment, but as I said, I give them the benefit of the doubt because they just opened up.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, unless this new owner doesn't like, doesn't take in, you know, doesn't like...
[SPEAKER_00]: Unless this owner actually does something in terms of writing this course and trying to draw more people in there in order to stay alive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me ask this question, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it maybe already a lost cause?
[SPEAKER_02]: It depends.
[SPEAKER_02]: How can you just turn it right around when you've invested the money?
[SPEAKER_00]: I know of another place like out in Queens in the city Peter Pan Games which is almost similar but it's more lopsided towards stuff that you can't find anywhere it's like the only best you know in other words New York's only 2DX machine is out there as well as like an unlocked X2 but it has redemption games but the thing is that these redemption aren't just like some Mickey Mouse prizes they're like real big ticket items like iPads
[SPEAKER_00]: and the coupled with the fact that it's on a strip mall with which gets a lot of foot traffic from the neighborhood so it's partly it's almost like what CF is but it's like what CF is right now is an infancy of what Peter Pan games is already at
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's at a point where unless they start drawing in something that will keep whales like myself, they'll draw them in there.
[SPEAKER_00]: In other words, you'll have a clientele that will constantly spend money there and will keep your place alive.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're just doomed to failure.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're going to need that type of customer or else they're just going to succumb to whatever tourists they get, if any.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Zaku, I've got to let you go so we can wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you have any final thoughts for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_00]: Other than cheating in MLB 2K12, I'm not a baseball fan, but the fact that people could actually exploit a game just to make money and 2K basically denying that the exploit was illegal, even though they originally said it was.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess they just have egg in their face right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like tainted that whole competition.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to have a shitty finale and they only have themselves to blame.
[SPEAKER_00]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_00]: And they basically fell on their own sword for basically denying that said cheat was illegal even though it's technically allowed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zaku, I gotta let you go, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: for an Xbox 360 Avatar Sonic hoodie, a Sonic 4 hoodie.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you want your Avatar on Xbox to be wearing a hoodie, we're going to give one of these away.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the good news is you can actually use this with male or female.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a male code and a female code.
[SPEAKER_02]: So technically you get two codes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm going to give it to one person, so maybe one for you and one for your SO or what have you.
[SPEAKER_02]: All you have to do is send me a private message in our chat room at vognetwork.com right now with one reason...
[SPEAKER_02]: you love VOG one reason you love VOG make it up, I don't care tell me one reason you love VOG it can be as silly or as serious as you want send Sky, just double click on my name and send me one reason you love VOG and we're gonna pick a random person to receive a Sonic 4 hoodie here on the Voice of Geeks Network tonight so there you go, and Ranma wants me to say this giveaway is brought to you by Anime Jam Session yes, fair enough, fair enough check out Anime Jam Session
[SPEAKER_02]: at AnimeJamSession.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, send those private messages into Sky right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And while I collect those messages, you have about three minutes to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: uh so yeah I have uh I guess the last minute story uh Taito put out a game for Akira about 25 years ago on the Famicom and it's finally been fan translated so you can check that there's a patch available for that um yeah so it's out there just google it um
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I was just going to talk a little bit about the whole MLB thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, the exploit they used is they adjusted the lineup of batters on the opposing team and removed the best players.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so it made it a little bit easier to...
[SPEAKER_03]: Pitch a Perfect Game
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or, well, we stand by the people that we chose as the top eight.
[SPEAKER_03]: so they're just kind of rolling with it and I mean if you think about it they fucked up and they didn't program this exclusive mode for this the perfect pitch mode or whatever perfect game challenge they fucked it up and unfortunately I guess they'll just next year patch that out but it is unfortunate that they don't just start the whole thing over again but that's the way that is alright
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else in the last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I'm not totally paying attention.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to collect the VOG stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to close it up, the contest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to read you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to read DarkSakura and Loki these answers here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You tell me which one's your favorite.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to tell you who said it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So here it is, and we'll pick a winner from this.
[SPEAKER_02]: So reasons you love VOG.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love VOG because it supports and promotes the indie side of gaming, music, and geekdom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because listening to VOG at work makes my day enjoyable.
[SPEAKER_02]: because we can chant VOG at wrestling events.
[SPEAKER_02]: V-O-G, V-O-G.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love VOG because it's got a host who asked Jiggly Kayente a question on the reunion of Drag Race.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love VOG because I want that stupid Sonic hoodie for name redacted because he would be so excited and that would keep him quiet for the whole night.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love VOG because every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: OLR is a great reason I love VOG.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reason I love VOG.
[SPEAKER_02]: OLR is on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love VOG because I can make the initials mean dumb stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: VOG is the only live podcast network I listen to often and look forward to the Bobby Blackwell Show and Orange Lounge Radio every week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a tough one.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_02]: You like the very first one?
[SPEAKER_02]: I love VOG because it supports and promotes the indie side of gaming, music, and geekdom.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could go with that I could go with that Alright, congratulations SSJ100 Matt The code's yours Good job Yay A winner is you
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100, Matt.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll email that to you later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, good answers though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet one of those was Shane.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, the Shane was the one with the name redacted.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because this sounded like something you would say.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would have picked the Jiggly Kayente one personally, but sorry, I should have stated you'd have to woo the other host over too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so congratulations again, SSJ100 Matt, the code is yours.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, if I had not been aware of RuPaul's Drag Race Jiggly Kayente sounds like a flavor of a Jello Jiggler.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that's about going to do it for another episode of Orange Laundry, but not before we go around and collect everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought tonight, I'm hungry, I'm ready to eat.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shwarma.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm hopefully going to play more games than Call of Duty this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is going to do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you guys so much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not only those of you that tune in live, but I especially want to thank the folks listening on the podcast feed as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys also listen to the whole show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll have giveaways for you in the future, I promise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Little things and big things and what have you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, if you do like what you hear here at Orange Lounge Radio, please tell a friend or two about Orange Lounge Radio, about VOG, our network now, and just help spread the word of independent radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Word of mouth is all we've got to promote the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't have this big magazine behind us.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now I can say this.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're a startup.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't got nothing but you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: to help carry the word of Orange Laundry Radio and of VOG everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks, you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be back to do it all again next week, all right?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have any mails or tweets in the meantime, send them in to twitter.com slash OLR or mailbag at orangelaundryradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you to everybody in chat for staying up with us tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks to the podcasties for downloading us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks to Random or Megaran for being here.
[SPEAKER_02]: And best of luck with your music.
[SPEAKER_02]: And thanks to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a wonderful week.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_08]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6 p.m.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pacific, 9 p.m.
[SPEAKER_08]: Eastern.
[SPEAKER_08]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know they were all still true See you next week