[SPEAKER_00]: All right, we're going to start tonight's afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nellie, get back in here, Nellie, right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nellie walked in here because she heard the outro going, and she wanted to show Loki what she bought.
[SPEAKER_00]: What did you get here?
[SPEAKER_00]: Welcome to the afterbirth, by the way, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is the Stuff That's Too Hot to Podcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: What did you get here?
[SPEAKER_08]: I got a pink helmet.
[SPEAKER_00]: A pink?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a bike helmet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm retarded.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if I fall, I don't want to hurt myself.
[SPEAKER_00]: You bought a pink bike helmet for no reason?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I bought it for a reason.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on, I'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess they can't see on the radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, they can't see on the radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not the real show.
[SPEAKER_00]: Tell Miklatov he needs to get in here too.
[SPEAKER_00]: Miklatov is going to make his way back in here too.
[SPEAKER_00]: You bought roller skates?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, I don't know how to... Hold on, we need to get her on mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I don't know how to do it, so Christopher was going to teach me.
[SPEAKER_08]: And he tried to teach me at Target, but I almost fell on him.
[SPEAKER_00]: I bought knee pads and elbow bobbers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Christopher made me, I didn't want to.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the whole point.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wanted pillows for my entire body.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I feel that's the safest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anybody want to go rollerblading with me?
[SPEAKER_00]: I can do that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have rollerblades in my car.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everybody's invited.
[SPEAKER_08]: The more people to hold me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I want to get regular street skates again because I used to have street skates.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't use inlines because of my ankle.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because of an old injury I had to my ankle.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now they say I can have roller skating sex.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's, uh... That's not easy.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's very nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: Where's Mikotov?
[SPEAKER_00]: Is he here?
[SPEAKER_09]: Where the hell is he?
[SPEAKER_00]: I know he was in the living room.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is he playing Silent Hill with Annie?
[SPEAKER_09]: It is.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm gonna go get him.
[SPEAKER_00]: You guys fill time.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a natural.
[SPEAKER_09]: All of these are so photoshopped.
[SPEAKER_00]: I bought them!
[SPEAKER_09]: I've read the first one.
[SPEAKER_09]: She wrote it under a pseudonym.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not porno.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's art.
[SPEAKER_09]: Erotica.
[SPEAKER_00]: Miklatov was supposed to come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's erotica.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Miklatov was supposed to come on and yell at people who didn't like Bomani in the U.S., but he pussied out.
[SPEAKER_00]: So forget what I said in chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not my fault, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: My name's Miklatov, and I'm a big chicken.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do you want to do Ask Nelly?
[SPEAKER_00]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you field the questions while I set up Cage Match here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Feel free to ask questions.
[SPEAKER_00]: Go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ask questions.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a new segment.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ask Nellie a question.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's ask Nellie questions.
[SPEAKER_00]: You guys ask me questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nellie, do you like your books?
Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wait, here.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can borrow my mic while I set up the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I love books.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Other than what?
[SPEAKER_00]: Didn't, didn't, here, just take my mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: You didn't play any other video games?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't play video games.
[SPEAKER_00]: I thought you played Tetris a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I played Tetris a little bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: But you got to level 16 on Bejeweled?
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, and 17 is the achievement, and I lost.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, why didn't you earn me my damn achievement?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why I need the helmet.
[SPEAKER_00]: Work!
[SPEAKER_00]: What do I... Because he beats me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously, if... Please help if he can't.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: There were no questions.
[SPEAKER_00]: What did you have for dinner, Nellie?
[SPEAKER_08]: I had one of those Frascata sandwiches from Wendy's.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was the turkey and Swiss, and I got it with no mayo, and I got a side salad with low-fat honey mustard dressing and a Diet Coke.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then Christopher just gave me an apple, because he's awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Whoever asked the question, says Nat.
[SPEAKER_00]: The other question was, have you ever gone skydiving, which I know is no.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't ask that question for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't speak for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should have a brownie bite.
[SPEAKER_00]: Where did the bad man touch you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Everywhere.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's about right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I eat whatever the crap I want diet now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nellie, what is your opinion on boobs?
[SPEAKER_08]: I love boobs.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know whose boobs I really like?
[SPEAKER_08]: Jessica Alba's.
[SPEAKER_00]: She has a no nudity clause and that really sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's because she's a biznatch.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I don't like, what's her face?
[SPEAKER_08]: The redhead with the freckles.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lindsay Lohan, yes, because her nipple is on top, and that's just not right.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like on the top of the boob.
[SPEAKER_00]: She was cuter when she, you know, more chubby and with the red hair.
[SPEAKER_08]: When she was a child, because you're a molester.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not a child molester.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lester the molester.
[SPEAKER_00]: She's now like anorexic.
[SPEAKER_00]: And Vilmar, you know, stupid.
[SPEAKER_00]: Please don't joke.
[SPEAKER_00]: Please don't joke about child molesting, not after the trial I went through this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Especially about Wilmer Valderrama.
[SPEAKER_00]: He has a show on MTV called Yo Mama, to which I said, God damn it, you ripped that off of In Living Color.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the fact that he's producing this show, he's like, this is my greatest idea ever.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a dumb show to begin with, yet for some reason I watched the final today.
[SPEAKER_00]: The best trash talker in LA and some retarded white guy who thinks he's black or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: The funniest part of that show was that the white guy got $5,000 in cash and he was surrounded by a bunch of blacks and Mexicans.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, he's not going to keep that.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's going to get mugged.
[SPEAKER_08]: because they're all behind him looking at him hatefully.
[SPEAKER_01]: I smell hate crime.
[SPEAKER_00]: We had to do the cage match.
[SPEAKER_00]: You want to sit in on the cage match tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm going to go play with my new toys.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right, have fun with your new toys.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for coming on the show, Nellie.
[SPEAKER_00]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for having me.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye, everybody.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange launch into the cage match.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway, let's get into tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_00]: Song number one was last week's winner, and it comes to us from a little band.
[SPEAKER_00]: You might have heard of it before.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not because Jamie doesn't talk about it every week on the show or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, I don't.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's true.
[SPEAKER_09]: Every other show.
[SPEAKER_00]: Every other show.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right, here it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: You voted it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It won.
[SPEAKER_00]: Here's a clip of last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_00]: Song number one, The Gorillas, Happy Landfill.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alrighty, so song number one, Gorillas with Happy Landfill.
[SPEAKER_00]: It must successfully beat two new songs to a bloody pulp, and that first song is going to come from Loki.
[SPEAKER_00]: What is your pick tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: My song is from Junkie XL again, but this time it's a collaboration with somebody else.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's called Nightmare, or Nightmares, I believe.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, well, yeah, it's short, so that's always good.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nightmares Featuring Infusion
Thank you for watching!
From the start it's easy to get lost in the darkness Darkness Darkness Darkness Darkness
[SPEAKER_00]: I kinda dig that one.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it was a little repetitive, I think, to get a full ten from, but it gets loose to nine.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's short.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like three minutes, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's very good for you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, I tried, um, it's, I don't know, this was like one of the only songs I liked on this album, and this album actually, it was like, um, Junkie XL, or JXL Radio from, um, the Computer Hell Cabin or something like that, which is a weird name, but, uh, it was one of the tracks on there, and, I don't know, it was the only one I liked, so, I give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, time for my song.
[SPEAKER_00]: and what nerd doesn't love our next artist?
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's been far too long since this person has released a song.
[SPEAKER_00]: But this guy put up this song on his website this last week saying, hey, I'm not dead.
[SPEAKER_00]: Here's a brand new song.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I said, that's great.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to put it in the cage match.
[SPEAKER_00]: So here it is, Weird Al Yankovic with You're Pitiful.
[SPEAKER_00]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_04]: My life is brilliant My life is brilliant Your life's a joke You're just pathetic You're always broke Your homemade Star Trek uniform Really ain't impressing me
[SPEAKER_05]: You're suffering from delusions of adequacy You're pitiful, you're pitiful, you're pitiful, it's true Never had a date that you couldn't inflate And you smell repulsive too
[SPEAKER_05]: What a bummer being you Well you just can't dance And forget romance Everybody you know still calls you
[SPEAKER_05]: Farty Pants, but you'll always have a job Well, I mean, as long as you still can work that slurpy machine You're pitiful, you're pitiful, you're pitiful, it's true
[SPEAKER_05]: You're half undressed Eating chips off your chest While you're playing Halo 2 No one's classier than you La la la la La la la la La la la la Loser
[SPEAKER_05]: You're pitiful, you're pitiful, you're pitiful, it's true Your dog would much rather play fetch by itself You still live with your mom when you're 42
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, song number three in tonight's cage match, Weird Al Yankovic with Your Pitiful.
[SPEAKER_00]: Was that song pitiful or magnificent, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_10]: Eleventy million.
[SPEAKER_00]: Eleventy million from DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_00]: Gorillaz, Happy Landfill
[SPEAKER_00]: And song number two you can vote for tonight is Junkie XL with Nightmares featuring Infusion.
[SPEAKER_00]: And song number three you can vote for tonight is Weird Al Yankovic with Your Pitiful.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody you know still calls you farty pants, but you won't.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right, place vote now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll tally them up, and we'll see who the wiener is.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I think I just heard DarkSakura say, I hope I lose.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: I've basically just, since you just put that up there, I've basically linked it to like seven people just now.
[SPEAKER_00]: A new song, really?
[SPEAKER_00]: Download this!
[SPEAKER_00]: That's great!
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_00]: There seems to be some anti-Weird Al people in our chat room, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I forgot to mention, and I just saw this thing on IGN.
[SPEAKER_00]: Tell us about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's good, because I can tally votes when I do that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hurry up and get your votes in now, because we don't have time.
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually have in my possession, and this is such a nerd of me, and we talked about this a while ago, that they were getting sent out.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have my Xbox Live Diamond card.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aren't you special?
[SPEAKER_00]: Great, now what the fuck can you do with it?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Impale people in the head!
[SPEAKER_00]: I can show people that I'm a member of Xbox Live!
[SPEAKER_00]: Mwah!
[SPEAKER_00]: Expires May 2007.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just thought I'd show that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can stab people in the head with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or give them evil paper cuts with your plastic card.
[SPEAKER_00]: Can't really give paper cuts with this, it's not sharp.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, you catch them just the right way on the edge, then you know, hey.
[SPEAKER_00]: But this is my nerd certification card.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would just like to point out, there are more votes in cage match tonight than I have ever seen in the four year history of this show.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm having a hard time tallying this up.
[SPEAKER_00]: You guys need to fill more time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anywho.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I have?
[SPEAKER_00]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Air, a whole lot of it, especially dead air like we're having on the show just to write about, you know, before I said something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I actually did some purchasing today.
[SPEAKER_09]: My X-Men fandom has resurged like massively, so I picked up one of the new X-Men graphic novels, except I need to go back and pick up the Astonishing X-Men one because they're written by Joss Whedon.
[SPEAKER_09]: who we all know is the god of sci-fi for giving us Firefly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Joss Whedon is my master now.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I think it's funny because he writes like Shadowcat perfectly and he based Buffy off of her.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'm a big, big nerd.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I love X-Men.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's actually a lot of businesses that support the Xbox Live Diamond Card and they have a whole list of them including...
[SPEAKER_00]: was a Hollywood Video Ace Hardware.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's actually some local businesses for at least me, like the El Dorado Hills Auto Care.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mind, Body, and Harmony.
[SPEAKER_00]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_00]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, I got all the votes tallied up whenever you guys are ready.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was hard.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dave and Busters, you can get $10 free gameplay with live.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ooh, now that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: You guys ready to hear tonight's cage match winner?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just to give you an idea of how many votes we got tonight.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sweet crap.
[SPEAKER_00]: Look how far the stars go out there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_00]: One song just took the other two out in the field and beat them senseless.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_00]: I am sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_00]: that I whooped you both tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't care, I wanted you to.
[SPEAKER_09]: In that way, I'm a winner too.
[SPEAKER_00]: Weird Al just swept the vote tonight.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, not to say song one and two weren't completely unloved, because they did get quite a few votes.
[SPEAKER_00]: In probably a normal week, song one or two might have won it, but you guys were nuts tonight.
[SPEAKER_00]: We loved the participation tonight.
[SPEAKER_00]: Loki, Xbox Live Diamond Card, the Pez Museum.
[SPEAKER_00]: Buy one in Mission, get the second free.
[SPEAKER_00]: Eh?
[SPEAKER_00]: Pez?
[SPEAKER_00]: You're a fan of Pez.
[SPEAKER_00]: I used to be.
[SPEAKER_00]: I used to collect Pez dispensers a long, long time ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bought you some.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got you a Wonder Woman one.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: And they're all sitting in a drawer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, hey, that way the sunlight doesn't damage them and they don't get dust.
[SPEAKER_00]: So someday I'll take them out and display them.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: When I have a house, that's my, that's my old fallback.
[SPEAKER_00]: When I have a house.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, ironically enough, all this stuff that's, you know, that these services are, they're all, like, local to us.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, Dublin, they have one in Dublin, California that's, uh, walks up.
[SPEAKER_00]: You receive 20% off your entire bill.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it because you put in your zip code before you went into that site?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, well maybe under my membership information or something like that, but I'm just surprised that they have these small ass companies that are on here.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I would think they'd just be big name companies and stuff, but there's like Omaha Steaks, they have 1-800-PetMeds.com, Doggy Daycare, there's some weird stuff on here, but I don't know, it's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_00]: We gotta get to chatroom FUs tonight, kids, because I know a lot of you guys have chatroom FUs.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I want to get to those.
[SPEAKER_00]: What?
[SPEAKER_00]: Why did I share what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going through the shared folders.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why are you... She's looking for the porn is what she's doing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, why did you share PaintShop Pro?
[SPEAKER_00]: Probably so I could do it on... Probably if I shared something really random, it was probably so I could get it up on Christopher's computer.
[SPEAKER_00]: GameStop.com PaintShop Pro 4 for life.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, no way.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know how I was all, Photoshop sucks, Photoshop sucks, Photoshop sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I used Photoshop CS.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I was like, PaintShop Pro sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Especially since PaintShop Pro doesn't recognize the angle sensitivity on my tablet.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, but for people who can't draw like me, PaintShop Pro 4 is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stick figures, yo.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, I could make a dancing graphic like Jeremy Todd did, probably.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, sadly, my artistic talent won't even do that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Loki, you want to get one more thought out there before I... Oh, I was just going to say, GameStop.com, if you use online site, if you purchase something over $75, you get $10 off with the card, or pretty much if you just enter in promotional code DIAMONDS.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, there you go, big secret right there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh no, whoo!
[SPEAKER_00]: Nintendo Maniac 64 is the first in chatroom to say MS Paint for the win.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've done touch-ups in Paint.
[SPEAKER_00]: I use MS Paint at work all the time.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's great for screenshots.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have begged and begged and begged.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look, if I'm doing all this crap for you, just give me Photoshop so I don't have to bring my laptop up here to do our flyers.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so I actually use Microsoft Photo Editor and Paint.
[SPEAKER_00]: I will website edit in Notepad for life.
[SPEAKER_09]: Notepad is awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Chatroom FUs, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_00]: And we're gonna start it off with MacMan!
[SPEAKER_00]: My FU is to Apple, my favorite goddamn company.
[SPEAKER_00]: They better not buy Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_00]: They will kill them.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Bandai Pin Pin 2 is not a good idea.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't worry, Macman.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just dirty rumors from fanboys.
[SPEAKER_00]: NintendoManiac64 says, F you to the chatroom for not answering my question after asking twice.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I'm asking you people at OLR.
[SPEAKER_00]: What is the fastest Wipeout and Extreme G game?
[SPEAKER_00]: I have F-Zero GX and beat all cups on Master and completed Story Mode and several chapters on Very Hard 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: I defer to Loki because I don't play Wipeout.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like Wipeout 3 and Wipeout Pure is pretty good, but those are the latest ones.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, that explains why no one answered your question.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nobody played the damn game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I'm not sure if this was a very fast game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I remember that Fatal Inertia was supposed to be pretty good on the PS3, but I heard that that game seemed kind of slow.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would just wait for Wipeout on the PS3 to come out, because that's probably going to be the fastest one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I just found your photo.
[SPEAKER_00]: You found my porn?
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you really?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I found your photo.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_00]: God.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, they're probably in there somewhere.
[SPEAKER_00]: Stop looking for my porn!
[SPEAKER_00]: Stop it!
[SPEAKER_00]: You can buy a dozen of Krispy Kreme donuts.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, I swear to God we're going to be here until midnight if I don't get moving, people.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkLionXVI wants to... Now I found it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkLion wants to say, hey, I play Wipeout, so enjoy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: You found Loki's porn or my porn?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't have porn.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm not shared.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, you know who that is?
[SPEAKER_00]: X-Verse.
[SPEAKER_08]: I found X-Verse porn.
[SPEAKER_00]: He shares it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, come on, I gotta get through this.
[SPEAKER_00]: BlackWolf says F you to Jesper.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well said.
[SPEAKER_00]: JeremyTodd1 says F you to Loki for no apparent reason.
[SPEAKER_00]: F you my car for having shitty brakes right now so I have to go get them fixed.
[SPEAKER_00]: F you to myself for not having a podcast again this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Damn work is making me too busy.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was supposed to be on his podcast, but...
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm traveling next week anyway, so we might have to reschedule.
[SPEAKER_00]: It just kind of came to my mind.
[SPEAKER_00]: DJ Tyrant says, F you to work and feeling sick.
[SPEAKER_00]: F you to having to sleep and getting a new job that requires me to actually get up early.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bandit says, I want to send a big F you to the Dallas Mavericks for thinking that they can actually beat the Miami Heat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hitstun would like to say, fuck you to Nintendo's Wi-Fi connection for not letting the four of us Mario Kart DS players in chat connect and play a game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dropping players and shit.
[SPEAKER_00]: DMN would like to say F you to any person under 16 who plays Gunbound.
[SPEAKER_00]: Half of you son of bitches act like you just discovered the internet and the other half think you are so fucking cool for taking a goddamn computer game like it's serious business.
[SPEAKER_00]: I hope you all die in a fire.
[SPEAKER_00]: Heart, DMN.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fireboma says, F you to Belmont Park for taking $34 of my money.
[SPEAKER_00]: Go, horsies, go.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Ichiban Crush says, F you to the bad rental skates I were given that utterly destroyed my feet when I went ice skating yesterday.
[SPEAKER_00]: I want to go ice skating.
[SPEAKER_00]: Funnydale says, F you to old people winning the lottery.
[SPEAKER_00]: There should be an age limit to how old you can be to win the damn lottery.
[SPEAKER_00]: Winning the lottery when you are 90 is like a blind person buying a car.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe they're going to give the money to their kids.
[SPEAKER_00]: DJ PooEater says, F you to the electric company for not supplying us with individual generators because we had a blackout and I missed the entire Orange Launch Radio show.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now I must listen to podcasts and explain it to all the bastards who ask, what are you listening to?
[SPEAKER_00]: And they look at me like I'm stupid.
[SPEAKER_00]: I hate the world, but I less than three OLR.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think he means he hates the world, but not us.
[SPEAKER_00]: Raven Stolpen says, F you Nintendo for making Apple-inspired Nintendo DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dark Knight says, my FU goes to me ending up being broke from the anime convention this weekend, but it was well worth it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anush says, FU, how in the I-405 when you're traveling at 75 already, you get past like you're standing still, and once you're in the carpool lane, you're forced to go 120 miles an hour.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I'm wondering, hello.
[SPEAKER_00]: Arimasen says, FU to the hot weather and making me unable to fast combo on poppin' music, my sticky hands sticking to the buttons.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a question for RMSN.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why does your name does not have?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: 23rdMagazine says, F you to Hordeside Altric Valley groups on Malstorm.
[SPEAKER_00]: Organizing 40 people is like herding cats.
[SPEAKER_00]: Three-legged dyslexic cats.
[SPEAKER_00]: F you to my computer locking up randomly whenever I play games.
[SPEAKER_00]: F you to whatever fucknugget thought the second half of Tales of Legendia didn't need voice acting.
[SPEAKER_00]: SSJ100 Matt says F you to high schoolers and middle schoolers invading all the malls, movie theaters, and arcade because they're off for the summer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Get jobs, dammit!
[SPEAKER_00]: And SSJ100 Matt continues F you to A-Rod Slump and F you to Kutaragi for not shutting the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_00]: Blaze says my F you is to my new boss.
[SPEAKER_00]: She is a bitch.
[SPEAKER_00]: You better hope she doesn't listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_00]: Xander K says F you to Microsoft for not putting Conker in the latest release of backward compatibility Legend of Zaku says F you to my college for being the dicks that they are billing me and everyone in my apartment complex almost $1.50 each for community damages that I didn't do Dark Tetsuya says F you to Sky who forgot he owed me a cage match pick get over it
[SPEAKER_00]: Sephiroth 1215 says, F you to Poor Designs and Anime Next, a con, with an extremely small game room where the same people sit there and won't leave the games, especially the DDR machine and 2DX.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, there was no room for the video room, so I couldn't see the movies.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bandit says, F you to the furry convention that was held in Pittsburgh this past weekend.
[SPEAKER_00]: Another F you to Raven's Dolphin for hating the Miami Heat, says Bandit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ooh, snap, we got a...
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, we are not having freaking sports chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Last FU.
[SPEAKER_00]: JeremyTodd1 says FU Raven's Dolphin for making that FU because the DS Lite is sexy.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's it, kids.
[SPEAKER_00]: We gotta go.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love my DSR.
[SPEAKER_00]: We gotta wrap it up and get out of here because... We're hungry.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have business to tend to.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I'm not hungry.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's stuff to be done.
[SPEAKER_00]: Macman sent me a private message saying, you have PC porn, you know you love it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know what the hell that's supposed to mean, but okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because he's Macman, and you have this reputation on Orange Launch Radio for not liking Mac, so... Okay, I am completely annoyed of those stupid Apple commercials where they have...
[SPEAKER_00]: Apple Guy and PC Guy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, I'm a Mac, I'm a PC.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, yeah, PCs are constantly... Yeah, my PC must be constantly rebooting during this show because, yeah, I'm never... I can't get anything done.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, I'll tell you this much.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know I love Apple.
[SPEAKER_00]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I kind of agree with that because I've been using this computer for I don't know how many years.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've never gotten a virus, ever.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_00]: I...
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: The world hangs on the bones.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because secretly DarkSakura and I are going to murder Loki tonight.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then that will change the future of our video.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not so much of a secret if you tell him.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, we're not going to kill you.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to feed you pie.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't like pie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or donuts with white frosting on them.
[SPEAKER_00]: Perhaps this song will fit Loki after tonight's staff meeting.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's our fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_00]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember when you ran away and I got on my knees and begged you not to leave because I go berserk?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you left me anyhow and then the days got worse and worse and now you see I've gone completely out of my mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, they're coming to take me away, ha ha, they're coming to take me away, ho ho, hee hee, ha ha, to the funny farm, where life is beautiful all the time, and I'll be happy to see those nice young men in their clean white coats, and they're coming to take me away, ha ha!
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was a joke and so you laughed, you laughed when I had said that losing you would make me flip my lid, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know you laughed, I heard you laugh, you laughed, you laughed and laughed and then you left, but now you know I'm utterly mad And they're coming to take me away, ha ha, they're coming to take me away, ho ho, hee hee, ha ha
[SPEAKER_07]: I cooked your food, I cleaned your house, and this is how you pay me back for all my kind, unselfish, loving deeds.
Huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you just wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll find you yet, and when they do, they'll put you in the ASPCA, you mangy mutt.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're coming to take me away, ha-ha They're coming to take me away, ho-ho, he-he, ha-ha To the funny farm where life is beautiful all the time And I'll be happy to see those nice young men in their clean white coats And they're coming to take me away, ha-ha To the happy home with trees and flowers and chirping birds And basket weavers who sit and smile and twiddle their thumbs and toes And they're coming to take me away
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_01]: We're not dead.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, I was just having printer drama.
[SPEAKER_00]: Printer drama!
[SPEAKER_00]: That's it, guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in, supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know we love you, staying up late, especially you crazy kids in the UK.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I think he finally went to bed.
[SPEAKER_00]: But thank you guys still so much for listening.
[SPEAKER_00]: We appreciate you, and we'll see you next week, alright?
[SPEAKER_00]: Our next live program is Tuesday night.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's DarkSakura's Pump Up the Volume.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wednesday night, there will be no live program because I will be in LA on a business trip.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you can try allgames.com instead because if I can, I'm going to make a cameo over there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Otherwise, you'll just have to listen to Jamie's show on Tuesday and our next live show on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sound good?
[SPEAKER_00]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, reconnect to the station in 15 seconds for more video game music.