[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_10]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here it is, episode number 186 for this June the 11th of 2006.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Loki's going to start off this set with a piece of news about the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, ooh, the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, they're saying that the early units are going to have the hardware to play the original, or the PlayStation 2 stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they're going to have PlayStation 2 hardware inside to be able to play the older games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And later, as time goes on, and they've
[SPEAKER_08]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: This time around, though, it's going to be more hardware than just one chip.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you could upscale on the original plate.
[SPEAKER_10]: You could do the faster loading and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but the thing is they have the original chip in there to be able to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just like this is going to have the PlayStation 2 hardware built in, but you can still upscale that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That doesn't have anything to do with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But later on, they're going to be going completely software with this.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this means that it's going to be even more hardware crammed inside of this thing, and as it is, I think they're having trouble fitting in the hardware in that case.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's going to end up being larger than the original Xbox by the time they're done with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Watch JP had an interview with Ken Kutaragi regarding the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically what happened is that the PlayStation 3 is, Kudaragi calls it a configuration, not a model.
[SPEAKER_10]: He says Sony wants to upgrade all aspects of the console as time goes on, like the hard drive size, maybe even the CPU specs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sony may release an upgraded version of the console every year.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Sony is really not thinking about the price or anything here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's the direct quote.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's okay to release an extended configuration every year, laugh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Though I say it like a joke, Dell will do it and Apple will do it too.
[SPEAKER_10]: In PC, if you fix the spec for two years, you'll be caught up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Computers should be changing, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's inevitable that 60 gigabytes will become short.
[SPEAKER_10]: Memory may become short too.
[SPEAKER_10]: There are many possibilities.
[SPEAKER_10]: So in other words, if you become an early adopter of the PlayStation 3...
[SPEAKER_10]: You may get screwed on this stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a console.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know they're thinking it's a PC, but if it's a PC, then get into the goddamn PC market.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't try to push this crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a fucking VAIO.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a goddamn PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, DarkSakura might have more info here on what Sony's thinking.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just might.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, Sony's basically going off about
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: When they brought it out in Europe, basically trying to push it as a computer and not as a game console, they were saying that basically importing game consoles into the European Union is a huge tax drain where computers are not.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they wanted to get out of paying the taxes that they actually released Linux for the PS2.
[SPEAKER_05]: So basically, the theory is that they're trying to do that again and we might even see Linux for the PS3.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Moving on, let's move over to the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was some more news on the Virtual Console this week, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, that's correct.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, Nintendo President Satoru Iwata, he announced, or basically outlined the price ranges of some of the games that are going to be on the Virtual Console for lease and download in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: He says they're going to be anywhere between 500 yen and 1,000 yen, and basically that
[SPEAKER_08]: is the equivalent of about $4.50 to $8.99 in the US.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that won't translate exactly, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would say $5 and $10, basically, to be competitive with Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe $4 and $8.
[SPEAKER_10]: They might try to undercut Xbox Live a little bit, who knows?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or do the old $0.99 for $4.99 and $9.99 and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wouldn't see, with some of these games, even their first party games or whatever, they could really do $0.99.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean,
[SPEAKER_08]: The thing is, is the Nintendo console, if you put the virtual console with, like, thousands of items on there... I believe what happened is that the story was slightly altered later or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was some clarification that came out that said that this is only in regards to new stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: This does not address the way that they're going to price the old Nintendo Entertainment System games, the Super Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is only about new things developed for the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the price range they're looking at.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm telling you, dude, if they do 99 cents per game...
[SPEAKER_08]: That's gonna be one sweet deal
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or like as an added incentive to say maybe Super Mario Galaxy bundle in the retro Mario games with that too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mario, Super Mario Brothers 2, um,
[SPEAKER_08]: and so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: DS software can be expanded using the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: The DS can access DS station services via the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we were kind of thinking that that might be one feature that you could download DS demos using your Wii, and I think that's a kick-butt idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's very smart.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, Nintendo's got some really interesting stuff in store, so we'll just have to see how it all works.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because sometimes things look good on paper.
[SPEAKER_10]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: systems.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, at least the stuff that they had, I mean, granted, it may not have been the best stuff for the system, but it was still pretty cool to play some NES games on the Game Boy Advance when you had Animal Crossing or, you know, using it in Crystal Chronicles, stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: One thing that they are mentioning, though, is that the release date is going to be announced before September.
[SPEAKER_08]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, um, that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we'll have to wait and see.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wonder why they're waiting so long.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe they, maybe they still, I'm starting to theorize, maybe, even though we've had all this speculation that we think October 18th's the date and everything, maybe Nintendo really still doesn't know what date they're gonna do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe they're waiting until they're absolutely certain they can hit it, and then they'll reveal it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just starting to wildly speculate here.
[SPEAKER_10]: But...
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe they feel they don't need this three-month hype going into it.
[SPEAKER_10]: They already have the hype coming off E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: They don't really need to announce, oh, it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_10]: They could do it six weeks in advance and still get away with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because let's say they announce the date in early September and the October 18th date turns out to be true.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would only be like six weeks.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's enough time.
[SPEAKER_10]: They can do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also...
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo has lots in store for the DS for the rest of the year.
[SPEAKER_10]: DS, by the way, has shipped 8.43 million units in Japan in just 18 months.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see, on July 20th, the company's going to release Shabiru DS o Ryori Navi.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a cooking program for the DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then on October, the company's going to release Nihon... I'm going to butcher these names so bad, I apologize.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my gosh, that's a huge name.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically...
[SPEAKER_10]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_10]: You want to read that whole thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, there's more?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Training DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, that is just common knowledge.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a brain training game called Common Knowledge.
[SPEAKER_10]: They plan on releasing three to four Touch Generation Series titles per year.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course, those are the games that are designed, like the brain training games and things that are really designed for the adult audience as well as kids.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're saying hardcore gamers will not be left out, but there was no mention of really any new games, but Iwata did mention that Final Fantasy 3 and Pokemon Diamond and Pearl are on their way.
[SPEAKER_10]: Final Fantasy 3 is set for an August 24th release, but again, that's Japan, but I imagine the U.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: won't be far behind.
[SPEAKER_10]: Speaking of Pokemon, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, Pokemon Battle Revolution, and I'm not a huge Pokemon fan, but
[SPEAKER_08]: What's interesting about this is the fact that the graphics look a lot better than what we saw at E3 on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that I thought was quite interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: The game actually, though, looks like it's going to tie in with the DS and Game Boy Advance versions of the new Pokemon games, as well as it's supposed to use the DS as a microphone for the game as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: What looks interesting, though, they actually have video up from it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like Final Fantasy X battles.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, basically, just really hardcore battles.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the graphics look pretty good, and I'm not sure if you've seen the picture yet, but, I mean, that looks pretty damn good for a
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: And this game is supposed to launch in 2006.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's kind of early then.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe the Wii is capable of even more and more and more.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, one interesting game that may be on its way out soon, DarkSakura, you have some news on this.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a Zelda spin-off for the DS called Mogitate Tinglebara Irui Rupeeland, which translates to Fresh Tingles Rose-Colored Rupeeland.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fresh Tingles.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tingle was in Wind Waker and Majora's Mask and also I might mention that Tingle actually really translates over to Tinkle they just changed it because that would be really bad
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, you are basically carted around by this person named Rupe... I guess it's Rupeji.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was supposed to be Old Man Rupe.
[SPEAKER_05]: It basically tells you to... Maybe Rupeji, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's written like it'd be Rupeji, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to basically collect rupees and throw them in a magic spring so you go to Rupeeland and you turn into Tingle.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you also get help from a fairy named Pingle who talks to you by a TV in your house.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you have to pay people and keep them happy and go through toll gates.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tingle and Pingle.
[SPEAKER_10]: This sounds like Teletubby's The Game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also another title that's coming up for DS is Kaito Wario 7.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: by the studio that brought us F-Zero Climax on the GBA and Rhythmic Star on Itoy.
[SPEAKER_10]: F-Zero Climax.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, F-Zero will make you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to win.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, let's get into some political-oriented news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hillary Clinton opened her big fat mouth, and she basically said that the federal government needs to step in to ensure that electronic media, including video games, isn't harming children's development.
[SPEAKER_08]: and what she's basically suggesting is that they approve a federal funded research program into the effects or broad effects of media from everything from television to video games to the internet on children.
[SPEAKER_08]: What she needs to research is a way that parents do their fucking job and she also needs a researcher goddamn new platform to be, you know, bitching about.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very interesting quote there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Parents do not need goddamn help.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on, I want to point this out too.
[SPEAKER_10]: This statement, by the way, came just like hours before the House of Representatives made that indecency fine increase.
[SPEAKER_10]: $32,500 up to $325,000.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was a 379 to 35 vote in the House.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not the place of our government to be sticking their nose into how parents do their job.
[SPEAKER_10]: Parents need to actually...
[SPEAKER_05]: Be the ones to do their job.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you're not ready to do that job, don't have the children.
[SPEAKER_08]: We mean they don't understand how to do their job.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a goddamn reading system that tells them what is appropriate for what age, what kind of content is in said product, and there's also parental controls on your console systems.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, how much more do I need to go over there and wipe their ass for them too?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it's apparently, oh, I'm so helpless, I can't possibly monitor what my kid sees.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, there's reading systems and everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: This has been done.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just the parents are too goddamn lazy to do this.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then when something bad happens, Oh my god, I didn't know!
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't know!
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm gonna sue for lots of money now!
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, that's basically what it comes down to.
[SPEAKER_08]: The parents are retarded, and then they get paid for being retarded.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you, America!
[SPEAKER_10]: Rewarding the retarded!
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Speaking of people not... This just keeps going.
[SPEAKER_10]: Speaking of people not doing their jobs...
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, guess what, uh, one of the, uh, judges in the John A. Gotti Jr.
[SPEAKER_05]: trial was doing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I already know the answer, but I'll act surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, basically, uh, he was playing solitaire.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the trial.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wasn't it a she?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it was, uh, I'm trying to find the name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shira, uh, Scheindlin.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who was, uh, playing, uh, solitaire during the trial.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, basically, while, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to see who the name was.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was Curtis Stilwell, one of the Guardian Angels from one of the anti-crime groups, basically, was testifying and the judge was playing solitaire.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I never...
[SPEAKER_10]: Until I had jury duty, I always thought the judge just kind of sat there and just kind of watched everything going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the judge really is doing other stuff while people are there testifying.
[SPEAKER_10]: When one of the lawyers yells objection, that's when the judge kind of looks over and will look at the last few things said and then make a ruling.
[SPEAKER_10]: Otherwise, the judge, I don't know if he's doing emails or looking up law things on the internet or maybe playing solitaire.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I doubt he is.
[SPEAKER_10]: He seems like a really smart guy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Poor no.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's interesting what the judges could possibly get away with.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I hadn't done jury duty this week, I would have never imagined that this could be humanly possible.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's an interesting quote here from Scylla, basically comparing...
[SPEAKER_05]: The New York Mayor Michael Bloomberg firing a city worker for playing solitaire at the desk.
[SPEAKER_05]: To quote, Should a federal judge be playing video solitaire when an employee of the New York City government gets fired for playing video solitaire?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think any of us are that good at multitasking.
[SPEAKER_05]: To me, it's an abuse and an outrage.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, you know, there's a type... I'm going to point out something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not everyone is aware of this.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is a type of learning called kinesthetic learning.
[SPEAKER_05]: What this means is that you learn better while you were doing other things, when you have something else pulling your attention.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, we did this at work, we did a study on this at work, where we were given toys, like Legos and stuff, to do while we were at one of our training classes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And at least half of the class actually retained the knowledge in our training class better.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, a lot of times when, you know, I have to listen to something, I'm doodling, I doodle in class, you know, people, some people learn, or actually I would say pay attention better when they've got something else going on, something that is, you know, when they keep one, I guess, one of their senses occupied, be it, you know, in playing solitaire.
[SPEAKER_05]: That, you know, they'll be able to better listen.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, there are people that are just like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And on top of that, you know, I would rather have a judge that's good at multitasking than having someone that can only focus on one thing at one time.
[SPEAKER_05]: And on top of that, it's also proven that people who play video games are better, have a better understanding for complex situations.
[SPEAKER_10]: It almost sounds like you're okay with her playing solitaire.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I am okay with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just cards.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the fact that you have a game on a computer with cards, that's solitaire as retarded.
[SPEAKER_10]: Solitaire is so last century.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to read the comments in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_10]: OrangeLoungeRadio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: SSJ100Matt says, they should be playing Phoenix Wright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, making the obvious joke there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blaze says, the judge does not watch porn, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Judges are heavily involved and can actually swing a trial for or against the prosecution defense.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, moving right along.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, you have some more political-oriented news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, as if this is a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: ESA is going to sue Minnesota.
[SPEAKER_08]: And why are they suing them?
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, because of the recent law that they passed that would fine kids $25 for buying or renting M or adult-rated games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And basically, they said that,
[SPEAKER_08]: This is definitely costing taxpayers a lot of money for a law that they can't really enforce in the first place.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they said, and I quote, The bill's tortured effort to end the run of the First Amendment by punishing kids directly fails under the Constitution because children have rights under the First Amendment like all other citizens.
[SPEAKER_08]: The state is attempting to impose liability on children because they know that the courts have constantly held
[SPEAKER_08]: We believe that the courts will agree that fighting children violates the First Amendment as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if this law is implemented, it will not only limit the First Amendment rights for Minnesota residents, it will create a huge amount of confusion for retailers, parents, and children.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm confident...
[SPEAKER_08]: That the court will affirm our position given the ruling on similar statutes in other jurisdictions.
[SPEAKER_08]: And here's my problem with the whole thing is why the hell did this law get passed in the first place?
[SPEAKER_08]: They don't have similar laws for R-rated movies or NC-17 movies.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fine for kids to see that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's more lifelike than games.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what the hell?
[SPEAKER_08]: This is stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really stupid and it will probably get overturned anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: So whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Moving on to another state and their political news, Louisiana, the Senate has unanimously passed a bill that had a lot of involvement by he who shall not be named on this program anymore, the Media Horn.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you don't know who we're talking about, his name rhymes with Mr. Fuck-Ompson.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jackass.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Measure was written by Representative Roy Burrell.
[SPEAKER_10]: and he was just a co-author on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's HB 1381 and it makes it illegal to sell, rent, or lease a game to a minor if it meets three conditions.
[SPEAKER_10]: If the average person would think appeals to the minor's morbid interest in violence or if it depicts violence in a manner patently offensive to prevailing standards
[SPEAKER_10]: and the game also qualifies if it lacks serious literary, artistic, political, or scientific value for minors.
[SPEAKER_10]: Violators could be fined between $102,000 and sentenced up to 12 months in a state prison.
[SPEAKER_10]: What a bunch of horse shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_10]: Where's the checks here?
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate these vague, vague laws that people are coming up with.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who determines if a game lacks serious literary, artistic, political, and scientific value for minors?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not the government's job to rate art.
[SPEAKER_05]: That same description there, it actually does go into a free speech right, because that actually is one of the defining rights for what allows free speech and what doesn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're basically trying to manipulate the Constitution into applying it toward video games instead of saying, oh, well, you're denying us our free speech right, trying to make it fall under what's allowable free speech.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me look up the First Amendment.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, actually, I want to hear this First Amendment passage here.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll read some more here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Governor of Louisiana, and of course the governor is expected to sign the bill because of the unanimous vote and the recent linking of games and teenage murder suspects in the Louisiana media.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course you can expect that the ESA will have a problem with this and file a lawsuit immediately.
[SPEAKER_10]: Any luck?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm trying to find it because basically it's a matter of court interpretation because we went over this in my law class, some of my law classes that I've taken.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, basically, just looking through this, we've been dealing with this since the country was created.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looking on here, there's also a note on here that basically...
[SPEAKER_05]: They can punish words that by their very nature invoke danger to the public peace and to the security of the state.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's one of the things listed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here it is on Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's the exact text right here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion or prohibiting the free exercise thereof or abridging the freedom of speech or the press or the right of the people peaceably to assemble and to petition the government for a redress of grievances.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to, there was, there were a number of cases though where they brought that in under, here it is, obscenity.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm quoting Wikipedia, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: The federal government and the states have long permitted to restrict obscene and pornographic speech.
[SPEAKER_05]: While obscene speech generally has no protection under the First Amendment, pornography is subject to little regulation.
[SPEAKER_05]: The exact definition of obscenity in pornography has changed over time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really recommend that people go on Wikipedia and read this.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a lot of stuff here.
[SPEAKER_05]: but um they're basically saying in Miller vs. California 1973 a work is obscene if it and this is basically what's referred to as the Miller test which is where the basis of that law in Louisiana a work is obscene if it would be found appealing to the prurient interest by an average person applying contemporary community standards to pick sexual conduct in a patently offensive way and has no serious literary artistic and political or scientific value so basically they're taking
[SPEAKER_05]: What they've applied to movies and applying it to video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's take this even a step further than that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's punish people for not sharing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because basically, right here, you're taking the parents' responsibility for deciding what their kids can see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go ahead and have the government step in for their other jobs, like making sure that the kids share their toys with their brothers and sisters.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think we should find the kids that do not share their toys.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we should also basically...
[SPEAKER_08]: and Penny Arcade as we mentioned before.
[SPEAKER_08]: is working on ads for the ESRB.
[SPEAKER_08]: And some of these were actually kind of shown a little bit at E3, and they've actually unveiled a couple of them so far.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they look pretty good.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've just got a character with text written around the outside.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, for example, I'm going to pull up one here for Sarah, one of the ones advertising the E rating.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says, because Sarah plays video games, there is a group of people making sure that the games she plays are rated.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're called the Entertainment Software Ratings Board.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's just the long way of saying it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Usually it's called the ESRB.
[SPEAKER_08]: They check games to help make sure... It's hard to read this.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's hard to read because it goes around the corner.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: That might be something in the app.
[SPEAKER_08]: To make sure it's right for you, your older brother, mom and dad, anybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody's got to do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: and they're the ones that do.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's basically an ad saying, you know what, this is being done.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the same thing is being done with film.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't understand, okay, they've done it in the past.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've, you know, gone after movies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But still though, it's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's media.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just because it's interactive, big deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, big deal if it's interactive, but it doesn't, it's still the same thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I can go watch, you know, a kung fu movie and when I
[SPEAKER_08]: Kick the crap out of people afterwards.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the same damn thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I don't know why they're not attacking all media at the same time.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Speaking of promotion, the ESRB trying to promote their rating system there.
[SPEAKER_10]: We like to promote good websites on this program, don't we, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure do.
[SPEAKER_10]: And DarkSakura is the queen of the Internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: She surfs the Internet up and down and finds a website that she would like to share with you guys in her website of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, DarkSakura, where should the kids be going this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I talked about them last week because I'd had a really good experience actually doing business with the business side of the site.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I wanted to actually promote the forums at Junkiespot.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's J-U-N-K-Y spot dot com.
[SPEAKER_05]: For anyone who's basically getting into, like I've been getting into the Dolphies, the model doll where you customize everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I swear I found more information on their forums than I have anywhere else in the entirety of the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: On top of that, it's a good place for communication for anybody who's into that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've had nothing but a good experience there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everyone's friendly.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like I haven't even seen... It's the only forum I've ever been to that I haven't seen any flaming at all on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is there going to be anything for me if I'm not into dollies?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I've talked to a few of our listeners who have gotten into it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I figured, you know, this is my...
[SPEAKER_05]: Casting my side of the week is my side of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: But also, though, there are actually some good painting tips, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, a lot of these, my husband was saying, yeah, that applies to model cars, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm being girly, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, if you like to dress up your models in Dead or Alive Beach Volleyball, maybe you want to dress up a dolly.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's people who have made...
[SPEAKER_05]: who have done basically cosplay Dolphies where they've actually made characters from different games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now that could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dolls based off of the characters.
[SPEAKER_10]: People would make those and sell them for tons of money at conventions.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can actually buy, though, pre-done...
[SPEAKER_05]: they're made by different companies but like they've actually started releasing I think they're the the cool girls line I'm trying to remember I think it's Takara that puts it out they have a cutie honey and they have Kusanagi whatever her name is from Ghost in the Shell they have a doll for that and a lot of different places but it's kind of a weird little niche thing it's a hobby I picked up while I was you know out of work but it's
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a good informative place.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Going back into some gaming news, Loki, some news in the Street Fighter world?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, and it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of a rumor at the point right now, but it says according to a website, snk-capcom.com, a DC vs. Street Fighter game may be indeed in the works.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they've confirmed with both parties at this year's E3 that the legalities of the game were being considered
[SPEAKER_08]: and um it'd be pretty interesting if they came out with that now you might remember they used to do like a Marvel versus Capcom and Marvel versus Street Fighter so DC versus Street Fighter would be kind of cool although I think Superman would kick everyone's ass in that so I don't know be interesting to see Superman versus like uh Chung Li I think he's gonna beat her ass we'll see just a little bit there she might have kryptonite panties on you never know oh okay all right uh
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, this is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you're a Final Fantasy fan, certainly you're anticipating Final Fantasy XIII, and this is why the PlayStation 3 is still cool for some people, because Final Fantasy XIII looks to be pretty ass-kicking.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Advent Children actually is inspiring Final Fantasy XIII somewhat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not maybe directly, but, you know, while the DVD kind of got some mixed reviews from people, it had some great kick-butt battle sequences in the movie, like some really fast-paced things.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, you guys have probably seen this in the trailer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, this is interesting because Final Fantasy XIII's director, Motomo Toriyama said, Final Fantasy XIII attempts to see how far it's possible to make Final Fantasy VII Advent Children's battles into a game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Final Fantasy VII Advent Children is a video production, and it showed us battles that have not been achievable in Final Fantasy so far.
[SPEAKER_10]: With Final Fantasy XIII, we're focusing on how far we can realize the video.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that might be a pretty sweet game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Imagine you're getting to control some of those battle sequences.
[SPEAKER_10]: That'll sell some PlayStation 3s.
[SPEAKER_10]: That'll get the Sony family back.
[SPEAKER_10]: That game ain't coming out until next year.
[SPEAKER_10]: Way late next year.
[SPEAKER_10]: If even that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that'll be in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, how long did Final Fantasy XII take to come out?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's still not out here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would say, I don't even think we're going to get it next year.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would say we will have Final Fantasy XIII Christmas 2008.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would anticipate.
[SPEAKER_10]: But what do I know?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just some guy on the internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, you have some news regarding online games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, actually, the online game market is huge.
[SPEAKER_08]: How huge?
[SPEAKER_08]: They're estimating it's going to reach $13 billion by the year 2011.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, of course, this is a lot in part for games such as World of Warcraft and EverQuest and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_08]: But just basically, even nowadays, you see tons of MMOs coming around.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's just the way everything's kind of headed nowadays.
[SPEAKER_08]: And even like Xbox Live Arcade and a lot of the online games, everything's really just heading online.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's no wonder that it's going to be that big.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I wouldn't be surprised if it hits $13 billion even sooner than that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of being safe.
[SPEAKER_10]: When it comes to big, it doesn't get much bigger than World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you know there was a story we talked about on this program, probably like
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: and basically the companies agreed to withdraw their previous takedown notices and drop all the infringement claims and also it was said that they'd refrain from filing any future takedown notices against the same items COP has already disputed through counter notices.
[SPEAKER_10]: And COP, by the way, will be retaining the book's disclaimers about its unofficial nature and he won't include links or instructions on how to locate cheats in the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's strictly a strategy guide without endorsing cheating.
[SPEAKER_10]: So a little bit of
[SPEAKER_10]: www.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_10]: or you can give us a phone call as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: The phone number is 916-226-9067 but please keep in mind that that is a toll call for most people so please if you don't own the phone line or pay the bills, please ask somebody before you give us a call.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we already have a phone call coming in so I'm going to go ahead and pick that up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, Sky, it's me, Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, Raven's Dolphin, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_10]: I just picked up the DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah, yes, the DS Lites are out today.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_10]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_10]: What's so great about it?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if I'm totally sold on the DS Lite yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tell me why I need to get this when I already have the DS, you know, fat.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just for one reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: This thing has brighter screens.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not saying this just because when I turned this thing on, I noticed a big difference from the original.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's colors I haven't seen before.
[SPEAKER_10]: It sure is.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know what else to call it.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's the DS... DS Heavy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like the DS Fat.
[SPEAKER_10]: The DS Fatty.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like Crappy.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not crappy.
[SPEAKER_10]: DS is a good system.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just a little fat.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like the light better.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about now?
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's somebody in our chat room here.
[SPEAKER_10]: VXJSNXV says, Brider is totally unnecessary.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you say to that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't say much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ari Mawson says, I got my DS Lite today.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love its death brightness setting.
[SPEAKER_10]: The red is more redder now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I like fourth is death.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, can I say something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I stand in line for three minutes for a DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one was at my ebb store.
[SPEAKER_10]: EB.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, there hasn't been a whole lot of promotion leading up to launch day.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's something Nintendo just kind of wants out there and is going to be circulating.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think there was really a huge push for a stellar launch for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but in Japan, people have been waiting in line for days to get a DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's because everybody else has imported one.
[SPEAKER_10]: They stand in line for Dragon Quest, too, yet here nobody cares, although they should.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but they at least Dragon Quest on a Sunday or a Saturday.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't support Sony.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Things can change.
[SPEAKER_10]: I realize the world is anti-Sony right now, but devil's advocate, you guys, Sony might say something that's going to win you back.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, Raven's Dolphin, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_10]: You too, bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, see you later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go to another phone call.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, you are on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're sounding a little distorted there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe pull the microphone back just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I'm going to go on a rant, if you don't mind.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're going to what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Go on a rant.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, go ahead and rant for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Put the microphone a little bit closer, but not as close as it was before, and then rant.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, I hate Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why?
[SPEAKER_01]: I have played it, I do not like it, I respect people who like it, but I do not like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, which one or all of them?
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, I have played all the big ones, Final Fantasy 7, 10, all those, and I do not like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you haven't played any of the classics?
[SPEAKER_10]: I just find it boring and a little just kind of weird and not too original.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: and, you know, I realize why sports games are out there, and there's some pretty good sports games out there if you're into those types of games, but for me, I don't really play sports games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't enjoy them.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's just kind of the type of game I'm not into.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm cool with you not liking Final Fantasy as long as, you know, you still have respect for people that are into it, because I respect people that play sports titles.
[SPEAKER_01]: And also, and I thank you for respecting it, but I've had many people say, you suck, you suck!
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, just...
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, instead of this, okay, instead of this, try a different approach.
[SPEAKER_10]: Instead, next time, knock it on Final Fantasy, tell your friends about the games you do like and make them play those games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Less hate, more love.
[SPEAKER_10]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_01]: And also, as you may have noticed, I tried it before I judged.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, well, that's good.
[SPEAKER_01]: That I can respect.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like one Mac hater that I will not mention.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to let you go, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: We got more calls coming in, but thanks for the call, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, later.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, let's take another call here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, this is the AmpliDude.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, AmpliDude.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just calling in.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't get to listen to much of the show besides the past 10 minutes.
[SPEAKER_07]: But as the last caller, Final Fantasy...
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy V is more of a good thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Amplitude Amplitude
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty much all RPGs.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was just playing Beatmania not too long ago before I called.
[SPEAKER_10]: US one or Japanese one?
[SPEAKER_07]: 7th Japanese.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, that's one of the styles I don't own.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I took a break from Beatmania for a little while.
[SPEAKER_05]: I skipped that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have 7th style.
[SPEAKER_10]: 7th has some of my favorite music in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I have 7th style.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't get 9th and up.
[SPEAKER_10]: I might need to borrow some of those from you at some point.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I miss a whole bunch.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I ever get mine back from George.
[SPEAKER_10]: I see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: B-Media is a good time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have you played Red yet?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually left it at home, so I had to deal with 7, but 11 is awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a beautiful setup.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need to play more of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I absolutely do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Any other thoughts for our listeners, Amplitude?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, my friend's girlfriend brought over her DS Lite today.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty kick-ass, I have to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are the Reds indeed redder?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a lot brighter.
[SPEAKER_07]: It feels a lot different than I would have expected.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I expected it to feel a lot different than it did.
[SPEAKER_10]: But is it worth $129?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is it worth that much money?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, since I've had mine since it came out, it kind of turned shitty, so I need to get myself a new one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm still on the fence with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe if I have extra money after my vacation coming up.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, Amplitude, thanks so much for the call, I'm gonna let you go so we can get some more calls, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: You too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go to at least one more call, maybe two.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go to this one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, Nintendo Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, Nintendo Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, first off, uh, what is his name, like, Gizem or Gizem or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: He really wanted me to call in.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, what do you want to call in about?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, first off, you can say about the DS Lite and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, you know, I was up in New York and stuff, and at Nintendo World, I actually saw them installing the DS Lite demo stations, which was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: What was the Nintendo store like?
[SPEAKER_10]: You went there for the launch?
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, no, I was just up there in New York for this art show my sister was in.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was for, like, Scholastics and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right, because didn't you put out the call in the last episode of the show you wanted to meet fans or something?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, um, nobody came, so, like,
[SPEAKER_11]: There's my SU for the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll come next time, if I have money.
[SPEAKER_10]: So did you get to actually play the DS Lite when you were there?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I did, but, like, I mean, sure, it was brighter and stuff, but, okay, whoop-de-doo.
[SPEAKER_10]: It wasn't that great to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah, so a little bit of a diss.
[SPEAKER_10]: The red's not so red.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it's real red.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, like, I just didn't care too much, and I got to phone some people at DDR Mario Mix,
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't played Mario Mix since E3 last year, so... But I don't want to void my warranty!
[SPEAKER_10]: Some of our warranties are already passed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, we have talked about that hack on previous episodes of the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: And just one last question.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: For any DS lighters out there who have them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Does any guys know if the DS light battery is the exact same shape and stuff as a regular DS battery?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, the DS battery stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, because we don't own one.
[SPEAKER_10]: I imagine it's probably the same charger, but I'll let someone in the chat answer that.
[SPEAKER_11]: My old charger's probably the same.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm saying that, like, you know how, like, battery life is, like, twice as long and stuff?
[SPEAKER_10]: I was just wondering if you could, like, somehow get the battery out of the new one, but in your old DS, what, you get, like, 40 hours or something?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, we'll see there, and Sakurina's agreeing.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see what the chatroom says, and I'll fill you in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, we're going to let you go, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll try and take one more call, alright?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, apparently my DSL just dropped out on me for a second.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you can always download the podcast.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I mean, it reconnects.
[SPEAKER_11]: It just does a standpoint.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_11]: See ya.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: Someone in chat room pointing out there that the battery life is, of course, shorter if you use the four times the brightness there.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the higher the brightness, the shorter the battery life, obviously.
[SPEAKER_10]: Same thing on most laptops, et cetera.
[SPEAKER_10]: Skype line is open.
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw somebody else trying to call in there, but you have a chance now if you want to get in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Our Skype line's name is Orange Lounge Radio, all one word.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or you can call us on the regular telephone as well, 916-226-9067.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: One last call for tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, you are on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Good evening, OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's DMN.
[SPEAKER_06]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, DMN.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd like to give an FU of the week to my own company.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't you work for Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_06]: I do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-oh, what do they do?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just a disturbing trend I've been seeing with the DS games since we've been on the subject of the DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_06]: With the games like Brain Training and Nintendogs, I don't know if you guys noticed this, but these games seem to have a shelf life of two weeks, and that's it, and people just toss them away.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I agree, I regret, I think at E3 last year I said Nintendogs was like the runner-up for Game of Show, I totally regret that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because it was fun for the hour I played at E3, or not even that, but it was fun for the time I played at E3, but when I actually got it home to play, it was, the thrill lasted a week, maybe two.
[SPEAKER_04]: I traded in my puppies yesterday.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's unfortunate because I've yet to see a DS game that's had a good replay value short of Mario Kart and Tetris.
[SPEAKER_06]: And those are the online games which obviously give those games more replay value.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't stand Prime Hunters because first person shooters on a portable are just a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, hopefully, and we're echoing really bad, by the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: You might want to back away from your speakers a little bit or turn it down.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully, there will be more online games in Nintendo's future.
[SPEAKER_10]: Many, many more.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, definitely.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to rant that, see what people thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully, I can get to my inside sources because I'm starting back up at Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we're starting Wii testing tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: So hopefully I can get more info on that for you guys as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_10]: Didn't you say that you were against, like on an earlier show, you were against the October date because the Wiis weren't in yet?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, that's what I've been hearing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah, so maybe it'll get interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, maybe it will.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also Operation Get Reggie Phil's Aim on the show is now underway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Please, I would love to make sweet love to Reggie through interview form on this program.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll be sure to wear protection during that show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, DMN, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for your call.
[SPEAKER_10]: We always appreciate the inside scoop.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: Later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alrighty, good Skyping tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_10]: Most of the Skype calls were pretty clear, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I appreciated that.
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys are calling Echo123 beforehand, like a good Skyper does.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, last minute stories, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do we have any last minute stories here in the studio?
[SPEAKER_10]: Anybody?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, not me.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was just some stupid thing about... I know we left out a lot from your roll this week, Loki, but there was just too damn much for two hours, and some of it was kind of... I don't know, but was there anything you really wanted to mention?
[SPEAKER_08]: There was some patent filed by Sony about some stupid electronic device that can roll up, almost like electric paper, but not... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but Sony does a lot of electronic things.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're saying that it's going to be used for a game system, and I say no.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, Sony does a lot of electronic things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I heard the Wii filed, or Nintendo had a patent on instant messaging, and my reaction was, duh.
[SPEAKER_10]: You think the Wii's going to have a service kind of like Xbox Lives where you can instant message people?
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not news.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why I didn't put it in the list for tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be PictoChat for a Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, that would be rad.
[SPEAKER_10]: PicktoChat on the internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that would be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would love to draw penises and have them seen worldwide.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I was going to say for more of our UK listeners, because I'm a huge fan of football.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, is this UK football or US football?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, like soccer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Love Football is available on Japanese Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can download the demo.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there's actually a link on...
[SPEAKER_08]: Gamers Report.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's www.gamersreport.com slash news slash 2820 and it'll teach you in case you didn't know how to create an account, a silver membership for under the Japanese territory to download those demos.
[SPEAKER_08]: I might have to do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Could I do that just by making a new account on my current Xbox?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I might do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, Oblivion got patched and all the golden duplication glitches, as you would put it, were removed.
[SPEAKER_08]: And also that patch is causing issues, freezes and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, there is that undocumented...
[SPEAKER_08]: function that was found in the Spring 360 update to clear your cache and it also removes any updates that have been done on live or any of the games so that you can actually if you accidentally play Oblivion connected to live you can unpatch it so that you can cheat in it again.
[SPEAKER_08]: The way you do that actually is pretty simple.
[SPEAKER_08]: Under the main menu or whatever you would push or actually going under the
[SPEAKER_08]: System, Blade, and then under Memory, you push Y on either the hard drive or the memory unit and push XX, left button, right button, XX.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it'll pop up a little blade saying, do you wish to perform maintenance?
[SPEAKER_08]: If you hit yes, all your updates are gone.
[SPEAKER_08]: But basically a safe way, if you haven't played it and updated it yet, just unhook it from live when you're playing the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pretty simple.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to go to our final story of the evening, and Loki, it looks like it's yours.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, anyways, I think we remember back a couple weeks ago, we talked about Codemasters and how they're basically making a game called The Turds.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, The Turds is actually a series, and they're being made available through a website called Funsta.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: When I think of turd, I don't think of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Funsta.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think of PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think of Taco Bell.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can actually play these games right now, or at least one of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some of the wonderful games you get to play would be Donkey Pong, which is going to be obviously turd-based.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, I've heard of Donkey Bong, but I think that's something different.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or no, I'm sorry, Donkey Punch, I think?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, this is Donkey Pong.
[SPEAKER_10]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Poopert.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dung Beetle Rally So wait, these guys just take games that we know and love and put poop in them?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Turd Herders, The Men in Crack, and Bogger, which is available now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I equate this with the, what is that, the Crazy Frog thing?
[SPEAKER_10]: That thing that sings the Axel F song?
[SPEAKER_10]: That thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I equate these turd games with that thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have to put that hideous thing in everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, it's a toy series that's in the UK.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why anyone would want to play with poop?
[SPEAKER_08]: But apparently, if you want to play any of these games, go to www.funsta.com That's F-U-N-S-T-A slash turds.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you can actually play Bogger, which I was playing a little bit during some of those Skype line calls.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it just plays like Frogger, but it's sewer and poop based, and it's
[SPEAKER_08]: Stupid, you can download poo tones and wallpapers also from that website, and turd merchandise.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they have a poo calculator to find out how much your turds are worth.
[SPEAKER_10]: This, by the way, will be the only time that Orange Lounge Radio endorses you playing with your poo.
[SPEAKER_10]: But even then, we're looking at you funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: So funsta.com, and you can check out Bogger.
[SPEAKER_08]: The rest of the games are coming out a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dung Beetle Rally June 20th Poopert July 4th You can play Donkey Pong and Bogger right now and July 18th Turd Herders Men in Crack And on that note it's time to end the show Let's go around and get everybody's final thought My final thought is I want this sinus infection to go away Loki, your final thought I want this pink guy to go away And DarkSakura, your final thought I want another cookie
[SPEAKER_05]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: You said you wanted it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's only my brain telling me that I want one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually quite satisfied with Swedish ginger cookies.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's going to do it for the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in, whether you were downloading, listening live, or what have you, and supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, did you know we're only like two weeks away from our four-year anniversary show?
[SPEAKER_10]: Our fourth birthday party.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mommy, wow, we're big kids now.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're out of training pants.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, uh,
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.OrangeLoungeRadio.com See you next week!