[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight, June 4th, 2006, DS Lights hit the street a bit early, could gaming be shown at the next Olympics?
[SPEAKER_02]: And more add-ons are announced for RPGs like Final Fantasy XI and Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody and welcome to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is episode number 185 for this June the 4th of 2006.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're here to talk about video games and gaming and the gaming culture and all the gaming news you guys really want to know about.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm here to help you do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might know me as Sky and she's here to help you too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Her name is DarkSakura, also known as Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_01]: I help those who help themselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the past, through emails and stuff, you've kind of been getting a lot of sickness in the past six months on the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: To not go into it in too much detail, all of the random illnesses that I've had have all stemmed from one thing, which is chronic fatigue syndrome.
[SPEAKER_01]: For those who think that taking an app will help you get over it, screw you, because it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a cumulative issue.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's something that just takes nutrition, time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Eventually it goes away.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some people have it their whole lives.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some people are bedridden for years with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just really tired.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was actually reading in Wikipedia about this because you were talking to me about this on AOL.
[SPEAKER_02]: You actually linked me to something in Wikipedia on it and it turns out you have something in common with Cher.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, joy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: if I could turn back time.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't have an affinity towards hay or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that must be the one and only Loki because here come the jokes from Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, Cher is like...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Everyone wondered what happened to Mr. Ed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cher is what happened to Mr. Ed.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're the same person!
[SPEAKER_02]: Same person!
[SPEAKER_02]: My mother loves Cher.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually went to a Cher concert.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you want to make all those jokes about, you know, because I'm gay I must love Cher.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's okay, but my mom loves her.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loves her.
[SPEAKER_01]: But she's made out of porcelain and ceramic and acrylic.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now wait, we're not share talk, so back to games for a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: In FanimeCon last week, somebody actually brought you chocolate, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, one of our listeners brought me chocolate and I'm very, very, very grateful.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it got all over the bottom of my purse, so I had to wash my purse.
[SPEAKER_01]: Only a couple pieces got out, all the rest of it were in my tummy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did share a couple pieces because I'm nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's no way I could eat all that chocolate.
[SPEAKER_02]: You didn't share it with me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would have if you'd hung around.
[SPEAKER_01]: I went nuts in the dealer's room Sunday I bought Dan a Famicom controller looking pencil box And I bought him an Ice Climbers cell phone strap It's all digitized I bought myself a slime plushie A lot of Kingdom Hearts, a lot of Final Fantasy, a lot of Squeenix love
[SPEAKER_01]: and I bought a doll.
[SPEAKER_02]: Red Octane had a booth that's about the size of this desk.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of a computer desk.
[SPEAKER_02]: A normal computer desk.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Red Octane wasn't really showing much, were they?
[SPEAKER_02]: They had Guitar Hero and they were selling controllers and that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But in the groove, absent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were selling the DDR pads but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were just selling stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were a vendor.
[SPEAKER_03]: They weren't trying to show off new games or anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's Our Crap By It, you know, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll tell you who was impressive, though, was Yes Japan, that's doing, they have, like, Japanese lessons, but they also are a label that are bringing out a lot of Japanese artists in the United States, and one of them is Guitar Vader, who did a lot of music in Jet Set Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Guitar Vader wasn't there this year, although their guitarist made it out, or one of their people made it out and was doing some stuff with a couple of the other bands there, but I didn't get to see it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was...
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it was near our panel or something around our panel, so I didn't actually get to see this, but I did get to talk with them, and who knows, you guys might hear something, some Guitar Vader on our station soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool, very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to say real quick, as far as live appearances go, we are confirmed for Fonamay 2007, and next year maybe we're looking to broadcast from the center stage, which should be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Our friend there is working on getting us broadcasting ability.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just other live appearances coming up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know in July, and not even these guys know about this yet, but there's the Sacramento thing is confirmed for July.
[SPEAKER_01]: How I knew about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I ordered a doll.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm getting into the 60 centimeter Volks of Bitsu dolls.
[SPEAKER_01]: I ordered from Junkie Spot and he called me today to make sure that my address was right.
[SPEAKER_01]: And just gave me all kinds of pointers and tips and said, and we're going to be at this convention.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was like, oh, I might be there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I find that ironic.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we're going to do that in Sacramento in July.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they're trying to get us to Seattle tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next year, if we can afford it, I know at least I'll go, and I think Jamie was talking about going, so maybe if we can get Loki, we'll all go to the SakuraCon next year.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's meCon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm hoping to do one East CoastCon next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what or when yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'll really be up to Ranma, who's my East Coast buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Foname07 on the Foname boards
[SPEAKER_02]: I played some Ragnarok and I made Assassin finally.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hit job level 50.
[SPEAKER_01]: and now I'm like assassin job level 24 and that happened in like a day and that's basically been it.
[SPEAKER_01]: There has been UNO going on in my house and we were going to buy a Whirlwind pinball machine but that fell through.
[SPEAKER_01]: We got back our Judge Dredd machine and as it's working out we've got a line in on a jackpot.
[SPEAKER_01]: A pin bot right now, but Dan's wanting to find a jack bot, which has the same play field as pin bot and has the same music as pin bot and the special music.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like a combination of pin bot and bride of pin bot with a souped up display and board and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, if you get that, I'm going to be at your house every day.
[SPEAKER_01]: I told Dan that, and he was like, well, half the reason we get the pins is for friends to play.
[SPEAKER_01]: So let's come over and play our other pins, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, what is with the sudden interest in pinball games?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sudden?
[SPEAKER_01]: My butt.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dan's been.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but you guys haven't really bought machines before.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, we had an apartment before.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have a garage now, which we intend on filling with machines.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Dan's been downloading the pinball emulators, like PinMame and some of those.
[SPEAKER_01]: for like ages and one of the machines that we're really really looking for although it's really expensive we want to get a good deal on one is a Black Knight 2000
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I've asked this on a previous show like a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Theater of Magic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Before we were podcasting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is Pin Mame based out of Sacramento?
[SPEAKER_02]: The people who do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nearby.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I've seen a car around town that has like a Pin Mame license plate.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm like, dude, is that the guy?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, dude, it's Carmichael.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think he's out of Carmichael because Dan's been by there.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to get that guy on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just a stone's throw away.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll have to get a hold of him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki practically... No, you're in Orangevale, not Carmichael.
[SPEAKER_01]: Goldfish
[SPEAKER_01]: You bet!
[SPEAKER_01]: I no longer like you.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're actually Pretzel Goldfish.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, your games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Games, oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been playing Goldfish the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually have been doing not a whole much of gaming.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been intending on sitting down with Kingdom Hearts, but I've been like, meh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Meh.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's just been pinball, pinball, pinball, pinball.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I play Dig Dug.
[SPEAKER_01]: On one of those little joystick-looking video game machines.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Machine and a Joystick.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, the Machine and a Joystick thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: They had a Pac-Man score tournament, and then I was like, screw y'all, I'm playing Dig Dug.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so I got further in Dig Dug than anybody in the house could.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: DigDugMan
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I don't like the kid size one, but they had an adult size one too that was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had the kid one at Stockton Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Lord of the Rings pinball is the win, but it was... The Lord of the Rings pinball and Star Wars pinball were the pinball... I think it was called Pinball 2000 series, which actually did not appeal to a lot of pinball players because it was more of an old school pinball thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I think those are the only two Pinball 2000 machines there are and we're not seeing any more.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think Williams stopped making pinball machines.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of the last pinball machines that I would love to play is...
[SPEAKER_01]: Big Bang Bar
[SPEAKER_01]: We need, yeah, we do need Orange Lounge Pinball.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Poo Eater says, OLR Pinball would be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get to bang around Loki's balls.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how Loki would feel about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do like DJ Poo Eater's other comment about, I like the Elvira Pinball, because Elvira's the shit.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't, you know, actually one of the old school ones that they had there that they were repairing was an Electra Pinball.
[SPEAKER_01]: That one that had the three levels, the inside level, the medium, and the outside level.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's actually pretty, from what I understand, pretty hard to get one of those.
[SPEAKER_01]: But we actually traded them our Fathom Pinball for Johnny Mnemonic.
[SPEAKER_02]: DMN has a great idea, Snakes on a Plane Pinball.
[SPEAKER_02]: As if.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's sad though is that I think that pinballs are like a dying breed.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think about pinball games on a video?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, they've actually, this is a good thing, the people who do Ultracade are doing Ultra Pin.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it really a replacement for an actual table, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: The whole thing about this is that it's actually going to emulate something like 30 to 60, I think, something classic tables, including Black Knight, Pinbot, Bride of Pinbot.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have to find some more information on it, but they've actually, I think, they're supposed to have some in test locations.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's cool, but I just don't like that idea as much as actually watching the metal ball go up the ramp and around.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd have to see it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I'd say, though, that for the sake of, you know, since these tables are getting harder and harder to find, I think that it's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a good idea to bring it out there for people who
[SPEAKER_01]: who missed the old school pinball action.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, before we turn into the pinball show, we better get back on some video games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, pinball's a video game.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's nothing wrong with pinball.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a video screen in the background with the dot matrix, but hey.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I try to play more games, but unfortunately the wife has been hogging the 360 to play Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is so weird to hear because the wife hates video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so what did I do yesterday?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I was playing...
[SPEAKER_03]: more new Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I'm already getting tired of the game I'm already on level 4 I've actually completely finished 1 through 3 gotten all the secret stuff and all that but I'm just kind of getting bored with it already and I don't know it's just not as good as some of the other games I guess um then I've been playing trying to get through Ghost Recon I'm almost done with that finally and then um
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, I've been trying a few other games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried that, uh... What was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Jewel Quest.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've already bought, like, almost every single live game or arcade game on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Except for, like, the crappy card games, because who wants crappy card games?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even if you had, like, Uno.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uno's fun!
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Uno.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uno's fun, but, like, you know, Hard With Hearts, Hard With Backgammon, I mean, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't really gotten anything new.
[SPEAKER_03]: No new games coming out that I really want.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hitman maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really don't know though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm thinking just waiting until July, August when some better games come out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have been to get Jaws on my PlayStation 2 hard drive so I can bust that game out because
[SPEAKER_03]: I heard the game is so damn glitchy and stuff, but it's worth trying because you can play it as a shark.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what though, with a concept like that, it might be cool to have a game as glitchy as Driver 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is as glitchy as Driver 3, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Driver 3, that was what made it fun, is the fact that it was so crappy.
[SPEAKER_03]: It had the perfect balance of really shitty AI and gameplay elements,
[SPEAKER_03]: with, you know, just, you know, an okay game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it wasn't so bad to where as you don't want to play it, but it wasn't, you know, so good as where as you need to pick it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just equally awful, you know, across all levels.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, that game's really fun, especially if you can get it cheap because it's so glitchy.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can literally play it for like an afternoon and just... So, it's like one of those... It's like a B-movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a bad B-movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so bad it's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like Jaws 3D.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Jaws on the consoles which just came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a cheap ass game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like $29.99 but just wait a couple of weeks once people buy it and say hey this game sucks and then they sell it back get those copies for even cheaper.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's what you need to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just Grand Theft Auto Liberty City Stories again.
[SPEAKER_02]: The usual.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going back to the team games we've been doing free-for-alls and
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still fun because we just find new ways to kill each other.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still a highlight of the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I should mention in our chat room right now over at OrangeLawnRadio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you are listening live here on Sunday night on our station, it looks like DMN is in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he, for whatever reason, has an extra Zelda GameCube collector's disc burning a hole in his pocket.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, the one that had all like the classic Zelda games on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he's just giving it away to a random chatter right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's asking trivia questions and making a game out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, you guys cool with that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got ripped out of the one that actually had the Zelda 1 and Zelda 2 on there as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I only got the one with both of the Nintendo 64 ones.
[SPEAKER_01]: I might have an extra.
[SPEAKER_03]: You could enter DMN's contest right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never played that one anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to get one of those multiplayer Pac-Man games.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was the one on the GameCube, remember?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Pac-Man Versus.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never did play that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looked fun, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, I want to go over to my gaming week, because I actually have quite a bit that I was playing this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: In my personal life, I got jury duty this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And most people were telling me that jury duty, you know, bring a book.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be boring.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to sit there all day long, and nothing's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I took my DS, and yeah, there was a lot of dead time there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the rest of it didn't go how they said it would.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said I would get dismissed by the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually got put on a jury for a trial that's going to last two weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess I'll be playing a lot of DS while I'm at the courthouse because there's a lot of down... I mean, we get like hour and a half lunches and all this crazy stuff, so I have a DS to keep me busy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been playing Final Fantasy 1, which I realize is not a DS game, but Extifer keeps forgetting to loan me the new Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: cartridge that I keep wanting to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the only other game I had ready available when I left for the courthouse was Super Princess Peach.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that game kind of... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: An action game isn't as easy to play...
[SPEAKER_02]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy 1, if you haven't played it before, the one on the Game Boy Advance, they really souped it up from the NES.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not as frustrating because they switched the battle system to more like Final Fantasy 4, where if your whole party attacks one monster and it dies, it doesn't end up being wasted attacks, it will attack a different monster.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that was one really frustrating thing about Final Fantasy 1 on the NES.
[SPEAKER_02]: but you know that kinda adds to the strategy element I suppose but that is different.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also got a chance to play something new 2DX Red Beatmania 2DX Red or 11 and this is the import game it's not here in America you do have to import it from Japan and of course if you know Beatmania in the US then I'm sure you have heard of the
[SPEAKER_02]: Japanese series that spawned it, and now it's up to its 11th home version game, 13th arcade game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The things I like about 2DX Red, the interface is great, it's slick, it's got an awesome interface, it's a customizable interface.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the things you unlock, you don't really unlock songs in 2DX anymore, you unlock either gallery art or you unlock customization pieces.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can actually change the picture that's on the turntable, the bar that is falling down during the parts of the song, what the notes look like when they explode when you hit the buttons, or you can change the whole damn skin around it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now there's only like seven or so preset ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you don't have total freedom, but it's still pretty cool because you can mix and match and kind of make the game your own a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I thought that was kind of a neat addition and something fun to unlock there.
[SPEAKER_02]: My only real problem with Beatmania 2DX Red is that I'm not a fan of the songs as much as previous styles.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some really good songs, but overall I think I prefer 9th, 7th, kind of going back to some of the older styles.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they did bring back some good older songs, except V isn't one of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: V is the song that has been in like every Beatmania 2DX game in Japan since 5th style, 5th, 6th, 7th, 8th, 9th, 10th.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is not in 11th.
[SPEAKER_02]: They finally gave it a rest for a little while.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, until they come up with the next, you know, was it 2DX 14 or whatever and it's gonna be V2 or something like that or VV or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: It'll be H, it'll be Handel.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other part that I love about 2DX Red is rival data.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Miklatov is the one that brought it to the house here, so I had a chance to play it, and I started playing on my memory card.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I was able to put in his memory card and load his scores onto my card.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what that would do is it would show me, hey, these are the songs you're doing better than Miklatov at, and these are the songs you need to improve on if you want to be better than Miklatov.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can, I think, load up to five people.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the other cool thing is you can do rival data against yourself, essentially.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you go into the options and you go all the way down to the bottom and you see this little turntable, you can change it so that if you're playing one player, you know how usually in Beatmania the right side of the screen, if you're playing left or vice versa, if you're a player two side person, the left side is just blank.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing happens there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what will happen instead is that that will be replaced by a bar graph that goes up showing you how your combo compares to the last game that you played.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, not your combo, but your Beatmania points.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get plus two for a flashing great, plus one for a great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It kind of shows that in bar graph.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very similar to Keyboard Mania.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you've ever played Keyboard Mania, it's almost like they stole it from Keyboard Mania.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: and yeah, so rival data is pretty cool and it kind of gives you incentive to keep playing because I have to be better than Miklatov, so that's 2DX Red.
[SPEAKER_02]: I definitely recommend it to music games fans that have a Japanese PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those of you guys that don't have a Japanese PlayStation 2, let's hope that Konami of America releases a Beatmania 2 here in the US and that they'll use this game's interface to model it off of because I think that would happen and that would be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: R2-Beat Beat Mania
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to play R2-B because R2-B is a real creative idea for a music game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really like it because it gets into the kind of competitive nature a little more, like some of the songs are very competitive.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you want to check this out, there's actually one of our listeners has a website that's all about this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you're going to have to kind of follow the directions on the forums of this website to be able to play the game because it's all in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_02]: So unless you read and understand Japanese fluently,
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ MaxxUS.bamanistyle.com
[SPEAKER_02]: It kind of makes me think of like a Mario Kart rhythm game because in one of the modes you can use items on other players and it's pretty creative some of the items they come up with like one of them will send out this giant King Kong type thing onto the racetrack that'll beat the racetrack so that your screen shakes so it's really hard to see the notes as they're coming down another item will like throw headphones onto your opponent's head that will change the song completely that they're hearing so that the beats won't match up or anything makes it very difficult for a couple measures
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of where I get the Mario Kart thing, because the items really add a whole different flair to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the pros about this game, it's free.
[SPEAKER_02]: Graphically, it's pretty kick-butt.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was given a tip, you can actually use Alt-Enter to play the game in a window if you don't like it taking up your whole screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's a real kind of clever music game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only cons that I really saw is that...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got a really steep learning curve because of the fact that the game's not in English.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you really have to be patient if you want to learn this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You will get frustrated with it very easy if the language barrier is going to be a problem for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I force myself to kind of get through the tutorial and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's not so bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can figure it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Use common sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'll figure out how to play the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you guys should check it out if you get a chance.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you like music games, because it's free.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if this is the type of game I would pay money for, just because it seems like the type of game I'll only play for a little while, even though it does offer some kind of customization, like you can change your hair, change your clothes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really see myself playing this the long term, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: They do have the fact that they can expand...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: It's part of a network of a bunch of other different kinds of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think in that way, it'll be great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually part of a network called GameChew.jp.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's their website, GameChew.jp.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think I would really enjoy this game as a part of a selection of games from a website.
[SPEAKER_02]: So check it out if you guys want to see a crazy-looking game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other than that...
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a buffet of Xbox Live arcade games and some Rockstar table tennis.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's get into some gaming news here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to start off tonight with Loki, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, and basically the story to start things off is about the DS Lite and how some stores just don't get street dates.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the store chains being Target, the other one being Walmart, and basically...
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, the shipments of these new systems have already come in to pretty much everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, I mean, my company that I work at, they actually have them right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, you know, like most things, you're not supposed to sell until street date, you know, to basically either make it, you know, fair for everybody, you know, so that one person doesn't have it sooner than the other and that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, companies don't realize this or either just ignore it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so, you know, in the case of like certain Targets and Walmarts,
[SPEAKER_03]: Just went ahead and sold it the day they got them.
[SPEAKER_03]: So people have already been picking them up, put them on eBay and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_03]: So basically if you're lucky enough to find one, more power to you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which is ridiculous since you can just order them online from Japan.
[SPEAKER_00]: Exactly, and it doesn't matter anyways.
[SPEAKER_00]: For almost the same price.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they're really coming out in about a week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, just wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: And by the way, this is not the first time Target's broken street date.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm surprised Toys R Us wasn't one of those.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they've done, like, you know, Katamari.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, We Are Katamari.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember when we called the Target.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: And these companies, you know, they think that they're getting away with this shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, Nintendo will know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's just like, you know, Namco.
[SPEAKER_03]: Namco is aware of the problem, you know, with We Heart Katamari.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or not We Heart Katamari.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, We Heart Katamari.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they basically, you know, those stores will not be getting their product on time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or they'll be getting it the day of or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: They won't get it early anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's not a good thing to do, to piss off Nintendo right before the Wii launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, if they don't have it, people are going out of their places, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not good for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's what they did with GameStop and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: When GameStop didn't have the pre-orders, people went to Best Buy, who didn't do pre-orders, and tried to get it that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so, I mean, if you can find them early, great.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be honest, it's just a redesign of the damn console.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, do you really need one right away?
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually don't think they're any more comfortable to play than the US ones anyway, because of that sharp edge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, do you have any news about the colors of the systems that we're seeing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, actually, in Europe, they're getting two colors.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're getting black and white.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty monochrome there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, that's interesting, because we're only getting white.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do they get black?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because they're special.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess getting screwed on the price finally.
[SPEAKER_02]: Karma pays off for them because they always get screwed on prices.
[SPEAKER_01]: Their price actually is going to be out on June 23rd in Europe.
[SPEAKER_01]: Their price is £99.99 or €149.99.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, as far as some games that they're getting on June 30th, the new Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_01]: will be out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Brain Training is on June 9th.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nintendogs Dalmatian and Friends is on June 16th.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're getting a Dalmatian one.
[SPEAKER_01]: which is actually, I would be jealous if I even played my Nintendogs anymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, VidPower in our chat room reminds us that there actually is a Frapper map.
[SPEAKER_02]: Horizons Radio has a Frapper map, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're on Frapper, F-R-A-P-P-R dot com, look us up.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you can also look up DS Lite Availability.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just cram that all together into one word.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're actually checking targets to see if any have the DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_02]: I already looked in this area and there are none.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of want one, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on with more news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: In other news, also Nintendo related, we've got information that the Wii is not going to have Dolby Digital out.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least no 5.1 surround sound.
[SPEAKER_03]: They will have ProLogic, which is still good, but I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think you really need it since they're not going to be doing HD anyway, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess, I don't know, I don't have Dolby Digital in my house anyway, so I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, I'm sure there's some people that will be kind of, hmm, but... Well, I'm kind of, uh... Well, you have Dolby Digital in my house.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well, literally, I mean, who... Okay, so you have it in your house.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, that's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, I mean, you have a ProLogic setup on yours, so it sounds great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it sounds fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: My receiver also has ProLogic, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not going to be the end of the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they're not supporting HD, true, I should say true HD or whatever anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, as long as the games are fun, I'm not going to worry too much about the sound.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus, we already know there's a speaker in the controller, which is kind of, you know, can't really get that, 5.1 or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Digital 5.1, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't have the speaker in the controller, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Is PlayStation 3 looking at it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that another thing they're trying to do?
[SPEAKER_03]: PlayStation 2 had optical digital audio out, so I wouldn't imagine that PlayStation 3 does as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then again, that could be on one of those lists of things that they've scrapped for the price point.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know a lot about audio setups.
[SPEAKER_02]: The different types kind of go over my head a little bit, so it's interesting.
Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony Computer Entertainment Europe's Phil Harrison
[SPEAKER_02]: In a way I understand why people say we stole Nintendo's idea, but it's a little stupid if you forgive the remark.
[SPEAKER_02]: When we brought the PlayStation to the market in 1994, we introduced real-time 3D graphics for the first time.
[SPEAKER_02]: When Nintendo launched its Nintendo 64 in 1996, it also had 3D graphics.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did we say Nintendo stole our idea?
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Star Fox PC Engine Duo 3D
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they are pretty much full of crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm surprised he's not actually researching it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got two questions.
[SPEAKER_02]: First, did Sony steal Nintendo's idea?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why or why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: I say no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they did something to make themselves competitive in that aspect, but I don't think they stole the idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: How easy would it have been to just come out with a controller?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They tried something a little bit different, and although I'm not the biggest fan of the idea, I wouldn't say they stole it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they just kind of tried to do something...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Any?
[SPEAKER_01]: Who's going to talk about who stole what from the Super Nintendo having been out?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's business.
[SPEAKER_01]: Companies steal from each other all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, remember when Vanilla Coke came out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we all loved Vanilla Coke at the time when it first came out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Vanilla Pepsi was a better product.
[SPEAKER_02]: Vanilla Pepsi came out like two months later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is Pepsi a bunch of thieves?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's what they do.
[SPEAKER_02]: They always copy each other.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the point of business to find out other businesses' trade secrets and cash in on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, you have a thought?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, okay, so they say, we didn't copy the way it's been in production for two years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Two years ago, there was a game put out on Game Boy Advance called WarioWare Twisted.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had the same kind of technology in there that has, you know, that's in the controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, fuck you, Sony, you're still copying somebody.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, whether you want, first off, you got your facts wrong anyway, so it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so they copied it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Great, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they've copied controller designs of the analog sticks and stuff from Nintendo 64, Rumble from Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Xbox Live, they're going to be copying that for the PlayStation 3 online service or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: it's what people like and so obviously you have to put it in your console but don't try to pass it off as this is an original idea that you came up with okay basically say yeah our competitions do it we need to do this in order to be competitive that's all you gotta say that is it pretty simple instead of being a jackass going we came up with it first no I don't think so so you know what great if it works for your console awesome
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's going to be stupid, and if they're going to be taking out the Rumble feature for this, I think it's a really bad trade-off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got to go to our chat room with some comments, because they're lit up right now a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spiritsnare would like to point out, Pepsi Blue came out, but Coke Blue never did.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's because Pepsi Blue was kind of crappy.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was like Windex.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't like it at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: It tastes like Windex, and it made your poo change colors.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for sharing.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else is there here?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: There was something else I was going to... Oh, here it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: O2G said maybe if they didn't implement it at the last minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think maybe the whole last minute implementation of this is what makes them look like they're thieving here?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it does.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if they were saying that, oh yeah, this is something we're thinking about or something like that, that would be a little different, you know, if that was something they were toying around with.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the fact that they brought it in, I mean, so what if they've been working on it for two years, we haven't heard anything about it, we haven't seen, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Warioware Sony Hate
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe if they put out a good product they'd earn our love.
[SPEAKER_03]: Their system right now, they don't have a great lineup of games coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Granted, okay, the system may be cool, but it's pumping out the same kind of graphics, same kind of gameplay as you're going to be getting on the Xbox 360, but it's more expensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: And because they think that they need a Blu-ray drive in there because they're really trying to push this whole...
[SPEAKER_03]: HD movie format on me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to pay the extra $200 for this thing when I've just a few years ago replaced all my VHS with DVDs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now they want me to do this again?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't own an HD TV that's going to benefit from this, so why should I have to spend the extra $200 for it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Plus they came out a year later, plus they're doing all these unoriginal ideas.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: If they do come out with some really good games like maybe a new Twisted Metal or something like that, that'd be great, but the whole thing
[SPEAKER_03]: Sony is a great company and all, but even after the PSP came out and the launch games for that, the launch games were pitiful for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were all just rehashed.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Twisted Metal head-on?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's Twisted Metal 2 all over again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Luminous being a glaring exception, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, but that's a third-party company, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a third-party... I mean, that game could have been made on the original PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's not something that really needed...
[SPEAKER_03]: and the PlayStation Portable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me interject here with some comments from chat, although some folks in chat are cheering you on there, BoyWonderZero and HintIrenee.
[SPEAKER_02]: Funnydale is mentioning, if anyone should sue anyone, it should be Ralph Baer.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was the guy who invented the idea for a home video game console and got almost nothing out of it himself.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll phrase a question towards DarkSakura, because I know you have not been a fan of Sony's PlayStation 3 stuff lately.
[SPEAKER_02]: What could Sony do...
[SPEAKER_02]: to win you over and you would be rah rah rah about this console on launch day.
[SPEAKER_02]: What could they do between now and launch day to win you back?
[SPEAKER_01]: Do we have time for me to list it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take a couple if you've got it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: First of all, drop the price.
[SPEAKER_01]: Take out all of the unnecessary shit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Take out the gyroscope.
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't fucking need it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, we don't need high def that not every system is going to be able to manage.
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't need two HDMI ports.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe one HDMI port.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, enough to, you know, because how many people are going to hook up two HDMI ports?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they only have one now.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did scale it back to one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, leave in the HDMI.
[SPEAKER_02]: But allow me to point out that the low-end system will not even have the HDMI at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know this.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wouldn't waste my money on a low-end system.
[SPEAKER_01]: But...
[SPEAKER_01]: they need to, you know the memory stick thing it's nice but they should have made them use the memory sticks from the beginning or a USB thing, you know they should have had something more universal that would last, if their vision was that big they should have had it last from system to system or they should at very least use the PS2 memory cards, you know there's price reduction right there they don't need to process the polys that they're saying that they can, no one is really going to care
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, they need to make sure that the games they put on there, first of all, take care of the whole anti-aliasing issue that you've had ever since the days of the PS1.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, fix that.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, um... Oh, God, I've got such a list in my head right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, Loki 1 Interject, anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's something else I liked about the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: The old controllers worked on the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: I spent the $300 or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did not have to go out and buy new hookups.
[SPEAKER_03]: It used the same hookups as the PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't have to buy new controllers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Granted, it came with one, but I didn't have to go out and buy a second one to play two-player games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had that already because I already owned the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Devil's Advocate, Xbox 360 didn't do that for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it didn't.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, you can use your Xbox controllers.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, you can't.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: F1 Racing for the PS3 has...
[SPEAKER_03]: Use the wing mirror basically as the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't need that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is a stupid example of the technology.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to ask one more question and then I want to get back to the news because we've spent an awful lot of time on this unplanned Sony discussion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's my last thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Should Sony push back the release of this to save themselves?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes or no?
[SPEAKER_01]: They're going to have to, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: Gears of War
[SPEAKER_03]: and just a lot of really big stuff that's coming out for the 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you delay it any further, like into spring, people are already going to be snapping up the Xbox 360 and they'll say to hell with the PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, if they do launch the PS3 now, you're going to get a lot of unfinished games, you're going to get a lot of things that may not work right, and it's going to be one big clusterfuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: GK128 PS3 in 2006?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll eat my hat if that happens!
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, Legend of Zaku says they need it to live or Nintendo will eat them alive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boy Wonder Zero says they can't do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bandit says the PlayStation 3 is too next-gen for this gen.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Sakurina says recap, fuck next-generation consoles, go retro.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I guess the Dreamcast is having a resurgence from what I understand, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to get back into some more news here, so let's keep it on moving here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, you have some news on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, also basically one of the big things about the Wii was that this Wii Connect 24 service that they're going to be having, they'll basically allow you to have updates.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, some of the things that they're talking about is daily content, and this can be anything from DS demos to movies, etc.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just basically new content each day for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think that's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's maybe a bit optimistic, but definitely I like the idea of having DS demos on there so you can actually play that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's something that Sony should copy, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, PS3 downloadable demos, that'd be a really good thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So hopefully, the other thing though is, I mean, granted there's only limited storage on this thing, hopefully they'll have some way to turn this off in case you don't want it, because
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: and that they are licensing to PC manufacturers right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we set up our launch title as Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Might sell some systems.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's supposed to be actually an on-demand game service.
[SPEAKER_01]: Deliver the games to the system in the living room through online memes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So correct me if I'm wrong, it sounds like GameTap on your TV, in a way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not with classic titles, but with new games.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what it's looking like.
[SPEAKER_01]: But they've changed their launch date now from mid-2006 to October.
[SPEAKER_01]: Their new CEO is basically going in saying that they're really pushing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're trying to get the Phantom Lapboard out worldwide.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which is a combination keyboard and mouse.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they're saying it's on schedule for first arrivals in October for the US market.
[SPEAKER_01]: But right now they're running at a $70 million loss.
[SPEAKER_01]: No product created.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe this is why Nintendo's afraid to announce the launch date for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're shaking in their boots over this Phantom launch.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's a hell of a... What?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, here's what they need to do with the Phantom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, what?
[SPEAKER_03]: If you really want to put this out and actually be successful with it and you're talking about on-demand service,
[SPEAKER_03]: Why don't you pitch it to cable companies?
[SPEAKER_03]: Cable companies now are starting to do this on-demand crap where you can download movies and karaoke and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why not games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just soup up their hardware right now and offer games where you can download them on-demand and play them.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to know something weird?
[SPEAKER_02]: Cable companies did this in the 80s.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know if it was something that was just being tested locally in this market, but my cable box back in like...
[SPEAKER_02]: Back when the only system we had was the Atari 2600, this is before the launch of the NES, we're talking that long ago, you could get games on demand, like poker and stuff, that had better graphics than the Atari 2600, and use your remote.
[SPEAKER_02]: For some reason, that never took off.
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember the Satellaview?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't have that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the Satellaview is what they had in Japan for the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Zelda Satellaview, which is actually, in my opinion, the best version of the first Zelda game ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember back in the day when they had the Sega Channel, and that was okay, but it was slow as hell.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nowadays, though, with everything being broadband, I think they should do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do this in hotel rooms right now, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, I see chat rooms.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have Xbox Arcade.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the same difference.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think that's something that they should really do, because in that way, you know, oh, I don't want to buy a game console, but, you know, maybe this game service or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: GameTap should fucking go in the business with these people, and, you know, I think that'd be good, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really where they need to be going, because the Phantom console as, like, a PC on-demand thing, people have done it for cheaper and better, so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let's keep it moving here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to talk about the ESRB for a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Penny Arcade is actually teaming up with ESRB.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gabe from Penny Arcade wrote that they have been signed by the ESRB to put together a new advertising campaign meant to educate gamers about the ESRB's rating systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to show up in magazines and websites and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like...
[SPEAKER_02]: Penny Arcade has a very funny approach to social issues sometimes, so I'll be very curious to see what they come up with for this ESRB.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it'll be very creative.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some very creative guys over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you remember they actually had a little thing teasing at it at E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: You probably saw those pillars that they had with the characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think any way to get the message out there is great, especially if it's something that parents can be able to use and so there's less confusion on
[SPEAKER_03]: The ESRB works as the parents that need to be educated.
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's hope whatever they're working on is geared towards parents.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I would say if it's educated, if it's aimed at gamers talking to parents about what they're playing, I think that's not a bad thing either.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I don't know, that would be kind of a hard thing to market.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, at Penny Arcade, they're creative, they can come up with something, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on, let's go on over to Loki, who has news on another video game law.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep, and this one's in, it's been passed in Minnesota.
[SPEAKER_03]: Their last, latest state law is basically...
[SPEAKER_03]: Finding, and this is interesting, finding the people that buy the game and not the sellers of the games.
[SPEAKER_03]: So basically, if you're a miner and you live in Minnesota and you happen to purchase an emirated game, well, the blame's going to fall on your hands.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to be fined $25 for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's smart.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the right approach to take.
[SPEAKER_01]: Really, whose responsibility is it?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the person who's paying out the money.
[SPEAKER_01]: They want the product.
[SPEAKER_01]: The game retailer, why should they parent other people's children for them?
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm fully in support of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, they're saying that they're not trying to punish gamers.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically, if you do get caught doing this and get fined, it would not go on your record.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just you'd be fined $25.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other thing, though, is they were saying that they don't know how they're going to enforce it, which is, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's the right approach.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, punish the people buying the games or maybe even the parents, you know, because
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe the fine should be, well, I don't know if it's a little bit too, you know, the right price point or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe a little bit higher of a fine would be a bit better, but I guess it's sort of a step in the right direction instead of, you know, just trying to say, oh, let's ban all bad video games type thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of bad things and games doing bad things to children, an affiliate of Fox, a Fox 9 TV station, further proving that the media does not get games sometimes, they ran a story recently that talked about how children are using a game device to access porn out of thin air.
[SPEAKER_02]: The gaming device in question, the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, if you consider that the PSP can access the internet...
[SPEAKER_02]: and that if you listen to Avenue Q, the internet is for porn.
[SPEAKER_02]: This does not make any surprise at all that you can download porn on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: This kind of reminds me of that other story that ran not that long ago about how predators can pick up children in PictoChat, whereas I never find people chatting in PictoChat.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is just kind of one of those, is this really news?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if you really understand that the PSP gets on the internet and you can get anything on the internet,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's easy to blame Fox and use that whole thing, but really, I think there's a lot of uneducated media folks out there in general.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's easy to pick on Fox in this case, but... My favorite, though, was the Penny Arcade response to the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, with the calculator?
[SPEAKER_02]: The edge of sketch in the calculator.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your calculator can say boobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of porn, DarkSakura likes to surf the internet up and down all day long for porn, but once in a while she stumbles upon a site she wants to share with you in a little segment we call DarkSakura's Website of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, where should the kids be surfing to this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Today's website of the week is... Actually, I had one, and then there was another one that I had found earlier that I'm going to stick with because of the article I found on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's at livescience.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you're going to this URL, it's livescience.com slash technology slash 050201 underscore cell underscore danger dot html.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, it's talking about how drivers on cell phones kill thousands of people.
[SPEAKER_01]: All the more reason to take old people off the road.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cell phone distractions cause 2,600 deaths and 330,000 injuries in the United States every year, according to the Human Factors and Ergonomics Society.
[SPEAKER_01]: Drivers talking on cell phones are 18% slower to react to brake lights, and they're also 12% greater following distance, at least that's one thing good, but they also took 17% longer to regain speed once they had a brake.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, basically, it slows down your reaction time.
[SPEAKER_01]: It makes you a danger to yourself and everybody else on the road.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I suggest that everybody read this article and hang up your goddamn phone.
[SPEAKER_01]: Everyone should read this.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's my side of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you want to call me to talk about this, I'll be driving to the bay tonight, so I'll have plenty of time to talk.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm dead serious about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's... Having known someone who lost her child because the other driver was talking on her cell phone when she ran him over, then yeah, I definitely am very much against it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going back to games now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, and the continuing saga of the Wii release date.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I think is interesting?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you check dig.com out this week, some story that was speculating like a November 11th launch or something got like a thousand digs or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it kind of struck me as amazing because they, not to knock the story, but their source was kind of like some guy anonymously told us.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you know I realize that you know our source to some people doesn't seem much better and that's fine but I was just kind of surprised that everybody seemed to be going they were jumping at that date based off of shaky evidence well Loki has further evidence that seems to point towards October take it with a grain of salt if you want but here it is and I'd like to preface something real quick I saw there was a little story on GameSpot this week talking about Activision's upcoming titles for the fourth quarter including some titles like Pimp My Ride the Game
[SPEAKER_03]: and some Cabela's Alaskan Hunt game or something like that and other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: You do remember way back when I talked about this months ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: When was that one event?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was during Destination PlayStation in Florida.
[SPEAKER_03]: They announced all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did anyone pay attention to that?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Download the show the week of Destination PlayStation that we did, and you'll hear Loki saying this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, I get this information, and nobody pays attention to it until a big site comes and repeats the same thing, and then everyone's like, oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyways, more Wii dates, of course, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're all around the same time again.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this time we've got Activision and Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: A little bit bigger companies out there should know when the Wii's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Granted, some of their games, though, like, for example, Call of Duty 3, that is on the launch date, which is great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't even know Call of Duty was coming to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I mentioned that also on that same podcast about Destination PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why didn't they show that at E3?
[SPEAKER_03]: They did, sort of, in movie form.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a pre-rendered movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was like, eh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tony Hawk's Downhill Jam Rayman 4
[SPEAKER_03]: and then Marvel Ultimate Alliance also coming out actually to coincide with the PlayStation 3 launch because that's being launched in every single system that day on November 16th so there's some more games for you granted not all of them are on October 18th but
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we still haven't gotten a lot of the company's stuff yet and obviously you're not going to be just announcing stuff for launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to be launching with more titles.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still within the launch window and it's about a week away from the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm still sticking with October 18th and I will be laughing my ass off when this does come out on October 18th or when they come out with the news that we're launching it on the anniversary of the original Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, what if it doesn't turn out that way though?
[SPEAKER_02]: What if they do come out and say it's November 11th?
[SPEAKER_02]: What are you going to do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, then, good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's coming out November 11th.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's coming out this date, and granted, there's powers that may not be able to make it at this launch date.
[SPEAKER_03]: Things can delay stuff, but it's too convenient not to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's too many coincidences.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: With, you know, more and more publishers every day, every week, you know, agreeing that this is a time frame.
[SPEAKER_03]: Notice all these dates aren't all in November.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not all hovering around November like it would be coming out in November.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's definitely, okay, definitely in October and most likely on the 18th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, now you have some definite for sure release dates to share with us, correct?
[SPEAKER_01]: I sure do.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now this isn't for the US, these are for the UK.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because screw the UK, I mean... You do live here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, damn it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, this is the release dates for our UK listeners coming up on the 9th of the following games.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have Zoo Tycoon 2... Oh, sorry, that was the second.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_01]: F-117A Stealth Fighter on PC is coming out Namco Museum 50th Anniversary on GameCube Sensible Soccer 2006 on PC Xbox, Playstation 2 and Talkman on PSP Also on the 13th we have Culpa Inata on PC That's though going to be the following Monday Alright, Loki do you have anything in the US?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, there's lots of fun stuff coming out this coming week here Of course
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, you know, it's kind of getting to a dead part of the month.
[SPEAKER_03]: Urban Chaos, Riot Response is supposed to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, that would be the following week.
[SPEAKER_03]: This week, though, we have Grand Theft Auto Liberty City Stories on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that should be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, there isn't multiplayer on it, so that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: But also, we've got Ant 1 Streetball coming out on PlayStation 2 and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe I talked about this last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gradius Collection is going to be coming out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, like I said, the following week, Urban Chaos, Right Response on PlayStation 2 and Xbox, and the Street Fighter Alpha Anthology on the PlayStation 2 as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, unfortunately, if you're waiting for 360 games, there's only going to be one this month, and that would be MotoGP 2006.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully, there'll be some more Xbox Live games, arcade games to go with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully, Luminous.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm hoping.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Live's been kind of dead since E3 with Uno.
[SPEAKER_01]: All you need is Uno.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uno's really the only game that's really come out in quite a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I realize Uno's a pretty good release, but after hearing some of the stuff they teased at E3, I'm like, come on, bring on the Contra, bring on the Luminous.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I've got a few more things real quick, because there's been some shuffling going around, obviously.
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR's been moving.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR moved?
[SPEAKER_02]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, dates change.
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's
[SPEAKER_03]: Get caught up here with what's been going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR Supernova, not coming out on the 13th, but coming out on the 2nd now of September.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: They moved that up a bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, Supernova also, I believe, moved up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's now coming out, let's see here, it was in October.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, also...
[SPEAKER_03]: One game that did get delayed, Final Fantasy XII, coming out on October 11th now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um... Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could that be more... Could that be something else to show that there's competition with the Wii there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because didn't Dragon Quest VIII get shuffled to come out right on the same day as the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't a very good...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I wasn't very good to... But Final Fantasy XII is a great counter-title.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's... Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, not super... Universe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ultraman XIV, October 2nd now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that got pushed up a little bit the same day as Elebits.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, we have for the 360 Universe, which is now November 2nd.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, they're really aiming on the second for a lot of these.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots of good games coming out, though, in the fall, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why would they all get shifted to the second?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are those all even Tuesdays?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would they do that?
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't come out on Tuesdays.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's usually Wednesdays and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you sure it's not going to change again next week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I could.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I'm never certain about dates until it actually gets to the week of, and even then I'm not certain sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, but, you know, when it comes down to Konami, they tend to really keep about the same dates for stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Tomb Raider Legend is at number 5, 6th place X-Men The Official Game, Da Vinci Code is at 8, Animal Crossing Wild World at number 7, that actually moved up from number 9, and Sims 2 is at number 10.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some of the debuts that came out though was Rise of Nations, Rise of Legends at 37, Super Princess Peach at 29.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically DS titles though all over the place.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're speculating that the new Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_01]: is going to really show up high as well as brain training.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's how it's looking right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently they love Hitman.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it is new.
[SPEAKER_03]: They mentioned in the chat that September 2nd is a Saturday.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know about that, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think somebody made a boo-boo.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I take that with a huge grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's going to go back to the way it was next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it just goes to show your database is not always foolproof.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not, but they're pretty close.
[SPEAKER_02]: Top Xbox 360 and Xbox Live games are out thanks to Major Nelson.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to know what folks are playing on the 360?
[SPEAKER_02]: The number one game, Call of Duty 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number two, Ghost Recon 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number three, Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the way on down to number ten, Hitman Blood Money demo making a new entry there on the chart.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rockstar Table Tennis coming in at number seven.
[SPEAKER_02]: The top games on the original Xbox, number one, Halo 2, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number two, Battlefield 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: And number three, Counter-Strike.
[SPEAKER_02]: all the way on down to Ghost Recon 2 at number 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: The rest of the titles, not a lot of new stuff there on the original Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I wanted to share with you guys a story coming in from Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were talking about the ESRB earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the CERO is Japan's equivalent, and they have a new rating system that they're going to use.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have two separate ratings for M-type games.
[SPEAKER_02]: A title gets what's called a D. Basically, there's letters A, B, C, D, and Z. A title gets a D rating if it's 17 years and older, and the Z rating is for adults 18 and up.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to know the type of games that are getting a Z rating right now, you have Killer7,
[SPEAKER_02]: Max Payne, Grand Theft Auto Vice City, The Getaway, Berserk.
[SPEAKER_02]: D-rated games, as in the 17 and older, you have things like Fable, Ninja Gaiden, Dead or Alive 4, God of War, Rumble Roses.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of interesting, this system they have there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's A, B, C, D, and Z.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where I guess C is 15 and up and B is 12 and up and A is everybody.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's like the movie rating system because 15 is basically their equivalent of the PG-13.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like Battle Royale, for example, was a 15 and up movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I always said for a long time we should just mirror the movie system here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm surprised that Berserk was mentioned being that that's an old Dreamcast title.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then again, though, it was pretty violent anime and manga.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, are we going to be seeing gaming at the Olympics soon?
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then again, I've seen weird stuff come to the Olympics, so who knows.
[SPEAKER_03]: But according to GameSpot, actually, the founder of the Global Gaming League is trying to get gaming as a demo sport in the 2008 Beijing Olympics, and basically is
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to see gaming as an Olympic event.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's not an event.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless they come out with a game that involves running around the goddamn track.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is not even close to being a sport, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: If they want to test someone's athletic ability, you've got the floor exercises for gymnastics.
[SPEAKER_01]: DDR is nothing compared to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Breakdancing would be a better sport than gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course we have the classic witty retort from the chatroom that DDR is a sport in the Netherlands.
[SPEAKER_02]: Norway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good for them Norway doesn't count Moving on DarkSakura, you have some news on Half-Life Do I?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know what Half-Life is That's what the notes say I was being witty I know DarkSakura needs food badly Don't shoot food No
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously, Half-Life 2 Episode 1 is out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Released at 6pm in the UK on June 1st.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, I'm all backwards today.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, it's...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's about, people can play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you actually can, they actually had it available for a pre-purchase as well too.
[SPEAKER_01]: But now you can pre-load it for $19.95 or you can buy it from scratch and download it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But right now though, they're saying the servers are pretty loaded on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: E.A.
[SPEAKER_01]: is distributing the game for £15.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically to Guitar Hero what Stepmania was to DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Free Tar Hero is released.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's available at a site.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called, I'm going to have to spell this for you guys, antonstruyk.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: FreeTar, FreeTar
[SPEAKER_02]: TAR HERO
[SPEAKER_02]: Some things are being developed for an old platform.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, the Dreamcast, which is ironic because actually iGen's been doing this thing now where they're re-revealing every single Dreamcast game that's ever been made and starting off with a lot of games.
[SPEAKER_03]: But according to Dreamcast Scene, actually, Goat Store Publishing firm has announced that they have plans to release 10 more games for the Dreamcast over the next year and a half.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Dreamcast Dreamcast Dreamcast Dreamcast Dreamcast
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's some of the games right now, and I don't know if these are going to be too exciting, but Feet of Fury 2, remember that DDR clone that they had for the Dreamcast, Donk, a Cryptic Illusions remake of the CDI game, DC, or DCastle, Age of the Beast Special Edition, which is basically a clone of Altered, not Altered Beast, um,
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very similar to that Beats of Rage that came out a while back, which is the Streets of Rage clone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Amnesia Adventure Game, a new graphic adventure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, a new adventure game from SF Software, a remake of a cancelled Lynx game inspired by Tempest 2000, a new 3D fighter using the Quake engine, Samurai Warrior using the enhanced Beats of Rage engine, and let's see,
[SPEAKER_03]: Project Firestorm Shmup Super Mario Bros 2.5D
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: One of their staff reviewed it and said they played it for about 30 seconds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aside from being hideously ugly, the game is sort of floaty feeling.
[SPEAKER_02]: None of the snappiness of the original.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the levels are not identical either.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a cute idea but needs some serious work.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so in case you're wondering where you can download this, www.plunder.com slash super-mario-bros-2-5d
[SPEAKER_02]: I saved the best for last for this break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, you have a story about Mac fans.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, well, their answer...
[SPEAKER_03]: Mac users aren't really into games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so, yeah, we're not quite sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if it entirely addresses the state of Mac gaming, but yeah, that's why.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mac users don't really like games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's according to who again?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's according to Business Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, just making sure you get your source out there when all the hate mail starts coming in for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Business Week says you don't like games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, not surprising.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rini in our chatroom, who I know is a Mac fan, says, whoever wrote that isn't trying.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not trying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you, Business Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we're going to go to a break here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: When we come back, we'll have plenty more news and information and that'll be coming up in just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for listening.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.