[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_09]: To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio episode number 185.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you guys so much for downloading our podcast or tuning in live whatever the case may be.
[SPEAKER_08]: and checking us out.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you ever do want to listen to us live, we do tape every Sunday night over at www.orangeloundtrader.com You can also hear a bonus segment when you listen live at allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: They rebroadcast our shows Monday night at 7 Pacific and I want to say it comes up a couple times on Tuesday as well during the day, so check out
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look at my ugly face while I play Uno.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, what?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's nothing to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're talking about one of the people testing the camera right now, and what they did is they put it on their dog.
[SPEAKER_07]: See their dog panting, just going, I think that's great, because, I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had something like this.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had the iToy chat, but it's a game.
[SPEAKER_07]: You had to buy it, and that was lame.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they should have totally done this before a lot of stuff just...
[SPEAKER_08]: What I want to know, how many games of Strip Uno are we going to see?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because that's really the only practical use of this peripheral that I can think of is Strip Uno.
[SPEAKER_08]: Voice chatting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does it do voice chatting?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you can use voice chat and you can do video chat and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that might be kind of cool because you might hear when a draw for a wild gets played on something, you'll hear, fuck you!
[SPEAKER_07]: People can actually do, imagine if you will, over live.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could have video phone sex.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you ever wanted to show your naughty bits to strangers, here you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: But please, 18 and over only.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are they going to stop slutty 17-year-olds from doing this?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't want to see that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's, you know...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how they're going to try to stop them, but that's still going to make for more interesting games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know!
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like, ah, I'm quitting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess they'll get warned.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess they figure the community will police itself.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, you know, they're going to use the peripheral to be able to map your face on characters.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, say, for example, playing multiplayer Rainbow Six Vegas or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, look, he has a penis for a head.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: How many boobs are you going to be playing against, literally?
[SPEAKER_08]: Go into the chat room over at OrangeLinesRadio.com and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guinness Goblin says, we strip Uno, fat naked gamers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amplitude1 says, strip Monopoly, I think, over in the chat room there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they are coming out with poker later, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, that's not the only peripheral that's coming out for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's apparently a mole within the Microsoft organization that has some news on other things that are coming out, and this all makes sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: New faceplates with Halo, Forza 2, and Viva Pinata are going to be on their way out.
[SPEAKER_08]: A wireless headset is coming out, but as far as I know...
[SPEAKER_08]: I was listening to another podcast, I want to say it was All Games Interactive, where they bought Scott for his birthday a headset that was wireless.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this must be the official Microsoft headset that's coming out, but you can already get a non-official one.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have some pretty cool looking ones that are out right now, but the new wireless one is kind of nifty looking.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really know how to describe it.
[SPEAKER_08]: A wireless gaming receiver is coming out too for $20.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does that mean like a router?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that receiver is actually for your PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to plug into the USB.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so you can use your wireless controllers and peripherals with your PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And a 256MB memory unit for those of you that are actually using memory units.
[SPEAKER_08]: All three of you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just spend the extra money and buy a hard drive.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_07]: Some controversy in the Xbox 360 community, yes?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Peter Moore said something retarded Basically, gamers don't care about backwards compatibility
[SPEAKER_07]: and, you know, he says, nobody is concerned about backwards compatibility.
[SPEAKER_07]: We under-promised and over-delivered on that, which, if I remember correctly, no they didn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's a very complicated thing, very complex work.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just stunned that we have hundreds of games that are backwards compatible.
[SPEAKER_07]: He also added, more are coming, but at some point you just go, there's enough, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_07]: or people aren't as worried about game being backwards compatible.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I like to think that we've upheld our end of the bargain in making at least two or maybe three hundred games backwards compatible.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, actually, I believe you said you were going to make them all backwards compatible, so that would not be upholding your end of the bargain there at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's your problem for doing that.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I, you know what, PlayStation 3, here's one good thing at least I can say about PlayStation 3, if it truly is backwards compatible with all PlayStation 2 and 1 games, that's a huge bonus.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now, what about the people now that say, why do you buy a new console to play all your old games on?
[SPEAKER_08]: What would be a response to people that are saying that?
[SPEAKER_07]: um well for example when you have one game coming out in the month and you may not want that game you know what it's nice to be able to buy some older games also drives more game sales because now there's more games you can play instead of you know maybe the 30 or 40 that are out right now you can go and play 300 and for those that may have limited shelf space too exactly and also you bought a new system you know maybe you sold your xbox maybe it took you know a
[SPEAKER_07]: and just, like, basically, you know, failed on you and now you have a new system and you want to be able... Or, for example, you know, what they should have done since, you know, the PlayStation 2 is backwards compatible with all the PlayStation 1 titles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Say, for example, you have an Xbox game that comes out and you want to play it, you know, and that might not be on the 360, like, say, for example, The Godfather because the 360 version hasn't come out yet and maybe you want to play that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well, you can't because it's not backwards compatible.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I...
[SPEAKER_07]: Granted, there is a point where you just have to say forget it, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unless they make a portable system that plays the old Xbox games or something like that, you never know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on, on a related note, there is a backwards compatibility update coming in the next couple weeks to Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: This was announced on the Gamerscore blog.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody from the Microsoft team said that there is a backwards compatibility update coming out
[SPEAKER_08]: within the next few weeks, quote unquote.
[SPEAKER_08]: But at the same time,
[SPEAKER_08]: I seem to recall hearing that that download things in the background patch was coming out last week and that didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I would imagine it's possible that the backwards compatibility thing will be pushed back.
[SPEAKER_08]: No word on what games are going to be backwards compatible.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's really sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't know if you're going to get your beach volleyball yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's the thing that's really sad is all these updates have come out.
[SPEAKER_07]: We had one that added most of the Tom Clancy games.
[SPEAKER_07]: We had another one that added three other games.
[SPEAKER_07]: What happened to updates every month?
[SPEAKER_07]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I feel sorry for the backwards compatibility team because it feels like we're picking on them a little bit, but probably they're just under, like, they probably got under-budgeted or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're probably working their butts off, but they just don't have the resources to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not their fault.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just saying, you know, don't promise that you're going to have updates every month.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't promise that you're going to have all the games backwards compatible if you're not going to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Say we're going to support the major titles, you know, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: More and more will be coming, you know,
[SPEAKER_07]: as the year progresses.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what you need to do instead of saying, yeah, all the games are going to be backwards compatible because basically you're lying.
[SPEAKER_07]: Say if I went out to buy a car right now and they promised me that that car is going to fly eventually.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's a blatant lie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Granted, technology may come out that may allow my car to fly one of these days, but if that's not something that you're currently working on doing or have no plans on doing, then don't fucking promise it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Simple as that.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on, Loki has some further news from Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, kind of.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is more a rumor department.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this is a rumor that keeps coming up in regards to Microsoft, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we talked about it a while back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember what podcast it was on.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyways, basically there's a group, the Diffusion group, that's saying that Microsoft is planning on launching a portable game system
[SPEAKER_07]: in the market in 2008.
[SPEAKER_07]: And basically they're giving the 360s some time to pick up steam.
[SPEAKER_07]: Possibly, I wouldn't see why they wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, because that's a market that, you know, granted Nintendo's doing pretty good in, Sony's doing okay in, but they're not really, I mean, it's not anything that's, you know, totally dominating the market.
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't have any, you know, must-have games.
[SPEAKER_07]: People aren't going out there and just dying to get a PSP because of X game on their
[SPEAKER_07]: So, sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know what show it was on that you talked about this before.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was right before E3 because you brought some story in from a business magazine saying X-Player or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: What happened with that?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I think they were talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's some team that they had working on that developed the 360 or something that was working on this.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I wish I had that magazine, but I threw it out a while ago, so we'd have to dig through the podcast to find exactly what I said.
[SPEAKER_07]: But
[SPEAKER_07]: That's basically it, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're working on something.
[SPEAKER_07]: If anything, you'll probably see it at E3 either next year or the year after that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Be a very interesting move by Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's get away from Microsoft for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, actually, this is a game that you can play on the 360, among other systems.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura has a little bit of news on Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: We all like our chocobos, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're tasty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_04]: They go good with honey sauce.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay, okay, okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, Squeenix is talking about raising your birds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, on the official site, um, they basically were comparing, uh, Chocobo raising to gardening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something that would require, uh, a little bit of your time for, uh, one to three months.
[SPEAKER_04]: You begin by finding an egg.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, that sort of makes me think of Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, you find your egg, and then you have to... But this, in this way, though, you care for your egg by spending, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: By helping it hatch, you use certain items to help it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you feed it, and you spend time with it, and you raise your baby chocobo, and you name your chocobo.
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently you'll just be able to do all kinds of stuff with your chocobo that I'm not at liberty to discuss because it sounds kind of strange.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you can apparently breed your chocobos with your friend's chocobos.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't sleep with it, do you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because that's really gross.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine, like, living in your mog house and you're talking about going, Mommy!
[SPEAKER_04]: Work, work!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it should be coming up on the next update.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, I believe I was reading something about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to check it every day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, this is just a way to suck you into the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Play me every day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Addict, addict, addict, addict.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get something cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although, I did also read something that there will be a way where you can get, like, if you're going on vacation or whatever, somebody can babysit your chugabow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chugabow sitter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, like a chugabow sitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should have the chugabow kennel.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it costs money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like on, remember on...
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Neopets.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you could, you know, if your animals were all dying, you could just like, you know, put them in the kennel.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're all fed.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't have to take care of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I also think of Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_08]: You could put your dogs that you didn't want anymore, you could take them to the kennel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or they could be put down.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the pound.
[SPEAKER_08]: They'll put them down if you leave them there for too long.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a scene in... Mine all ran away.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a scene in Nintendogs that we needed.
[SPEAKER_07]: and Ten Dogs where your puppy gets rabies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gotta put him down, son.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, Paul, let me do it!
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on, Loki, you have some news about another very popular RPG.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Oblivion's getting yet another add-on, which is excellent.
[SPEAKER_07]: The new add-on is basically...
[SPEAKER_07]: A quest that revolves around finding a powerful mage who has set off in search of the Daedric artifact Mephroon's Razor.
[SPEAKER_07]: And basically the Razor has the ability to instantly kill enemies.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the mage intends to use it to overthrow the Empire.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's up to you to make sure that you find it first so it doesn't fall into the wrong hands.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically this download is going to be the most expensive download yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Coming in at $2.99 for the PC users.
[SPEAKER_07]: And no price yet on the Xbox Live Marketplace, but it's assumed to be about the same.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's supposed to give you a massive, massive dungeon to be able to go through.
[SPEAKER_07]: As well as adding 17 new magic items and a ton of new books.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, might add though, if you do happen to find the item, you get to keep it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a death to everybody!
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, going to another very popular, this one an MMO, World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't actually have a lot of news about the actual game itself, but there is a trading card game that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to do a card game, it's actually Upper Deck that's doing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're doing a game based on World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the cool thing about doing the card game is that now, since the video game's been out a little while...
[SPEAKER_08]: The Gabe of Penny Arcade did the artwork
[SPEAKER_08]: And actually, I know this doesn't make for very good radio, but I can show you guys here in studio, and I'll post this in chat, a picture of what the card looks like.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you look at the card, you can actually see it looks like the warrior, he's got the big sword, and he's foaming at the mouth, like ready to go into battle.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because if you know the story of Leroy Jenkins, it kind of fits, so that's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: in such an amazingly fantastic way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, we love being interactive, and one of the ways we get you guys to participate in our program is we welcome your emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you can email us on just about anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com is the place to send those emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: And once a week, Jamie puts on her hazmat suit and dives in the mailbag and pulls out some of her favorites that hopefully do not have anthrax in them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's hope not this time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't need any more disease.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, who emailed us this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: First one is MacMan from DreamStationCC.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know what's coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, Loki!
[SPEAKER_04]: Apple runs Microsoft on their computers.
[SPEAKER_04]: We all have Microsoft programs on our Macs, even your goddamn games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and for only print media thing, iLife, iMovie, iDVD, iTunes, GarageBand, and iPhoto, where is your god now?
[SPEAKER_07]: Designed by Macman, I who have superb taste in computers, unlike Loki Okay, so they have programs to do the same things that PCs do, but they're not better than PCs Can't we all just get along?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, seriously, this fucking debate's been going on for like six months It's done Hey, it's alright, it's okay, I understand that, okay, maybe Macs don't have as many games It doesn't matter, Mac users don't like games, so that's fine
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm getting a Mac and I like games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look, I don't even want it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the magazine said.
[SPEAKER_04]: The magazine is a lying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Buy and use whatever makes you happy.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's your money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Spend it on whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Linux on a toaster.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly, that is the point.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I bought an iBook and I love it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Loki, you can just, if you don't like that, you can kiss my butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a MacBook with a docking station and a new monitor instead of an iMac.
[SPEAKER_08]: I should have waited.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's better ones coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: MacBook is hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's keep it moving.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guy message from David.
[SPEAKER_04]: I found this thing on Google Video by accident.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a video of a group of people who put together a play of the first level of the original Mario Brothers.
[SPEAKER_04]: The music was a little off-timing at some parts, but I thought it was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd also be pretty awesome if you guys could do a Flash website for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm working on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think the problem with Flash on the PSP right now is it's slow.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's only Flash 2.0.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's slow, so... Which I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I started working with Flash 8, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: Urge Sony to get their Flash a little better and then we'll look into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I planned on playing with it, but honestly I don't know too much about the older versions of Flash to make it work right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll also do a Wii website when it comes out because they have Opera and it supports Opera 9, which is the newest Opera browser right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make sure you'll get E3 on Wii!
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, E3 and PSP, I don't know if I'll want to do that next year.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: We also got one from Robway.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Cue the 8-Bit Sound Effects.
[SPEAKER_04]: He linked me a story that's talking about, and this is on Wired News.
[SPEAKER_04]: Strap Up and Jump Like Mario.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Nintendo Amusement Park is by the same group of New York University students who did the Pac-Manhattan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, actually it was in the same big games class.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Pac-Manhattan was a recreation of Pac-Man using the streets of New York with Central Park being the ghost area.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now they're doing an amusement park where you strap yourselves in and basically you jump through a recreation of the first level of Super Mario Brothers with hooks and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Mario can jump four times the normal...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: So it actually looks like it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're talking about how to basically do video game physics in real life.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I thought it was a pretty cool application.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little silly, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can all get a little silly sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a pretty fun idea, unlike the thing that they said was going to be at E3 next year, which wasn't quite as cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, to the next email, I got one, another one from, actually no, that's the same one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Got one from Spoon.
[SPEAKER_04]: As opposed to Fork.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's three O's.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Spoon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, I've been listening to your podcast for about four months and it's good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good to hear the different takes and the fact one of you, he shall remain unnamed, hates Max so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's supposed to be unnamed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I named him, so ha.
[SPEAKER_04]: Max and Nintendo go hand in hand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Build a machine that can do what it's set out for correctly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo equals gameplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Max equals work.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted to share with you another... Loki, just bite your tongue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bite it.
[SPEAKER_04]: He actually linked us to another podcast that talks about DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called AskANinja.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I've heard of Ask a Ninja.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're really popular.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they're a video cast, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are, and it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't see the DDR episode.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I haven't seen that either, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I always said that if there was ever a new video game channel, they would have to put them in as a segment.
[SPEAKER_08]: How much does it cost to start a TV channel?
[SPEAKER_08]: We should start one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello there, Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you doing on this fine Friday afternoon?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hot two days late.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing just fine, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I sent you this message to ask if you three would honor me on your input on Luminous Mobile.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have the game and I absolutely am in love with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Many fans out there do not even know of this game's existence, which makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is also a chance for many out there who do not own a PSP to finally experience the genius of this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for taking the time to read this and keep kicking ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those of you that listen to the show know I am not a big fan of mobile gaming, but I am a huge fan of Luminous.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if my carrier offers it, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have Sprint, who's kind of like the black sheep of the cell phone carrier, so I don't even know if they have Luminous, but I'll check it out if it's out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't even know my game can play games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, there's a little dyslexia there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if my phone can...
[SPEAKER_07]: I imagine it can, but I haven't tried because God knows how expensive that would be.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll check during our next break.
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw a review on it, and the guy that reviewed it said he liked it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it looked very similar.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only thing they didn't like is that the music's not like MP3.
[SPEAKER_07]: It can't be, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's MIDI, and yeah, it's not very MIDI-tastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got one more email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I got this to my own box, Jamie at OrangeDollsRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm just going to paraphrase this a little bit, but it's from a guy named Chris, who is a contributor to WeebleStuff.com, who was our website of the week last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to say, that was two weeks ago, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Two weeks ago, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's your website of the week, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, so somebody heard it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, he listens to our podcast, is a big fan.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, he says on here...
[SPEAKER_04]: that since it seems none of the other guys on the staff listens to OLR to their great detriment, of course, I felt I should say a big thanks for giving us a plug.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been a fan of OLR for a long time now, and I've got to say you guys are consistently among the best independent gaming podcasts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I appreciate that you bothered to mention UK, European games news and release dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: I sometimes suspect you guys are the only American games media outlet who are even aware of this little continent's existence.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we tried.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had replied back, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm actually not reading my own email.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean, basically, I don't think that it's... With a lot of the content now coming out of, you know, US and, you know, a bit out of Japan, you know, at least for the more niche market, you know, I really think that the rest of the world sort of gets overlooked.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, gamers are everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got our person from Serbia who emailed us.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to make sure that because we have listeners everywhere that it's not just United States.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have listeners in Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have listeners in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have listeners in China.
[SPEAKER_04]: I found that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have listeners all over Europe, UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to make sure that you're a gamer too.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want your voice heard just as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to get you the news.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it's happening in your area of the world,
[SPEAKER_04]: If we don't know about it, let us know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll mention it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know one of our listeners started a Frapper map a while back.
[SPEAKER_08]: We want to see where you guys are, so please take a minute to stop by.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's frappr.com and then just search for Orange Lounge and put a pin on the map so we can see where our listeners are because that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just kind of neat knowing where all you guys are.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even if you're in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: because it maps that too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would really like for our listeners...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to have a thread on our forums at orangeoddsradio.com Go to the forums link on the left side of the page.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let us know where you're from.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let us know where you're listening from.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd be really cool just to put names.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't want to think of just statistics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because all we see are numbers when we look at our stat pages.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to know who you are, why you listen to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love hearing from our listeners everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you say that was the last one?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the last one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saved the last one for last.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send us emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mailbag at OrangeLondrina.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can ask us whatever, and as long as it's clean, we'll answer it during the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks a lot, those of you guys that email us.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if it's dirty, I'll save it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: She'll bookmark it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, back into some news, some more Sony antics.
[SPEAKER_07]: I swear to God, in the last few days, if this guy David Reeves, you know,
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not hating on Sony, but he's the one that's saying it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, his quote is this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Market share?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not that important.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who needs market share?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know?
[SPEAKER_07]: The name of the game is not market share.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's how fast we can grow the industry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our ambition is to grow 15% a year on hardware and software.
[SPEAKER_07]: If we can, we want to try and double digital entertainment in the next 5 to 6 years.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whether we have 40, 50, or 60% of the market share, it's not that important.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's a little thing to kind of be scared about what he said here.
[SPEAKER_07]: They want to
[SPEAKER_07]: Double the digital entertainment world.
[SPEAKER_07]: XBOX or NINTENDO
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, I find the whole story just a little odd.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just an odd thing to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, this is the same guy, he was saying that, you know, who cares, gamers will just have to pay more for their system because you'll buy whatever it is, even if the system didn't come out with games, you'll buy it because it's Sony.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, this is the same jackass that said that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, what they need to do is shut him up because he's saying really stupid stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on to more Sony-related news.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a new controller coming out for the PlayStation 2 and PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a tilt controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the E-Dimensional G-Pad Pro Gyroscopic Game Pad.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it has tilt-sensing technology, and it's the same thing that the PlayStation 3 has.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's coming out for the PC and the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: And by the way, though, it also has rumble.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, Sony's not putting this out, but didn't Sony say that they can't do rumble in the tilt thing because it'll mess it up?
[SPEAKER_08]: PC, PlayStation 2
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know so much about PS2.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, we had a letter in the mailbag about a mobile game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have some news that kind of affects another one?
[SPEAKER_04]: I sure do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dirge of Cerberus for mobile is actually called Dirge of Cerberus Lost Episode, which is one of the Final Fantasy VII titles coming out, and it's going to be on Amped Mobile for three months starting in the summer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, there's no word on if it's going to be out for the UK,
[SPEAKER_04]: You know I played through Final Fantasy 7 and I never even got Vincent?
[SPEAKER_04]: What a loss.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually got him without using an FAQ or anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know, on Final Fantasy, because I played Final Fantasy VII when it first came out, you know, as you guys, I'm an older gamer, so there wasn't really the whole GameFAQs.com didn't really exist then.
[SPEAKER_04]: I found him by accident and just randomly asked the right questions.
[SPEAKER_04]: I also got Yuffie right the first time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yuffie's the one he asked the questions to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Vincent was the safe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Vincent, you still had to do... Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, I never did the save.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to answer the right thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, I never figured out the save.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I got both Yuffie and Vincent.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yuffie I figured out just through trial and error.
[SPEAKER_08]: She showed up once in the forest.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she keeps stealing your crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and I kept running around that same forest until she finally joined my damn party.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I somehow or the other managed to ask the right questions the first time.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have some news about the way items are packaged.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just read it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blister packaging.
[SPEAKER_07]: You gotta love it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, if you don't know what that is, if you've ever seen anything, especially nowadays, any game peripheral or anything out there, it's that hard packaging that is goddamn impossible to open without killing yourself.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I know for a fact trying to open the Xbox 360 accessories and stuff, I...
[SPEAKER_07]: That stuff's like glass.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really scary.
[SPEAKER_07]: But actually, it's funny because Wired News did a little article here called Tales from Packaging Hell.
[SPEAKER_07]: And basically, the whole thing behind the packaging is that it's meant to avoid, obviously, theft.
[SPEAKER_07]: But a lot of people have really gotten hurt by this.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they have some pictures, actually, of people with...
[SPEAKER_07]: Major gashes on their hands and people being sent to the hospital.
[SPEAKER_07]: This one guy, George from Atlanta, sliced his hand open and there was a
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: And when it takes me like 10 minutes, just the... I nearly... I really... You can't use scissors, because scissors aren't sharp enough to get through this.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you have to use a knife.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to stab it in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the knife... The knife, most of the time, unless it's relatively dull, or if it's not as sharp as it can be, it'll slip, and it'll cut yourself the knife.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then if you manage to do get it open, the edges are really sharp and jaggedy, and it's just... It's like cutting open glass.
[SPEAKER_07]: And basically...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: The FUs of the Week time.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, start us off.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU of the Week goes toward... It's a number of people who have... It's actually a misconception I'm going to put my FU of the Week toward.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I've said at the beginning of the last segment, I was diagnosed with chronic fatigue syndrome, which is why I was really sick with what I call the plague in November and December, and have been consistently not feeling well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, there's people who say, oh, well, you'll be just fine when you get back from your medical leave.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not how it works.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, it's just, it's something that a lot of people think is either an all-in-your-head sort of thing, you know, or something that you can just fix with a drug, or something that if you just sleep a lot, you'll get over it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the whole thing about it is that no matter how much sleep you get, you still feel tired.
[SPEAKER_04]: You feel like you haven't slept.
[SPEAKER_04]: You go through phases of being really hungry and then not being hungry at all and nothing will ever make you feel satisfied if you're in one of those phases.
[SPEAKER_04]: You feel like your muscles hurt all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for anyone who thinks that it's just an all-in-your-head type of thing, fuck you, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's a fully diagnosed thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's something that they have to rule out physical practice before they diagnose you with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But taking a nap doesn't help.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been sleeping for upwards of 10 hours a day while I've been on my medical leave, and it still hasn't helped hardly any.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get to learn how to give myself shots on Wednesday, though, which is not fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, so for anyone who thinks that it's an all-in-your-head sort of thing and that a little rest or some vitamins will help you get over it, it may help, but it's not the cure.
[SPEAKER_04]: So stop telling me that I'll feel better when my leave is up, because I don't think I will.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: A couple things.
[SPEAKER_07]: First off, fuck you to Christopher for the smell that's coming from his desk, and I'm going to guess it's from these three empty McFlurry containers, which are probably rotting right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a really nasty, like, rotten milk smell that's... Ugh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, so fuck you to that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you to the stupid people that are in my apartment complex who are parking their car in the middle of...
[SPEAKER_07]: And then finally, um... I don't know, I'm just... Fuck you and me being hungry...
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and, uh, fucking needles, because every time I get poked with a needle by a doctor, I almost pass out.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it's not necessarily medication or something, but my body, like, goes into shock whenever I have a needle.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, uh, yeah, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, my F.U.
[SPEAKER_08]: goes to this humongous zit that's on my face right now that won't go away, no matter what I put on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it makes me feel really ugly and sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: No matter what I put on it part.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_08]: because it makes me feel ugly and sad and makes me not want to be social because I feel ugly.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it'll go away, and then I'll be pretty again.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, anyway, let's move on to another story.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, it's all you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I'm wondering if this shouldn't have been before the FU's, but anyways, higher prices for...
[SPEAKER_07]: PlayStation 3 and Wii are confirmed by Atari.
[SPEAKER_07]: And actually Atari is the distributor for Sega in some parts of Europe.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's basically some of the Sega games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sonic the Hedgehog on the PS3 for example is going to cost 67.99 euros.
[SPEAKER_07]: While some other games like World Snooker Championship 2007 will be 73.99 euros.
[SPEAKER_07]: and basically on the Wii, Sonic, Wildfire and Super Monkey Ball Banana Blitz will both be available for 59.99 euros.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's a lot more than what we got to pay for them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn, Texas.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Microsoft made a pretty interesting statement this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was Chris Lewis.
[SPEAKER_08]: Works for Microsoft was speaking about Sony's online service saying, I'm flattered that they followed our clear direction.
[SPEAKER_08]: Plagiarism is a good thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: That in itself isn't such a problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's what the market wants.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we've known that's what the market wanted all along.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that, by the way, was in an interview with Eurogamer.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Microsoft kind of taking a swing there that PlayStation 3 is just downright copying them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: But again, you kind of expect that you're going to get copied in some elements, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, you have some news about Wii web browsing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Opera, of course, as everybody knows, is going to be the web browser on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they've actually...
[SPEAKER_07]: Release some information of what this is going to support and some of the details on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: First off, Opera will be embedded on the Wii's Flash ROM, unlike the DS version, which is actually a cart-based operating system.
[SPEAKER_07]: The browser may take advantage of some of the gesture-based navigation and interaction that's available with the Wii controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: No advertisements will be included within the browser.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, you shouldn't rule out that there won't be in-game advertising delivered via Opera.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think it's pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another thing that someone was bringing up about the Dreamcast browser is that they had special features for when you're programming webpages, you can actually make the Dreamcast VMU rumble or display things.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that would be really cool if they added that kind of
[SPEAKER_07]: to the Wii browser where you can make the controller rumble or special tags or something to use the Wii controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, something to think about.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a little weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's also basically going to be compatible with Opera 9, which is the one that's out currently right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it is supposed to support most everything, including Java, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura DarkSakura DarkSakura DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, yeah, there's going to be game rentals in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: It actually started on the 3rd.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, Koei will put out its first rent-a-net video store at the Taito Game Center in Kanagawa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, it's not
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not any real rental franchises like we have here, not like Blockbuster or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this is a very, very new thing there.
[SPEAKER_04]: New games will basically rent for 2,800 yen, which is 2,450 over here for five days.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you bring them back.
[SPEAKER_07]: $24, that's expensive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything is more expensive in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just wanted to say real quick, I had to correct something I said earlier.
[SPEAKER_08]: Funnydale actually in the chat room corrected me on something I said about GameFAQs wasn't around when Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_08]: It actually started in 1995.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they actually were around, it's just not a lot of people knew about them, including me.
[SPEAKER_08]: But certainly they weren't the site they are now then.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been a long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually used them for Super Nintendo stuff back in the day.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I used eBay when they first came out, but back when they were... Well, not back when they were Pez dispensers, but just after that, before they got all commercialized.
[SPEAKER_08]: I bought Super Metroid on eBay, like, in 97.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Websites were different back then, because browsers weren't the same.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, one more story here, guys, and we're going to go to our Skype line over at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, what's up?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, a British... What was it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: The SCI, some British publication, was saying that they're going to be extending Eidos' licenses for Hitman and Tomb Raider to the gambling franchises, including online.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're basically going to see some video slot machines based on both Lara Croft and Agent 47.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should know, though, that they're still going to steal your money just as well as all the other video slot machines out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately, no boobies in the slot machines either.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't get too excited about slot machines because I personally hate those video slot machines.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that they're a big waste of money, especially the nickel ones.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to put more nickels in.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Instead of quarters.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, more of the same, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: This is Nintendo Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, Nintendo Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're a little quiet, but what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, well, it's probably because I'm actually using my regular phone.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, my mic jack died on my laptop.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, get out your thoughts anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, anyway, I have an announcement to make.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let me see if I can load up my test.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: From June 7th to 10th, I'm going to be in New York City.
[SPEAKER_11]: Since we're getting an art award for this art show season, um,
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll be at the Nintendo World Store on Friday at 11 a.m.
[SPEAKER_11]: So if you're not there, come visit me if you want.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll be wearing that pancake button.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll be wearing a shirt with that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a topic here on the forum.
[SPEAKER_11]: More details, I'll get you a small link for it.
[SPEAKER_11]: xrl.us
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I heard about half of that because of the connection we have here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me get this right.
[SPEAKER_08]: You said you're going to be at the Nintendo store on Friday and you want to meet other listeners of the show or something?
[SPEAKER_11]: Sure, at like 11 a.m.
[SPEAKER_08]: At 11 a.m.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what are you going to be wearing?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to be wearing...
[SPEAKER_11]: a shirt with the pancake bunny on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Oolong.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oolong, the pancake bunny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Poor dead bunny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, that guy rocks.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the URL, just in case if somebody missed it, it's xrl.us slash mz5k.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm glad you could use this program to help make yourself more friends in person.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have fun at the store.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I'll take you at the store.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, I'm letting you go now because your connection sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: See ya.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, so much for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to go meet listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: We did that last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we did.
[SPEAKER_08]: We did meet a few listeners last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to call us, it's OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Click on Interact With Us over on Skype.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's username OrangeLoungeRadio, all one word.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or again on the telephone, it's 916-226-9067 Let's go to another call Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Good evening, it's DMN, how are you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Good, oh, your connection's much better than the last guy What's on your mind, DMN?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, as you announced earlier, I had that little contest of exclusive Zelda questions That's right, did you get a winner?
[SPEAKER_10]: I did.
[SPEAKER_10]: T23M is the winner.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's 23Megas.
[SPEAKER_08]: He should be disqualified because he comes on the show once.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let him have it.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's a local.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, going back to jumping release dates, I've heard that Nintendo's practices generally they give those offending retailers shipments late or very low shipments later on.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I don't...
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think Nintendo is going to give a company like Target a big spanking?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think so because I remember Microsoft released Project Gotham 2, I believe it was, a couple of days early and they got beat down for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I recall that they got Halo 2, a very low shipment of Halo 2, I think a half shipment of Halo 2 in each store.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I think
[SPEAKER_10]: I think Target's going to be in big trouble for releasing the DS Lite early.
[SPEAKER_08]: But on the other side, hey, you know, we can get some DS Lites that are already out there, and word of mouth I'm sure travels, and it kind of created a sudden surge of interest a little bit on the blogs while people frantically hunted these down, so I don't think the news is all bad for Nintendo here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh no, not at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can actually tell you firsthand, the DS Lite is awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to say the guy that we invited who called in.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Silent Wind.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: He had one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think he brought it to show us.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking at mine right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rub it in.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, did you go to a Target to get it, or do you get it from a special, like you work for Nintendo, your special thing?
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually got mine from an import store.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo just got theirs in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_10]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_10]: Take care, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks, everybody, for participating in the contest.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully, there will be more in the future.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for the fun, DMN.
[SPEAKER_08]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, chat's a whole experience.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even if we sometimes, you know, get so caught up in our own conversation we forget to read chat room, there's all types of fun stuff they're doing in chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's been, you know, like over 50 people every show in chat room, so it's been very nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: We really appreciate you guys heading on over to chat and checking us out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have time to take a couple more calls if anyone else wants to call in.
[SPEAKER_08]: OrangeLawnTrader.com, click on Interact With Us, or head on over to your telephone and dial 916-226-
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Just waiting to see here if we get any more phone calls.
[SPEAKER_08]: If not, we'll just go ahead and wrap things up for tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does anybody have any last-minute stories they want to share?
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki or DarkSakura, any last-minute stories for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_07]: I was just going to talk really quickly about Forza 2 because there are some updates on IGN about it, including that it's going to be built using a completely new 360 engine.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a Forza 1 in HD.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice little slap at Sony there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Forza 2 is going to run at 60 frames per second with reflection mapping on all the cars.
[SPEAKER_07]: running at 60 frames per second as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to support the new wireless racing wheel.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll feature 60 tracks, 18 environments, 13 real-world licensed circuits, and will feature over 300 cars from more than 50 of the world's leading manufacturers, including Ferrari, Porsche, Nissan, VW, GM, and Lamborghini, to name a few.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Forza will allow people to
[SPEAKER_07]: to a new degree of stylization, including alternative engines, suspension kits, bolt-on superchargers, brakes, rims, racing slicks, and work on advanced suspension settings, tire pressure, and gear ratios.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it sounds like Gran Turismo to the extreme.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anybody else have any other last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: HappyHardcore.com
[SPEAKER_07]: Featuring Lisa Abbott, Desire the Comet Remix And also on Universe, The Acolyte with Treble Basin Attitude Which is going to be a Eurotrans song And Treble Basin Attitude is actually the one that's on the official trailer for Universe So, kind of neat
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't tell me you flew over there just to play Supernova.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nah, I'd barely seen Supernova where I was at in Spain, and through parts of Paris and Milan and Rome.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, wait, you're of Spanish descent, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm Peruvian, actually, but we do have family in Spain.
[SPEAKER_08]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought I remember on a previous episode you saying something about that, but whoa-ho, what is wrong with your connection?
[SPEAKER_08]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_08]: You got some weird thing going on there with your mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fix it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mic?
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, for some reason, you said that Supernova was supposed to come out last mid-May, which was a couple of weeks before it actually made the trip out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: Came back, it doesn't seem to me that nothing has appeared.
[SPEAKER_03]: By now, if it did come out like Konami said they would...
[SPEAKER_03]: I would see... I would see... about, you know, about all the songs from each part of the country.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, here it is, here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: It probably got pushed back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is anyone really surprised?
[SPEAKER_08]: Games get pushed back all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, wouldn't it be prudent to just make that correction?
[SPEAKER_03]: To just say that, you know, it might have been released last May or because of what I'm hearing.
[SPEAKER_08]: With arcade games, it's usually not the same thing as console because you are not the one that purchases an arcade game.
[SPEAKER_08]: The arcade owners do.
[SPEAKER_08]: So to come on the fan side, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little different when we're talking about console games, I think, versus arcade games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I guess, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just to keep that in mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: I understand where you're coming from.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sephiroth1215 is yelling out it's mid-June now, so I guess we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's what it was saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_03]: So far, did I miss anything in the past two weeks?
[SPEAKER_03]: Any gaming news?
[SPEAKER_08]: We took some video of the Ultramix stuff and Universe stuff at E3, and it's on YouTube if you search for OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, I don't know, go listen to our old podcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: Check it out at OrangeLaunchRadio.com, and you'll get caught up on all your gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you like that plug?
[SPEAKER_03]: One more thing, stuff in Europe is... Even DDR games, you know, here is about above 30...
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Zach, I'm hanging up on you.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're breaking up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry to hear it was so expensive.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hope you had fun, though, you lucky bastard.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least you get to travel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_08]: He said everything's more expensive over there is kind of what I picked up from that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I forgot we have a voicemail I have to play, too, so we'll play that in a moment.
[SPEAKER_08]: But let's do some more calls here real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, what's up, man?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is Bandit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, Bandit.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, that last guy that was just talking about the supernova?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I called Betson Air Prizes last week, and they actually told me it's shipping the last two weeks of June.
[SPEAKER_06]: You went right to the horse's mouth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I actually called the number that was on Konami's website, and they forwarded me to a guy who handles the machines in the Pittsburgh area.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, do you work for an arcade, or are you just a crazed fan?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm not a crazed fan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe a little bit, but you know what I used to?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, a hardcore fan.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was the owner of the local arcade, and he went ahead and gave me that information.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess it's good to know.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, hey, it'll be out just in time for my birthday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of which, chat room, what are you getting me for my birthday?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's June 26th, and I do accept cash.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll take chocolate, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie's shaking my hand.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give me your present now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else on your mind, Bandit?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, no, that's all for now, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but I think it's hot, but I don't like iPod White.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you don't like the color?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I hate it
[SPEAKER_08]: and then take it into EB Games and say it broke.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want a new one.
[SPEAKER_08]: And voila, you get your new one in a new color.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, that's what I did with my PSP and that's what I'm probably going to do with this.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: I shouldn't be endorsing such scamming, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I kind of get irritated that I always get asked no matter what store I go into about those damn replacement plans, so maybe they'll get rid of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You remember you were talking about the Minnesota thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, if you're 18, it's $50.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're 16, it's $75.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, that's a really big slap on the wrist.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then again, what 16-year-old has $75 that they didn't get from mom or dad?
[SPEAKER_08]: And also, if you're 18 years old, there's no games you can't play.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you could be buying the games for somebody else.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: As far as the 16-year-old goes, if it was my 16-year-old that did that and got the $75 fine and expecting me to pay it as the parent, I'd be all, you better start learning how to say you like fries with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's how you're going to pay it off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else, Ravenstolphin?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, have you ever landed that plane in Top Gun?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, God, back on the NES?
[SPEAKER_08]: Refueling it was a pain in the ass enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even remember trying to land it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Internet Relay Service
[SPEAKER_00]: CA 8617 with a message from Connie E. Chla, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is Nintendo Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm using an online program that allows you to call people using the Internet, no long-distance charge.
[SPEAKER_00]: You type a message in and hit the GA button, and your message will be read by a randomly selected talker.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can first test it out by calling yourself.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can check this out at SprintIP.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have fun and avoid any giant enemy crabs.
[SPEAKER_04]: GA, that's like for a teletype writer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, basically.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just thought it was cool that he just got some random, you know, poor older lady there to have to tell us to avoid giant enemy crabs.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was all kinds of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, guys, don't start sending us a barrage of messages doing this, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: The first time is cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: The second and third and fourth and fifth times will be annoying.
[SPEAKER_08]: So don't get these poor people to say all these random things.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do not want any voicemails left on the line with, you know, hi, we're calling from the teletype service, Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I will come to your house and beat you up if you do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll have them call you back and yell obscenities at you.
[SPEAKER_08]: WonderDog Harold in our chatroom says the internet relay lady was hot sounding.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura just made a face.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: But funny, and that's the important part.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: In a very wrong way.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's only funny until someone gets hurt, then it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of hilarious... When you get it on tape, it's ludicrous.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have one more story for you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you remember back in the day... This actually has nothing to do with video games, but it does have to do with games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that does make it a very important story.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you guys remember those books when we were kids, the Choose Your Own Adventure books?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah!
[SPEAKER_08]: You know those were first published in 1979?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: That's how you do the 50 books.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, get this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Choose your own adventure.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're coming back.
[SPEAKER_08]: This summer, eight of the original titles will return to bookstores and they're going to be revamped with 21st century references like cell phones.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the news.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all there is to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do this, you're dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a whole new generation to enjoy.
[SPEAKER_04]: After reading the book 50 million times, you actually find the one that you live through.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're driving down a street and your cell phone rings.
[SPEAKER_07]: Answer it or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Answer it, you're dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: Answer it, you crashed into a car.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't answer it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone else on their cell phone crashed into you.
You're dead.
[SPEAKER_08]: You are standing in front of a white house.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is a mailbox here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Turn to page seven.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have been eaten by a grue.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you get that reference, I love you.
[SPEAKER_08]: We should do Orange Lounge, the Choose Your Own Adventure.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we had Illusion wrote a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have the game, but we need our own Choose Your Own Adventure book.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need a Choose Your Own Adventure book.
[SPEAKER_04]: We could do that on a webpage.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura needs food badly.
[SPEAKER_08]: we'll see you guys next week with more Orange Lounge Radio we appreciate you guys tuning in have a great week see you next time