[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, June 11th, 2006, Xbox gets updates and is the luminous release around the corner.
[SPEAKER_01]: Video game addicts get their own version of the Betty Ford Clinic, and a game of Solitaire comes into play during the high-profile trial.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are here to talk about all the news that gamers really want to know about.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're here to help you through that.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joining me as always, say hello to the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Water.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sandwich.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I think I might start referring to her as the queen of the internet.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not the queen of the internet.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm the goddess of the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bow down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Watch that ego there.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: What ego?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's only explosive.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Over there, say hello to the other queen of the internet, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not a queen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you're not.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be Rob, the queen of the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, how are you doing, Loki, Tech Master Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you want to start off the show by issuing any apologies this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: You sure?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I know we got a large sharpened emails this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, because I... Because Loki misstated, misrepresented some facts last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, I made a mistake.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, they caught him!
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_03]: Big deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I already sent emails to said people, so I have nothing more to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: You sure?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't notice the optical audio out on every single cable that I own for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the only mistake I made, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ever, ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I somehow doubt that, but we know that when Loki makes mistakes, the Mac fans will be there to catch him.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's always good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it wasn't about Macs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know it wasn't about Macs, but they're the ones that are looking to, you know, get you the best they can.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I noticed that, well, there was a story this week too, but maybe we'll get into that later.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, let's start off the show as we always start off the show, talking about our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, start us off.
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, DarkSakura has a mouthful of sandwich.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's start with Loki, then.
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I played a lot of Xbox Live Arcade stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been playing, what was it, Joel Quest for some reason, because the achievements are easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, I don't know, the game was really easy until the last few levels, and then it gets really frustrating.
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't really kind of...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, balance out the difficulty over the course of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It should be getting, you know, increasingly harder as it goes along, not just easy, easy, easy, hard, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I didn't think they did that very well.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's really a crapshoot whether it's easy or not because, like, the level I just played a few minutes ago, you know, I played about four times before and I couldn't pass it because it was just impossible to get the blocks in the right positions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, you know, I started up and boom, it's super easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I finished it, like, in no time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Luck plays a huge role in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe sign back on or something, because sometimes if the game doesn't pick up your achievement right away, when you sign back on, it'll give it to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: That happened to me in Uno.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was missing two achievements I should have had, and I went back in the game later, and it gave them to me, just right off the bat, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then what else was I playing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Some other game, I think it was Never Ending Warning or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like some...
[SPEAKER_03]: Shadow of the Colossus
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a PC game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was for Neverending Story 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: That doesn't count.
[SPEAKER_02]: No wonder it was bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: That movie had The Flash in it.
[SPEAKER_00]: The guy who played The Flash on TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need to make a game based off the original.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Played a little bit of New Super Mario Bros., but I'm really sick of that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, really sick of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you supposed to be able to unlock some mini-games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I've played it through most of the games so far, and nothing's unlocked.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all the same ones that used to be on the Mario 64.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hear you do unlock others, but I haven't played it quite enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there are some hidden secrets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, have you gotten to the two completely hidden worlds, 4 and 7, yet?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are easy to get to, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, but you might miss them if you don't look for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm all the way through 7.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've played through, I've unlocked all those, but I haven't unlocked any of the minigames.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless they're just multiplayer exclusive minigames that are brand new to this, but I haven't seen anything new unlocked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ion671 seems to agree with you New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: gets old fast
[SPEAKER_02]: We need a re-release of The Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't we have this discussion a while back that somebody owns the rights to that that's never going to make it a new version?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Broderbund went under.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all on Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just go to Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the answers are there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I remember.
[SPEAKER_00]: I need to actually get an MSX.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and I play Blazing Angels multiplayer, which is fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dogfighting during lunch.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game, though, the only thing that's really disappointing about that game is that you can't crash the planes into each other.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's just say, thankfully, that game's not $60, and it's getting some price cuts to a more reasonable amount, so that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do think, though, that Burnout Revenge has a really well-done multiplayer mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think multiplayer's a lot of fun to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: The way it kind of set up, and when you're crashing into people and doing the takedowns, it kind of shows you who your enemies are before the match, and it's all kind of like a movie, the way it presents everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: It kind of gives you this running commentary on the top of the screen,
[SPEAKER_02]: So and so has just crashed.
[SPEAKER_02]: So and so took down so and so.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just kind of neat the way it's all presented.
[SPEAKER_03]: But don't you hate though when you're playing the game and the camera switches and then you crash into something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because the camera switched, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's a little bit annoying.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you don't get that so much in multiplayer because it can't really stop time as much in multiplayer because everybody's racing at the same time so you don't really get that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um... Otherwise, pretty much more of the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've also been playing new Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not quite sick of that yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, somebody in chatroom there says, uh... Uh... Ion671 says the new Super Mario games are multi.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's where you unlock those, is they're the multiplayer games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, the multiplayer games are a hell of a lot of fun in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: You gotta play them at least once.
[SPEAKER_02]: For multiplayer DS games, they're a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you gotta try it at least once before you knock it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Otherwise, you know, I'm still on jury duty.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you were listening to last week's show, I've been on a jury.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I still can't talk about the trial, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's supposed to be done early next week, so maybe I can talk about it next Sunday.
[SPEAKER_02]: But meanwhile, during the downtime, I've been playing Final Fantasy I still.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a good game to play at the courthouse.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keeps me busy when there's a lot, a lot of downtime.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did buy off the Xbox Live Arcade WIC Fable of Souls just because...
[SPEAKER_02]: They haven't released anything on Xbox Live Arcade in forever, so I decided to buy something I didn't have yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I like the concept.
[SPEAKER_02]: It seems kind of neat so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty lame, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't think it was as bad as you said it was in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_02]: It seems like I'll have fun with it for a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's definitely a $5, $10 title.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's $10, and I couldn't see paying much more for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's definitely the type of thing, like a Flash game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll entertain me for a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually didn't really play much of anything this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, I've had a whole week where I've had the time off, and I haven't really felt like playing anything.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I took a mini vacation from games this week, except that I actually moved a bunch of our game stuff around.
[SPEAKER_00]: And we have a lot of game stuff at my house.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh yeah, we almost got rid of our Virtual Boy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why would you do that?
[SPEAKER_00]: We were going to trade it for help on a pinball machine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did I say we got another pinball machine?
[SPEAKER_00]: We did.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've had some games this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: We got a Last Action Hero pinball machine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which actually has romantic significance for me and Dan.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because when I used to work at GNC back in the day... Bit of a big shock, me working at GNC.
[SPEAKER_00]: When we used to take the deposit, the deposit box was right next to, at the time, a Godfather's Pizza store.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dan's getting our DS lights today.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I totally forgot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Until I came into chat room this evening and somebody was talking about it, I forgot that DS Lights had been released today.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, oh yeah, I was going to get one of those.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm holding off this time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo is not going to get my money until the new colors come out that I want.
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually want a white one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to hold off for something like maybe green, purple, hot pink.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I know we have some stories coming up in the second half of the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll talk about functionality between the Wii and the DS, so it'll be kind of interesting to see if they start marketing the two systems together.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I did a little bit of drawing.
[SPEAKER_00]: I did some Kingdom Hearts-related drawing over the week, but other than that, my week's been pretty.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forgot I played one more game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played DDR this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_03]: I played
[SPEAKER_03]: We went to Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were going to go play Miniature Golf, but then we found out that they're closing early because of the grad night thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They wanted me to play DDR, but there's people playing the DDR machines except for Disney's Rave, which wasn't being played.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I had to play Disney's Rave, and I have no stamina anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, I accidentally picked Twilight Zone on doubles, which is a 10, and that's not fun, especially when you're out of shape.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, how many more pounds do you weigh now than when you played DDR religiously?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyways, good escape.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we went and played QZAR instead, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I heard.
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard Extraverse say you guys had gone to QZAR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beat the crap out of everyone like I normally do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loser.
[SPEAKER_02]: How many games of QZAR have you played in your life?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Neo Geo, Puzzle Bobble
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess I will go ahead and start us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, Xbox 360 got some updates finally this week, as you guys may have noticed.
[SPEAKER_02]: They released it on 6.6.6, which was a great day for 360 to get some new upgrades.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, when you power on your Xbox and connect to Xbox Live, you'll have to download the update.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't take very long at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now you can download up to six movies, demos, whatever, at a time.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've kind of re-laid out the store a little bit so that you can find stuff quicker.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have more categories, and I think they have some...
[SPEAKER_02]: I still think they need to just reorganize the store completely like the way it's presented, but at least they made improvements to the setup they've got, so I guess I can't complain too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the things I noticed right off the bat was custom soundtracks.
[SPEAKER_02]: They made a whole lot better because I use custom soundtracks quite a bit in Uno, which has some really god-awful music, and even in Burnout.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to listen to the...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: I noticed Xbox Live Arcade games load a lot faster because what it does is when it's scanning your drive for arcade games, it only does that once.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like it used to do it twice.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would do it once on the main menu and then when you went in to actually select a game, you'd watch all your games fill in again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now it kind of bypasses that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's kind of nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can get to your games a little faster, especially when you have like 17 games like I do in the Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, if you want to see the full list of upgrades, because there's a whole bunch, DVD player and all that stuff, head on over to Xbox.com and it's in their recent news.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I downloaded it and I put this thing to the test, not just with the custom soundtracks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I downloaded three trailers all at once and it worked great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I even made them, I powered off my machine while one was downloading and then I thought, oh crap, that probably was not a smart idea because you're not supposed to
[SPEAKER_02]: Turn your machines off while it's riding to the hard drive, but I just kind of forgot it was going.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I turned it back on and nothing was wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: It picked right back up and started going again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't recommend you guys do this because you might hurt something, but it's nice to know that it's not going to kill your Xbox to turn off the power once or twice while it's downloading.
[SPEAKER_02]: So those are the updates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, did you get a chance to check out the updates at all on your Xbox?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I had the update anyways, but no.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really use custom soundtracks just because I haven't loaded anything on there yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when it comes to burnout anyways, I just normally forward to today.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there's like 40 some tracks in there of all crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there is a way.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can actually sort what plays when.
[SPEAKER_02]: What I do is I stream over the Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how I get the custom soundtracks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I stream my MP3 collection from the computer using the MediaConnect thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I stream that over the Wi-Fi and it works great.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can set up playlists in Winamp and Xbox 360 will read those.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course I will.
[SPEAKER_00]: Guess what's coming out on the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_02]: Street Fighter 2 eventually, I hope?
[SPEAKER_02]: Tetris!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, well that's cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep, apparently THQ could get things settled and now we've got Tetris on the 360.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, there was a lawsuit last year against the Tetris company saying that they had breached a contract about releasing the DS version.
[SPEAKER_00]: So now we're getting it on the 360.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: We already have it on 360 in Japan.
[SPEAKER_00]: But not in US and Europe.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's coming out actually both in US and Europe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why isn't it supposed to be coming out like... I mean, I couldn't imagine that there's too much to localize with Tetris.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's not so much a localization thing as a Nintendo has a Tetris game out right now, so I think there's licensing dispute-y things that have been going on behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_00]: But they released it first party.
[SPEAKER_00]: So they couldn't say anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope it's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't touched the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just hope...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: It was so, so stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, you have some more news on Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, the creator of such wonderful games like Dead Rising and Lost Planet, Keiji Inafune, basically has come out saying, you know, the Xbox right now, they're up to about 60% of
[SPEAKER_03]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, his comment was, the more years you study a platform, the better you get.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some games you'll see in three to four years will be truly amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, pretty much you can say the same thing about the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, I mean, that goes with all game systems out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, this wasn't huge news, because usually when game systems first come out, they aren't exactly reaching their full potential.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, then you get lazy companies that just want to port crap over, you know, like EA.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not to say EA is the only one, Activision.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to put out for the record, I looked up Jellico on Wikipedia and they are still in business.
[SPEAKER_02]: But their English website has nothing on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a picture and a placeholder.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't think they're making a lot, but they're still around.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're probably more of a developer now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might have made them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going off memory, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty sure they were the ones that had made that.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, now I need to look that up too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dead Rising is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tetris Plus.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dead Rising is going to be fucking great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lost Planet, I wish it was coming out sooner, but it's supposed to be coming out, I think, January.
[SPEAKER_03]: That should be amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: The demo is really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not really my kind of game, but I can see where people are really into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looked pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rumble Roses Double X
[SPEAKER_02]: A demo is now up on Xbox Live, as well as brand new maps for Perfect Dark Zero.
[SPEAKER_02]: These were things that were supposed to come out sooner, and there was even an announcement that went out that they'd gone out, but then they got pulled.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're now out there on Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're out there now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Plaza Trench Rooftops and Gas Plant for 500 points.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's about 625.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if that interests you, check that out on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Perfect Dark Zero just couldn't really get into that game either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the maps in the world won't make that a better game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of one of those games I'll go back to maybe in a few months and try it again, see if maybe I can kind of get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But as far as first-person shooters go, I play so few of them anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, Halo is cool, and Quake 3, but not Quake 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wasn't feeling Perfect Dark Zero.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're in the age now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like 2006.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're approaching 2007.
[SPEAKER_03]: and yet companies can't grasp jump technology.
[SPEAKER_03]: The ability to jump in games is very important because we have feet.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do other things other than walk and run.
[SPEAKER_03]: They can jump.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe that should have been in Perfect Dark.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, you have some more news about Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, there's a whole bunch of releases that were supposedly leaked out there from a magazine.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of those, of course, being Street Fighter 2, which is supposed to be coming out in July, we hope.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't believe it anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I thought it was June.
[SPEAKER_02]: June, July.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't believe it anymore, anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's been so many release dates for that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be out whenever they're ready.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sick of speculating on dates.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're saying June, but then again, this is from a magazine, and if we've come to learn anything from magazines, they're printed way the hell in advance, and
[SPEAKER_03]: Luminous Live $1200
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be 200, 300, 100 points to download Madonna, you know, whatever else they're planning on putting in there from other artists.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those high-name artists will probably cost a little money.
[SPEAKER_02]: If there's profit to be made, Luminous will cost even more money.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, the game on the PSP costs $19.99, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, of course, on that one you have the perk of you have it on the go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of the other ones that were confirmed, though, and this is actually confirmed with Namco...
[SPEAKER_03]: Pac-Man is going to be out sometime in August or September for 400 Microsoft points or 5 bucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, supposedly coming around the same time, I believe, was Frogger.
[SPEAKER_03]: Supposed to be coming out from Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also about the same price.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there was another Namco game, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it Pac-Man or Galaxian?
[SPEAKER_03]: Galaxian was the other one, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, some other ones that they mentioned...
[SPEAKER_03]: The Cameo Hardcore Package featuring more difficult versions of the single-player campaign and co-op campaigns.
[SPEAKER_03]: More skins and new leaderboards, plus some more co-op competitive elements.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's supposed to be coming out in July for 500 Microsoft points, or 625.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cloning Clyde, also in July for 800 Microsoft points, or 10 bucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Robo Blitz, sometime in August or September.
[SPEAKER_03]: for 800 Microsoft Points or $10.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they need some games to come out in June because there's only one Xbox 360... No, two now because one moved to June again.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Over G Fighters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Over G Fighters and MotoGP 2006 are the only ones coming out in June right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Comments from our chat room over at OrangeLoungeTrader.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Funnydale says, If anything, Microsoft should give us $6.25 for making us play Perfect Dark.
[SPEAKER_02]: DMN says Sky Rare refuses to use jump features in their first person shooters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wonder where that comes from.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyway, going over to DarkSakura who has some more news for us.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one also relating to Xbox.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, there's a...
[SPEAKER_00]: Rumor out from an introversion that Darwinia is going to be available on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really, some of the support for this is that basically there's other versions of Darwinia out.
[SPEAKER_00]: They said there's been talk actually from Microsoft, I think, that they've been really wanting to use it.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's been a lot of just talk going around that says it's really going to happen.
[SPEAKER_00]: See, I've heard a lot of good about Darwinia.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's a really popular indie title, and I know we've gotten emails on it even before, and I've heard a discussion about the game on other shows.
[SPEAKER_00]: Some of our listeners overseas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and that would be really cool if that does hit Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's huge exposure for it, and it's a good marriage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox Live Arcade is supposed to be set up to help out the indie developers, so I hope it works out for them and give it some easy achievements for the achievement points horse.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, for those that like to do things to their Xbox 360s that could void the warranty, there's some news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: Modchip's coming out, finally.
[SPEAKER_03]: This website, devil360.com, actually they were trying to release it on 666, but weren't done in time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they're actually trying to improve it right now to try to protect it from any type of updates, make it programmable via PC, and able to boot unsigned code.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll allow you to swap the hard drive with a larger drive using a special interface between the 360 and the hard drive, and a lot more.
[SPEAKER_03]: So basically they're saying that it's going to be due out probably sometime by the end of this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they're still working on it right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's coming soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Coming soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Won't Microsoft just put out a patch?
[SPEAKER_03]: It might be something that they might not be able to patch because they may be able to... I mean, if you think about it, okay, Xbox, the original Xbox...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, don't forget, you can hook in a keyboard into your Xbox 360, kind of like Final Fantasy XI on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can play it with a controller, but I really wouldn't recommend it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I mean, okay, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can use the controller if you have really good macros set up, but even to put in the macros, you really need a keyboard to do all that and to chat with people, I mean, if you ever want to chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you can get away with most of the basic elements using, you know, good macros with a controller, but you really need a keyboard for that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I joined some server extifers on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something about get the characters to level 19 and do nothing but battlegrounds is what they're wanting to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Him and some other friends.
[SPEAKER_00]: Can I have my server with me too?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll do one that's all the way to level 60 if I stick with the game that long.
[SPEAKER_02]: What server are you on?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm on Scarlet Crusade for my alliance and Bronzebeard for my horde.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm on Elder Thalys is the one I'm working with the level 19 on.
[SPEAKER_00]: I might make one on there.
[SPEAKER_00]: My characters are still noob level.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_00]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to go to the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Best Buy has listed Nintendo Wii games for pre-order.
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually, I'm checking the link right now to see if they're actually still up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, sure enough, they are.
[SPEAKER_02]: It shows Red Steel, Super Mario Galaxy, and Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brawl all coming out December 1st, 2006.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you believe those release dates... You're an idiot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously those release dates are just in the system to try and get pre-orders moving, you know, amongst some of those really hotly talked about games such as Mario Galaxy and Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really don't know why this is news, but just for those people that think these are actual release dates and this points to, oh, the Wii's coming out December 1st.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, the Wii will be out before the day before Thanksgiving, or the day after Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd be surprised if the PS3 launches on the date that they said it will.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't be surprised if it doesn't launch until next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not to say they can't pull it off and it could be a really great system with lots of cool games.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they're going to be working some massive overtime over it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to seriously need the help of some leprechauns to make this thing happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't count Sony out yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what if they kind of lost E3, so to speak, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: They could come back.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Sony fanboys know that in the back of their mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the best interest of Sony right now is to get all of their upper people to stop saying stupid shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what they need to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually...
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe Sony could benefit from a gag order.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of like Nintendo has, kind of, sort of.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo doesn't really, but Nintendo they don't let out a lot of secrets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or when they do let out secrets, it's very carefully timed.
[SPEAKER_02]: The way they do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's because Nintendo hires smart people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, moving on to some release dates that we do know about.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, you like to travel the globe and tell our buddies in Europe what they have to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, some
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, not very exciting things unless you're a PC gamer, I guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: Copa Inata is coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ship Simulator 2006 is coming out on the 15th.
[SPEAKER_00]: The first game was out on the 13th.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then coming up on the 16th is Glory of the Roman Empire.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also on the 16th for DS we have Miss Spider, Harvest Time, Hop and Fly, and The Lord of the Rings, The Battle for Middle Earth 2 on Xbox 360 on the 16th.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving over stateside, Loki, you know any good releases for the US coming up?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's actually some pretty cool stuff, and one of them that I'm definitely getting this week, Point Blank for the DS is coming out, finally.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the Game Boy Advance, if you're a fan of the Mega Man Battle Network games, Mega Man Battle Network 6, Falzar, and Gregar are going to be both coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, coming out on PC, we've got Darwinia.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um,
[SPEAKER_03]: Ultimate Quake, Rush for Berlin, Rise and Fall of Civilizations at War, Deep Sea Tycoon, a bunch of other miscellaneous stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also on PlayStation 2, of course, Armored Core Last Raven, Street Fighter Alpha Anthology, and Urban Chaos Riot Response, which is also coming out on Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then for the PSP, you've got the Metal Gear Solid Digital Collection,
[SPEAKER_03]: and 360 MotoGP 2006
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on, we were talking about the PlayStation 3 a little bit ago, and of course one game a lot of folks are looking forward to on the PlayStation 3 is Metal Gear Solid 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there were some new details about Metal Gear Solid 4 announced in a very recent interview.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hideo Kojima said that there's a new camo suit that Snake's going to have.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the OctoCam.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what this will do is it will change shape and color to match the surroundings that Snake has.
[SPEAKER_02]: These chameleon effects are going to happen automatically whenever Snake is resting.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it sounds kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of like the trailer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could be a graphically impressive sort of event, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Kojima's dropping little hints left and right about Metal Gear Solid 4, just enough to remind the fans it's coming out and they better be supporting PlayStation 3, like it or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, here's another game that as the release date gets pushed back and pushed back, it's harder and harder to support, but the fans love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically...
[SPEAKER_03]: Take Two has said that Duke Nukem Forever will be out by December 31st.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a bold statement.
[SPEAKER_03]: You mean it this time?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you really mean it this time?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they've got an incentive now.
[SPEAKER_03]: As it was, they're not giving the full funding for the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe originally it was $6 million.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now they're down to $4.25 million.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's a $500,000 incentive
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's mighty breath to hold right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game better kick ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: With all this anticipation and all this waiting that's gone into it, this game better kick some ass so we can all eat our words and we've been bashing all these delays.
[SPEAKER_02]: It better be worth it.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game will have to be better than sex.
[SPEAKER_03]: This game will have to do my laundry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: So whether or not it'll come out,
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think anyone cares at this point.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Duke Nukem 3D, a lot of love for that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even 10 years later after the game was released, still a lot of love for that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's people out there that will support it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Put it on the goddamn Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: What, Duke Nukem 3D?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would actually be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: You think realistically that would ever happen?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: No?
[SPEAKER_03]: But it could.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, the game's small enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, well, I would imagine that the Xbox 360 would have the power to, I don't know, play that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I think it could be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: They should have done the same thing with Quake 2 instead of releasing it with Quake 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that could have been pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: In reference to a topic we were talking about earlier, JeremyTodd1 says, Duke Nukem is the never-starting story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we had never-ending story, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now everybody's talking about vaporware, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fireboma says, hey guys, let's go play on our Phantoms.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, Phantoms are coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, but so is Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, yeah, but I'm saying that they've, I mean, even though they've kept pushing back the date, they actually did have a date set for release.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, and yeah, sure, they'll hit that, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe they will and we can all... I say at the end of the year it goes and it hasn't released at that point, I'll consider it vaporware.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like I'm actually going to care about getting one, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: QuickSilver over in our chatroom is saying, I want Mortal Kombat on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are coming out with Mortal Kombat 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's either Mortal Kombat 3 or Ultimate Mortal Kombat or one of those.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why can't they put out the only good one they had, which was Mortal Kombat 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe because, well, see... Mortal Kombat 3 was like when the series started to go crappy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mortal Kombat 2 is available on the Midway packs or whatever, but then again, so is Mortal Kombat 3, but I don't think, I could be wrong, but I don't think Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 was available in those Midway treasures or whatever it was called.
[SPEAKER_02]: And plus, you couldn't play them online either, which is a huge...
[SPEAKER_02]: All it is is that because Street Fighter is coming out, Mortal Kombat has to come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one of the greatest video game competitions ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Street Fighter vs. Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what we need is a new Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know, but that would make me so happy.
[SPEAKER_00]: That would make me happy too.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was a Killer Instinct fangirl.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they'd take out the jump feature in that one too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we're going to go over to our mailbag over at mailbag at orangelauntrader.com is our email address.
[SPEAKER_02]: And DarkSakura likes to dig through the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's going to put on her hazmat suit and pull out some emails and share them with us so we can taunt your emails live on air.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: We love getting mail of all types.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even the hate mail we got this week thanks to Loki's uninformed statement on Xbox Sound Support last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good job, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, DarkSakura, what's in the mailbag?
[SPEAKER_00]: The first one comes from Kurt, one of our listeners It's like, hey I was wondering if you guys could fill me in on the rules that Sony may have regarding how many PS3s each person will be allowed to buy Or is there only one per household allowed?
[SPEAKER_00]: Will people be selling the PS3 on eBay for megabucks like the PS2 and the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I'm sure they will
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure they'll be selling as many as they can possibly sell.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think Sony sets those limits though, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: It stores the retailers how many they can sell to make sure that they fit all the orders.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, retailers will be setting those limits and most retailers, if the PS3 is a hot commodity, will have the one limit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And probably at launch, I think Sony's still going to pull out an ace somehow.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to make this work somehow and have at least one title out there that the fanboys are going to have to have.
[SPEAKER_00]: I still say if you're going to buy one, pre-order it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Put down a reserve on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: That is the smart way to do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: And like all of you people who tried to go in and buy your Xbox 360 on launch day.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ha ha!
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't count on E3's bust for Sony, essentially, to be meaning that they're going to be easy to get.
[SPEAKER_00]: Stores are only going to get limited quantities.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you don't pre-order it, I doubt you're going to get one on launch day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it doesn't matter anyways, because you're not going to get one on launch day even if you do pre-order it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember the 360?
[SPEAKER_03]: People were getting them in March.
[SPEAKER_00]: The people who pre-ordered theirs first got theirs first.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're supposed to be altering that, so it doesn't happen this time either.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't pre-order them right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last year, you could have pre-ordered a 360 right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, at this time last year.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they're not doing that with the PlayStation 3 because they learned their lesson.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least the big, big retailers.
[SPEAKER_02]: GameStop and EB Games, as far as games go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, more mail.
[SPEAKER_00]: Another of our listeners asked if we know of any upcoming DVR games for PS2.
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR Supernova.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's pretty much the only one here in the States.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure UK is getting Dancing Stage Supernova as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR Supernova, there's actually a little in-depth look on our website, and I think it's still on the front page.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it's rolled off yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Over at www.orangenautorated.com, and there's video of it in motion and everything.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was from John, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, thank you, John.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, that's pretty much all there is to look forward to as far as DDR goes and Supernova.
[SPEAKER_02]: So far for the past, what,
[SPEAKER_02]: 5 years now, Konami's been putting out pretty regularly a new DDR game every year on Sony's platform.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can count on probably another one next year as well, unless for some unknown reason Supernova doesn't sell, but I really don't see that happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it'll sell just as well as the other games, if not better.
[SPEAKER_00]: Next one up is JVmon, who I am very, very proud of, writing a letter to the senator.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yes, I remember talking about that on a previous episode.
[SPEAKER_00]: And basically, just in closing, said, so any help and input would be greatly appreciated.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I love OLR, Sky and DarkSakura, you inspired me to write my senator.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh yeah, and Loki is awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: But yeah, I'm not going to go into it because it's fairly long already.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the arguments are basically what we've been talking about, about the parents' responsibility to decide what their children do.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't want to put the pen to the paper for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would say the only suggestions we really have is just be professional.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make sure you sound professional.
[SPEAKER_00]: Research your points.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, best you can.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if you've been listening to, you read enough video game websites, especially things like Game Politics that really have their eye on these types of things, and listen to enough shows, you probably are well-educated on the subjects.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just write maturely.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you're trying to, I say if you're trying to refute an argument, though, have facts to back up why you're refuting it and what's gonna, that's what I meant.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have the facts there to support your argument.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, please don't write your senator a letter that says, Dear Senator, I am a registered voter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you, you fucking fuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't do that because that's just going to get thrown away and you'll look stupid.
[SPEAKER_00]: They'll probably laugh at you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so you need to write something mature.
[SPEAKER_00]: So we got an email from, I'm going to hopefully pronounce this right, Tasete Pueri, I guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's also, I think, in our chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: I'd say it all depends on what you're going for.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you want something that's going to be a good work-oriented computer, something that you can run your programs well on, something you can do graphics in well, something that you can write on well, something that you can basically use as a work system, Mac is the way to go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Something that's going to be on a more professional level.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you want something that you can play games on and just futz around on the internet with, PC is the way to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: My advice, try before you buy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any computer store, if you're going to make a major purchase like that,
[SPEAKER_02]: Any major computer store is going to have the computers out there on the show floor, especially like the Apple Store.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they encourage people to be playing on their Macs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, any type of big retailer for PCs, Best Buy, Fry's, whatever, they have laptops out on the floor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Try it before you buy.
[SPEAKER_00]: And also, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take all the time you need.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't rush the decision.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, yeah, there's a bar mitzvah on Saturday, so.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mazel tov.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I just thought that we would go ahead and give you our public yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_00]: Jeremy Todd writes in just to read the letter I just want to thank you for giving me something to listen to during work to help make the hours go by faster my job is a pretty boring job at times we won't tell your boss and having something to listen to really helps a lot I have been downloading a few older episodes of OLR and listen to them while I'm at work so thank you for providing such a good podcast to listen to in desperate times you're welcome
[SPEAKER_02]: We do this show for fun, and we always get a kick out of the fact that people listen to this and provide feedback and all that stuff, so it really keeps us motivated, so thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: We also got an email from Tony.
[SPEAKER_00]: I haven't had a chance to watch the file yet, so I'm just going to read the email.
[SPEAKER_00]: It says, I just watched a rerun of the Colbert Report on Comedy Central for June 8th.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you don't watch a lot of TV, so I'll forgive you for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually the Colbert Report.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, I don't watch TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you don't watch TV, but...
[SPEAKER_00]: Steven's guest explains how video games are actually helping this generation of kids and implies that GTA might contribute to this nation's decrease in carjackings and teen pregnancies.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all done... The show is a parody, essentially, of shows like The O'Reilly Factor, and so it's all very tongue-in-cheek when they do that stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's still a point, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could see how maybe World of Warcraft would lead to decline of pregnancy because they're too busy playing the video game in order to, I don't know, have sex.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Sex or an instance?
[SPEAKER_02]: sex is any time and instance is in like two minutes seriously I don't know it depends on sometimes sex is an instance but hey alright anyway la la la la la la that's it alright if you want to send us emails please do mailbag at orange lounge radio dot com
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, speaking of MMOs and sex and instances, what a good follow-up.
[SPEAKER_02]: You got a story for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, lots of gamers are finding love online in fake virtual worlds like World of Warcraft and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, a survey conducted by Stanford University's Nick Yee, a PhD student there, found that 29% of women and 8% of men have admitted to have gone on dates with people that they've met in the games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the
[SPEAKER_03]: He attributes that phenomenon to the trust-building exercises of working in team scenarios.
[SPEAKER_03]: How one player acts during an in-game raid may reveal traits relative to the avatar's personality through situations that are less common in the real world.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, say for example, we would take, you know, Leroy Jenkins.
[SPEAKER_03]: He might rush into things a little bit, you know, too quickly.
[SPEAKER_03]: He might not be a good mate.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, uh... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was interesting they mentioned one guy was setting up for two weddings, one in real life and one in game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nerd!
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, hey, hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, I met my husband online.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know... Through our geekdom.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I realized in this...
[SPEAKER_02]: Day and age that we live in, the internet is a place that we can meet people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember back in the day, maybe if you have an older brother or sister, they talked about party lines that you could call into on the phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what chat rooms are.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's party lines, basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_00]: Cybersex is like phone sex too.
[SPEAKER_02]: But when you throw the MMO into it, it does get a little weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you know, because people are like roleplaying elves and dwarves and all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, you were a hot elf in that game, but now you're a fat cow.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't know, this kind of mixes things up a bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time, you know, I'm not going to knock.
[SPEAKER_02]: Two people falling in love.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it's genuine, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Love's a great thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Doesn't matter how it happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: I had Dan's high school photo to go on when we first met.
[SPEAKER_00]: Keep in mind, I was 22 when I moved out here.
[SPEAKER_00]: God, it was that long ago.
[SPEAKER_00]: I thought it was great because we actually got to know each other as people without having the whole
[SPEAKER_00]: I do think it is important, though, to make sure that the person that you're talking to is not looking like a yeti.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think it matters what the other person looks like as long as their heart is good and you love them for themselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeti people need love too, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't mean you have to love them, but you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, somebody might have a Yeti fetish.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there are furry fetishes out there.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's really sad, though, just how much people base their whole relationship on, oh, well, this person's hot, or, oh, well, this person is this, you know, aesthetically, instead of actually putting the importance on who they are on the inside.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so I think that, I honestly think that you open yourself up for a lot of risk.
[SPEAKER_00]: However, if you do happen to hit pay dirt, then you're going to get someone who I think is a bit,
[SPEAKER_00]: I think that you have a chance of getting a more genuine person when you do find somebody.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I'm looking for a good running car or whatever, I don't want one that's all beat up on the outside.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I am from somebody who said that two of her friends met on World of Warcraft and got married three months ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Let them do whatever they want.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they want to roleplay taurens and orcs in the bedroom, have fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do your thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't put it on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to see it.
[SPEAKER_00]: But still, I think that people who meet through online methods, whether it be an MMO, whether it be through a chat, through a message board, if it works for you, more power to you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or at a bar.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Picking up people at a bar is pretty scummy.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, not always.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not always, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of times it can be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bars are pretty sleazy sometimes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Meet people at church.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the only clean place.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not a clean place.
[SPEAKER_03]: Church going people.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bob in our chat room says, well, what about those balloon fetish people?
[SPEAKER_02]: Pop a balloon and they'll be all over you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a feeling someone missed the point there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dirty Thief said someone's going to bang a chocobo.
[SPEAKER_02]: And in reference to doing the MMOs, sex and the MMOs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boy, you kids have a lot of free time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you do play too many video games, you might need to take a trip to the Netherlands.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they have set up an addiction center.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the first detox clinic for video game addicts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Video games may look innocent, but they can be just as addictive as gambling or drugs and just as hard to kick, says Keith Backer, director of Amsterdam-based Smith & Jones Addiction Consultants.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's already treated 20 video game addicts aged 13 to 30.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of them will show withdrawal systems, shaking, sweating, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: His detox program begins in July 2021.
[SPEAKER_02]: It runs 4-8 weeks and has therapy sessions, wilderness excursions, healthy lifestyle workshops, and possibly medication.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, another quote here from Backer.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have kids who don't know how to communicate with people face-to-face because they've spent the last three years talking to somebody in Korea through a computer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Their social network has completely disappeared.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, hey, hey, they can't be blaming this on Korea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hike van der Heijen 28 was a graduate of the Amsterdam side of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: He started playing video games when he was 8.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the time he was in college, he was gaming 14 hours a day and using drugs to play longer, which is
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pathetic.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a whole other problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not a gaming problem.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's called obsessive compulsive disorder.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does that count as cheating on live?
[SPEAKER_02]: Getting coked up before playing?
[SPEAKER_02]: If I'm on speed, I have that advantage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I say the quote, please?
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the quote from the kid.
[SPEAKER_02]: For me, one joint would never be enough, or five minutes of gaming would never be enough, he said.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would just keep going until I crashed out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so like when I first read about this story, I was kind of laughing at it, because my thought went to, you know, I've been downtown all week at the courthouse, you know, during the jury duty, and one of the things I walk by is a, I'm not, I don't want to knock
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to name what religion it is, but you go by a very religious type of like a store type thing, and they have in the window, do you have a gaming addiction problem?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's listed in listening.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, are you addicted to sex, violence, gaming?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was kind of like...
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh boy, you know, I just kind of roll my eyes at it and keep on walking.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, these guys that I'm reading about in this story, they really do have problems and do need some type of intervention.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe this isn't such a bad idea as it seems.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the media is just kind of putting a spin on this story where, you know, it's about, you know, oh, it's gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just, they're obsessed with gaming and gaming is the problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, these guys obviously have a lot of other problems.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's something.
[SPEAKER_00]: Underline.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gaming just contributes too.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you start reading these testimonials, I mean, if he was doing drugs too, that's a whole nother problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was getting sex, he wouldn't have any of these problems.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the moral of the story, kids, you know, what was one of the treatments here?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wilderness excursions.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can go on your own wilderness excursion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's what you do.
[SPEAKER_02]: After you've played the game, like if you've played the game for more than like four hours a day, it's time to go outside for an hour.
[SPEAKER_02]: Walk around, breathe in some fresh air, take a wilderness excursion, and don't let this become you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if wilderness excursions are a good idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: How do you think LARPs came around?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, do we really need more of that?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, LARPs are, I used to do LARPs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could play games outside!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fireball!
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the same as going to reenactments.
[SPEAKER_00]: Reenactments actually have historical significance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or going to Ren Faire.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's reenact the Civil War, but this time the South won.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, I'm not one to knock what somebody else is into, but I did go to a Ren Faire once.
[SPEAKER_02]: and kind of roll my eyes at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just wasn't for me.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I'm not going to... A Ren Faire is fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to knock people... Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, do what makes you happy.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's all about getting your pint of ale and chatting up the men in tights.
[SPEAKER_02]: A Ren Faire is like... Maybe the Ren Faire I went to just sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: A Ren Faire is just like an old-fashioned Hooters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots of boobs, lots of chicken.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's basically what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's nothing wrong with a Ren Faire.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plus, you get to see people fight with swords.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the only thing missing from Hooters is sword fighting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes I wonder why we have you on the show, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you say little gems like that to remind me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to another story now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I'm curious what the chat room has to say in feedback to the detox story here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Raven's Dolphin says they need an OLR clinic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am addicted.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's lovely.
[SPEAKER_02]: But just remember, you can put Orange Lounge Radio on your iPod or whatever MP3 player you have, and you can go outside and take a walk and listen to Orange Lounge Radio if you wanted to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, you have another story for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it's about the Federal Trade Commission and their never-ending quest to waste my tax money.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, they've investigated the hot coffee problem and they found out that, well, apparently Take-Two didn't fully reveal the content of the PC versions to the ESRB.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, what are they doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they're saying, better not do it again or else we'll fine you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're going to fine them, supposedly, a civil fine up to $11,000 per violation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, what the violation may be, or if it's per title, or per copy sold, oh, none of that was ever said.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish I knew more about what Take-Two kind of defended themselves with in this.
[SPEAKER_00]: A machete.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would have been like, listen, bitch, we didn't fucking put it in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some person hacked it in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you that goddamn dumb that you can't see this?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're like, no, but games suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was on the disc, Loki, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was on the disc.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to be a devil's advocate.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it was not accessible by normal means.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was lazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, I go back to my old, it was lazy programming.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't even think it was so much lazy.
[SPEAKER_00]: It happens in games all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: They took out the pointer and somebody put it back in with a hack code.
[SPEAKER_02]: So dumb, it's so dumb!
[SPEAKER_00]: On top of that, you have to do other stuff in addition to it, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's ridiculous, and the fact that they're wasting our money investigating this?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, for what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, to prove that this is a mature-rated game?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like saying, oh, well, this R-rated movie said it only had blood and violence, but I was totally shocked when I saw the boobies in there, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ PooEater over in chatroom says, What?
[SPEAKER_02]: A breast?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is an AO game now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the killing and use of the word nigga is cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, it's like the whole thing with movies and full frontal nudity when it comes to guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's okay in an R-rated movie, but when you get a naked guy in there, oh, NC-17, oh my god, horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the same thing with this, you know, once you add a little bit of nudity in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, which, you know, if you think about it... Actually, in the 70s, it wasn't a big deal at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you go look at movies that were made in the 70s, like Porky's.
[SPEAKER_02]: Life of Brian.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's Wang left and right in those movies, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, what about... They were just art.
[SPEAKER_03]: What about, like, God of War, where there's actual, you know, nudity in that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they had a sex game, and they're granted, they didn't show anything, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if you saw this game and actually played the hot coffee game or whatever, you would have been, this is ridiculous and stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is like a sex game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's about as ridiculous as Custard's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it didn't really show anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just showed some stupid, really low-res models dry-humping each other, basically, and a woman, you know, climaxing, I guess, when this meter got up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's continue moving on talking about video games and their reputation out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a columnist.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's John Roseman.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's a syndicated Christian columnist.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's got 11 books on parenting.
[SPEAKER_02]: He believes that collective common sense concerning children has been swamped by tidal waves of psychobabble that's lasted some 40 years now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, he had a column that ran in Monday's edition of the Charlotte Observer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me give you a quote from it.
[SPEAKER_02]: When video games first came out, I warned my readers that they were not appropriate for children.
[SPEAKER_02]: I maintained that they were not games, rather.
[SPEAKER_02]: They produced stress and were addictive, literally.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was not a popular stance.
[SPEAKER_02]: He says, before entering into it, I told you so story about a mother and father dealing with introducing video games into their lives, their young children.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's some other gem quotes from the article here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quote, since then, hundreds of parents have shared with me their negative experiences with these nefarious devices.
[SPEAKER_02]: The stories go in my I told you so file.
[SPEAKER_02]: The following, written by the mother of several young children, is the latest edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another quote.
[SPEAKER_02]: When they played, there would be fighting and tears.
[SPEAKER_02]: When the parents turned it off, the kids would mope around to complain of having nothing to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Were these the same children who pre-Xbox have never had a problem entertaining themselves?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, they were not the same children at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were beginning to exhibit addictive behavior, and as anyone who has ever lived with one will testify, an addict and the former non-addict are two entirely different people.
[SPEAKER_02]: The story ends with a warning to all parents.
[SPEAKER_02]: I firmly believe that video games are dangerous to children and families.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do not buy one.
[SPEAKER_02]: You cannot control it.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, I love how this guy says, when video games first came out, I warned my readers.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this guy was writing columns when Space War first came out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Pong?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, so what, in the early 70s, late 60s?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, there were games well before that, too.
[SPEAKER_00]: So what about board games, huh?
[SPEAKER_00]: Are board games addictive?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, or when it rains outside and the children mope around because they can't go outside and play football?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, that's just how children are.
[SPEAKER_00]: Say that you give them a sit and spin, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then you take it away.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the sit and spin was their favorite thing to do.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, how are they going to act?
[SPEAKER_00]: They're going to cry.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're going to be mopey.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you've got multiple children and you've got a single thing, they're going to fight over it.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's just how siblings are.
[SPEAKER_02]: If a child's moping around that they have nothing to do, have them do the dishes or mop the floor.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what my mom made me do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never was to complain I have nothing to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: My mom always said, if you tell me you have nothing to do, I'll find something for you to do.
[SPEAKER_00]: I knew how to do laundry when I was six years old.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't give me this nothing to do crap.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have children to do your housework for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe if you didn't sit your kids in front of the TV and just have the TV raise them, and then when you take that away, then they don't have anything to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe you should teach them, I don't know, to use their imagination or maybe play with toys.
[SPEAKER_03]: My cousin was the same way.
[SPEAKER_03]: You would give him Legos and he wouldn't know what to do with them because no one taught him how to play by himself or entertain himself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead, they would have to entertain him by either putting a movie on or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: He didn't have video games, but you know,
[SPEAKER_04]: These are the same difference.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's basically, you don't teach your kids, because, oh my god, you know, having the kid and stuff was so much stress and stuff, and now we don't have time to ourselves, and oh, I'm just so tired with this, and now I need something to entertain my kids, and now they won't get along, and it's all this video game stuff, because they must have been addicted to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they're not addicted to the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just kids, and they whine, and
[SPEAKER_03]: Subtitles by the Amara.org community
[SPEAKER_00]: What I used to do with my little brothers, because my little brothers are about, the oldest of them is seven years younger than I am.
[SPEAKER_00]: When my mom would be busy, I would teach them how to do something and say, okay, go do this.
[SPEAKER_00]: And when I come back, I want to see what you've done.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would break out the Lincoln Logs.
[SPEAKER_00]: I had Lincoln Logs when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_00]: I break out the Lincoln Logs, come back.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was Tinker Toy Kid.
[SPEAKER_00]: We had Tinker Toys too.
[SPEAKER_00]: My brothers would have built like a whole fort out of stuff because I showed them how to put them together.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had the large size Tinker Toys.
[SPEAKER_03]: The ones that were like ginormous.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tinker Toy times 100.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to go to chat room because they have some great comments right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Legend of Zaku says, Sky, this guy is nothing more than the advocate of the American Taliban.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's some harsh words, but okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's your quote, not mine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they start talking about board games.
[SPEAKER_02]: The chat room is just going off on board games here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fireboma says Monopoly causes domestic violence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you ever seen a family fight over a good old-fashioned game of Monopoly?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of my friends' favorite stories that they always make me tell whenever we're drinking or whatever is the story about my mom and I fighting over the bag of M&M's.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you know, families fight over the dumbest shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: They really do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Siblings fight vicious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Legend of Zaku says Frogger is animal cruelty.
[SPEAKER_02]: GS191, think about the children.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ban Connect 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Legend of Zaku says Mystery Date causes premarital sex.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fireboma says life, you know, the game of life, causes kids to think that having children out of wedlock is okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, get this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, toys are even more dangerous than video games, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, Linkin Logs, they make great catapults.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, those... What was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not K'nex, but... Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_03]: I used to make... Tinker Toys?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not Tinker Toys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we have the life-size Tinker Toys, and those things were...
[SPEAKER_00]: I remember flicking the little circular knob off of the stick when you pull it back and then flick it off the stick and I used to hit my brother in the head with that all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's why he's a marine now.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you think the video games are dangerous, try dealing with a kid with a crossbow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this comment is really good, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted to share this so we can move on here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blaze in our chatroom says, I'm a devout Christian, and I hate these people who are on a useless crusade to try and reform society through their political bullshit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: That wasn't a pun, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've had these very strange puns come out of nowhere tonight.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't make daddy taught daughters to sneak out at night.
[SPEAKER_00]: I need a game to teach me how to sneak out of the house.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did the game Cootie teach us?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_00]: How to play with bugs.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been doing a lot of research into food and eating, given that I've been looking for natural treatments for the chronic fatigue immunodeficiency syndrome.
[SPEAKER_00]: which I try not to go off on that one but I've been trying to do a lot of natural you know research into how to naturally treat it and they're basically stating that a lot of the the ideals that were taught as children by our parents who of course learn this from their parents learn it from their parents are you know not necessarily the best thing to actually do
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, you're taught to clean your plate no matter how full you are.
[SPEAKER_00]: So as you grow up, you're taught to overeat.
[SPEAKER_00]: When you are full, you're done, not when you're satisfied.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I think that a lot of that, plus a lot of, you know, a lot of the different, you know, technology we have now that basically promotes being lazy, you know, a lot of easy food, things that are packed full of calories and bad for you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, our society is built around a very, very vicious relationship with food.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so, I personally am trying to go into breaking some of those habits of myself.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I encourage, you know, parents, when your child says they're full, don't make them eat anymore.
[SPEAKER_00]: Start with them young.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, teach them how to go out and play.
[SPEAKER_00]: Teach them how to eat right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't make them clean their plate, because if they're satisfied, there's no need to stuff them.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's what I have to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, ref you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, fuck you to think I... Yeah!
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_03]: You got pink eye this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, conjunctivitis, but they basically said that's pink eye, but I guess it's just it sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't it really conjunctivitis?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm throwing it towards you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I think it's just conjunctivitis or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sucks, seeing his eyes all red.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't hurt, though, so that's kind of good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just really annoying having your eye water all day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, yeah, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, uh, my FU of the week goes to my sinus issues or whatever, because you guys were listening to last week's show, I was sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still, I feel, it's something about the weekends are making me sick lately, because I'm sick again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I woke up this morning feeling all, you know, congesty and stuff, and it sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate being sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go away.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not supposed to have allergies and sinus problems.
[SPEAKER_02]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're making me sleep too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was our angst for the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we'll go over to DarkSakura, as you know she likes to keep an eye on what's going on overseas.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what is going on overseas?
[SPEAKER_00]: A bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's actually some UK gaming events going on.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I thought that it's a good idea for our overseas listeners.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, we like to make sure that they stay in touch, so...
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, there's the Women in Games UK at the University of Teesside, uh, 10th through 11th in July.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, it's, uh, 50 pounds for students, 100 pounds for, uh, non-students, and then after, uh, July 14th, it's 75 pounds for students and 150 for non-students.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, sex and games, panel on, uh, hiring, retaining next-gen positions, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Heh heh.
[SPEAKER_00]: Develop Conference Brighton, 11th through 13th in July.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the conference before the 10th, then in June it's 435 pounds and 570 after that.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's going to be people from Bungie hanging out there, different lectures, different
[SPEAKER_00]: information on DirectX10.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then there's the games edu conference in Brighton the 14th of July.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to be up to the 10th of June.
[SPEAKER_00]: It'll be 95 pounds, 110 after 10th June.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically it's going to be game design, academics,
[SPEAKER_00]: furthering the UK talent pool.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's the Edinburgh Interactive Entertainment Festival, which is the 21st through 22nd of August, which is game screening, award ceremonies, and game ratings.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Games Market Europe in London, 6th through 17th September.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's also going to be some playable titles there, networking opportunities.
[SPEAKER_00]: GDC London, the 3rd through 4th October, and no information yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: There should be more information coming later in June.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: And if any of you guys go to this, let us know how it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_00]: We'd love to write it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's go over to Loki, who has news.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, there's all these tycoon games.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's, what, Railroad Tycoon, of course, and there was, let's see, the Amusement Park one, Roller Coaster Tycoon, Lemonade Tycoon.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's all these games.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this might be one I actually want to check out, Loki, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've announced Hell Tycoon.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, announced it on Tuesday, which was June 6, 2006.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you sure this wasn't a joke?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_03]: The official website is up right now, and you can go check it out, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, it should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's healthhycoon.com, obviously.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically, you have to manage the misery of others and make sure that...
[SPEAKER_00]: I so will play this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to the site right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: This site has noise, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, you guys might hear this come up on the screen, but I have to see this for myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loading, loading, loading.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Evil noises.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, it says, When Armageddon comes, the demon armies of hells will be defeated.
[SPEAKER_03]: This can only mean one thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: The devil isn't doing his job.
[SPEAKER_03]: You are the new ruler of hell.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your job is to keep Abyss stocked with torqued souls, reform all nine planes of hell with fire and brimstone.
[SPEAKER_03]: On Judgment Day, will you be ready?
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, it's no secret that politicians are controlled by the devil.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now you know why Washington, D.C.
[SPEAKER_03]: is built around a giant pentagram.
[SPEAKER_02]: This scene just goes on and on.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's funny, so go check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to get the makers of Hell Tycoon on this program.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to talk to them and find out what's wrong with them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, seriously, how messed up do you have to be to think of something like this?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: That actually sounds kind of smart.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to check this out, I think, when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Dartetsuya says, sounds like Loki's kind of game, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bob Dole says, that sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: HitStun wants to know, does anybody own the Tycoon name?
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess not, because you see all these Tycoon games, like, all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And JeremyTodd1 made the mandatory joke, I suppose, beating this joke into the ground.
[SPEAKER_02]: Giant Enemy Crab cartoon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Tycoon.
[SPEAKER_00]: Journey Tycoon, where you manage the band journey.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of a joke that never gets old, Uwe Boll has sued the distributor of Blood Rain.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: refusing to pay the producers their share of the gross proceeds and not using the $10 million that Bull's production company had given them for promotion and advertising of the film.
[SPEAKER_02]: This suit has been confirmed that it is going on there, but who knows what will actually happen with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to look for a comment here.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did comment and basically...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that was all bullshit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Romar Entertainment co-founder Jane Schramm had a comment here.
[SPEAKER_02]: He had such bad publicity that I felt bad and I wanted to help him out.
[SPEAKER_02]: We made no money on this movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: We lost.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was a complete financial loss.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he has the audacity to remove us off the credits.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that was the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: When the DVD came out, they removed them off the credits.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they made it look like it was distributed by Uwe Boll instead of Romar.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, he's a jackass.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't have known because there's no way I'm going to watch that DVD.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, we're going to go ahead and take a break.
[SPEAKER_02]: And when we come back, there'll be plenty more Orange Lounge Radio where this came from.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll see you in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.