[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 188 for this June the 25th of 2006.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're here.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to get back into the news very shortly here.
[SPEAKER_11]: However, I wanted to grill our special guest in studio, 23rd Magus, here for just a minute here about something he had told me about on break.
[SPEAKER_11]: You were talking about World of Warcraft, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you were talking about the add-ons for World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, there was one that I thought was very interesting that you said you had installed that messes with the chat somehow.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've never heard of this.
[SPEAKER_08]: This sounds great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it's an add-on called Eloquence.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a chat filter.
[SPEAKER_08]: I refer to it as a sanity filter for the grammar freaks out there who are tired of the noob speak, the dude speak, the lead speak, or just plain dumb speak.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, it filters through whatever comes through your chat and
[SPEAKER_08]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_08]: and most of the add-ons for the WoW players you can go to ui.worldofwar.net or curse-gaming.com and pick up some add-ons to kind of enhance your play experience.
[SPEAKER_11]: So this filter basically...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Except for the times where you do it as a joke when it's funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: Still, I love good grammar, and I like to see good grammar when I'm about in my MMOs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then you send me that for Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_11]: Beautiful thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just wanted you to be able to share that with our listeners, because I didn't know about that, but I'm only a casual World of Warcraft player.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not hardcore.
[SPEAKER_08]: You are a casual's casual, Robyn.
[SPEAKER_11]: A casual casual who has never even hit 60.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you'll have more fun when you hit 60.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some news out of Nintendo this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some power players over at Nintendo, namely Iwata and Miyamoto, have been discussing the Wii, the Nintendo DS, and more.
[SPEAKER_11]: And there's a full in-depth article over on Gamasutra.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought maybe I'd pull some choice quotes out of here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Iwata talked about the GameCube launch.
[SPEAKER_11]: When we launched GameCube, the initial sales were good, and all the hardware was manufactured at the time we were sold through.
[SPEAKER_11]: However, at this period, we could not provide the market with strong software titles in a timely fashion.
[SPEAKER_11]: As a result, we could not leverage the initial launch time momentum, and sales of GameCube slowed down.
[SPEAKER_11]: To avoid repeating this with Wii, we have been intensifying the software development, both internally at Nintendo and at developers outside the company, in order to prepare an aggressive software lineup for Wii and after the launch.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it kind of sounds like they're learning from some of the mistakes they made with GameCube, which was namely, you know, kind of a dead period, which kind of happened with the DS, too, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, I remember for a couple months after the DS came out, even on this show, because we were up and running by the time the DS was out, and I remember earlier episodes of this program, during that lull, we were kind of like, come on, Nintendo, where's our games?
[SPEAKER_11]: Ping Pals ain't gonna cut it!
[SPEAKER_11]: Come on!
[SPEAKER_08]: And suddenly, boom!
[SPEAKER_08]: Hit games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, and then, like, just one hit game after another.
[SPEAKER_11]: Miyamoto, I'm sure you guys want to know what he said.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's a quote from Miyamoto.
[SPEAKER_11]: While I feel that we need more internal software development resources at Nintendo, we have not increased the number greatly.
[SPEAKER_11]: When we combine the total number of people working for Nintendo's first party and second party titles, however, there are far more than 1,500 people working on the titles today.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some quotes there from the main men themselves that they're trying to learn from their mistakes with the GameCube and go forth with that.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I applaud Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just think it's good business sense.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what any business needs to progress is learn from their mistakes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and you can't just assume that the business is going to be there no matter what, and I will not...
[SPEAKER_11]: Name any companies here who seem to be guilty of making that mistake recently, but it's four letters, starts with an S, ends with Oni.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speaking of progressive thinking, the brand new MacBook, basically running off of some really crappy integrated graphics chip that
[SPEAKER_09]: It's unable to run most games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, fear not.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least you can use it sort of like the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: Using the accelerometer that's built into it, it's basically designed to detect if the computer is falling.
[SPEAKER_09]: you know stop the hard drive so that doesn't you know ruin any of your data well a clever gamer has actually used this program called the AMS 2 HID which is used with this program Neverball to basically make the modern-day equivalent of a wooden labyrinth so by tilting your computer you can use it to control games
[SPEAKER_09]: Crappy games, yes, but you can control games.
[SPEAKER_11]: I knew you would not be able to get through that story without taking a swing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, it can't run anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: It says right in the article here.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's using basically this integrated graphics chip that's designed by Apple, and it doesn't run anything because it's not ATI or NVIDIA compliant.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I'm sorry, StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_09]: A.T.I.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chip in this one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I do think it's a silly idea, but, you know, whatever, some guy's bored and wants to do, you know, Labyrinth, whatever, but I don't really see it being the next trend in gaming.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is more one of those, you know, isn't that funny stories to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, I mean, if you, it's just like, was it, like that stupid game that they had with, um,
[SPEAKER_09]: Windows 98, that bumper car game thing that came with.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that sucked too.
[SPEAKER_09]: None of the games made by Microsoft or Apple that come with their systems.
[SPEAKER_09]: Granted, they're not supposed to be that great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just, they all suck.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, you can't really innovate on Solitaire.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kiss my ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chip's challenged with the shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Didn't come with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You had to buy it separately.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, we were talking about Wii-type technology there a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: But what is really coming to the Wii?
[SPEAKER_11]: Perhaps some new trademarks registered by Nintendo of Japan give some hints.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wii Culture was something that was recently trademarked by them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wii Pointer, which kind of sounds like it might be the name of what we've been calling the Wii Mode or the Rev Mode.
[SPEAKER_11]: What were you calling it, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_11]: I've always been calling it the Wii Mode.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Wii Con.
[SPEAKER_11]: You were calling it the Wii Con.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it sounds like the official name is probably going to be the Wii Pointer because I don't know what else that could be.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, they've registered Exclamation Point, Exclamation Point M. And you can actually look that up online if you want to see that trademark for yourself.
[SPEAKER_11]: It seems like...
[SPEAKER_11]: Exclamation, exclamation, M could be some type of instant messaging because that kind of looks like I am when you look at it.
[SPEAKER_11]: However, we don't know anything 100% for sure until the system actually comes out.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we shall see.
[SPEAKER_11]: But we like to speculate based on what's going on behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the instant messenger.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was that announced for sure?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I'm making that up.
[SPEAKER_01]: and Nintendo Maniac 64 is pointing out that it's way upside down.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, we figured that one out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, and that's a cutesy thing to do, which would make sense for Nintendo, but we'll find out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It could be, I guess, instant messaging, but who knows.
[SPEAKER_09]: One thing, though, that Nintendo does have in store, at least, is the fact that their controller actually vibrates, and it is wireless, so that's one step ahead of Sony.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, of course, Immersion says that they're wondering now if Nintendo copied them, and that there could possibly be a lawsuit against Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_09]: We know for a fact, of course, Microsoft actually licenses the Immersion technology or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't believe that they're the first company to think of rumbling controllers.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're basically going to keep a close eye on the Wii to see if the technology is the same and if they can make some money off of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: So what is it?
[SPEAKER_11]: We've got our eye on you.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got our eye on you.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're the only one who can get to work, so obviously you copied us.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, that's basically what it's, you know, backwards thinking.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm starting to wonder about these guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't like them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just because of this?
[SPEAKER_09]: I just don't like immersion.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_09]: You've got to tell me why.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why don't I like them?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because they're basically trying to profit off of all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Granted, they're trying to sue for... Why didn't they sue them back in the day when they had the Rumble Pack or something like that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Why didn't they sue back when the original PlayStation came out?
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Bullymania has an interesting perspective on this in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_09]: When capitalism no longer works, you sue.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting perspective.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Excuse me, I had a, uh, something caught in my throat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hairball?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, hairball.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, with as much hair as I managed to brush off the cat last night, I wouldn't be surprised.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, um, well, you know how Sony was saying, you know, the, uh,
[SPEAKER_01]: PS3 as a computer, the PS3 as a computer, blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I remember a story about this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you brought this up a couple weeks ago, yeah, about the computer thing with the PS3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, basically there was a, the UK Court of Appeals has said that the PlayStation 2 is not a computer.
[SPEAKER_01]: They basically pretty much laughed at Sony.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lord Justice C. Chadwick said that Sony's skeleton argument was, to quote, beyond what can be regarded as acceptable written advocacy.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, Sony got pwned.
[SPEAKER_11]: They got served.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: So what does this mean?
[SPEAKER_11]: Those tax breaks they were looking forward to may not happen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_01]: The UK Court of Appeals also denied Sony any right to bring the case to the European Court of Justice.
[SPEAKER_09]: The other thing they should note is it doesn't matter anyways if the PS3 is considered a computer or not because those taxes on electronics are gone now.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it wouldn't matter if it's categorized as a
[SPEAKER_09]: Game console, has a PC, has a vibrator, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's still going to be taxed for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think any way to make more money, it seems like nowadays, it's just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very desperate.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very crazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Crazy like Kojima and his comparisons to steak.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, what may I be talking about?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, actually...
[SPEAKER_09]: PS3, PS4, PS5
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, of course, for the 360, if they want a great steak dinner, a great steak with their family, a little bit more casual during the weekends, they might select the 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't understand how these comparisons of steak work, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, of course, then to the Wii, why not have a great steak at your house every day, and then you might choose the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: Does that make any sense to you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it doesn't make any sense to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, usually it's the eccentric people that are making these comparisons to food and other things that, I don't know, it's a very strange comparison to be making.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then he was talking about movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: PlayStation 3 is like a movie theater for people who want to see this movie on a big screen with THX and 5.1 audio, even if they have to pay a high price.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whereas the 360...
[SPEAKER_09]: The 360 is like a DVD.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically, you don't know what movie you want to see, so you go to the store and see if you can pick up a good one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then the Wii is like a TV for when you're at home.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't know what you want to watch, but you want to have that variety.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, one of the best people I got to meet at E3, Igarashi Koji, is actually...
[SPEAKER_01]: I made some comments about the Playstation 3 at E3 and he's quoted as saying maybe it's too expensive but he did actually have an interview with Game Informer
[SPEAKER_01]: Talking about Microsoft, he said he wasn't really negative about Microsoft, but to quote, for some reason they tend to back off a little when it comes to something really foreign.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if Japanese developers would say they're working on Final Fantasy or Dragon Quest or Metal Gear maybe, then I guess Japanese consumers would take it seriously and consider purchasing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's also stated that as far as the New Castlevania game is going for Portrait of Ruin, the next installment after Dawn of Sorrow, it might feature unlockable co-op missions to be played over Wi-Fi, but that's not confirmed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, he's quoted as saying it's not confirmed because he hasn't started working on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So he's thinking that it would be something unlockable.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was also mentioned that basically there's going to be the two-screen display for Portrait of Ruin, again for the DS, different collectible items in there, but it's not stated whether or not it's going to be skills and items rather than souls.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's what I had to say, but there was the potential about...
[SPEAKER_01]: and possibly working on the PlayStation 3 and the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll still come up in that interview.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure many folks would be very much looking forward to a Castlevania on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just loved his reaction.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Perhaps it's a bit too expensive.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, another game that people are really looking forward to is Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_11]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_11]: And there's a new rumor floating around.
[SPEAKER_11]: It started at GoNintendo.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Ubisoft is going to be getting into the game there with some of their characters.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you think about what that would bring to the table, that could be Jade from Beyond Good and Evil, Rayman, Sam Fisher, which would be an interesting counterpart to Solid Snake if you think about it, and the Prince from Prince of Persia, which I think probably from that list, Rayman and the Prince would seem most likely, especially Rayman.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be an interesting addition.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I could see that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that was developer Mashihiro Sakurai saying that other third-party characters would be a definite possibility.
[SPEAKER_11]: And GoNintendo.com, I suppose, is speculating that Ubisoft is possibly the other third party being involved there.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what would be cool, though, if they did it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Since they're releasing Rayman's Raving Rabbits, have the rabbits as one of the characters.
[SPEAKER_09]: You just want to kill bunnies.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just think they're funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: You just want to murder bunnies.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know how you are.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cute animals need to die.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: And of course, every time we bring up Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_11]: Brawl, folks in the chatroom start talking about what characters they want to see in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yuri Lever talking about Katamari.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be an interesting third-party thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the only thing about that is they've said that it hasn't been on the system already, so probably not.
[SPEAKER_11]: PooEater says the Jet Set guy, he could spray your face, but again, also not on any Nintendo system.
[SPEAKER_11]: I still say Sonica.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think Sonic and Bonk are actually the ones I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, that's a good point, especially with the recent Genesis and TurboGrafx love, thanks to the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a brilliant idea.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope it happens.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, anyway, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_11]: We get letters once in a while, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, they send them to mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Real quick last thought, sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nestor and Howard.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a little too old school for most people, I think.
[SPEAKER_11]: I remember Nestor and Howard.
[SPEAKER_01]: Especially the Mega Man one that went on for like three issues.
[SPEAKER_01]: That one was great.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do we ever get emails about Nestor and Howard?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: We should.
[SPEAKER_11]: People should email us their favorite memories.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, DarkSakura, tell us about what they're emailing us about at MailbagAtOrangeLawnTrader.com this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Our listeners are very emo.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, I'm going to start from the beginning.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got one from DJ Ratchet, who's been on our boards for quite a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just to go ahead and read this.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been behind on your podcast and I've been listening to a few of the slightly older episodes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a few responses to some of the things said.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number one, congrats on Loki for getting married, even though everyone said it a hundred times.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not just OLR with the Sony hate.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty much every other podcast I've listened to has nothing but bad things to say about Sony.
[SPEAKER_01]: At least you guys are trying to be fair.
[SPEAKER_01]: Others are being real fanboyish about the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm one of the suckers who are going to get a PS3 though.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm trying, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm really trying to be devil's advocate when it comes to Sony, but...
[SPEAKER_11]: Guys, it's tough.
[SPEAKER_11]: And even the Sony fanboys have to recognize right now the odds are not in your favor.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: The system is only as good as the games on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: E3 was not a good setup for Sony fanboys.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll do what we can the rest of the year.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe Sony will throw us a few frickin' bones before Christmas, or the launch of the system, really.
[SPEAKER_01]: They had cool commercials, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I guess there's something.
[SPEAKER_11]: If they get Castlevania, that's a huge plus.
[SPEAKER_01]: To return to the email.
[SPEAKER_01]: Harmonix does need to make another Amplitude frequency game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm still hooked to those games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Guitar Hero looks like Amplitude with a guitar peripheral and nothing else.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the reason I have not bought Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_01]: Quick question.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is Space Channel 5 Special Edition for the PS2 a straight port of the Dreamcast version?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm considering buying it.
[SPEAKER_01]: To answer the question, actually it's both.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's Space Channel 5 2 and the Dreamcast 1.
[SPEAKER_01]: I own it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have not played it yet because I have the Japanese Space Channel 5 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, another thing that he wanted to add is that his mother, who knows nothing about video games, thinks that the Blu-ray is the biggest ripoff in the world.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, the players are like, I don't know, $700 or something, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, that was something I saw this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: I saw an HD DVD player in action at Best Buy or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Not ready to drop $1,000 on it, that's for sure.
$600?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Honestly, $360 if they're going to release that, they're going to have to do it like $200 at most for that player for me to be interested in it because the picture quality is not that much better.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if Blu-ray is only supposed to look that good, I am not impressed with the technology at this time.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just don't think there's going to be... It's not that huge of an improvement over...
[SPEAKER_01]: We have another email from Mark from Australia.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a very interesting email.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go ahead and read this out loud.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've just finished listening to episode 187 and once again I hear you guys defending violent content in video games.
[SPEAKER_01]: It seems to be a topic that is forever raising its ugly head in almost every single show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, although I'm a gamer and particularly love violent content in the games I play, I find your arguments always seem to be one-sided.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've never heard anyone from Orange Lounge Radio seriously and intelligently consider whether it's bad for kids, or more so, if it's bad for adults.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously, can simulated killing really be good for your head?
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki asks the question, what's worse, simulated killing or killing a deer?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sure Loki has no idea about the answer to this question, but proceeds to speak in a high-pitched voice mimicking the mothers of the affected kids.
[SPEAKER_01]: His only objective is to try to offend them.
[SPEAKER_01]: If he calmed down and put some thought into his answers, he might seem credible.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually responded to him and in my email I said that the viewpoint we've been coming from is more on the rebuttal standpoint where we're given a limited scope of what to defend.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, we have all these people and I honestly think that the ones that are saying, you know, ban it, ban it, ban it, are...
[SPEAKER_01]: Very one-sided, very, you know, not willing to put a lot of thought into it.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I fully agree.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I've actually said this in the past.
[SPEAKER_01]: I said it today.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, there is a certain age where you have to be careful with what you expose your children to.
[SPEAKER_01]: But any, I should say, mature adult, any person who's above a certain age and has a certain ability to tell reality from...
[SPEAKER_01]: Fantasy would be able to intelligently know the difference between picking up your controller and killing a bunch of pixels or 3D rendered models than taking an Uzi and blowing away your school.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that an intelligent, sane human being would be able to tell the difference.
[SPEAKER_11]: I absolutely agree with that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think the listener who wrote us an email said,
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: To play this game that I'm going to buy for them with my money.
[SPEAKER_11]: And certainly there are some games that some children should not be playing.
[SPEAKER_11]: But that's really up to the parent to make the decision there.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's kind of just my thoughts on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, do you have anything you want to say about the mom impressions or whatever?
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty, any idiot can tell you that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, if I kill, you know, a virtual hooker, I guess, it's not a real person.
[SPEAKER_09]: They don't have feelings.
[SPEAKER_09]: Their family's not going to worry about, you know, they're not going to be all upset if I kill her.
[SPEAKER_09]: She just respawns later and I go kill her again.
[SPEAKER_09]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whereas, you know, if I go kill, you know, my next door neighbor, that's a little different.
[SPEAKER_09]: More people are impacted by that.
[SPEAKER_09]: So how can you say that I'm wrong in saying that killing a virtual person is
[SPEAKER_09]: No where near to the effect of killing something real.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even if it's not a human person, say you kill
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, an animal or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, kids are brought up knowing that animals are cute and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you take them out into the wilderness without obviously educating them and stuff, and you go and blow away Bambi, I mean, that's going to be a little, you know, that's going to probably shock them more than saying, killing virtual, you know, prostitute Betty.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: And also, you know, speaking of that, you know, what's worse, going out and killing a deer for the sport of it or killing a deer because you're hungry and you need food?
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, that there's, I think everything is situational, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: Or what about, say someone has broken into your house and has a gun at your head, I'm going to shoot them, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't care, I will do what it takes to defend my house.
[SPEAKER_01]: If they are in my property, and they're threatening to kill me, hell yeah, I would strike out at them.
[SPEAKER_11]: It seems to be going a little into the what ifs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Firebomber was pointing out that I'm at Ted Nugent's level.
[SPEAKER_01]: I killed deers in Deer Hunter 3
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for the email.
[SPEAKER_11]: We like thought-provoking, intelligently written emails.
[SPEAKER_01]: In a year, I'm planning on having a sproutlet.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm planning on breeding.
[SPEAKER_11]: A spawn.
[SPEAKER_01]: A spawn of Jamie.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, I'm not going to have my little kid going out and playing Halo when he's three or four.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, when I'm sure that my kid understands the difference between reality and fantasy, then I wouldn't mind if they're in there watching me play Halo as long as they understand the difference.
[SPEAKER_01]: If they start reenacting it, they get their butt popped and I tell them no.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: It is your responsibility to make sure that they learn how to be a proper adult.
[SPEAKER_01]: Childhood is what prepares you for being a grown-up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think you might get more letters from this one.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want more letters!
[SPEAKER_11]: As long as they're intelligently written, that's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, and have good grammar.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got an email from Cameron.
[SPEAKER_01]: saying, hey, I was wondering your thoughts on Banjo-Kazooie for DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rare is already porting Diddy Kong Racing from the 64 DS and EGM rumored that a Banjo-Kazooie game was also coming to DS as a port or new.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to know if you think it will happen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, do you think any Banjo-Kazooie games will make it to live arcade?
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you, thank you for the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: First of all, I won't make it to live arcade because...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, does Nintendo still have part of the rights on that?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, when it comes to Banjo-Kazooie, who technically owns that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Rare or Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_11]: Rare has it, then definitely, I don't think you'd see it on DS at all for that reason, but Xbox Live Arcade, definite possibility, but not for a long time.
[SPEAKER_11]: I honestly didn't like the Banjo-Kazooie series, so I haven't... Yeah, I gotta be honest, it wasn't really a series of games I played a whole lot of.
[SPEAKER_11]: Magus, you seem to be a little more up on the know on that, do you have any thoughts?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, no, I haven't played Banjo-Kazooie since it came out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, this listener's going to be very disappointed in our feedback on that one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, if it's rare, though, I think rare Microsoft's really where they're headed.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wouldn't...
[SPEAKER_11]: D.S.
[SPEAKER_11]: Diddy Kong
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow, I need more time to think about that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Worst experience at a video game store?
[SPEAKER_01]: I have to say it was EB before the games got merged.
[SPEAKER_01]: There were some really not knowledgeable people at a couple of the EVs I've been to.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've never had a problem at a GameStop, but then again, they all know me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you're kind of lucky in that regard.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, I would say, more recently, this is kind of a weak answer, but I didn't have a lot of time to think about this one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Walking into a gaming store time and time again, not being able to locate an Xbox 360 for many months, and kind of being laughed at when asking about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like, you know, come on, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Out of the... No, Julie was with me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I don't recall it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Julie was with me because we were picking up one before some convention and no one was coming.
[SPEAKER_01]: We asked people, oh, I don't know, I don't have a key, and they weren't finding anyone, but that was Walmart.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, do you have any stories?
[SPEAKER_11]: Or Magus, anybody?
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say... There was one time I was buying that memory card thing, kind of like a...
[SPEAKER_09]: Where you can rip memory card saves off of like a Playstation card
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, like a dextro, but not as a third-party thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And... The guy was acting stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't remember what he was doing.
[SPEAKER_09]: He was acting really retarded.
[SPEAKER_09]: But then there was another time I was trying to buy a PSP at launch.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's like, good luck finding one!
[SPEAKER_09]: Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_09]: It went to Best Buy, and there was like a ton of them sitting there.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I remember, like I said last week, I overheard in one of the GameStops that they don't even...
[SPEAKER_09]: inform their employees on what games are coming out and what the games are.
[SPEAKER_09]: They basically are told to read the Game Informer magazine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which, that's stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: Eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Magus?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mine's more of a general thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just, okay, tip to GameStop, EB Games, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your employees...
[SPEAKER_08]: are selling games.
[SPEAKER_08]: They should know something about the games they're selling.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you have a person that's completely clueless, you don't employ them or you have them learn first, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: From what I understand from GameStop employees I've talked to, at least that chain, GameStop, has a policy where they can get magazines for free to read up on what's going on.
[SPEAKER_11]: How many employees take advantage of that or whether they're encouraged to, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't worked there.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I do know at least they have that policy, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm probably going to have to second the issue with employees mocking customers who didn't pre-order their product and then are surprised that it's not in stock.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we know we can't always pre-order things, but you don't have to get in our face for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Honestly, I think that
[SPEAKER_01]: If you know something's going to be hard to get and you want to make sure you have your copy, freaking pre-order it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's $5 out of your pocket, and if it turns out it's something that you don't want, you can move it to something else.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not hard.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't agree.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't pre-order games, and I don't like that kind of commitment, and I feel like it's almost like I don't want to commit that I'm going to buy.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're not committing that you're buying it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's $60.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're not committing... $60, that's a hell of a commitment.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're not...
[SPEAKER_01]: For a game, it's $5.
[SPEAKER_09]: For a game, it's $5.
[SPEAKER_09]: What about a game system?
[SPEAKER_09]: Games are easy to come by.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if you don't want it, you can get your money back.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not that hard.
[SPEAKER_11]: I feel like those stores try to force me into it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't like being told I have to do something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nobody does.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, I pre-ordered my Xbox 360 system about...
[SPEAKER_01]: And do you think that they're responsible for Microsoft's error?
[SPEAKER_09]: They did take the number of pre-orders that they thought they were getting systems and then Microsoft screwed them over.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, that's called stupid customer That's called the customer is a lazy ass
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's up to the retailer to inform their customers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Inform them exactly the source.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, they had shortages before with the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: If they knew that this was going to be a typical problem, they could say, you know what...
[SPEAKER_01]: How is what one company do illustrate what another company is going to do?
[SPEAKER_01]: Please answer that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tell me exactly how is the behavior of a completely different entity going to explain how another completely different entity is going to perform.
[SPEAKER_09]: The companies operate in a similar fashion as far as hardware launches.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, Microsoft doesn't have to deal with having their orders come from basically a foreign source.
[SPEAKER_01]: Microsoft is all located this side of the country.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anything that Sony does has to have approval from Sony of Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, Microsoft Systems, I believe, were being manufactured in foreign countries.
[SPEAKER_01]: It doesn't matter where it's manufactured.
[SPEAKER_01]: It matters where the business decisions are being made.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, to go on to the next email.
[SPEAKER_01]: We also have one from Ricky.
[SPEAKER_01]: It says, one of our 15-year-old listeners...
[SPEAKER_01]: says he's been listening to our show for the past two years and he's quite impressed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's get to the point is what it says.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, I was browsing around on the net and I stumbled across a gif which happened to be someone's avatar for a certain forum from the image of this year's E3.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was Ken Kutaragi.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, he did spell it right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kudos to you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mouthing his mouth to the phrase Ridge Racer and it kept playing the words back and forth.
[SPEAKER_01]: He recognized a face in this
[SPEAKER_01]: It says that none other... It actually said it was Rob in this GIF.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I've actually... You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Somebody posted something similar in our forums that supposedly there's some reaction shot of me at some press conference.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's the thing, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not me.
[SPEAKER_11]: At least the picture I saw wasn't me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess... I didn't even think the guy looked like me, but...
[SPEAKER_11]: I tried going into the mailbag and looking at it and there was no GIF image attached so I would ask that listener to try resending it but just so you know when the Sony press conference was going on we were not there we were not at any of the big three press conferences I wish we were that popular amongst them
[SPEAKER_11]: But unfortunately, not all those companies have embraced podcasting yet, with the exception of Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_11]: But of course, you know, Major Nelson works for them, so that's the podcast that's definitely going to be... Actually, I would say Microsoft a little more than the others, you know, even because I know some other friendly podcasts we know of went to that conference, so that's cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: But anyway, regardless, during the Sony Prep Conference, we were actually at the...
[SPEAKER_11]: Arena Lounge in Santa Monica watching it on the big screen TV on a live feed and nobody was taking pictures of our reaction shots.
[SPEAKER_11]: And really, I didn't have a problem with Sony's conference until the very end, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then kind of sitting back and reflecting on it, it just kind of got worse.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I really don't think that picture's me because I don't know where it came from.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like eating bad McDonald's.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was bad to begin with and then it just kind of festers in your stomach.
[SPEAKER_11]: And also, I spent most of E3 hanging out with either Loki, DarkSakura, or Bobby from All Games.
[SPEAKER_11]: So if you don't see them in the picture either, it's probably not me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, we got an email and I'm using this as an example.
[SPEAKER_01]: Someone sent us an email that consists of only, Hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't send me emails that just say, Hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because what I'm going to do in the future when I see emails like this is I'm going to delete it and keep a list of your name.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, hi back, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: I appreciate you taking the time to send such a thoughtful and well-written email.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not mentioning the person's name on.
[SPEAKER_01]: They also didn't put a subject in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: All they wrote was, Hi.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know now we're going to get like 30 emails this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just say hi, hi, hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: And what I will do is on our form, I will post their email address.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that we can sign them up for some porn filters.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think you really need it by posting them to the forum and probably just do that automatically with all those bots out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, there is that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Any other emails besides the hi mail?
[SPEAKER_01]: Just the ones that worship me as their goddess.
[SPEAKER_01]: Those I usually just send to my personal email.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, all one of those emails.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_01]: You can shut the hell up right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Meg has got a total zing there.
[SPEAKER_11]: You sent yourself.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is bull.
[SPEAKER_01]: My husband sent them.
[SPEAKER_11]: DMM, I need some ATH points for Magus.
[SPEAKER_11]: A good five points for him, please.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: You need to... I think he's upgraded from toilet paper to a cardboard box for his joke book.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, we've got to keep it moving here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Again, if you have emails, mail back at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: During the break here, live only, we were talking about some gaming pieces that were in the media recently.
[SPEAKER_11]: One piece we were saving here for Part B was
[SPEAKER_11]: Nightline.
[SPEAKER_11]: Basically what happened is that Nightline recently did this story here talking about
[SPEAKER_11]: The Pentagon, and how kind of dumb they looked when they mistook a bit of Mashima for a terrorist training tool and showed it to the House Intelligence Committee.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tapper basically said this, terrorists twisting an American video game into a jihadist training tool, and then proceeds to lay out how the whole thing happened, including getting an anonymous interview with a European gamer who created the now infamous terrorist battlefield clip.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Pentagon is still claiming that the Moshima is being used by terrorists.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tapper is calling bullshit on this excuse and tells the Pentagon so, basically.
[SPEAKER_11]: And there's a quote here, We should really be questioning the kind of advice that Congress is getting.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that comes from Georgia Tech Ian Boggist, who's in the piece.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a parody of Team America World Police.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what the Machimo is.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was interesting, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stupid intelligence.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, um, kind of unrelated to that whole thing, the Frag Dolls and the PMS Clan, they're boycotting the World Series of Video Gaming Girl Love, I guess, contest or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're doing some pageant contest that has to do with the World Series of Video Games.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Miss...
[SPEAKER_09]: WSVG Contest
[SPEAKER_09]: PMS Amber Dalton Courier Journal
[SPEAKER_09]: and basically, I don't know, one of the funny things I keep seeing back is the, like for example, the World Series of Video Gaming they shot back with.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Frag Dolls and PMS Clan have stated that they plan to run the Mr. WSVG competition in the Taurus Next Stop in Dallas.
[SPEAKER_09]: If this happens, in order to be fair, the World Series of Video Gaming may feel compelled to run another beauty contest as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: and then of course other gamers who have been reading this are saying, well, those two clans suck anyways as far as gaming goes.
[SPEAKER_09]: They don't even compete on a professional level.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I thought that was funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't really know enough about those clans to pass judgment on it, so I'm just going to refrain from commenting, although I would love to have a representative on the program at some point to kind of give their perspective.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know that they've been giving a lot of shit online about how many I think the PMS clan specifically they have their gamer cards linked on Xbox.com and I think like most of them have under 1k points except one girl's got a ton
[SPEAKER_11]: But then they say, well that's because we're playing Halo 2 and you don't get points for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, they have Halo 2, but the other thing I thought was funny was... And with all respect to them, because again, I don't know them, it does seem interesting though, they are linked from Xbox.com, wouldn't you, knowing that, want to buff up the 360 games?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know they play Halo 2 a lot, granted, and one of the funny things I was reading is that they're actually coming out with...
[SPEAKER_09]: Their casual gaming portion of the clan.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there's going to be some experts at Uno or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I'm all for a casual game.
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't have to be hardcore all the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just thought that was funny though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you going to be entering the Hotman competition, Loki?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think you should be in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it would be funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you know they're going to get all these male models.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, here's the problem, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Loki should be up there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's the problem, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's in Dallas.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's also... They're a ways away.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chat room?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think we should have someone go in there in an asbestos suit and set themselves on fire.
[SPEAKER_11]: Chat room?
[SPEAKER_11]: Who would like to contribute to a Send Loki to Dallas fund?
[SPEAKER_09]: You'd win, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our other sales branch is in Dallas.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: You need to take a work trip.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, the whole argument with the fact that they don't have a lot of game points doesn't really count with me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, I mean, if you're playing a lot of multiplayer games and stuff, not a lot of points may be coming from that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Especially if you're not playing, like, you know, which, although, although, the PMS clan, I think it was the PMS clan, I can't remember which one's sponsored by Ubisoft, they have, they better be, you know, have a high achievement.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have nothing against female clans.
[SPEAKER_09]: Especially if they're competing out there, great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just
[SPEAKER_09]: Great.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, just don't, you know, make it sound like you're the best people in the world.
[SPEAKER_01]: We need to have, like, the O.L.
[SPEAKER_01]: Army as a gaming clan.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except they suck.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have a lot of girls that listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_01]: For just various games.
[SPEAKER_11]: That aren't your supermodel girl types that Microsoft would want to flaunt about at their booth or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's just fine by me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like my girls normal.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not that I date girls, but I like socializing with normal girls.
[SPEAKER_11]: I say we form a clan and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Send some emails.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you're interested, send emails to mailbag at orangezonesradio.com It's not just women.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can have a clan on Chromehounds.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to be the multi-game clan.
[SPEAKER_01]: The OL Army.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to have actual clans in Chromehounds.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can have the OL Army.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, anyway, let's move on here.
[SPEAKER_11]: We got to get to the story about the PSP.
[SPEAKER_11]: into PSP friendly formats.
[SPEAKER_11]: By the way, you can also convert it for iPod or Trio.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's only going to cost $25 for that functionality, which, by the way, you can find utilities on the internet to do it for free, but okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to be a legal and blessed thing from TiVo, so it's kind of interesting because now the PSP can kind of have that
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, put your TiVo programs here on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_11]: That might be something to sell the PSP and certainly make it more competitive with the iPod, even though, I don't know, iPod and PSP are so different anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: But for some people, when it's one or the other, that might be something that kind of, you know, makes the PSP look a little more alluring too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's just that they're going to be planning on doing this anyways with the whole PS3 and their, you know, was it their wireless streaming system that they've got there?
[SPEAKER_09]: Johnny Depp is doing his, uh, lending his voice talent to the game for Captain Jack Sparrow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that game I thought was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, it had all kinds of little hidden stuff thrown in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, what I did notice, you know, remember though that they didn't have a dude in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why is the name suddenly escaping me?
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: Johnny Depp, thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orlando Bloom?
[SPEAKER_01]: Orlando Bloom, thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: He isn't.
[SPEAKER_01]: They actually got a voice, a similar voice to it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But there's a...
[SPEAKER_01]: Quote on here from Johnny Depp said, Doing voiceovers is a great fun and a lot easier than stumbling about pretending to be Keith Richards or having scissors glued to your fingers all day.
[SPEAKER_01]: He did not add.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, all things considered, the game looked decent.
[SPEAKER_01]: That wasn't a quote, by the way.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It looked...
[SPEAKER_11]: Your typical movie to game translation, but they didn't fuck it up.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the Charlie and the Chocolate Factory games, they didn't fuck it up.
[SPEAKER_11]: It looked pretty solid.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think the Johnny Depp quotient is going to sell a lot more of this title.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it was a smart clinching there to get the game on board.
[SPEAKER_01]: This announcement here is from Eurogamer, so I love the jokes they're putting in here.
[SPEAKER_01]: For example, they said, why are pirates called pirates?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because they are.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's so bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, as far as Xbox Live, there's going to be some demos coming soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: The first one, of course, which should have come out by now but hasn't, Prey, is supposed to be hitting Xbox Live Arcade, or Xbox Live's Marketplace, pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you can't wait, though, and you have a decent enough PC, you can actually download the PC demo for free on a lot of the major gaming sites, so definitely check that out.
[SPEAKER_09]: The other demo is also slated for August 1st,
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: All over and tries to find the website that you need to be looking at this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: So DarkSakura, where should kids be pointing their browsers this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: This is a site that I spend quite a bit of time on and it's not actually just because I also moderate there.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's Gorilla Zone Official.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was a big fan of this site before I was asked on as one of the moderators there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, this site
[SPEAKER_01]: I have to say, 2J, he's so amazing with how quickly he gets the updates up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Any new information that he has up on there, they're linked through LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you add Gorillas News to your LiveJournal feed, it goes directly off GorillasUnofficial.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's actually Gorillas-Unofficial.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: The forums there are great, well-maintained.
[SPEAKER_01]: Again, not just because I'm also working there, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: But everybody there is just really terrific.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're not just that, but if you go into the site, actually on the splash page there's new art features by people in the fan art community.
[SPEAKER_01]: You'll see something different every time.
[SPEAKER_01]: On top of that, this has probably, I'd say, one of the most complete lyrics, image, discography, everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: And there's even a translation on here by my friend Haruna, who translated what Noodle said on the Apex tapes back when she was only speaking Japanese.
[SPEAKER_01]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very cool site.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been impressed with them from day one.
[SPEAKER_11]: But what if I don't like gorillas?
[SPEAKER_11]: Then screw you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then why don't you?
[SPEAKER_01]: What's wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_11]: I like gorillas just fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know I love to be devil's advocate though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't really want to comment on that game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, what's kind of interesting is they described the brand new damage system in Forza 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is all coming from the latest issue of the 360 Magazine, including that it took six months to create.
[SPEAKER_09]: Three damage settings will be available in the game, low, normal, and simulation, for those who don't want to...
[SPEAKER_09]: They joke.
[SPEAKER_09]: Reenact the great Gizmondo Ferrari crash.
[SPEAKER_09]: For photo and TV modes, they're actually collaborating with the Project Gotham development team, Bizarre Creations.
[SPEAKER_09]: So they're going to have something similar to Forza TV, very similar to Gotham TV that was in Project Gotham Racing 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: And of course, better AI, better graphics, downloadable content, yadda yadda yadda yadda.
[SPEAKER_11]: Blizzard's got some new ideas for World of Warcraft
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, really.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, they're preparing a new transfer system that will let World of Warcraft players move their characters to less polluted realms for a $25 fee.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're basically wanting to offer these services for convenience as opposed to encouraging people to spread out through the realms.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, the alternative is just to re-roll in completely new characters, so it's not much of a decision there.
[SPEAKER_01]: There will be restrictions on realm transfers.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can only bring a character once every six months, and once you've transferred, you can't take them back.
[SPEAKER_01]: The character has to be at least level 10.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's the amount of cash you can bring with you, 300 gold for levels 10 through 30, 1,000 for 31 through 50, and 5,000 through 51 and above.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can only transfer to realms of the same type.
[SPEAKER_01]: PvP, PvE, I guess roleplay ones too.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're also talking about Cross Realm Battlegrounds feature that's coming in with Patch 1.12.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: It will link Altric Valley, Warsong Gulch, and Arathi Basin so you can fight with players from other realms.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hopefully they don't link the fucking Looking for Group channel across multiple servers.
[SPEAKER_11]: LFG, WSG...
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, okay, devil's advocate here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay, so we can have our blue bee groups trashed by tier three, no matter where they are.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, what are the odds, you figure, of Cross Realm Battlegrounds having, okay, you have this basic pickup group, unskilled players facing completely organized over voice chat people are just going to roll straight over them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Same rule on Ragnarok, you know, if you don't wanna, you know, you don't do War of Imperium if you're level 10.
[SPEAKER_08]: Step up or ship out, bitch!
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a big gap between raiders and non-raiders, and you see that a lot on the forums.
[SPEAKER_08]: The people who do the big raid instances do better in PvP.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not much a matter of skill.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think they should call it World of Warcraft Hardcore Edition.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is for the hardcore.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, Patch 1.12 is going to bring in a new type of world PvP.
[SPEAKER_01]: You will see Horde and Alliance players trying to gain control of strategic positions.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Rogues will get a talent review.
[SPEAKER_08]: To this I say it's about damn time on both counts.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rogues have needed a talent change for a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: They just need some tweaks.
[SPEAKER_08]: And world PvP, because of Battlegrounds, because...
[SPEAKER_08]: are actually objectives in Battlegrounds has effectively killed off world PvP.
[SPEAKER_08]: So both of those need a revamp.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm glad they're getting them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Going back to the price for a minute for character transfer, I think $25 is fair, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: I do agree.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because it makes sure that people really want to do it and it's not just people taking advantage of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because even if it was $5, I think $25 means that it's only people who really want to be with their friends and really want to do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because otherwise...
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_11]: What are you doing over there, Loki?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Searching for Porn.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm trying to get my program newsletcher to work because it's not.
[SPEAKER_09]: It wants me to buy it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, although if you don't want to buy stuff and you want to save some money, well, you're still going to have to buy stuff, but
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: www.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_11]: and just kind of our reasonings why we're doing it.
[SPEAKER_11]: First off, we here at Orange Launch Radio do not like to edit the show unless we absolutely have to.
[SPEAKER_11]: We would never edit out someone's opinion on anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: The only thing we edit out are complete fuck-ups like, you know, we forget to start the show right or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: The story's not up that we need or what have you.
[SPEAKER_11]: and now though we're going to start editing out Skype calls that are not up to a certain quality standard and we don't want to scare you guys off from calling in.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's not what we're trying to do.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're never going to censor your opinions but the problem is just based on some feedback that we're getting from folks that are listening to the show and posting on the forums and talking to friends is that
[SPEAKER_11]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: www.darksakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: And you can actually call in and leave us a voicemail And actually, what I'd like to know your opinions on this week for the voicemail We're going to start making this a regular segment I would really like to hear your voicemails later Actually, I'll give you the topic after the Skype calls Because then otherwise people want to call in and talk about it But we're going to have like a weekly topic to call in about So anyway, let's go to the phone's Skype line and see what you guys have to say
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can you hear me now?
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course I can hear you.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's up, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_11]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_11]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_07]: I finally recovered from Anime Next last weekend.
[SPEAKER_11]: From Anime Next?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was that?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was fun, but there was a lot of drama with the game room, but I'll save that for later.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, no, I want to hear it.
[SPEAKER_11]: What was the drama in the game room?
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you heard of Desktop Arcade?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: They were banned from Anime Next
[SPEAKER_07]: It seems that somebody stole their passes from last year, photocopied them, and went into the game room.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it seems that the guy who runs the game room, Kevin, who's also known as Assembler, who owns Assembler.org, basically blacklisted them from the con.
[SPEAKER_07]: And whenever you mention it on the forums about why they weren't there, he will go in and edit your post and delete it as if it never existed.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a little weird.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's almost a little too hardcore.
[SPEAKER_11]: They didn't post anything like why they're gone or whatever?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every time you ask them why or whatever, your post is deleted.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's freaky.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's like a KGB thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I came very close to getting banned on the forums, but I stopped.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because if I got banned, I know senior staffs that would probably have his head on a fucking platter.
[SPEAKER_11]: Should we make a call to Desktop Arcade, get one of them on the show, try to get their side of the story?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: I can arrange that.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Open invite.
[SPEAKER_11]: You tell them we want them.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'd love to hear it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wouldn't you guys?
[SPEAKER_11]: I see heads.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, sorry buddy, what else is going on in Anime Next?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was hot as hell, but luckily my hotel was like 15 feet away from the expo center.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was huge, it was great.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only thing that really sucked was the acoustics.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hmm, what was wrong with the acoustics?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just, you know, hard to hear things and sound bouncing everywhere or what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, think of it as like a giant warehouse and they were dividing everything with these heavy curtains.
[SPEAKER_11]: What kind of cool video game related things did you see there?
[SPEAKER_11]: I know it's a lot of anime, but since we're a gaming show, what kind of cool video game things did you see there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not too much, because I went into the game room, the funk just hit me and I passed out.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I did go into the dealer's room and I did see some DS lights on imports, white PSPs, and I saw a lot of import games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ronma, I was actually hanging out with my friend Julie yesterday and she's going to Anime Expo this year.
[SPEAKER_01]: The only reason I see to go there this year is because Clamp's there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I want to go, but my wizard costume's not done.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, she's talking about buying some of those miniature bottles of Febreze to go around spraying the fanboy funk.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: It is important that you bathe on a regular basis, that you use soap to clean the germs off your body, and that you use something like deodorant, cologne, I don't know, something to make sure that you're going to smell unoffensive when you're in a room tightly packed, especially a hot room, as Ranma's telling us his con was pretty hot, around all these people.
[SPEAKER_11]: So please, don't give gamers a bad name, such as these folks at Anime Next, that were stinking up the room.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bathe regularly, and you know,
[SPEAKER_11]: Bring the smell of flowers into gaming rooms everywhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go on, go on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually met somebody at Anime Expo a few years ago who actually was one of those I'm going to sleep in the lobby of the hotel or in the movie room type people.
[SPEAKER_01]: Only he actually would go into the men's room and clean himself at the sink.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bandit in the chat room has the best idea ever for a cosplay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Someone should dress up as a big bottle of Febreze.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's one for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: One anime con when they passed out their registration bags had little bars of soap in each of the bags.
[SPEAKER_07]: And don't you know the people got pissed off and offended.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would actually like to quote my friend Megzi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Herbo.
[SPEAKER_01]: Horrible otaku body odor.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why would you be offended at that?
[SPEAKER_11]: I look at it as a free gift.
[SPEAKER_11]: People fucking steal hotel soap all the time.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what I say the cons should do?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: They should have an anonymous shower room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take one of the hotel rooms, someone just stands there with a sheet.
[SPEAKER_07]: You go in, sign it, take your shower, and leave.
[SPEAKER_07]: 100% anonymous.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, anyway, we gotta wrap this up so we can get to another call.
[SPEAKER_11]: But any other thoughts on the cons or gaming or what have you?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was fun overall.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm gonna post a couple of links and that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first one's for Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ranma would have cosplay in full effect.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was a bunch of Ranma would have cosplays running around.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, thank you very much Ranma for the call.
[SPEAKER_11]: We appreciate it, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Sure, no problem.
[SPEAKER_11]: Later, buddy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Later.
[SPEAKER_11]: We always like it when he calls in.
[SPEAKER_11]: DMN, I need some ATH points to Bandit.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know it's your contest, but Bandit, come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was some points right there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go to another phone call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, Sky.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's RavensDolphin.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, RavensDolphin.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_11]: Phoenix Wright.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, I've kind of looked at this game a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have you just recently started playing this game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought it for a week and I found it in EB for $30 and it rocks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lucky you.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you like about Phoenix Wright?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I just like that the music is great.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you nail someone, it goes like, Objection!
[SPEAKER_05]: You did this!
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, wait.
[SPEAKER_11]: Miklatov just walked in the room, so I've got to put him on the spot here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Miklatov, you've been playing Phoenix Wright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I finished it.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you love so much about the game?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like playing Law and Order.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty much what I like.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really, really funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's so funny about it?
[SPEAKER_11]: There's nothing funny about Law.
[SPEAKER_03]: The writing is really hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the names they come up with for the characters, like Law to Heart and Somebody Von Karma.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forget his name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Manfred Von Karma and it was seriously he's the one with the evil voice right objection it's i couldn't put it down until i finished it i have all these other games i was playing too i was like i'm not taking this out of my ds it just seems to me like that game is an awful lot of reading though so what keeps this game kind of guy interesting yes raven's dolphin uh because it has a lot of reading i i read pretty well i don't i can't read a
[SPEAKER_11]: Mike Meekins You will find out once you play through it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mike Meekins
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm getting that launch day for this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta get it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, okay, Phoenix Wright 2, Justice for All.
[SPEAKER_11]: Megatop, tell us real quick, wait, before you go back, how does it work in Japan?
[SPEAKER_11]: There's the different games in Japan.
[SPEAKER_11]: How many are out in Japan, and what's been translated over here?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's three on Game Boy Advance, and then they're making a new one on DS4, and it doesn't have Phoenix Wright in it anymore, at least that we know of so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a different attorney this time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And...
[SPEAKER_03]: What's really cool is my coworker, she wasn't able to get the American one, but they just re-released the Japanese one in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it has a, well, of course they released it in Japan if it's Japanese.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you can toggle between English or Japanese in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you can't find it in America right now, you can go on an import site and just get that re-release of the Japanese one.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can still play it in English.
[SPEAKER_11]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Gravis Dolphin, any other thoughts there on Phoenix Riot or gaming in general?
[SPEAKER_05]: What was the worst game you ever played in your life?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can tell you mine.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was Deadly Towers for the Nest.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game was horrible.
[SPEAKER_11]: Worst game I've ever played in my life.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you remember Color Dreams, which was a company that played these games on the NES that were in those really colored cartridges?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Master Chu and the Drunk Nerd Who The NES version of X-Men Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_08]: That was awful!
[SPEAKER_08]: or most people would say... The Atari 2600 version of Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or E.T.
[SPEAKER_11]: E.T.
[SPEAKER_08]: was worse.
[SPEAKER_08]: Superman 64.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate to be trendy here and kind of saying what everybody else says, but honestly, dude, Wand of Gamelon, Zelda...
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really that bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm sure you can even download the movies on YouTube and that doesn't even begin just because the gameplay itself is horrible.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, what was Nintendo thinking letting these guys just poop on the Link franchise?
[SPEAKER_11]: These guys literally shit on Link.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, now that you're our guinea pig, go play Big Rigs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would rather not.
[SPEAKER_05]: They crapped on Mario 2?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mario's Hotel?
[SPEAKER_05]: That was horrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh god, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Ravenstaff and thanks for the question.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, there's another game that I thought was pretty awful.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Final Fantasy Mystic Quest.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wouldn't put it in worst game ever, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not worst game ever.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, it shouldn't have carried the Final Fantasy name because it was way too much of a child's game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: It fit the niche that it was designed for, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was an entry-level RPG.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right, but you're right.
[SPEAKER_11]: A, it shouldn't have been Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_11]: It shouldn't have been Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_11]: What I will give that game, though, is that it actually has a pretty kick-ass soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: All things considered.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, whoever did it, I know it was a female that did the music there, and I think she came over to, I could be wrong, but I think she made some of the music in 11.
[SPEAKER_11]: I might be wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't quote me on that.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's got a great soundtrack, Final Fantasy Mystic Quest.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, now that I think about it, Final Fantasy Mystic Quest would probably have fit in better had they called it a saga.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not Romancing Saga, but Saga.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's what I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because, honestly, it wasn't ever a Final Fantasy game.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's great, because all the other Saga games are shit.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, they're not!
[SPEAKER_01]: I hate you, Ben!
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't like the Saga games at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: Saga Frontier 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Saga 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't like Saga at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry, Romancing Saga 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Romancing Saga 3, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: But...
[SPEAKER_01]: Raven's Dolphin, Ping Pals
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that was horrible.
[SPEAKER_11]: I bought that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I bought two copies.
[SPEAKER_11]: I feel sorry because I know somebody gave it to me as a gift, but it really is a bad game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Play Burnout Legends on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll cry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, I've got to let you go, Ravensdoth.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've got to keep moving on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is way too long.
[SPEAKER_11]: Appreciate it, buddy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, he just hung up.
[SPEAKER_11]: We appreciate the call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, you're on Orange Lodge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the one and only Legend of Zaku Hi, Legend of Zaku, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, Coney Island just got Supernova last Friday, um, and it started to trickle, it started to trickle down on the east coast from what I'm hearing.
[SPEAKER_11]: So what are your impressions of DDR Supernova after playing it, which I imagine you have?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, from one, from one, from one thing, I, we seem to, we seem to agree that it might be a beta cab because after comparing it to the one in Jersey Gardens, which I happened to play, which was a location test, it was a lot of differences in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: First of all, certain songs were coming in very early.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, in other words, there was early timing on songs such as You're Not Here.
[SPEAKER_06]: The pads, you know, were really stiff, obviously, because they're brand new.
[SPEAKER_06]: Besides that, you know, a lot of things that are just, you know, just the fact that, not really, I'm trying to think right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just, we're not sure if this is it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, it looks to me like it's the same build that I played before.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, Zaku, thumbs up, thumbs down, thumbs middle?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so and so, I just hope Konami's playing the cards right, because if this is the final version, God help us all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just because of the early timings and stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, just because of the fact that it's harder to get perfects now, it's harder to get double A's, because the timing window's really tight now.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought people were bitching that DDR was too easy, all the In The Groove fans were bitching it was too easy.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but I think they OD'd on the timing window.
[SPEAKER_06]: At first it started to be too loose, and now it's starting to be too tight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it should have been right there in the middle.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Besides that... What's been the general, because I imagine these arcades are packed, what's the general fan consensus that you're picking up?
[SPEAKER_11]: Are people happy to see a new DDR game back in arcades?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or are people bitching on these little... They're not bitching, so to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: They just really don't know what to believe, whether or not they are betas or real.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the only way we're going to find that out is the second location in New York City when it's set up tomorrow, which is in Chinatown.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, we'll be eagerly awaiting a forum post letting us know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I'm going to link you to one right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to link you to a thread that actually shows the reaction from New Yorkers about the Supernova set up in Coney Island.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's in our chat room over at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't have time to read it right now because we're trying to do a show, but I'll check it out later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, just keep in mind that Konami's just fooling around with the whole release date thing, so I really don't know what to believe right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know whether, as I said, I don't know whether these are betas, or is this the final thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's up in the air right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: What else are people playing in New York City besides DDR?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just stuff in the groove and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that all people do in New York, just dance?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that all people do in New York is dance?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but they do other things like, you know, in Chinatown they play fighting games, but, you know, they have lives to live as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's something we do on the side.
[SPEAKER_11]: Zaka, we gotta let you go so we can wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Later.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I gotta let this call through.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: This is Bandit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, Bandit.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, you won points earlier, so I decided to take one more call because I saw it was you.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks, yeah, I appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_04]: He wasn't giving me points anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jerk.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll take him.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's his we.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just on the last call.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was complaining about the timing window.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing they did differently is they just made the marvelous timing the perfect timing now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Supposedly from the post I've been reading.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all they did.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, I mean...
[SPEAKER_11]: Bandit, I asked Zaku this, and I'll ask you this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Weren't most DDR players that went over to In The Groove or whatever claiming, and honestly, guys, just play both and enjoy both, but weren't people that went over to In The Groove kind of complaining that the difficulty was too easy on DDR, which is kind of why they wanted a harder game like In The Groove, and now that Konami's went and made the game harder, they're upset?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I've argued with so many people about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people went to ITG just because they thought there weren't going to be a new DDR coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then they complain about the difficulty in DDR, or not being hard enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not because of the grading, it's because of the actual step charts of the song that I keep getting people complaining to me about.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're always like, oh, this step chart's not hard enough, or this isn't like this and that, on in the groove, and they keep comparing it back and forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they got to remember, there wouldn't be any ITG without DDR first.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are harder step charts in DDR now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless they're AAAing everything, I don't want to hear any complaints.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to hear any of this stuff again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you live in an area where Supernova is on its way, or what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I live in Pittsburgh.
[SPEAKER_04]: We didn't get one yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's on its way, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, Bandit, thanks so much for calling in and giving your perspective on Supernova.
[SPEAKER_11]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright man, thanks for the points.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, no problem.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm getting razzed for that in the chat room now because apparently I've ruffled the panties of DMN and he's a little upset now because I was arguing with him whether you should have points or not and I should just keep my big fat opinion out of it and let him run his contest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just keep on leeching points for me, you bastard.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, Bandit, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, you guys do the same.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, I realize DMN does not have to be doing a contest.
[SPEAKER_11]: I am very grateful.
[SPEAKER_11]: He already knows that.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I still have to give him shit because that's what I do on this program is I give our chatters shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: But know that I do that because I love you very much.
[SPEAKER_11]: Last minute stories, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anything final you guys want to bring up?
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I do.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of my friends on LiveJournal linked this story on Kotaku.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a contest going on through July where if you buy a copy of Tetris during that time period and register the serial at Club Nintendo, you can choose to battle Utada Hikaru or get concert tickets.
[SPEAKER_01]: 30 people will be chosen to play against her and 504 pairs of tickets will be given out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, now the thing is, though, is that there's a video of her playing, and it's actually up on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_01]: She completely owns this guy.
[SPEAKER_01]: She plays really, really well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, you can either see the movie file up on Kotaku, or you can check it out, do a search on YouTube, but, yeah, she's really good at Tetris.
[SPEAKER_11]: DMN is putting out a challenge right there.
[SPEAKER_11]: He says, I'll fuck up Utada.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that's a Tetris DS challenge in the making right there.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's on.
[SPEAKER_11]: The gauntlet's been thrown down.
[SPEAKER_11]: Utada, if you're listening.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would love to play her because actually the thing I noticed, she plays Tetris the same way I do, which is build up for the four line and it keeps hopping up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Even them out to where you have the full four lines down the next one.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's exactly how I play Tetris.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that would be very fun, I think.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now that's a girl gamer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well done.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anything last minute?
[SPEAKER_09]: Anybody else?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, there was something interesting I should point out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was pointed out that 99 Nights, one of the things that happens to be on Microsoft's site, I believe, is showing the product info for 99 Nights.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's interesting because it says hard drive required.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of the things that I thought Microsoft was not going to do
[SPEAKER_09]: with their games is require you to have a hard drive.
[SPEAKER_09]: And such an anticipated game, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_09]: So all of those out there that don't have a hard drive, you're kind of fucked.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unless this pans out to be just a mistake or something, but that's pretty... Well, they had that one, was it Football Manager or something like that?
[SPEAKER_09]: They required the hard drive.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm thinking this is the way they're going.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why they're releasing the 256 megabyte card then is beyond me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just lower the price of the hard drive or release a larger hard drive.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, but it has hard drive required and hard drive enhanced is two of the things on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I thought that was interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anything else last minute, you guys?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was another thing also I had.
[SPEAKER_09]: Genesis Collection is coming to PlayStation 2 and the PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to have a collection of old Genesis games, 28 of them, and
[SPEAKER_09]: with the additional three being unlocked, including Shinobi 2, Sonic the Hedgehog, Golden Axe 1, 2, and 3, Virtual Fighter 2, Altered Beast, Echo the Dolphin, and Phantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rise from your grave.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, well, then I guess that's going to do it for tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're just about wrapped up here, but we want to go around first and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's been a long time.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you very much for your support of Orange Entree over the years and glad to see you're local and can drop by once in a while.
[SPEAKER_11]: Final thought?
[SPEAKER_08]: I got sex appeal because I dual wield.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to play this game Senko no Ronde for the 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like Einhander.
[SPEAKER_11]: And my final thought is Head Hurts must run Ice Cube.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ice Cube shampoo would be great right now for my sunburned head.
[SPEAKER_11]: For those of you guys listening to my FU in Part A. Dark Sakura, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_01]: Reject false icons and give me a taco.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!