[SPEAKER_06]: Tonight, the PlayStation 3 gets a website, Prey gets a release date, and what is the Wii hiding under that little flap?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello everybody and welcome to another edition of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are that podcast dedicated to video games and gamer news.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Gamer Culture as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, now we can hear you.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are you looking at over there on the laptop?
[SPEAKER_06]: You've been staring intently there for like... I'm trying to confirm something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, one of the stories we're doing tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it's quite important.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, we are a bit of a special episode this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is only going to be one part of this week's episode.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's not going to be a part A and part B. The reason for that is that we're taping far in advance this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually Thursday evening when we're taping this week's show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Partially because I'm fleeing the country tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to be gone for just under a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're pre-taping our live show on Thursday night.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are live.
[SPEAKER_06]: If anybody is listening to our regular live stream, we are here.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're in our chat room, which is on a brand new server, might I add.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're on a brand new chat server.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the details are over at OrangeLoungeTrader.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've moved from Other Side IRC to Game Surge.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: My gaming week was a lot of Dead or Alive 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of it, as in that's all everybody played when I got home from work yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: My husband's cousin and his girlfriend were over, and then other people showed up, and so it was pinball slash Dead or Alive Fest all in our house.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I tried to play a little Warcraft, and I'm going to probably start on whatever server that is that you're on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll say it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's my airy peak.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played Animal Crossing during a meeting at work
[SPEAKER_06]: Must not have been a very important meeting.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it was basically, just to give a little overview, the company I work for was purchased by another company.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they want to keep us, they want to keep everybody, it was good, but they're all like, they just announced it like the day before, and we're having this big HR meeting and crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: So me and Julie... Where was everybody doing the panicky, oh my god, Zoraga and Pink Slips?
[SPEAKER_08]: They're asking stupid questions that we all knew, they were reading off of the same stuff that was on the website at work.
[SPEAKER_08]: and then, oh, we can't answer that at this time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, we don't know the answer to this at this time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I'm sure information will be available as, you know, that type of crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: So me and customme19 and another one of our co-worker friends were sitting in the back and our friend was reading a book and we were playing Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were sitting on the floor behind people.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys are going to get fired.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's been there longer than I have.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: She actually trained me at my job.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to ask why all the dead are alive for?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it was on when I came home.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was on!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's on!
[SPEAKER_06]: Bouncy boobs, it's what's on the tube.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jeff's girlfriend though, she's really good at the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dan's best friend Eric, she was completely kicking his ass and he's such a masher.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: You could totally get away with button mashing on him.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, if you knew his moves without mashing, then it was even better.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, he's the mashers character.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was it in Tekken 4?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a girl?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was Christy.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was like his student or some crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: I play with Huarong anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can also mash with him too.
[SPEAKER_06]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: But mine was always Jin and Julia.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll never forget old school button mashing.
[SPEAKER_06]: When I used to play Street Fighter 2 back in the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Playing Honda?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, eHonda, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that's crazy, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because all you had to do was hit the buttons a bunch.
[SPEAKER_06]: You did that hand thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: How would she move?
[SPEAKER_08]: Though he also had the charging stuff too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the same deal with Blanka, just electrocute, electrocute, electrocute.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chun-Li did the feet thing too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: The old days of cheese.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did I ever tell you about the time...
[SPEAKER_06]: Storytime with Rob
[SPEAKER_06]: I played that game, and I wasn't a huge Street Fighter player, but I was on that game, and I was kicking all these guys' asses with Chun-Li for like an hour straight.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then finally, some girl came up and also used Chun-Li and worked me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, she owned me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll never forget her, although, well, I don't remember her name, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: My days of massive pwnage on fighting games, I have three major milestones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: And then it was me and my friend Marcy.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were like the killer instinct people.
[SPEAKER_08]: We would trade off and just like own guys all day.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I've told the story many times.
[SPEAKER_08]: My Tekken 3 escapade at Cyber Station in Mobile, Alabama at Bel Air Mall.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you've told this on the show before, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, these guys have been in there playing from like 10 a.m.
[SPEAKER_08]: to 2 in the afternoon, doing nothing but King, playing his throws over and over.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I was like, I want to play.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I shoved one of them off the machine and played Julia and kept beating them because she has the combo block, the throw blocks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Killer Instinct, my god, I haven't played that game in forever I really want to play that game, like right now And then Killer Instinct 2 came out when I lived in the dorms So we would go over to the bar, it was like a bar deli arcade And we'd just play Killer Instinct 2 all night What was the name of the skeleton guy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that was the guy I always used I know, sad I don't remember the name I know who you mean, Spinal Yes, Spinal I'll never forget that Combo Breaker
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played a little bit more of Blazing Angels.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm almost finished with that game now, finally.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's funny, though, because all the achievements kind of get unlocked at the same time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you get an achievement for if you ace all the missions, you get something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then as you finish the game, I think your rank ends up being, like,
[SPEAKER_04]: Corporal, or whatever it needs to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then all the medals.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you ace all the missions, you unlock like four achievements at the same time, which is most of the achievements in the game anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, I'm trying to beat this game for achievements.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Points, whore!
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I've been playing the Chromehounds demo, and that was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought that wasn't released in the US.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, you have an account somewhere else, don't you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, everybody knows you can get an account in another country.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just set up an account for Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once you download, you can play it with any account.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all in English anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't there a 99 Nights demo in Japan?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought there was.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's Love Football.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the only other demo that we don't have.
[SPEAKER_04]: But still, though, I mean, it's all in English.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, completely.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can select different languages, I guess, initially or whatever, but it's all in English.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't understand why they didn't release it over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's stupid, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can still get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, on Major Nelson's blog earlier this week, he talked about why, or there's like an FAQ, why don't things come to certain regions?
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's always like licensing, permission, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're downloading it now for your servers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, people are getting it anyway, so it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's it matter?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, a lot of the feedback I read on the demo was really negative, but you enjoyed it?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's because they're stupid and they don't understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: They think that these mechs represent all the mechs in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're slow.
[SPEAKER_04]: The mechs are heavy mechs that move slow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's not like Speed Racer mechs.
[SPEAKER_04]: The mechs are slow by...
[SPEAKER_04]: you can make lighter mechs that are faster or you have these heavier mechs which are damn slow and that's the two missions there's a sniping mission and like a soldier mission and they're both with heavy mechs and they're like these mechs move so slow it's gonna be 15 seconds to turn around yeah it's a heavy mech it's supposed to move slow because it's armored as hell you can get a light mech or a mech with like you know hovercraft bottom or wheels or whatever and it moves fast
[SPEAKER_06]: Tonight's story time on Orange Launch Radio, but I don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you ever play at Dave & Buster's, the mech game they have there?
[SPEAKER_04]: I played it back when it was at BattleTech in Virtual World.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played it when it was over at American Life.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those things were really slow, but it was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, because, you know... I beg to differ.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got motion sick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but you get motion sick, and that's a whole other Oprah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: If you didn't have that, wouldn't you agree that the game is somewhat fun, at least?
[SPEAKER_06]: Somewhat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, it's a fun game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the multiplayer is going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got the online...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: They're doing a lot of things with this, and this is kind of positioning itself to be like the next, you know, Mecha Assault, you know, game, and that's what kind of people are looking for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've been playing more of that still.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally, was it Vice City Stories has a date now, October 18th, which is about when the last one came out, so it's not...
[SPEAKER_04]: I know they're not because they're fucking lazy but they better fix the multiplayer because it's really messed up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So playable but really messed up.
[SPEAKER_06]: My gaming week was actually not that exciting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did mention during Jamie's gaming week I played World of Warcraft and I did do an instance this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Horde's first instance is always the Ragefire Chasm and so I did that instance this week and that's fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Burnout
[SPEAKER_06]: and I'm finding it's kind of hard to get the achievements in Burnout.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am having a hard time getting perfects on a lot of those early races, but I find that what you can do is you play a ways and you get the really nice cars and then you go back to the first levels and use the nice cars to beat them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_08]: I forgot one more part of my week, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go for it, because I don't have anything else.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to actually bring it and play it on my laptop.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've got a game, an advanced copy to review.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to be doing a review on Dragon's Lair HD.
[SPEAKER_08]: It will be on the stuff.orangenounsradio.com blog.
[SPEAKER_08]: So everybody should keep their eyes on our board for when I post.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: You were talking about that on last week's show, I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it arrived.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm looking forward to checking that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: The box is very nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you going to let me play with your copy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_08]: But I was planning on trying to hook up my laptop to our widescreen TV and see how it looked on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dragon's Lair.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, let's get into the news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who wants to start us off tonight with some news?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I think that I could do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd have to try really hard, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, guess what has officially launched other than a few ships going out to sea?
[SPEAKER_06]: No idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: The official PS3 site.
[SPEAKER_08]: actually both US and UK I haven't bothered checking every other country I assume that it's come out for the US though it is www.us.playstation.com.ps3 for UK it's actually I guess it's eu.playstation.com.ps3 and it's got all the beginning stuff on it any new information at all?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks just really cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ours is sort of, look, it's a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Theirs is like sleek black stuff with flash animation and reflection.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ah, I can't stand it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like a hot dog.
What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Eddie is a joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I was like, PlayStation 3, can't stand it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like a hot dog.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I'm still looking at stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to have to mess everything up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of the PlayStation, this is more kind of on the PSP, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're saying that they're going to be able to support up to 7,000 PlayStation 1 games with the new emulator, which pretty much is every game out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, there were 7,000 PlayStation games?
[SPEAKER_04]: There were not 7,000 games.
[SPEAKER_04]: There were 7,000 different versions of games, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, that's their way of saying they're going to be able to support every single game.
[SPEAKER_04]: A few holes in that whole statement there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what that sounds like?
[SPEAKER_06]: You remember those old 64-in-1 cartridges that were on the NES, and like 20 of them were just Contra with different color players?
[SPEAKER_08]: All kinds of different hacks.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what this sounds like to me when they say 7,000.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although I personally own a few hundred myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but still, 7,000?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's...
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's what the UK PSP magazine is reporting.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I would say more around all the games that were on the system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's my only thing about that though.
[SPEAKER_04]: The PSP does not have a second analog stick and the PSP only has one L and one R button.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but the very first PS1 controller didn't have an analog stick at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: True, but if it's going to be supporting all the games, there are games that require the analog stick, and a lot of those games do use the L1 and L2 buttons.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that eliminates a lot of that 7,000 there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dumbasses freaking promising the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, they do have a good selection of stuff that they are promising.
[SPEAKER_04]: These are going to be available when they launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Castlevania Symphony of the Night, Final Fantasy VII, Final Fantasy VIII, Silent Hill, and Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really want to see another Tomb Raider since they were doing the remake anyways, and Tomb Raider sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, it was a groundbreaking PlayStation game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tomb Raider Legends is actually fairly decent.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the new one, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't like it at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't like Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did like breaking her, you know, by throwing her off the cliff.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, that was all about Tomb Raider 2, where you can make her explode, lock the butler in the walk-in freezer, and then make her jump off the balcony where she breaks her neck.
[SPEAKER_08]: The sound was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tomb Raider 2 is by far the best.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tomb Raider 2 is by far the best.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they like pushing the digital distribution thing, so why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray for Castlevania Symphony of the Night being on that list.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably the best PlayStation game, in my opinion, period.
[SPEAKER_06]: The best PlayStation game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Boo for no Intelligent Cube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, these are only five.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can go to hell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, maybe one of the 7,000.
[SPEAKER_08]: What we need is freaking Einhound.
[SPEAKER_06]: How come Ridge Racer wasn't on that list?
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought that was the big thing that they were touting at E3 was Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's just a given.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, anyway, I have to mention, speaking of Ridge Racer, there is a brand new Ridge Racer title coming to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Rid Racer 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rid Racer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Racer 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can I edit that out?
[SPEAKER_06]: Ridge Racer 2 in the latest issue of Famitsu Magazine.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to start off with the last game left off.
[SPEAKER_06]: It will have a return of the Nitro system as well as all the drift-based racing that makes Ridge Racer what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what it is?
[SPEAKER_06]: If I don't say it, Ridge Racer, then I can't say it at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the problem now.
[SPEAKER_04]: The thing about Ridge Racer, each game's been exactly the same as the last one.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, no, no, no, it has not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so it's R4.
[SPEAKER_08]: R4 was the best of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: You didn't let me finish.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are new modes.
[SPEAKER_06]: as opposed to Ridge Racer 1 on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is, of course, the returning World Tours, Time Attack, Wireless, but now there is Arcade, Duel, and Survival Mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Arcade Mode is kind of like an arcade racing game where you try to get to a goal in a certain amount of time and then you get more time as you get to each checkpoint.
[SPEAKER_08]: Survival is where you play chicken.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be like Twisted Metal Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, so anyway, rumor is the game is 70% complete, and the Japanese release should be September 14th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of Ridge Racer and Sony, Sony is actually claiming that Microsoft is copying them, that they are completely cloning the PlayStation 3 with the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I'm not sure where in that argument that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, seeing as the PlayStation 3 is not even out yet, I'm not sure what this is all... I mean, is it the camera and the eye toy thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, this was an interview that was done in the official PlayStation magazine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: That won't be biased at all, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which, yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it says, brings up how everyone is comparing Microsoft to Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the Sony rep claims as soon as they do something, they see Microsoft trailing behind them, following their strategies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh, that's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will give them credit on one thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: One thing only.
[SPEAKER_04]: The fact that they have dual analog sticks on the controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, that's, you know, I think that was the first system, the PlayStation, to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I'm giving them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the DualShock controller is easily one of the top three controllers of all time, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But in turn, wasn't the DualShock controller just a grown-up version of the Super Nintendo controller in a way?
[SPEAKER_04]: This was Kaz Hirai's...
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess and another quote that was taken from the interview here and the other thing is you look you take a look at for example the fact that we incorporate the blu-ray drive from day one you're not going to be asking me so talk to me about this blu-ray add-on that you have does it work for games is it just for movies that's exactly the kind of pitfall you fall into if you launch something that's too early to premature no
[SPEAKER_04]: You're launching a year late.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gag order, Sony.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've said it before on this program.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody needs to stop talking right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's working for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of them talk, but they don't talk as much as you do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're copying a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to admit, the whole live thing... Granted, it's a great business model.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can't say they're completely original.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're copying the business model, basically.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trying to make it their own...
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's fine, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's something that needs to be done, just like the controllers look kind of the same, they're pretty much the same nowadays.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fine, but don't go and claim that you're the one that created it when your system's not even out there yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell, we don't even know what their online marketplace is like, and to say that, oh, well, Microsoft ripped us off, well, that's kind of impossible to do if you don't, you know, you can't rip off the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wasn't there some rumor going around this week, and I apologize if I'm
[SPEAKER_06]: Spoiling somebody else's story for later in the show, but I don't remember this coming up.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I seem to recall something about the Xbox 360 had hinted that they wanted to add something to their controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like there's some type of... It was kind of pointing like they might do motion sensing in their controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't see that happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I heard that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, I think I heard it on another show or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some other stories that we'll have that kind of hints that they're copying...
[SPEAKER_04]: and more.
[SPEAKER_06]: from Kaz Harai.
[SPEAKER_06]: Generally speaking, over the past 12 years or so, there has been a consumer expectation that disc-based games are maybe $59 on the high end to $39 on the low end.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what I can say now is, I think it would be a bit of a stretch to think that we could suddenly turn around and say, PlayStation 3 games now $99.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think consumers expect software pricing to suddenly double.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the quick answer is that we want to make it as affordable as possible knowing that there is a set consumer expectation for what software has cost the past 12 years.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of the best answer I can give you.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if it becomes a bit higher than $59, don't ding me.
[SPEAKER_06]: But again, I don't expect it to be $100.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing, and I don't want to sound like a broken record.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, honestly, I am trying to find the good side of the whole Sony argument here.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's what?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to be as unbiased as possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is why people say we're anti-Sony, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen, I owned a Sony PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_04]: I owned a PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said, fuck Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not buying an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was right there with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said, fuck Xbox when it first came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And even still, when the PlayStation 3, when they were talking about it originally, I'm like, yeah, I'm going to own a PlayStation 3 and an Xbox 360 because I love the PlayStation 3 games and stuff, and it sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: But
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the E3, it was like, you lost me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like Crazy World over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the thing is... I think the expectations were met perfectly.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're trying to basically say, our games, you have to understand, you're paying for HD games, you're paying for...
[SPEAKER_04]: Games that have higher development costs.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're paying for media that's $20 for blanks or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is why the games are more expensive.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to have to pay for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the thing is, when people are developing games on both platforms, and it's even been said before, you can't tell the difference between them.
[SPEAKER_04]: So why the hell?
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is also, Microsoft is doing the same thing with the Xbox and Xbox 360 games, especially at launch, that were only slightly different, OK?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why should I pay more money for a game that looks exactly the same and probably plays exactly the same on a system that's even more expensive?
[SPEAKER_04]: People aren't, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be a problem for them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, that argument seems a little Nintendo fanboy-ish to me for some reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you know, the way you phrase that makes it sound like you're all about the Wii in that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is okay, I mean, you're into whatever you're into.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just saying if they are going to be pushing a system that this is, you know, the games are $79, I better see a vast improvement between that and the 360 version.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those games better do my fucking dishes if they're going to be $80.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's insane.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least 360 has $5 games on their marketplace that kick butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see stuff that they were showing in those E3 videos or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the Game Developer Conference videos.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want my next Jak and Daxter game or Ratchet and Clank to look like a goddamn movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I want to see if it's going to be this expensive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sigh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, we don't know until about a month before or maybe two months before when the actual pricing is announced.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, if that's their argument is that, oh, well, we have to price it this way because we're taking full advantage of the HD, da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, you're taking full advantage of the HD, but how much of the marketplace is ready to take full advantage of the HD?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a lot this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe this time next year even, or the year after, because with each Christmas, the price of the HDTVs are going to get lower and lower.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe we'll be ready to talk.
[SPEAKER_06]: But honestly, it's not like HD... I mean, I am an HDTV owner.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love it, and I would highly recommend it to everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: But looking at even just regular television, there's not a lot of embracing of HDTV yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's not a whole lot of incentive to go to HDTV right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you're going with the Sony concept here...
[SPEAKER_04]: Your HDTV would not be good enough because it does not display 1080p.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It might.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has HDMI.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not every TV is going to be able to.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll actually say, usually in your manual that comes with your TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, then Sony can suck it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hooray for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know I'll buy one anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to have one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to play Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm that sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will buy the damn machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'll probably bitch about it if I'm not satisfied, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: And like, you're going to buy one too.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're sitting here all anti-Sony, I hate Sony, but you're going to buy one too.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, I was anti-Xbox and I bought one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, listen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I buy everything new that comes out.
[SPEAKER_08]: You probably buy a fucking 3D.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a GameCom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I understand.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a virtual employee.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to own it all.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like Veruca Salt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mine, mine, mine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me, me, me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want it all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not getting it at launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am not getting it at launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't get 360 at launch and I turned out okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm just saying just based on what games are coming out right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really hate to bring this story to light because it's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: It really, you gotta wonder what crazy ass people they got working at Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, this news came from a website called Gamefront.de.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a German site that has a lot of information on Sony PlayStation and the Wii and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: They noticed, and I was looking for it right before the show, that Sony has registered a patent in the Japanese patent office
[SPEAKER_04]: Poo's
[SPEAKER_04]: They're saying that the circles might actually represent the analog 6.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what you have here is them copying the Wii in the name of, but the controller is called... It's a PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get PS.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand, you know, with the little circles, I guess that could be kind of... The Poos?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Poos?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Poocon!
[SPEAKER_06]: And the Wii?
[SPEAKER_06]: Poocon!
[SPEAKER_06]: The Pooh and the Wii?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's the Xbox 360 going to come out with?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Sphincter!
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's?
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell are they thinking?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, show me the logo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: You said you had a picture of it, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a picture of the logo, and I will show it to you, and I will actually probably post this in our forum just so everyone can look at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Convince me this isn't fake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, because I look at this and I go, this is some anti-Sony person's idea of a really bad joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: I looked at the website.
[SPEAKER_04]: I couldn't see.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing I couldn't look up the patent, or not the patent, the trademark on there, because I have no idea how to look up those trademarks on that website.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't search by company or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to know the trademark number.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I looked at their screenshot, and it looks like off that website.
[SPEAKER_04]: So granted, it could be an elaborate hoax or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember the morning that the Wii was announced?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, Nintendo fanboys were like, oh, that's not right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a lie.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not called the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop fucking with us, Sony fanboys.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like having one of those moments.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, seriously, you can't be calling this the poos.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to realize what you're doing here.
[SPEAKER_06]: But see, that logo is too...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, it's too simplistic to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: It screams fake.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think I'd buy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm just going by what it looks like here.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't look so much like an Infinity, but it looks like an 8.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, seriously, because the left side is smaller than the right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I think what that might mean or whatever is, I don't know, have something to do with the tilting of it or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: if they were showing it tilted it would have been at a completely different ratio I don't know what they're thinking but anyways I still call bullshit I don't think they're dumb enough to name their console the poos I'm looking and you know what I'll try to find this and I seriously think just looking at the screenshot that is a shot straight off that website I know just from browsing the website it looks exactly like it so you know what it could be a hoax but if
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: It should be in there somewhere, and we should be able to find it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, either way, you're going to find out pretty soon, and if it is, that's really weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm taking that with a huge grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if that turns out to be the real name, if we're back here next week with some type of confirmation stuff, I'm just going to shed more tears for Sony, because the poos.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I realize, okay, it's an infinity sign.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not OO, but you're saying that's how they've trademarked it, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's P space O-O space S is what it's on.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that doesn't sound a little anti-Sony fanboy to you?
[SPEAKER_04]: That doesn't sound... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole story from them, and I don't have it translated, unfortunately, it was just saying that they had registered a patent for the controller, or a trademark for the controller, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: It says that they speculate, okay, the PNNS, of course, is PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_04]: The two circles are the analog sticks.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't draw the distinction that it's naughty, you know, poo, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't laugh about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just, like, basically reported it as a story.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it had a picture of the logo on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our few chatters that are here today want to see the article for themselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: So link it in the chat room so you can see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gamefront.de And if you scroll down quite a bit, there's a story about the Eye of Judgment right below it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of poo.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not just poo.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's like the poo of poo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Silly console names make us crazy and cause us to get a little angsty.
[SPEAKER_06]: and that makes us want to get really, really angsty and do our FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: How's that sound, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_08]: My FU of the week is actually not what it was going to originally be.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's actually toward my work for having these stupid, retarded meetings for two hours about crap they don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, what about our pension?
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't know that yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, what about our thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't know that either.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, but what about this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me read directly off of our website that's been posted for the last three days.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ugh, people.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's two words for that meaning.
[SPEAKER_08]: Premature and pathetic.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was no call for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's basically, I think, just to smooth things over.
[SPEAKER_08]: But really, all it did was, like, just piss people off.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, a big...
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to that stupid meeting, how pointless it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, give us a meeting when we actually have some information on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yeah, the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: My F you is going to Sony because every day I read something crazy and crazier from them and it's such a disappointment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that was quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: My FU of the week goes to myself because I'm leaving the country tomorrow and I haven't even started packing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go me!
[SPEAKER_06]: I rock.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did get a lot of laundry done though, so I'll at least smell clean when I go to Canada.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I hear they check for that at the border.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does Skye smell laundry fresh?
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on... Oh, that was you?
Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: There actually is a little bit of release news for our dear friends in the UK.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take-Two's game Prey has been announced to be released on July 14th, which is actually three days after we're going to get it here.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's also going to be a limited edition version for the PC, and there's a thing likely that there's going to be a demo for the Xbox 360 showing up on live pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's another one of those things everybody's on Major Nelson's blog going, where's our Prey demo?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where's the demo?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where's Street Fighter?
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, for anyone who doesn't know, Prey is, you're playing as a garage mechanic who gets kidnapped by aliens and has to save the world with his dead grandfather to guide him.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, isn't that fantastic?
[SPEAKER_08]: That really makes me want to play Prey.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to play that game so that I can throw up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, because of motion sickness and all that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't really care for first-person shooters.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't liked a first-person shooter since Hexen, really.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't played one a lot since Halo 2, probably, but I'll give it a shot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I'll watch it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got a lot of hype.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's got to be something about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually could sit through Perfect Dark Zero without getting sick for a little while.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, I tried to get into that and I just couldn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm personally not too excited about Prey, however, I know some of our listeners are.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Prey's coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, that game looks actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to have really awesome multiplayer, apparently.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of multiplayer, actually, Oblivion's got another mod for the PC, and that's a multiplayer mod.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of in alpha right now, but it allows you right now to basically exist in the same world with somebody else.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're hoping that later on they're going to be able to add support up to eight players along with deathmatch and capture the flag.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it's kind of nifty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, Oblivion?
[SPEAKER_06]: Multiplayer Capture the Flag.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's crazy though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody built multiplayer into Oblivion?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: You would think that they would want to put that in the game themselves and charge five bucks for it on Xbox 360 next to the horsey armor and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they were even to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't...
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a weird add-on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it sounds great, but that seems like it would change the game significantly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it would be pretty cool to go, not even if you can't do Deathmatch, but do co-op.
[SPEAKER_04]: Co-op would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that's like a whole other idea for an Oblivion game, honestly.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's crazy that somebody built that into... That takes some real talent and skill and sleepless nights and coffee to be able to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of Oblivion, kind of an exclusive here, another wonderful item appeared in my system at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be Oblivion on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be coming out currently at launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: My guess is probably after launch sometime, but it is coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so why haven't we heard until today?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: People don't watch the retails.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do watch GameSpot and EB, because I noticed my similar stories to the one we talked about on Sunday night have appeared on Monday Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because they saw the box art from GameStop, apparently, which pulled it off their website, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: And funny enough, all those titles I said were correct.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, whoo, heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except they didn't get the 100...
[SPEAKER_04]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oblivion, of course, is a really big game on Xbox 360, but the biggest game on the regular Xbox was no doubt Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when Halo 2 was first released, there was a company, Plantronics, and they created a special edition Halo 2 headset.
[SPEAKER_06]: It cost about $49.95 to $59.95, but the cool thing was that they were donating $1 of the proceeds to the Plantronics Gamecom United Way Katrina Relief Fund.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I know that doesn't sound like a whole lot of the cost, but something to note is that the price of those headsets has now dropped to $14.95 to $19.95 for your Xbox Communicator Special Halo 2 Edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And some of it goes to charity so you can feel good about yourself as you go kill people on Halo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, killing people is not a good thing to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unless they're in your way.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, there are prisoners who are at Wakefield Prison in the UK who have to get rid of their PlayStation 2s.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, boo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I mean, being in prison, wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: But basically, there were inmates at this prison who,
[SPEAKER_08]: who were found that they were watching porn on their PlayStation 2s.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so they received 200 pounds each for every confiscated machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like... Oh, so wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: They took them, but then they paid them for it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't that great?
[SPEAKER_06]: 200 pounds?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, yeah, that's a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't that more than what one costs new?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm pretty sure, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because a pound's worth more than a dollar right now, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: So basically, yeah, for the nine prisoners who had theirs taken away, that's 1,800 pounds, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, now, did they have all the porn taken away, too?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because maybe that justifies why they were paid so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because they probably had some really impressive collections of pornography, I mean.
[SPEAKER_08]: But even so, keep in mind that this is probably coming out of the...
[SPEAKER_08]: Pockets of People.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, the prison service is saying that they're refunding the prisoners because they bought the PlayStation 2s with their own money.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's also been a mention that not compensating them might have been a breach of human rights.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that they breached the rights of whoever they violated when needed whatever crime they did to put themselves in jail.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're in jail as punishment.
[SPEAKER_08]: It shouldn't be happy fun time.
[SPEAKER_08]: They should get a brick wall with a toilet attached to it and a piece of board to lay on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, not that bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: But seriously, if you've killed somebody, yeah, you get a cell.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, who knows what these people were?
[SPEAKER_08]: This is a maximum security case.
[SPEAKER_06]: They could have been drug criminals.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're saying that among those that it was taken from, they were sex offenders.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, we're watching porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's lovely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I had absolutely no sympathy for a sex offender.
[SPEAKER_08]: But also, it was quoted by Norman Brennan, who's the chairman of the Victim of Crime Trust.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was quoted in the Yorkshire Post that it made a mockery of the whole criminal justice system.
[SPEAKER_08]: And honestly, I don't know what to think about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's kind of sad that they had him to begin with.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, better porn than shower rapes, I mean, honestly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think if you're in prison for something, it shouldn't be happy fun time.
[SPEAKER_08]: It should be pay your penalty time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, I'd rather, without getting into a political discussion, I'd rather they take out their sexual frustrations on porno than shower rape.
[SPEAKER_08]: Beat the meat instead of beating each other
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll take place during some show that's going on over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Ripspeed Donnie Carr Show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if that's any big thing that's... Did you say car show?
[SPEAKER_04]: Car show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's supposed to get in... It's supposed to... It's Sunday, Sunday, Sunday!
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on down to the car show and video game tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, it's going to be happening... Babes in Halo.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's supposed to be happening on the 13th of August, and if you're curious, you can look it up at www.donnyshow.co.uk That's D-O-N-N-Y show.co.uk And they're expecting to get 20,000 visitors.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if that's big for a car show or not, but it's going to take place at the North Weld Airfield in Essex.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what you can expect there, though, they're going to be having the Xbox Cup, which is a four-and-a-half-hour live broadcast of the Adidas World of Football in Berlin, which is going to be on Saturday, this Saturday, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, well, by the time you get this podcast, probably yesterday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I hope you watched it, or else TiVo'd it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways, for that one that's actually going on during the car show, they're going to be doing Project Gotham 3 tournament.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do they have TiVo in the UK?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure they have some type of DVR.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to be having a Project Gotham Racing 3 tournament at the car show, which is appropriate since it is a car show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And... Yeah, so basically the Extreme Sports Channel has...
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're bringing together hundreds of UK's very best gamers to compete in the UK's first live televised pro racing games tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: After seven days of grueling heats on Xbox Live in the morning at Ripspeed Donny, the final 16 competitors will be pitting their racing skills against the very best the UK has to offer.
[SPEAKER_04]: They will be playing Project Gotham Racing 3 on an open-air 20-foot by 15-foot LED screen on live television, and the pressure will be on to give the best performance with a huge audience and a hot list of prizes up for grabs.
[SPEAKER_06]: All three of them?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I said, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, TiVo's only in the US!
[SPEAKER_06]: Not HD.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, I don't mean... Forget it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they have that pal thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's also going to be rebroadcast, or the four 30-minute live broadcasts are going to be on Sunday, the 13th of August, with the programming repeated between 9 p.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: and 11 p.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: and midnight to 2 a.m., so... Fun, fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: But hey, that's kind of neat, though, especially with the Gotham TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gotham TV, if they actually do it right, they can make it look pretty cool, so... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Saint Seiya's Coming to Europe
[SPEAKER_08]: Saint Seiya is a freaking old-ass anime.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know why it's taking this long.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Atari and Namco Bandai are bringing out Saint Seiya the Hades to Europe later on in the year.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's based off the manga and anime.
[SPEAKER_08]: Over here it was called Night to the Zodiac or some stupid crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they had Saint Seiya over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm?
[SPEAKER_04]: They had Saint Seiya over here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought it came out over here as Night to the Zodiac.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they had it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, but basically it's supposed to be full-on anime style.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have the Cosmo system pulled in.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's supposed to be out in autumn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's pretty spiffy there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, the anime games don't seem to do too well, at least I know from a work standpoint.
[SPEAKER_08]: It isn't Dragon Ball anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's always Dragon Ball.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_06]: Does Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_06]: count as anime?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's more of a card game than anime, but... Well, Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_06]: What did it start as?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did it start as a card game or did it start as anime?
[SPEAKER_06]: It started as a card game, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it started as the card game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, it was another thing before that, like Dual Monsters, and then it was Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_08]: And I actually have Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_08]: manga from a Shonen Jump from 1991.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, wait, wait, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Put the brakes on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just realized we're wasting time on this show talking about Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a deck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so as far as stuff coming out this week...
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, absolutely almost nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and Tuesdays are big release days, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: And Tuesdays are 4th of July, which is a big holiday here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no, not Tuesdays.
[SPEAKER_04]: Usually it's around Wednesdays or so, but whatever, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, if you do have a 360, Lord of the Rings Battle for Middle-Earth 2 is going to be coming out, so yippee.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's about the only good game that's coming out this week, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's like, literally on my pre-book sheet that I was ordering for people, four games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Four.
[SPEAKER_04]: And most of them were, like there was, was it Board Game Classics 20-1?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hooray!
[SPEAKER_04]: Some soccer game that was on the, Sony's official soccer game on the PSP is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is funny, because it's still 06, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: That one's coming out, and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And even the week after that's even... Actually, the week after that's going to be pretty good, because that's when you're going to get Parade and Chromehands and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so, well, we aren't getting crap in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is the U.K.
[SPEAKER_06]: faring any better?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know, it would be fantastic if that was actually the case, but not always.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I'll tell you what, there actually are some interesting things going to be out coming up in the first week of July.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although, honestly, I don't see what's too exciting about Alex Rider's Stormbreaker.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sounded pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, my cell phone went off in studio.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's also Earache Extreme Metal Racing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although, I have to say, on the 7th, they do get Chromehounds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alex Rider's going to be pretty sweet, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got a DS in that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they get Electroplankton.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Pirates of the Caribbean, The Legend of Jack Sparrow.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Super Dragon Ball Z. And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Big Brain Academy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've heard Big Brain Academy is way better than brain training, but I've only played it myself for like five minutes, so I need more time with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it looks like there's a lot more to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love Electroplankton.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was playing that demo in line at E3 last year like the whole time.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it sounds like a lot of good stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're actually getting a lot of good games though in July.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, just later on, there's coming out with Civ IV, Civ City Rome, Shin Megami Tensei, which I saw some of at E3 Prey.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's actually some pretty decent stuff coming out in July.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, speaking of stuff coming out, Eevee and GameStop are going to be getting a special edition of Final Fantasy XII, when that finally comes out around Halloween.
[SPEAKER_04]: Included in that, of course, will be a steel bookcase, developers interviews, history of Final Fantasy featurettes,
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XII US trailers, Final Fantasy XII Japanese trailers, Final Fantasy XII art galleries as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cosplay footage, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can get that for $59.99 when that comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Halloween.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: So what we want to ask is our voicemail question of the week is, do you pre-order games?
[SPEAKER_06]: If so, what do you believe are the advantages of pre-ordering games?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't pre-order games, why don't you do it?
[SPEAKER_06]: We want to hear your feedback.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll play some of your responses on the air.
[SPEAKER_06]: Give our voicemail a call any time during the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's 916-226-9067.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please keep in mind, boys and girls, that that may be a toll call unless you happen to be local to where we are.
[SPEAKER_06]: So please make sure you have the permission of whoever's paying the phone bill before you give that a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we want your opinion on pre-ordering games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And are you going to pre-order Final Fantasy XII to get that super special limited edition?
[SPEAKER_06]: I might.
[SPEAKER_06]: I usually don't pre-order games, but I might because I'm that big of a XII whore that I might want to have all that special shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, I mentioned earlier in the program that Major Nelson's blog's been pretty active this week and he wrote a pretty lengthy blog earlier this week about...
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody's been bitching and leaving comments in his blog Where's Street Fighter 2?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where's the demo for Prey?
[SPEAKER_06]: And you see these maintenance shutdowns going on And they even really cock-teased us with Street Fighter 2 Because we have the theme and the gamer pictures But yet no games yet So Major Nelson's getting a lot of heat for this Being the community face there
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, he's saying blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes developers are not aware of the intense Microsoft certification process.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes they promise dates and they don't know what the complexity is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I understand Major Nelson shouldn't be really taking the blame for this crap, so don't blame him.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at the same time,
[SPEAKER_06]: How many different freaking release dates has Capcom announced for Street Fighter 2 in various ways?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's kind of their own damn faults.
[SPEAKER_06]: They shouldn't have announced the game was coming out if they weren't done with certification or didn't realize or I don't know what.
[SPEAKER_06]: They shouldn't have announced the damn game coming out at all or should have been very vague in it and not get our hopes up time and time again because that's what causes people to get frustrated.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really wish they'd just release more games, period, on live.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand they have to go through quality controls and yada yada yada.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand why Street Fighter is being delayed because of the online lag that they have, and they need to really get that fixed, but
[SPEAKER_04]: In the same time, I don't understand why they just can't... Like, for example, the thing I'm pissed off and it doesn't really have to do with live too much is how, you know the official Xbox magazine?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they have a disc with it that comes with demos that are on live.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, well, it comes with demos.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a lot of demos are already on live, have been on live for like months.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what the hell am I paying for this magazine for demos that I can already download, you know, now?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Which I would say, actually, I'm going to make a bold statement here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's part of UNO's huge success right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Obviously, it's a solid game and it's a fun thing to play online, but honestly, I think the reason people are still talking about it and people are so into it is that it's all they've really got that's new in the past many months.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because before that, what was the newest game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Astro Pop or some crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you really want to play hard with backgammon?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: Does anyone play Backgammon anymore?
[SPEAKER_06]: My dad might.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean... If I want to play Backgammon, I'll have a table.
[SPEAKER_08]: An actual board game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, that's their prerogative and how they want to do things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anywho... By the way, DMN in our chatroom would like to point out that he would like to play Hardwood Backgammon.
[SPEAKER_06]: And is offering to fight you, I believe.
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe he's calling you out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Backgammon sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was always on the other side of the checkerboard, and I was like, what the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to play this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, speaking of stuff that isn't out there, or is not coming out, Australia, Reservoir Dogs the Game, not coming out, because they banned it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why did they ban it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, apparently it was awfully violent, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: Players, participants in a bank heist, can literally blow the heads off of hostages and police as well as execute hostages at point-blank range with the gun shot to the head.
[SPEAKER_04]: Use a series of so-called signature torture moves.
[SPEAKER_04]: Players can use different means to torture hostages and thereby cause the police to lay down their weapons, such as repeated pistol whippings to the side of the head with blood spray evident, burning the eyes of a hostage with a cigar until they scream and die, cutting the fingers off of a hostage with blood bursts as the victim screams in pain.
[SPEAKER_04]: In lieu of taking hostages, the players can opt to a more violent scenario where a slow motion shootout occurs, accentuating the violence.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am buying this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, it's like Australia just gave free advertising for the game for all the other countries.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that is a little odd that they'd ban it before it's even released.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why aren't they going after this game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why isn't... Okay, when this game comes out, the MPA better get off of Hot Coffee's ass for a little bit of sex because this has slicing out fingers and burning out eyes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a little worse.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, there's no nudity, so... Out of curiosity... What about the movie?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, out of curiosity, can I still walk into an Australian video store and pick up Reservoir Dogs, the movie?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you can.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's an interesting little...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's industry's double standard.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a double standard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: How stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's the player that gets to do it, because the interactiveness makes it worse, I guess?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that the theory behind it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am so buying it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I didn't realize the game was going to be that violent.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that would be kind of stupid to not think a Reservoir Dogs game was going to be violent.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was going to be a cheap-ass port, and now I really want to play this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, oh, good comment in chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkTetsuya says, I can't wait to hear He Who Shall Remain Nameless's reaction to that game when it comes out here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just call him You Know Who.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, You Know Who.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jackie Poo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, You Know Who emails us every week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't, but DarkSakura does because she's our mailbag mistress.
[SPEAKER_06]: So when you email mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com, she puts on her hazmat suit, dives into the email bag, and pulls out her favorite and most, mostly, I was about to say most least favorite, her least favorite emails, her mostest, leastest emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: My mostestly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just read the damn emails, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, jeez.
[SPEAKER_08]: First email comes from JeremyTodd1.
[SPEAKER_08]: He says, It's JeremyTodd1 again!
[SPEAKER_08]: As if I didn't get that first email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, haven't you read his emails like the past four weeks in a row?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm skipping it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: But he does say House of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_08]: And House of the Dead has zombie exploding action.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to make sure everybody gets heard.
[SPEAKER_08]: He wants to know what we think about arcade type shooters going on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like House of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I was listening to I want to say All Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: they had some type of rumor about like a lightsaber game being on the Wii and I was thinking like you know the Star Wars trilogy game like in the last stage you could actually fight Darth Vader one on one with a lightsaber and I was thinking I'm not a huge Star Wars fan but that would be one of the most fucking badass things ever to play would be like a lightsaber game first person fighter with the Wii controller that is so freaking hardcore they need a Bluntman and Chronic game where you fight Mark Hamill as the cock knocker
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are so lame.
[SPEAKER_06]: But funny, but lame.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would also like to see Point Blank, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of Point Blank, actually, one of our other listeners, Robert M., says, if you're still having trouble finding Point Blank DS, try GameCrazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: He says that apparently they've been pretty good to find him there.
[SPEAKER_08]: He found his copy and Trauma Center.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about it, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: You gonna go?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a game craze nearby here.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I thought the one that was in the Hollywood video by me closed down, but I think it's... Go buy Kmart on Sunrise.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really care to play that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I'll go get it eventually.
[SPEAKER_06]: You bitched about it for two weeks straight on this show that you couldn't find it, and now we're telling you, here it is, go get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're like, well, I don't know if I want to go get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I want to go to GameStop because I have credit there, and so I don't want to have to actually pay money.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, wants to know...
[SPEAKER_08]: Regarding the upcoming Transformers movie, what if the official movie poster were one large web sign?
[SPEAKER_08]: Make it really damn hard to see the... You know when you held your thumb over the Autobot symbol?
[SPEAKER_04]: You heard that the teaser trailer came up today, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and I tried to watch it on YouTube and it says, this is unavailable.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did see, though, an image from what they thought was going to be Bumblebee.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know why he's not a VW Beetle?
[SPEAKER_08]: Couldn't get licensing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, Jazz isn't going to be a Porsche.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blink, blink.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got to be honest.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember what Transformers was all about, but you name characters and I go whoosh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jazz was the one whose voice was done by a dude who was Hong Kong phooey.
[SPEAKER_08]: Scatman Crothers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whoosh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, well you know Casey Kasem did voices in that too.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't do that on television.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gummy Bears.
[SPEAKER_08]: Move to Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: Casey Kasem is a transformer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Casey Kasem?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the old radio DJ?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, he transforms into stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was Cliffjumper.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: And he also was Shaggy in Scooby-Doo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was also Casey Kasem.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was also Casey Kasem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_08]: Casey Kasem's top 40.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, one from, uh, H Master Osha, says, Happy Birthday, Sky!
[SPEAKER_05]: Aw, thanks.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is my first email to Orange Lounge, but I've been listening since the episode of someone, I think it was a guest, someone like DJ Ranma S, or someone who called in frequently, swore off boners, oh, that was explicit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh no, that was explicit, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, swore off boners for Lent.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was, uh, before the podcast and live show merged, cause we didn't, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Old school.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, our old live shows used to be nuts.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'd talk about really crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you think we're off topic on this show, geez, you should have heard our old live show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was probably last year's Lent, I think, was when he did that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And he said that your gift is something found on Google looking for World of Warcraft AMVs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hope you find it as funny as I did, but there's not a link to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're all doing a great job, even with an anti-Mac co-host.
[SPEAKER_08]: And before I forget, he actually gave me what I'm using as my side of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, thank you for the birthday wishes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I haven't gotten a chance to watch the video yet because I think my Outlook didn't like the attachment.
[SPEAKER_06]: But maybe email it to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send it to me as a web link or something and I'll try to get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send it to me on YouSendIt or one of those sites.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's usually the best way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't see the attachment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because Outlook doesn't like attachments from people for some reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why I don't use Outlook to check our mail.
[SPEAKER_08]: I use the web mail because I can check it from work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, stop it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next up is a
[SPEAKER_08]: Carlos, emailing us.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it says, hey guys, congrats on four years.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been enjoying this podcast since August something and it's still made of win and awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aw, that's sweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's where our cake was made of too, win and awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, I went to my local GameStop to pick up Mega Man EX E6 poster they kept for me because I'm a family.
[SPEAKER_08]: And while I was talking to the manager, we're friends, out of the corner of my eye I noticed a Nintendo DS package with something in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looked like a GBA cartridge.
[SPEAKER_08]: I inquired about this and found out it was a rumble pack for Super Princess Peach, Metroid Pinball, and two other games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now this didn't surprise me, and I thought gimmicks gimmicks until I saw the price tag, $99.99.
[SPEAKER_08]: In closing, I'd just like to say, what the fuck, Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think the Rumble fact's $99.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's $9.99 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it was just a mistype or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no way that's $100.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I think maybe it was just a little oopsie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, speaking of oopsies, there's still more email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually really going through the email because I got quite a bit in just a few days.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're taping early this week, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good job, listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: Drown her in that email.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, dude.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry if I blew out somebody's speakers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Another one.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's not a name.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's actually Trace said, Hey, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was wondering if any of you have played the game Bumpies.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a DOS game, and I think there would be a remake for the PSP like they did with Lemmings.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've never heard of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never heard of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send us more info or a link or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially if it's free.
[SPEAKER_06]: Free rocks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did get an email that at first sort of pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is going to be, I'm not trying to be TMI about anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know when I said, made the comment that, yeah, if I ever saw any of my kids reenacting something from a violent video game, I'd pop them one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it wasn't necessarily that I would treat violence with violence because we got an email from one of our listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: You didn't mean you were going to pop the kid with a baseball bat, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I used my hand.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, this is what I think about.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you hit like a girl.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to get hit.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're going to get hit like a girl.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: But seriously, and I'm not going to go into any detail because it's nobody's business, but I do firsthand know the difference between abuse and punishment.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so I think that I very well know where the limits, the line would be drawn.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that
[SPEAKER_08]: The video game shouldn't be as much as the concern as the home environment that one is raised in as far as what determines if someone's going to turn out a violent person or not.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that if me just going, oh, well, don't do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, well, don't do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stand in the corner.
[SPEAKER_08]: If that's not going to do the job, I'm not beyond, you know, doing a little physical discipline.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I was spanked as a kid.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've had much worse.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, when you...
[SPEAKER_08]: You've learned the difference.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was this an email?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it was an email.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is this why I'm not going into any detail on the email?
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'd just like to clarify that, that that's my feelings toward it.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it's going to save my child growing up to be some sort of serial killer,
[SPEAKER_08]: or knowing that it's not right to go and kick somebody because they pissed you off, then I'm not beyond it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me try to spin it this way, because I like to be the one that likes to make the happy, politically correct, make everybody happy statement, so try to humor me on this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are certain choices that you get to make as a parent in the way you want to raise your kid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, there's many choices that you get to make, as long, you know, obviously you don't break the law, but, you know, there's choices that you get to make.
[SPEAKER_06]: And one of those choices is what we're talking about here, but another one that relates to the bigger topic at hand is, you know, do you want your child exposed to violent video games?
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you believe is right for your child?
[SPEAKER_06]: And so on.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's exactly my point.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that if they're four years old, yeah, sitting them down with dead rights isn't necessarily a good idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe if they're like 13, that's not so much of a deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's not just the games.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to look at it environmentally.
[SPEAKER_08]: How many children are raised with violence in their homes every day and don't own a video game system?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's my point on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, I think it starts with how parents choose to discipline their children and what they allow them to be exposed to.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was my point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's more.
[SPEAKER_08]: Two more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like I said, got a lot of emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, we may have to have a two-part show tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Crispy Creamy wants to know if you have to have an Xbox 360 to be part of the OLR army.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, what are the requirements?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, you know, I said starting up the whole...
[SPEAKER_06]: One minor bitch correction.
[SPEAKER_06]: When it was coined, the phrase, it's actually O-L-R, uppercase, M-Y, lowercase, O-L-R-M-E.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_08]: You can thank me for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think we ever specifically said how we wanted to do the O-L-R-M-E.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the jury's out on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we want to have gaming cliques all over, not just 360, but other games too.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have a Super Nintendo...
[SPEAKER_08]: We want our Street Fighter 2 Championship Edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_08]: Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_06]: That should be one branch of the OL Army, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: More to come on the OL Army when we have some ideas.
[SPEAKER_08]: But for any folks that are on MMOs, plug, plug, plug, I have a site, roleplay.darksakura.com, where I'm hosting MMO chats.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, Death Cakes still hosted there to this day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, my old Final Fantasy XI link show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even though none of us are there.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, they've been going pretty strong on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, if we get a big enough group, you know, I pick the people who are the most responsible to make moderators on the board.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, temporary hosting at least for the MMOs and even tabletop gamers will be up on roleplay.darksakura.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: In other words, the hardcore nerds.
[SPEAKER_08]: The hardcore nerds.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, I do tabletop gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you're also a hardcore nerd.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nerd pride, yo.
[SPEAKER_08]: The last one is the biggest email ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Really.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a multi-paragraph email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this was sent by Joey.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, Orange Lounge Royalty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, I like this guy already.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Second time writing.
[SPEAKER_08]: First time was on MySpace asking for Genesis titles.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd first like to thank you in the chatroom for giving some great recommendations to pimp out my Genesis 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our chatroom's getting love.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would love to join an Orange Lounge clan.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just don't call it the OC or something stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Army sounds good.
[SPEAKER_06]: We would never relate this program to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Give us a little credit, dude.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Army sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's actually OL Army, but we just said that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Though I'm getting rid of a couple of my Xbox 360 games.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's... GR, AW, and Burnout Revenge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only reason I am getting rid of...
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I'm trying to think of what GR, because my brain... Ghost Recon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ghost Recon, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, I don't play that.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's because of Chapter 2, basically the way I feel about the upgrade packs is that they are a buy them or have fun finding a game online anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have no problem with paying for more stuff but not $15.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I bought Chapter 2, I would have spent a total of approximately $80 considering taxes.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Gross Recon was fun, but hardly worth $65 taxes again, and not worth $80 to me, so I'm going to get $35 available towards something else.
[SPEAKER_08]: With Burnout, I'm simply just burned out from playing an HD Xbox clone.
[SPEAKER_08]: I looked up all the prices for stuff and I should have around $120.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm having a little battle of conscience of whether or not to put it to my inevitable purchase of a Nintendo Wii, bless you, or spend the money on some of the, I guess, delish looking Xbox 360 titles and accessories.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would like input, but I don't expect it because people are really cautious of saying anything these days.
[SPEAKER_08]: Going forward, leaning towards the Wii because I already have Zelda Twilight Princess for GameCube reserved.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will switch it to Wii most likely.
[SPEAKER_06]: In my opinion, either way, you're going to be saving that money because if you were listening to the release date segment, there's really not a lot out there right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And honestly, it sounds like you've kind of torn through a lot of the big Xbox 360 titles.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you know, I like Burnout.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's fun for a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's still fun for me right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it sounds like you've got most of the good stuff already taken care of.
[SPEAKER_06]: So right now, there's really not a lot out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you want good Xbox 360 titles, one I'm pretty excited about that looks pretty hot to me is 99 Nights.
[SPEAKER_06]: but that's not coming out until August so you'd have to be saving your money for that so I think either way you're going to end up saving your money so whether you decide to put it towards a Wii or whatever you know maybe wait and see when we get a little more information on the Wii or what have you you'll notice that my gaming week personally has slowed down a little bit and I've been talking about the same games each week because there hasn't been a lot of new stuff that's been that exciting I think most of us are kind of like we're catching up on old stuff or something so it's kind of a slow period for games right now and I think you'll end up just saving your money for the fall
[SPEAKER_08]: Play Animal Crossing with us.
[SPEAKER_08]: and then they look at the talent.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why they had them running around the E3 doing interviews.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm in no way saying that there isn't talent in those clans.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're really decent clans.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just saying that because you have to have both looks and talent to be in them.
[SPEAKER_08]: So saying that the beauty contest and whatnot is unfair because you don't actually have to be a hardcore gamer is kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: That just makes it like every other modeling show that has ever existed that they have never boycotted.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope they actually do have the Mr. Video Game Beauty contest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Average men would take competitions like these a lot more lighthearted than the ladies, and it would actually be fun and maybe even funny in a lighthearted sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: This just applies to this type of contest, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sports for men is a different story.
[SPEAKER_08]: And he also wants to know what the song we used for my Website of the Week segment.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Candy from DDR Ohasta, which is a Japanese import-only game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good luck finding that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: There are nefarious ways.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well done emails this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I applaud the listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's keep it moving.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, speaking of fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take-Two has been subpoenaed over the hot coffee.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Just when you think your tax dollars are going to something good, they're not.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yes, basically, Take-Two has received grand jury subpoenas, and this is being issued by the District Attorney of the County of New York, requesting the production of documents covering various periods beginning on October 1st, 2001, including those relating to the hot coffee issue and the creation, inclusion, and programming of hidden scenes.
[SPEAKER_04]: and also it should be noted that some people might be able to face jail time which I think is funny because the whole system is a voluntary system so how the hell are they going to go to jail over that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's time for everybody to get past it already.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just so sick of hearing about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm all about the new... Listen, you know, Grand Theft Auto San Andreas, that's a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm all about the Reservoir Dogs game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm very interested to see what happens with Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: The Nintendo DS is looking to one-up the competition, even though they don't exactly need it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're doing pretty well on the market right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, you may have heard that there is a new Opera browser coming out for the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: In Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: In Japan, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's coming out just in, like, what, less than a month?
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is a Japanese website.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo Japan has a website that talks all about the new browser.
[SPEAKER_06]: The browser will support stylus-based controls for scrolling, going between pages, inputting characters with handwriting or a keyboard on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, the bad news is the browser won't be able to display Flash, won't be able to do PDFs, and it's not going to do video or sound.
[SPEAKER_06]: So no YouTubing on your Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still a start.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope it supports good JavaScript, because then you can still do like, you know, I know they already have Homebrew for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The first PSP browser didn't support a lot of that either.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the PDFs still aren't supported on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, whatever, but still though, I mean... It's better than nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might be able to program a chatroom out of that, or an MRC client.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now we're going to have to do OLRDS.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sound like a project you want to do, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Bless them for sticking with us when we've been pretty harsh on Sony.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've been giving them a good lashing on this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bless you guys for sticking with us and realizing that we're just trying to
[SPEAKER_06]: See the big picture here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got Sony stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got two PSPs myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually have like three PlayStations.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like my PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got two PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a stack of three old school PlayStations.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dan and I tore up a KB Toys trying to find one of the last ones that had the IO port in the back before they put out the New Deal shocks.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, enough Sony penis talk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's...
[SPEAKER_06]: Talk about what other sites you can browse on your Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, you will want to visit first DarkSakura's website of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, DarkSakura, what website should the kids be looking at this week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, this site was sent to me by one of the lovely listeners whose email I read.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kawainot.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: K-A-W-A-I-N-O-T dot com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kawaii, for those who don't know any Japanese at all, means cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's cutenot.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: This site is messed up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, it's called The Comic for Cute Gone Bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: And just to describe some of this, it's all really adorable, really cutesy stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, the page I'm on right now has a necktie.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's smiling.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a four-panel, you know, vertical comic.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it keeps going down.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then the very last thing has the caption, I'm slowly strangling you.
[SPEAKER_08]: But my favorite one on here is actually the very, very first one.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has two little puffballs meeting up.
[SPEAKER_08]: The first one goes, I'm a cloud.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then nothing in the second panel.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then the third panel, it says, I'm a fart.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the last panel is the cloud one going, ah.
[SPEAKER_08]: This sight.
[SPEAKER_08]: It really follows some of the potty humor, but it's just so, huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, it earns Website of the Week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Great suggestions.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love potty humor, so good choice.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to link this particular one in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go potty humor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where you won't find potty humor, 99 Nights.
[SPEAKER_04]: And speaking of 99 Nights, you don't need a hard drive to play the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a boo-boo on the website staff at Xbox.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fired!
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody's getting fired!
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just saying that they support a hard drive for game saves.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or a memory unit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Either way, as long as you have that, good.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it is optimized for the hard drive, so that's good to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you don't need it, so go out and buy the game when it comes out in August.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, this may be a little bit of potty humor, I don't know, but everybody's been wanting to check out what's under the Wii's flap.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know there's that little flap on the Wii and everybody wants to peek under the flap and see what's there?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's so hot!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, here's what's the latest internet rumor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, not so much a rumor.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think this has been confirmed now.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is underneath that damn Wii flap?
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a tip on GoNintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Working at the Nintendo booth this year at E3 after close on the last day, everyone was involved in the tearing down and boxing up of everything that was to be sent back to corporate.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: The memory card slot is there as well as the... I thought I read somewhere that Reggie had confirmed that the GameCube stuff was there too.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, the GameCube is on top.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or side, however you have that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be in, I guess, the picture where you're looking at the front.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be on top.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, gotcha.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this...
[SPEAKER_04]: The memory card slot, he said that was what, that was, you know, under there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And people were just, you know, expecting there was another button under there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the sync... OMG, another button!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh no, sync button, which, you know, no, it's not to sync up to your Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's to, you know, sync up to your wireless controllers, just like the Xbox 360 has, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't even know there was a sync button on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: How'd you set up?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, you have wired controllers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, I have wired controllers.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you don't need a sync of... Well, when you get wireless controllers one of these days... I don't want wireless controllers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wireless controllers will get lost.
[SPEAKER_06]: The couch will eat them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't mind wired controllers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're USB.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can use them on the computer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just saying that's what it is for, so... All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, um... You know, I'm sure that they've got some more secrets, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll just have to wait and see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of stuff that has been out before, Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently it's getting made into a movie by Paul W.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anderson.
[SPEAKER_04]: He did Mortal Kombat, didn't he?
[SPEAKER_04]: He did Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't he also do Mortal Kombat?
[SPEAKER_04]: Castlevania, he's not going to shoot until he's done with the Death Race 3000 remix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Death Race 3000 Remake
[SPEAKER_04]: and there's lots of unnecessary nudity and violence.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically a movie that would have inspired Carmageddon.
[SPEAKER_04]: So just take it as that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They roll out old grannies into the street and they run through them with you and kill people.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why it's Death Race.
[SPEAKER_04]: Must watch the DVD.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's on PSP too.
[SPEAKER_04]: This has what to do with Castlevania?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I just like Death Race.
[SPEAKER_04]: But he's going to make the game and he says it's going to basically be a
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you'd say a reinterpretation, but it's basically going to cover the origins of the Belmont family and Dracula and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he's also going to do DOA, the horrible, horrible movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: He didn't do that movie, did he?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anderson did?
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: That movie frightens me.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, somebody else did that movie, didn't he?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm looking on IMDB right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: You tell us the updates, I'll tell you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jeremy Bolt, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, uh, yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are the updates?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's new on Dinner Live?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to make a sequel to it also.
Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the movie hasn't even come out yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: What if it flops?
[SPEAKER_06]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm most happy about Resident Evil movie because I actually did like Resident Evil Apocalypse.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I didn't see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it says basically Bolt confirms that... Or Bolt's head.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess Bolt might be the company.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jeremy Bolt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where's the lion?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming out with a sequel to this movie that's crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like Charlie's Angels 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look, you haven't seen the movie yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The trailer did suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to answer this question because Loki can't freaking do his research.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_06]: Directed by Corey Ewan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does that say Anderson to you?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's Corey.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good job, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hooked on phonics.
[SPEAKER_08]: Worked for Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dead or Alive should star only porn stars.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's also, you can call us, 916-226-9067.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, please have mommy or daddy's permission if you're not the one paying the phone bill.
[SPEAKER_06]: While we wait for a phone call, I'd like to ask if there's any last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a story on the internet about how awesome I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure there is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also about how modest and... Oh, look, we have a call.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is DMN, and Loki, I think the idea of putting porn stars in a Dead or Alive movie has to have been the worst idea I've ever heard come out of your mouth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait a minute, why?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want porn stars fucking up my fighting game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your fighting game's already fucked up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you seen the trailer?
[SPEAKER_03]: I stopped playing after three.
[SPEAKER_03]: because I don't want to get a 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, you're the ultra-est of Nintendo fanboys, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is not true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just because I work at Nintendo does not mean I'm a Nintendo fanboy.
[SPEAKER_06]: So in the next Gen Wars, which console are you going to buy?
[SPEAKER_03]: First, I'm buying a Wii just because I conveniently work at Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, but is there going to be a second?
[SPEAKER_03]: If somebody puts a gun to my head, I will probably break down and buy a 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: No love for PS3?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, because I had a little light for him, but after what I was reading about Kazurai being the pot calling the kettle black, that's not happening anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did you want to call in about tonight, besides berating Loki, which I appreciate?
[SPEAKER_06]: I've seen the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have seen Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have seen Wii, and I have not seen it in my department, so I can talk about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were doing a little retail tech demo of it at corporate.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looked pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to test it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm really excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me ask you a vague question.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't want to answer it, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you see anything that we didn't see at E3?
[SPEAKER_03]: I only saw people playing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't get a chance to see any screens, but they looked like they were genuinely enjoying using that software and the hardware.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, these are real people, not actors?
[SPEAKER_06]: These are real people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, wow, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, but a lot of people at E3 had a lot of fun with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had fun with the Wii at E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm definitely buying one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, I am too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just for the price alone, because I know it's going to be under $250.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no question.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything else on your mind tonight, Mr. DMN?
[SPEAKER_03]: Happy birthday.
[SPEAKER_03]: You suck for not staying in Seattle longer than two hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a layover.
[SPEAKER_06]: Give me a break.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, thank you for the birthday wishes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Too bad I went and got sunburned all over my scalp on my birthday.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now it's all gross and peeling and nasty.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'll leave you with those happy thoughts, all right?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any other last minute stories anyone would like to share?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh wait, never mind, we got another call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that was quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, you call every week and you manage to get through.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've got the luck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, what's on your mind, Raven's Dolphin?
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't believe I missed this.
[SPEAKER_06]: You missed what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well, we didn't really play up the fact that we were taping on Thursday this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, life goes on.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did you think of the show you heard so far?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can download the rest on Sunday like everyone else.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess I have two things a lot, Skype.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, stuff about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just called in to say... What was I supposed to call in to say?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh... Phoenix Wright Rules.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh... What else?
[SPEAKER_07]: The Xbox... Oh, do you have any problems with the Xbox hooking up to your PC?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, mine works fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: What kind of problems are you having with the Xbox and the PC?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I just don't want to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just...
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have Service Pack 2 installed on your PC?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I got everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just don't want to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been so long since I did it, I don't even remember what the process was.
[SPEAKER_06]: What point of the process, like are you trying to sync it on, like you downloaded the program on the PC, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it just doesn't see your Xbox at all?
[SPEAKER_06]: Doesn't see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It goes like, hey, nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go to hell.
[SPEAKER_06]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you guys on wireless networks?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, wireless wired.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have your Xbox 360 hooked to a wireless router of its own?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's not going to pick up just, like, it doesn't have Wi-Fi built inside it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to have a separate... Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to figure that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, maybe that's what's wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I have one last thing to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to buy a PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't say anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, then why, what is making you deciding to buy a PS3?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because of the Blu-ray, I want to see how it works.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to spend $500, $600 on a console to see how it works.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I have no time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't you just look at a demo at retail and make a decision there?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'll take this home and destroy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, then you sound like a collector.
[SPEAKER_06]: You sound like one of the hardcore dorks that has to have it all, like DarkSakura and myself.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's kind of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why I still have my original Game Boy and my Game Boy Color in my pocket.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I knew you were a nerd.
[SPEAKER_06]: Only nerds listen to this show, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, any other thoughts, Raven Stolfen?
[SPEAKER_08]: Only nerds host this show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just wanted to say that I can't believe I missed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to pre-tape next week's show on Saturday night because I'm going back to L.A.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a crazy schedule, and I appreciate DarkSakura and Loki putting up with my crap schedule.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we'll be taping on Saturday next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Happy birthday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll see if anyone else wants to get through.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll go for one more call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does anyone have a last-minute story they want to do?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a couple last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Code Masters is working on trying to get the original Sensible Soccer that was on Amigo, or Sensible World of Soccer, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was actually supposed to be an unlockable in Sensible Soccer 2006.
[SPEAKER_08]: They couldn't do it, so they're actually trying to, there's talk about them putting a Sensible World of Soccer on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's for our UK friends, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray for new arcade games.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got a call coming in, so I'm going to interrupt you before the second story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who else would it be?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ranma!
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, are you the one that gave up boners for Lent?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that wasn't me.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was explicit.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would never be Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it was explicit.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm not passing the buck.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, what's on your mind, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_02]: DOA the movie will rock because of one reason and one reason only.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it because that chick from Sin City's in it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I knew it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can read a straight guy's mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know exactly...
[SPEAKER_08]: What's her face from... She doesn't get naked.
[SPEAKER_08]: Too Fast, Too Furious is in it, too, as Kasumi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that the same chick?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the same chick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you see Sin City?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sin City was okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: A little overrated by the dork culture, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: A little overrated.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it was all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if Angelina Jolie truly isn't the second one, that's pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I actually...
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though I hate tabloid news, and I don't know what the fuck this has to do with gaming, as much as I hate tabloid news and all that stuff, I actually really like Angelina Jolie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, she's supposed to be doing Tomb Raider 3 right now, so hey.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, well I guess that is game related then, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what else is on your mind besides making love to whatever her name is, Devon is her name?
[SPEAKER_02]: Devon Aoki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Devon Aoki.
[SPEAKER_06]: What else is on your mind besides making sweet love to her?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Circuit City $8.96 massive fire sale.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I heard about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Weren't they like selling Final Fantasy 4?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you bring this up on Sunday's show?
[SPEAKER_06]: Everything's a blur now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Weren't they selling like Final Fantasy 4 for like $9 and you could turn around and sell it at Walmart for $18?
[SPEAKER_02]: That wasn't me.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was Set Rock 1215 and SSJ100.
[SPEAKER_02]: Man, I can't do it because I'm not crossing the bridge to Jersey to pull it off.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if I'd read it on the forums or where the hell I'd read that, but I was like, that's dirty.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's dirty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you go to the sale?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you pick anything up?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I went Saturday morning.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hit three different Circuit City.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got The Legend of Zelda, Link to the Past, Pitfall Bundled.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got Dig Dug, Digging Strike.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also picked up Final Fantasy IV, but it was $19.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was supposed to be going down to $8.96 next week, so I'm going to get that price match.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, they have Digging Strike?
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of want that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still have it sealed if you want it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: I kind of want it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send me an email.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Dig Dug.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've really been curious to check out the DS one.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's nothing else coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe when my trips die down, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to check our local Circuit City.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if they don't have it, then I'll shoot you an email.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I also picked up Dr. Mario Puzzle League.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that reminds me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tetris DS should have been called Tetris Classic NES Edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, Tetris D, yeah, I mean, sure, they hoard the NES stuff, but what's also interesting about it is that there was so much more there than just Tetris.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that mode, I can't remember what it's called, but the Metroid one, with Metroid in the background, I think it's a different game altogether.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm playing through the game, I hear the remix from Gyromite, I almost fell out of my seat, flipping out how awesome that was, and I realized, damn, I'm old.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo knows how to milk their retro factor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Believe it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Got that right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything else on your mind, Rama?
[SPEAKER_02]: Next Sunday, when the sale is official, I'm going to hit those Circuit City stores again for two more games.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they don't have it, I'm bringing my papers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to Best Buy, Target, all in just a price match and track the games down.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep us posted on your bargain hunting process, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I will be.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will.
[SPEAKER_06]: And stay away from those boners.
[SPEAKER_08]: Runtime.
[SPEAKER_08]: Final May 2007.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sweet brew party.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, crazy kids.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: You too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you just say holla at the end?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, that's all the calls for tonight, kids.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to start to wrap things up here with one more story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had your last minute thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and you completely cut me off.
[SPEAKER_06]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, then Von Chun is very well worth it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have some news for our World of Warcraft players.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then this is something I might want to know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Realm Transfer went live.
[SPEAKER_08]: Five servers are supporting it right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: is Altar of Storms, Argent Dawn, Demon's Soul, Illidian, and Warsong.
[SPEAKER_08]: Others are going to be following soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: European players should see it coming up not too far afterwards.
[SPEAKER_08]: And again, it is $25 to move between servers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just check out Blizzard's site on worldofwarcraft.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, World of Warcraft Burning Crusade.
[SPEAKER_08]: The trailer is out now.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is showing off what the new accessory in the game is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Flying Mount.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's going to be a lot of people excited about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: The trailer is actually available on Eurogamer TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you go to Eurogamer.net slash TV video, there should be a link up there to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to be watching that shortly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Last up is Dance Factory.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, basically, it's, uh, trying to, I guess, dethrone Dancing Stage in the UK, with Dancing Stage being DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's this really crappy, um, game that you can put, it's made by Comaster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's what I was... You put it in a CD and it generates steps for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a neat concept.
[SPEAKER_08]: It really is a neat concept.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, part of the fun of DDR is, you know, the interesting things that Konami likes to pass us in the music.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, uh,
[SPEAKER_08]: That's my last minute news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unless you're interested in playing Diner Dash on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I've played Diner Dash 2 on the computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't ask me why.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think because Loki was playing it at E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I was like, I want to play that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I actually downloaded it.
[SPEAKER_06]: How sad am I?
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually have one more bit of news also for our UK listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: Disgaea 2 is coming out in the UK.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I damn well hope so.
[SPEAKER_06]: That has a huge cult following to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good to hear.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks pretty interesting at E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's it, I promise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dot com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, we've got a last minute story here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, we know that the Japanese are really trying to promote the movie over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what's kind of interesting is they're doing this brand new kind of like a cafe thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Akihabara's Made in Japan That's pretty much the whole electronic district Made in Japan It's basically a cafe that's covered with Silent Hill posters which are just everywhere all sorts of memorabilia including white nurse zombies in super short skirts serving red pyramid curry and tomato juice That's awesome
[SPEAKER_06]: And one of the pictures on that site, they had the little pyramid head guy in the back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you post that in your live journal?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that was something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was from the haunted house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, this is different.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, this is something different.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nurses are pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't look like zombies.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, if you're in Japan, check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take pictures.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send them to us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Looking at the Japanese website, it's maidin.jp slash silent.html.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's some very interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, it has a picture of the tomato juice and it has a picture of the pyramid head curry, which looks very tasty, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you saw the movie, it might not be so tasty.
[SPEAKER_08]: and a huge-ass picture of Red Pyramid sitting in the background.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that was it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to remind you guys there is no Part B this week, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Part A is like an hour and a half, well over that, so you guys got a good show this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in to us and supporting Internet Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will be back next week with episode number 190.
[SPEAKER_06]: For those folks that like to listen live, please keep in mind that's going to be taped Saturday night,
[SPEAKER_06]: at 7pm due to the fact I'm going on a work trip to LA.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just can't stop traveling this July.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then we'll be back on a regular Sunday slot the week after that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So in the meantime, have a great week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Enjoy your games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's made in, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Write us some emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: Write us some voicemails.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't mean to cut you off.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: We haven't done our last thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm getting to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, fine then, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_08]: Bite my butt, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_08]: Eat your red pyramid curry.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is I hope you washed it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, baby, just for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't find this trademark and it's driving me nuts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it's here.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem is it's really hard to search this stupid Japanese trademark database.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a great week, kids.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see you next week for more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!