[SPEAKER_05]: Tonight, June 25th, 2006.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting developments with the Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: TiVo is coming to your PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: And happy birthday to... Sonic the Hedgehog.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good evening everybody and welcome to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is June 25th, 2006 and you're listening to episode number 188 of our little program.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining me as always, say hello to DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
Sleepy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a little exhausted.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll get into wine in a little while though.
[SPEAKER_04]: But say hello also to Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also joining us tonight, say hello to our special guest, the 23rd Magus.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yo, what's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Caffeinated.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, you just had a birthday recently.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, 21st.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I was going to say, it's a big one.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's 21st.
[SPEAKER_04]: So how did you celebrate the 21st birthday?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you go to a bar, get tossed?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Had a Guinness, went to bed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think my 21st birthday was probably about that exciting too, so it's all good.
[SPEAKER_02]: No big deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's like you do everything bad and then when you're 21 it's like, eh, no big deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I'm actually old enough to be doing this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I can do it legally.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, what's the reason to?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go ahead and start this show off.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are here to talk about video games and gaming news and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're going to get into how is your gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, just a couple announcements.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, join our chat room, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Click on chat if you are listening live here on this Sunday evening.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should head on over there and listen.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can always listen to our program live on OrangeLoungeRadio.com every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you can listen to us live on All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's AllGames.com every Monday night at 7 p.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: with a couple repeats Tuesday afternoon.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you can't do chat during then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, because we can only be here live once.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, the other announcement I wanted to say was it's our fourth birthday this week, officially.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: The First Episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: Antidisestablishmentarianism Duck Hunt We just dated ourselves I'm the low B here You need to gain a few more levels
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, start us off!
[SPEAKER_00]: I played a little World of Warcraft pretty much long enough to make a character on a server with my coworkers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, my coworkers play World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_00]: Played some Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Holding off getting my copy of Oendon for a little bit just because stupid stuff getting in the way of my fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I did my tabletop gaming this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, I do tabletop gaming.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's really about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of tabletop game are you guys playing?
[SPEAKER_04]: We're playing Werewolf.
[SPEAKER_00]: Our Buffy game is on hiatus for a season.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not only have you dated yourself this evening, now you've made yourself an obvious nerd.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who plays Buffy roleplay?
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to be a hardcore nerd to be doing Buffy roleplay.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're the one that picked up the GURPS book today.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't know what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, what's a GURP?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that like a LARP?
[SPEAKER_00]: I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, my second roleplay ever was GURPS.
[SPEAKER_00]: My third was Shadowrun.
[SPEAKER_00]: My fourth was D&D.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, you have dated yourself.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have definitely not progressed past third edition D&D.
[SPEAKER_00]: I refuse to play third edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: I started on second edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: I still had first edition books.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not the first person I've heard say something negative about third edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's so bad about it?
[SPEAKER_00]: Everything.
[SPEAKER_00]: Except for constitution-based magic casting, I miss Thacko.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it's so easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Call of Duty 2 Call of Duty 2
[SPEAKER_03]: Download for free to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there was one of the maps that had this giant silo on it, and you basically climb up to the top and snipe people down from the top of the... So that's actually pretty fun, to play just that map.
[SPEAKER_03]: Played a little bit more Blazing Angels, trying to beat the damn thing all the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played a little bit of Mutant Storm Reloaded, because I'm on level 89, and I have to beat it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then again, all the effort I put into that, and I looked at the achievement that that unlocks, and that's like 15 points.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like,
[SPEAKER_03]: is it really worth the 15 points?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you're on level 89 at this point, you might as well finish it.
[SPEAKER_04]: How many levels are there?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like 95 or something, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, 89.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're on the very last level and you just can't beat it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: The difficulty, like, it ramps up very strange.
[SPEAKER_03]: It gets really hard, then it kind of gets easier, then it's super duper hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it's an okay game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just need to finish this and get the damn achievement.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Gauntlet for a little bit, and I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I tried that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Achievement points?
[SPEAKER_04]: You want more achievement points?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I was looking at your profile, and you don't have any achievement points for Gauntlet, and I have like 25.
[SPEAKER_04]: Therefore, I am the better Gauntlet player than you.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because I haven't played Gauntlet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, what else did I play?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I played...
[SPEAKER_00]: Wack-a-mole
[SPEAKER_03]: A whole lot of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've been trying to see how we can exploit the demo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I keep forgetting to download that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fun because the cars, the police cars are stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: They downloaded that at Arena the week of E3 and I played it like once and it was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I haven't been excited about a test drive game since like the days of Commodore 64 and this one looks pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: We managed to, I was playing it, the Lamborghini goes quite fast off-road, ironically enough, and
[SPEAKER_03]: The police cannot get you if you're off-road.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we took an SUV, we slammed into it, and we knocked it into the ocean.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well done.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should get points for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We knocked it into the ocean, which is supposed to be just, like, you know, a few inches deep when it's washing ashore, but apparently the way the game's designed, it's just a cliff, and the car just disappeared.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I jumped the fence, and I jumped into this yard that I couldn't get out of, which was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I also got my car smashed...
[SPEAKER_03]: Stuck Between a Rock and a House, and what other fun stuff did we do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, we jumped a mountain.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the game is very flawed, but I guess it's just a demo right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's obviously not even near finished, but there's a lot of things that got fixed on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot, a lot of things.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the game that my boss says we'll get him to buy in Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, you know, there's a lot of better games out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why this one?
[SPEAKER_04]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: My gaming week was also kind of unexciting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't really play a lot of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played Burnout, you know, because there's nothing more fun than doing the synth pop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Burnout, running through the traffic attack.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then once in a while I'll throw in Journey Greatest Hits or ABBA or something like really, you know, weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's fun to drive to.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I was playing World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was on LA for most of the week with a business trip.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which reminds me, if you go to All Games Interactive's show, and I know a lot of you guys listen to them over at allgames.com, I'm on their Tuesday show this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: because I dropped by Arena right after work on Tuesday, and I was in a really bad mood on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I know I was wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: I woke up at 3.30 in the morning on Tuesday, so I really beat up on a couple of their regulars, and I almost felt bad when I listened to the playback of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, God, I was rude.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like going to someone's house and drinking all their soda and eating all their food.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of what I did on Tuesday, so
[SPEAKER_04]: Check it out if you want to see me being a bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, as far as new games go, I did look at Big Brain Academy for like five seconds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fortunately, I'll have to wait and give a full review on that next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, let me talk about a book.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you might be thinking, wait, why would you talk about a book on a video game show?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it has to do with gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: My birthday happens to be tomorrow, and Dark Sakura treated me to a queen for a day, took me out to lunch, took me out to dessert, and then took me to a bookstore and said...
[SPEAKER_04]: I Am 8-Bit
[SPEAKER_04]: And Mario looks kind of, yeah, it's got a little titty in the book, which makes it even better, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Some porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, you said it was erotica.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm sorry, it was erotica.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Jamie was making fun of me, like, ah, you're buying porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, no, it's erotica.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Mario's all looking confused, like he doesn't know what to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you see, you know how sometimes guys, when they don't know what to do, they'll write notes on their hand?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, when they want to break up and don't know what to say, they'll write it on their hand?
[SPEAKER_04]: I Am 8-Bit
[SPEAKER_04]: WonderDog Harold says, I'm sorry Mario, but my dress is in another castle.
[SPEAKER_04]: In reference to the photo I was describing there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: and to the chatter that gets the most points or the average points, the best average points, wins a Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it just is incentive to participate live in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you're not there, you should be asking yourself, why am I not there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, getting into some gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are not the only ones celebrating a birthday today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, Sonic is also celebrating his 15th anniversary.
[SPEAKER_04]: And GameTap's getting in on the fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're offering subscribers a trio of titles, which are the lock-on versions of Sonic.
[SPEAKER_04]: For instance, Sonic the Hedgehog and Knuckles, Knuckles and Sonic 2, and Sonic 3, Sonic and Knuckles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember how you could use the cart and plug it into the old carts and you have a new game?
[SPEAKER_00]: That was amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: What a cute technology that you never really saw outside of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least I don't remember it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I liked how you could plug in random Sega games on the cartridge, and then you could do the special stages in different ways with different games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't even know you could use it with other games.
[SPEAKER_00]: You'd have to... Oh, I forgot what it was.
[SPEAKER_00]: You had to hold down the buttons while you loaded the game, and it would load up all the special stages on different cartridges.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, anyway, you can download those on GameTap.
[SPEAKER_04]: No plug-in, no cartridges needed, all that good stuff if you're a GameTap member.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, they added on to GameTap TV three behind-the-scenes looks at Sonic the Hedgehog.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you like to watch that stuff that GameTap TV produces, which is far better than anything GeForce is producing currently, check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, just to join in on the fun here, Sega has revealed that they're going to be doing two new portable Sonic games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's a first look at those screens there.
[SPEAKER_04]: What they're basically doing is that they're going to do Sonic the Hedgehog Genesis for the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's going to have additions to...
[SPEAKER_04]: I played the hell out of that at E3 Oh, what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's so good And I won all the time and they gave me a t-shirt But it really is, it's almost like playing, you know
[SPEAKER_00]: Old School Sonic with updated graphics, but instead your goal is just to make it through the level as fast as humanly possible.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like doing the old Tails races in Sonic Adventure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just on 2D.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you play it at all?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, it's definitely one that I would suggest everyone to get out.
[SPEAKER_00]: But you know...
[SPEAKER_00]: We've had a lot of game purchases go on lately.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, Mario cut half a million copies in the US in over one month.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just over a month.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're saying basically 20 copies were sold every minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I think they did the math and that didn't end up being correct.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, it's a lot.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, in the first two days they sold 136,500 units.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, basically, that's just
[SPEAKER_00]: Pretty hardcore for game sales.
[SPEAKER_00]: Half a million, you said?
[SPEAKER_00]: Half a million, 500,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty darn good for a game that really hasn't been out that long, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's at the top of the charts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's having the same... The rated E games are taking over.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's having the same non-stop hysteria-ness here that it's been having in Japan, essentially.
[SPEAKER_02]: This goes to show that old school will win you points for the masses.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially when it comes to Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Sony were to release a new Crash Bandicoot for the PSP, I don't know if it would have the same... Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Crash Bandicoot, they've really beaten into the ground.
[SPEAKER_04]: But isn't that weird that we feel burnt out on Crash Bandicoot, yet Nintendo has way hord Mario more often.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't need to deviate from the formula, because it works.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other thing too is Crash Bandicoot is in the first party character.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, I tried to think of a Sony mascot and that's the best thing I can come up with.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's because it was at one point their mascot because that's all they really had.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now they don't really have a mascot.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have giant crabs, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Giant crabs could be the mascot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: XBOX Live Arcade is coming to the retailers!
[SPEAKER_03]: and Casual Games would extend the 360's appeal to non-hardcore audiences and also those people that and I don't know why people don't have broadband yet but the people that don't have broadband can't download them but ironically enough
[SPEAKER_03]: Information arrived to me this week, saying that actually this is going to be happening sooner than later.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is going to be a game coming out in September called the Xbox Live Arcade Unplugged.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what it's going to contain is a few games, including Geometry Wars, Texas Hold'em, which is supposed to be coming out in July, I think, Wick, Bejeweled 2, Outpost's Cloaky X, Hardwood Backgammon, which I don't believe is out yet, and
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Badgammon is on the marketplace, I'm pretty sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hearts and Badgammon, I'm pretty sure, like the hardwood games or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll also come with a free month of gold, which they include with almost every game nowadays, and 100 free Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can download some crappy icons.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because that's about what 100 points will buy you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's coming, and it's supposed to retail for about $39.99 for the whole package.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's pretty sweet if you don't have access to broadband and live and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other than that, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could see them doing this later on and stuff with maybe some more games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, you said the information came to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: How did you get this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anonymous tip or were you listening in a top secret board meeting?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I saw on Joystick when they ran the article, I saw that there was a little addendum and they said, thanks for the tip, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm like...
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_04]: What is Loki doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: I look every day at least like four or five times a day for new information.
[SPEAKER_04]: That surprises me that the mainstream gaming press doesn't have their nose in retail somehow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they do.
[SPEAKER_04]: They watch their Best Buy release dates and how awfully long those are.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting, that's so interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, also, Xbox Live, one thing they're definitely looking forward to over on Xbox Live is Luminous.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's interesting about this, though, you know, we've talked a little bit about Luminous and how it's supposed to be one of the more expensive Xbox Live arcade games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to go for 1,200 Microsoft points or $15.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get this, supposedly, it's not going to have Xbox Live multiplayer on it by default.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's going on is Tetsuya Mitsugushi, who created the game, he actually detailed some plans where he's saying that the multiplayer support is going to be an add-on that's separately buyable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, they have not finalized the decision on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, um, that's basically saying that, okay, even though you're spending $15 on the game, it's not gonna be multiplayer unless you spend a little more money.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, also, you're gonna have to do licensed music, backgrounds, that's all gonna be premium downloads as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, now, an interesting comparison's been made where, if you think about it, Luminous, when it first came out on the PSP, was $40.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this makes this whole Luminous Live thing look like a real deal, but, uh,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of think, you know, if the creators of this game wanted to they could probably get away with releasing this as an over-the-counter title in the nice little clamshell and everything for $39.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, they release these games all the time, especially early on in a console's life period, where the game takes up very little space on the disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: Think about the first PlayStation 2 games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were all on CD.
[SPEAKER_04]: They barely took up any space at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if the creators of this game wanted to, they didn't have to sell it on arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: They probably could have done an in-store release for $40 and gotten away with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll bet you anything they do that too, just like because now we're seeing it with, you know, the thing you were talking about where they have the arcade titles coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: for retail for those folks who aren't plugged in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll bet you anything, Luminous does come out that way as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, and only kind of when I put it in that light where it's, well, at least you're not paying 40 bucks for the clamshell, am I not pissed off about this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then you also get the games like Call of Duty 2 that released, you know, the game of your edition, which just basically has the game and the downloadable content for it on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they re-skew it as something new.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of,
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting way of, you know, selling things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to our chatroom at OrangeLoungeRadio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Funnydale says, So, what are you telling me?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that a game that costs $20 on the PSP is going to cost me $200 to play the full version on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know about $200.
[SPEAKER_04]: That might be a little extreme.
[SPEAKER_04]: But by the time all these micropayments and, you know, multiplayer and extra skins and stuff add up, yeah, you're probably looking at about $40, which is what the original game would have cost you on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: But again, I kind of go back to that scenario, you know, they could get away with... If they had never said this was going to be on arcade, if they just said Luminous is coming out for the Xbox 360, I don't think people would have batted an eye at a $40 price tag for it, because that's what all the other games cost.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the thing is, and I would still be kind of pissed off about it, is that they didn't really do anything with...
[SPEAKER_03]: The graphics and stuff, it's not improved in any way.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just a port.
[SPEAKER_04]: From what we saw of Luminous 2 at E3, not a damn thing's changed there either.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't know if that was just an early announcement build or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope so, because that would be very disappointing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Luminous is a fantastic game, and I hope they're not going to screw the series by milking it without giving us something new with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's kind of what happened with Tetris.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why Tetris kind of went downhill for a long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, granted, it's had a resurgence a couple times, Tetris DS being the latest one, but there was a while there where we were just all burned out on Tetris, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: You kind of see Tetris on the shelf, you go, oh, goody, another Tetris clone, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, speaking of live games, the Xbox Live Arcade Unplugged wasn't the only thing that I heard about that was coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: We actually got updates on all of the Xbox...
[SPEAKER_03]: 360 accessories so they're going to be coming out including Xbox Live Vision which we now have a date which is supposed to be September 20th around there you know it shouldn't change too much I can confirm though it is going to be coming with Uno bundled in there as well as yet again a one month trial to Xbox Live Gold and a headset is going to be packaged with that as well
[SPEAKER_03]: So you will be getting the nice little camera and all that other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's also cool is the camera can work with your PC, which I think is really neat also.
[SPEAKER_03]: No price yet on that though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also going to be coming out in November on the 15th so far is the 256 megabyte memory unit.
[SPEAKER_03]: No price on that yet either, but of course...
[SPEAKER_03]: for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I also know...
[SPEAKER_03]: that the HD DVD player is supposed to be coming out around that same time too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go into our chat room, orangelunchradio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: GK128 says, Bastards already bought Uno.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure that's the way most of us feel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do we get if we already have Uno?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they going to give us some points?
[SPEAKER_03]: They should just give us Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's just going to be a sucker type thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sucker.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got to play for all these months before the game came out on shelves.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm surprised they don't sell the live arcade games in stores.
[SPEAKER_03]: For example, when I bought my live 12-month kit that came with the headset, because I bought a core system and I didn't have a headset, which I never really used a headset either, but it came with Bank Shop Billiards 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just one of those cards that you pull the tab off and it has a code on it and you redeem it for a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm surprised they don't sell those in the stores.
[SPEAKER_04]: My all thought was that the reason why they did it that way is because they're bypassing retail when they sell it on Xbox Live Arcade and that's how they can get away with doing it so cheap.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, $5 for Geometry Wars, that's a freaking steal.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they had released that game through a retailer, you would have had so many people to go through that want a bite of the money coming from the consumer, they would not be able to sell that game for $5.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would have been at least $20, if not more.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's kind of why I always felt that
[SPEAKER_04]: XBOX Live Arcade
[SPEAKER_02]: Various games, Half-Life 2, Sin episodes, Darwinia, things like that Downloadable content, they can offer it for cheaper And in some cases a lot easier than just going to the store Okay
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, also something that could be coming out for the 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know if this is going to be for sure yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, this is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, Peter Moore recently gave an interview on another podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've talked about these guys before.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gamertag Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: They snagged Peter Moore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lucky guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: When Peter Moore was on that station, he was saying that shoulder buttons, triggers, analog sticks, D-pads, there's a lot going on when you compare it to an Atari 2600 button and stick.
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically what he's saying is that he's imagining that he's kind of insinuating that they're going to be doing a simpler controller, basically with the Xbox Live Arcade downloads in mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because if you think about a lot of those Xbox Live Arcade downloads, Uno, Geometry Wars, you don't really use a lot of the buttons on the Xbox 360 controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: They could get away with releasing a controller with one or two buttons, and most of the games would support that there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, nothing is being confirmed by Microsoft directly,
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're basically saying that, yeah, we're going to continue to innovate wherever we can.
[SPEAKER_04]: But still, it's kind of interesting when Peter Moore says this.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know he's in the know of what's going on at Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's so stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're buying a 360, you obviously know how to use a controller anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, all the other games you're playing use the entire controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think you should be familiar enough with it to all of a sudden become retarded when you start playing an Xbox Live Arcade game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And don't tell me you're just buying the system to play those Live Arcade games because that's even more retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about the whole trying to make the system accessible to people who aren't the hardcore gamers?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I know quite a few people would probably think the idea of playing UNO is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: That aren't the hardcore gamers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are they going to be buying a 360 to play UNO?
[SPEAKER_03]: Please don't tell me that they're actually going to go spend $400 on a system to play UNO.
[SPEAKER_00]: UNO!
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, if they need something so simple, they can just go to Walmart and buy a UNO deck.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the other thing, too, is they don't have to use the analog sticks.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's way too complex, you know, using an analog nub on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, and most of the games anyways are about one or two buttons.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not like they have to remember which button they have to push.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about in trying to justify it as a family purchase?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, that, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And I can tell you this much, buying accessories for a 360, it's expensive as it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Each one of those controllers is about 50 bucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what, I think you should be fine with just the one controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, again, Devil's Advocate, why then do they sell DVD remotes separately?
[SPEAKER_04]: For like PlayStation 2, you don't need it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well the reason why they sell those separately is sometimes those DVD remotes have features that you can't normally do, like angle change and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Normally you can pull up all that on the PlayStation, you just have to know your way around the menus.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you can do it through menus, but why bother doing it through menus when you have dedicated buttons for that?
[SPEAKER_00]: That's not to say, you know... That's for the convenience of the consumer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it is for the convenience.
[SPEAKER_03]: But here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still convenient to use the same buttons on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have triggers and analog sticks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, how hard is it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not like I can't figure out the buttons.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty simplified.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we welcome your feedback on this issue.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can always send us an email.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or we'll open up the Skype line a little later on in the program.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I suppose they can, you know, save some money, you know, especially since, you know, the 360 is supposedly going to, well, the rumor is going around that it's supposed to drop in price around Christmas.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think that's a big bunch of crap, if you ask me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, you know, this has been going back and forth, you know, people saying, oh, yeah, it's going to drop, you know, we heard it from such and such person.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to drop $100 to make it look, you know, more enticing for people, you know, not to buy the Wii and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then, again, at the same time, you know, why do they need to drop the price when the PS3 is, you know, $600?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it's going to drop, and if I remember correctly, I think Peter Moore actually said, no, they're not dropping the price of the system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's saying that the price is going to drop?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it just internet rumor in general?
[SPEAKER_03]: A source close to Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Joe Nobody, basically saying that it's going to drop.
[SPEAKER_04]: A friend of a friend's cousin's brother's uncle's.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, who probably works in the help center and is an expert on everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it's going to drop.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually see a small price cut reasonable.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think like $100, but I could see like maybe they throw in a game, like a cheapy game.
[SPEAKER_04]: A bundle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, or they cut it by $20, $40, maybe $50.
[SPEAKER_04]: That seems a lot more possible, especially around the holidays.
[SPEAKER_03]: That seems feasible, like Forza 2 and the 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could see that happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: That makes more sense because you spend the money on the game system.
[SPEAKER_03]: You want to have something to play on Christmas morning.
[SPEAKER_03]: There, that makes more sense than dropping the price of the system $100.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I don't think that's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going over to our chat room, Jada2006 says, I laugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone actually named Joe Nobody is listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess maybe there's somebody he knows who's actually named Joe Nobody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good job, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jeremy Todd 1 says, if the Wii launches at $250, then the 360 price will drop to $250 and $350.
[SPEAKER_04]: He seems pretty convinced that that drop would happen to be competitive with the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, let's see, HitStun has a question.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, how much is an original Xbox now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it still $199?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aren't they $179?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're cheaper than that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's around $150, if not $99.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know it's supposed to drop to $99.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could see them doing that to compete with the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will research very quickly here while we move on to some other stories.
[SPEAKER_00]: There is something you can do with the money that you're saving on an Xbox 360 if they do drop the price.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Buy porn?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, that too.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can spend $25,000 on a Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: This sushi place was crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a couple of them that were $100,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Now I know which restaurant I'm going to knock off if I'm going to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, this restaurant carries diamonds.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going there.
[SPEAKER_00]: I wonder if you complain if you get it for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically you have this equivalent of Game Boys.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, there's a $25,000 Game Boy put out by Swiss Supply Direct.
[SPEAKER_03]: Figures a Swiss would come up with something crazy like this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, it's my turn.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, we might have listeners there, jackass.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway, it has a diamond set on the display screen.
[SPEAKER_00]: It has diamond off-on buttons.
[SPEAKER_00]: It has the original cables, extra game cartridges, a blue leather display case.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's made out of solid 18-karat gold.
[SPEAKER_03]: The question is, does it have a knife and a corkscrew in it as well?
[SPEAKER_00]: I think so, you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it weighs 27 ounces, it's supposed to be, you know, the price is supposed to be just, like, right on, you know, cost of material and sale.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, um, and the thing is, is that it's not even, like, a cool Game Boy, it's like an old Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, it's not even a fucking DS or a GBA or a Micro?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it's a freaking Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a Game Brick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why didn't they just do, like, a Game Boy Micro?
[SPEAKER_03]: They would have spent less money on it, and then...
[SPEAKER_03]: Outro Music
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey guys, you should play my new game, Diamond Quest.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be on my $25,000 Swiss game wine.
[SPEAKER_03]: You saw that they renamed that game to Diamond Quest so that she didn't look like a complete idiot.
[SPEAKER_03]: They should rename it to Stupid Spoiled Whores Game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stupid Spoiled Whore the Game.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, I hate her.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, sorry, we do that once in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: The four years of Orange Lounge Radio, we've actually slipped into Paris Hilton's chat a couple times.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_04]: It keeps coming back to her.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's scary.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go way off topic here again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't help it, but I've actually caught some of the third season of The Simple Life.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that show is basically like...
[SPEAKER_03]: If I were the husband in any one of those situations, I would be getting my ass handed to me because they get them in so much trouble and then their wives basically just rip into them.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, it's like basically... Excuse me, I have a question.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this a video game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm getting to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, actually I'm not.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, um... Okay, completely off topic there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of talked about something that we talked about last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Louisiana and their game laws.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically the one where they were going to be fining the hell out of retailers for selling indecent stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, a couple things have happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, Judge has actually gotten the law temporarily blocked.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically, of course, this is all the ESA is doing as far as being able to
[SPEAKER_03]: The ESEA and EMA have filed suit last Friday to overturn the law.
[SPEAKER_03]: According to the court filings later that day, a federal judge, James J. Brady, granted the trade group's request for a temporary restraining order preventing the law from being enforced.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, the three reasons why they... It's very...
[SPEAKER_03]: Controversial and goes against a lot of the First Amendment and I think goes the 14th Amendment of the Constitution.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically the ESA's comment on this was, not only does the act directly restrict the decimation and receipt of considerable amounts
[SPEAKER_03]: A fully protected expression.
[SPEAKER_03]: But because of its numerous vague terms, the act also creates a chilling effect on a great deal of speech as video game creators, publishers, manufacturers, distributors, and retailers will respond to the act's uncertainty by self-censoring, depriving both adults and children access of undeniably protected expression.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically what they're saying is, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: What exactly is obscene?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's nothing really defining it in this.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, because of this, game publishers and companies will have to start self-censoring the games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's never good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So on top of that, though, the Louisiana governor has a second bill that's gone in place, which I actually kind of like this one.
[SPEAKER_03]: basically add games to lists of media that can be harmful to minors and the ESA is actually for this one and what it's supposed to do is basically just kind of give actual guidelines to what is obscene and basically not meant for kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of like the same loss that the normal
[SPEAKER_03]: and other media like TV and movies go by.
[SPEAKER_03]: That one's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that one actually got signed into law.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's always good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they did the same thing in Maryland actually with that kind of law where basically falls under the obscenity laws.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: So is this going off the ESRB or what's going to determine... It's basically they have the guidelines.
[SPEAKER_03]: What it is is
[SPEAKER_03]: If the material is designed to incite or appeal to the... I hate law terminology.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's so stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyways, it's basically if it's obscenely offensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: If the game is Baby Raper 2000 or something like that, that's not going to be... They'll have the right to pull that off the shelves.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would want to try out Baby Raper 2000 before I start knocking on it, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just kidding, Jesus, God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, basically, it's, you know, if it's harmful to minors, and I think that they're gonna go by the ESRB's, you know, rating system for this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not sure, you know, because, to be honest, they can take laws nowadays and just spin them any way they, you know, benefits them, and
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I guess if the ESA isn't arguing with it, then I guess I can go for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know what I think is also pretty ridiculous, though, is that actually the Parents Television Council is actually pretty upset about the...
[SPEAKER_00]: ESRB's commitment to parent campaign.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's got sand in their vagina about it?
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, Tim Winter, who is the executive director, basically said in his press release, to quote, yet another dodge by the video game industry to avoid accountability for the harm it inflicts on children.
[SPEAKER_00]: What they don't seem to understand is that it isn't the industry's job to protect their children.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the parents' job to protect their children.
[SPEAKER_00]: by limiting another facility's free speech, they're basically passing on the responsibility that they agreed to as parents to another facility.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, I do agree that at a certain age, there are certain things you should not be exposed to.
[SPEAKER_00]: However, when you have a child, you accept the responsibility of guarding your children from those things that you don't want them to see.
[SPEAKER_00]: and this is just them not wanting to take responsibility for what they need to be doing.
[SPEAKER_00]: They want to put the blame on somebody else instead of their own failures.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's how I see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would love to get that guy on this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, so would I. We should send an email.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we should.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm all for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't you work on it?
[SPEAKER_00]: I will work on trying to get him on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you like how I passed the buck there?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll table it for future discussion.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what happens when we get pissed off?
[SPEAKER_04]: People die.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the FUs of the week are brought upon us.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because I must destroy them all.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, my FU of the week goes toward the stupid drunk girl from last night.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, I took my friend Julie to Berkeley yesterday for her birthday.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, you know, because I wasn't going to get to hang out with her tonight for her birthday party.
[SPEAKER_00]: And we had a good time.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was really, really worn out and tired, you know, on the way home, so I dropped Julie off and rested for a little bit at her house so that I'd have enough energy to get home.
[SPEAKER_00]: And as I was approaching one of the major intersections, for anybody who's in the Sacramento area or who has been here, is when you're going down White Avenue toward the interstate on-ramp
[SPEAKER_00]: Right before Marconi, basically this girl, I was in the far left lane, there was a lane between us, and there was a girl in the far right lane ahead of me.
[SPEAKER_00]: And she suddenly spins out of control in her little Mini Cooper.
[SPEAKER_00]: And spun right and then swerved around left and just went into a full 360 in the middle of the road.
[SPEAKER_00]: And was heading directly for me.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I threw on my brakes and swerved and she did the same and we actually avoided a head-on collision by less than four inches.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, uh, yeah, it was pretty scary.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, uh... Did your whole life flash before your eyes and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_00]: I think my brain shut down.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was so... I was tired already, you know, but I was good to get home.
[SPEAKER_00]: This just had my adrenaline going so bad, which actually I'm supposed to avoid, you know, by my doctor's orders, but... Anyway, I pulled up ahead, I watched from my rearview mirror to see what was going on.
[SPEAKER_00]: She turned around and started heading out, so I just decided to go home because I was too shaken up by it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because, I mean, I had headlights flashed in my eyes.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was pretty scary.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't let this comment in chat go by, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to hear this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jeremy Todd 1 says, Jamie, you have a lot of close calls in traffic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you're actually the one that's a bad driver.
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: Trust me.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not the one who drives drunk, who spins out in the middle of the road.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not the one who bumped into a couple other cars.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it was actually my good driving that saved my life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Only when she's playing Mario Kart is she a bad driver.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't play Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: What driving games do you play?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you play any driving games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Red Racer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Red Racer, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do you play Mario Kart?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway, I got up to one of the lights a few blocks up, and a guy in a Camaro who I knew was a little bit behind me in the other lane pulled up and said, hey, what happened, what happened?
[SPEAKER_00]: And then she pulled up next to him, so he just turned and talked to her.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's like, what were you thinking?
[SPEAKER_00]: What was going on?
[SPEAKER_00]: What's wrong?
[SPEAKER_00]: She's like, I just want to go home.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sorry, I just want to go home.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's, by the way, exactly what she sounded like, I'm not joking.
[SPEAKER_00]: And he's like, are you drunk?
[SPEAKER_00]: And she's like, no, yeah, a little.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just so you know, DarkSakura, Fireboma and Chad is backing you up, saying it's because she lives in California, kids.
[SPEAKER_00]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_04]: People here can't drive, they really can't.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nor can they in certain parts of Georgia.
[SPEAKER_00]: Isn't that right, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_00]: If he's listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby had to leave, but he was listening.
[SPEAKER_00]: But no, I should have stopped and got her license plate number, but honestly, I was like, I'm getting away from her, and just shot up onto the freeway and went home.
[SPEAKER_00]: But that was seriously really scary.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's why, you know, you've got the, oh, don't drink and drive, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, don't do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you do, you're a fucking retard.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you have... It takes...
[SPEAKER_00]: For, I think, a double shot of liquor, depending on your metabolism too, by the way, but for a double shot of liquor, it takes about three hours to get it fully out of your system.
[SPEAKER_00]: For a beer, it's about the same.
[SPEAKER_00]: She, her eyes were so dilated, it wasn't funny.
[SPEAKER_00]: I could see from, you know, two lanes over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Marin in chat says, she plays Derby Owners Club.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of like driving, right guys?
[SPEAKER_04]: Guys?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've beaten my horse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, but,
[SPEAKER_00]: Fuck her!
[SPEAKER_00]: And everybody who drives drunk, a big, humongous, horkin' fuck you.
[SPEAKER_00]: I hope that you get arrested.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, I kinda have, I just, you know, her whole story reminds me of the time that I was driving, don't ask me why, to play DDR at like midnight over at, you know, CCL, you know, Country Club Lanes, the ultra ghetto bowling alley that had DDR bits up in 24 hours a day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, that was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's this guy who was in a van who, um, swerved across all the traffic and swerved back over and went on the off-ramp, but except for making the turn for the off-ramp, just kind of jumped over the lane and kind of drove off-road for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I was like, I'm all, man, that guy's, like, not really, you know, paying attention to where he's going.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, whoa, oh, he just went over the edge.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that was funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, um, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: On to our views.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, fuck you, stupid 24-hour fitness...
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I went and signed up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, granted, this is how every single place is, where they have your sign-up fee or whatever, and then they have a processing fee of like $70.
[SPEAKER_03]: What exactly are they doing for that $70?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I saw her process the account and basically type it into a computer for about one minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that was $77 worth of work right there?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: And by the way, for $77, she needs to learn how to type.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU goes to that great big ball of fire in the sky, the sun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went to a theme park in the Bay Area called Great America yesterday to kind of celebrate my birthday with some friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: And believe me, I'm not stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I put sunscreen like all over, all over, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's SPF 60 because I want to make sure I wasn't going to get burned up.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, it didn't really occur to me that, oh, Rob, you have spiky hair now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should probably put some sunblock on your scalp.
[SPEAKER_04]: because basically what I ended up with is a sunburned scalp and you can see a little bit of the redness there here in studio where basically the top of my head got sunburned.
[SPEAKER_04]: So F you to the sun for burning people.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a nice thing to do to the creatures of the earth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Magus, we'll give you one quick F you if you got one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, this is not normally something I F you but first I'm going to hear this.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to Blizzard in the 1.11 patch which just came out
[SPEAKER_02]: On Tuesday, they added new content, Nexramus, that kind of stuff, revamped a lot of things, Mage and Shaman talent reviews, but they made one crucial error.
[SPEAKER_02]: They made the Looking for Group channel global across the entire population of the server.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wild players, if you know Goldshire, if you know Baron's Chat, it's now across the entire server.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't even try to use the LFG channel to LFG.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, they had failed to take into account how utterly stupid 95% of their player base is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wondered why that channel was freaking off the charts in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, there cannot be this many people looking for, like, you know, Ragefire Chasm and Deadmines in Silver Pine Forest.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, what the hell is wrong?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, that was stupid of Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good job, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, wow, that was like our longest FU segment ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, I wanted to say real quick before we get back into the news.
[SPEAKER_04]: To follow up to the chat question earlier, how much does an original Xbox cost?
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the weird thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've gone to like five different sites.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not able to find a new Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did they stop making them and I just forgot they did?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just, wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I guess then here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can get them on GameStop.com and I imagine EB as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: A refurb system is $99 for most of the used ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can get a factory refurb for $129.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it looks like if you want a new one from Microsoft themselves, tough poop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tough poopy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so yeah, that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Need for Speed Carbon, which, um,
[SPEAKER_03]: Need for Speed Carbon Copy Need for Speed Carbon Copy
[SPEAKER_03]: You will fly over the edge and die!
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the soundtrack to that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love how the commercials for that totally spoiled the after credits ending thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't even bother to... I could care less, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could care less about that movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, to cleanse the palate of drifting, we actually have some confirmation by Uchiyama Daisuke, who is Namco Bandai's chief producer, stating that there will be both Tekken and Soul Calibur games being worked on...
[SPEAKER_00]: on the... Well, they're not saying specifically what system it's going to be on, but we are going to get a new Soul Calibur, a new Tekken, and the guess is that it will be PS3.
[SPEAKER_00]: Especially since there was already some sort of tech demo for Tekken on PS3 already.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I soon remember something at Sony's press conference, too, about that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Soul Calibur 3 was a PlayStation 2 exclusive, so that would seem to indicate maybe it'll continue, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Pantsless Pope Pantsless Pope
[SPEAKER_04]: Soul Calibur II Soul Calibur III
[SPEAKER_04]: Soul Calibur 2 is just much more of a big release than Soul Calibur 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm hoping that Soul Calibur 4 can maybe live up to that bar that Soul Calibur 2 set.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's hard to say that Soul Calibur 3 didn't live up to the bar, but in some ways it didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though it was a great game, it wasn't a... When I look back in 15 years, I'm going to remember this next to Soul Calibur 2 type game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you guys feel differently.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you, chat room?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Soul Calibur, I don't know, I think Soul Calibur 3 didn't do as well as 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially the fact when you release something on one system as opposed to 3, you're obviously going to get less sales.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now, of course, we have the chat room is lighting up with some feedback there, which is what I was hoping here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jeremy Todd 1 says, Link on Soul Calibur 2 rocked my socks.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's one reason many people are going to remember Soul Calibur 2 was the addition of Link, which seemed so random at the time, but just was awesome for the GameCube owners.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bandit says, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Tekken is so much better than Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_04]: So he's more excited about the Tekken game that's coming out on PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Dark Knight says, hey, what about the original Soul Edge game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Castelvania
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think any other Castlevania game they ever released will come close to the greatness of Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even more so than the original, for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know, that's kind of how I feel about Soul Calibur, but I'm sure you guys feel differently, but we've all got opinions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, another game that had tons and tons and tons of sequels was King's Quest.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember this whole game, King's Quest?
[SPEAKER_04]: on the PC years ago, Roberta Williams, King Quest, and they had 5 and 6 for some of the first games on CD-ROM.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they went back, Sierra, and they remade 1 and 2 a while ago, and they gave them fancy VGA graphics, but one game they never really went back and upgraded that much was King's Quest 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what's happened is that the fans, and you remember a while back when we even had some of the King's Quest fan community on here, and they were making like the
[SPEAKER_04]: The Fan Game in the series.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, King's Quest fans are passionate about these games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this just goes to prove it.
[SPEAKER_04]: King's Quest 3, to air as human, has been remade.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this has been remade by Infamous Adventures, and this remake features all new VGA backgrounds, enhanced close-up cutscenes, dialogue portraits for all the characters, original music by a professional composer, a full speech pack, and a new point-and-click interface.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, Infamous Adventures believes this game is still relevant, and no profit is being made off the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can download it free of charge for...
[SPEAKER_04]: 43.2 megabytes is how big the game is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's at infamous-adventures.com And honestly, guys, if you don't have GameTap, because GameTap has a lot of King's Quest games in there, I would highly recommend you guys check this out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just going to assume it's like the original.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't had a chance to check it out myself yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would highly recommend you download it as quick as possible because it'll probably be pulled off by some copywriter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now that one person's downloaded it, it'll forever be floating in the internet somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, check this out.
[SPEAKER_04]: King's Quest was a great series of games.
[SPEAKER_00]: King's Quest was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just, you know, I couldn't get into it too much, but I think I want to play Peasant's Quest.
[SPEAKER_00]: Peasant's Quest?
[SPEAKER_00]: What?
[SPEAKER_00]: On the Homestar Runner site.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, actually, I... Damn you, Chogdor!
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the easiest one to get into out of the series, and I don't know, King's Quest hardcore fans may disagree with me, but I think King's Quest 4...
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually tried to start with King's Quest 5 and I couldn't get into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: And Magus, you're saying 5.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm saying 5 because I got started on the series on NES and it was the first King's Quest release that I got to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, I didn't really get into it past 5, but I did get to go into the previous games a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to start on 5, so I think it was the easiest for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, going to the chat room for some quick feedback before we move on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: VidPower says, I'd like to point out that while Sierra did remake KQ1, it was a total market failure.
[SPEAKER_04]: AGD took over the reins of remaking it, and for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's kind of an interesting point there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Sierra had a couple of their old games remade back in the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some folks, SexyStalker is commenting, shameless game tap plug.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't pay us.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just think they do have a pretty interesting service, but it's really up to you guys if you want it or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then Gamerman55 in chat says, Sky, we want some real news, not old games.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though, yes, this is an old game, I think this speaks more volumes about what fan communities in the gaming world are capable of doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it is not an easy task to remake a game with graphics.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know I sure as hell couldn't program it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it is kind of noteworthy when these gaming fan communities go above the Akala fandom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of which, there has been another remake that's kind of been a little off the radar.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of FPS fans know that
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, there's loving a game, and then there's loving a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, these guys love their game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have release dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so some non-fan games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, some of these are fan-ish, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: These games may have fans very soon.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, one of the titles surprises me, because I thought you couldn't use Ninja in a title in the UK, but I guess you can.
[SPEAKER_00]: Coming out on the 30th, a whole crap load of games.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have Shinobi Doei of the Ninja.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have Over G Fighters on Xbox 360, New Super Mario Bros., Micro Machines, Flat Out 2, Devil May Cry 3 Special Edition, Def Jam Fight for New York, Brick'em All.
[SPEAKER_00]: We've also got Super Monkey Ball Adventure, Swords of Destiny, Syphon Filter, Dark Mirror, Titan Quest, Untold Legends, The Warrior Code, and also before that on the 29th is Panzer Command Operation Winter Storm on PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about in the U.S.? ?
[SPEAKER_03]: US, not a whole lot, but if you're a Pirates of the Caribbean fan and you happen to have a portable console, then you'll be happy to know that Pirates of the Caribbean Dead Man's Chest has arrived.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I played a little bit of it at E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's your typical action game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, Micro Machines, though, is coming out on PlayStation 2, Micro Machines Volume 4, as well as the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are Micro Machines still around?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Magus is shaking his head no.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the game looks fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I guess if it's fun, who cares?
[SPEAKER_03]: Number two, Ultimate Ninja for the anime fighting fans.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, let's see here, Rough Trigger the Vanacore Conspiracy, which is some weird budget game where you play a werewolf.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe there was one 360 game which was Over G Fighters is coming out this week, which is supposed to be kind of like Ace Combat.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, I don't know, not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a whole lot at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a slow period for games, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sudoku Gridmaster, that was the other one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whoopee!
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's by Nintendo... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm burned out on Sudoku.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you own a GameCube, though, nada anything for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what your retail says.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyways, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We can't be all buying this.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that reminds me, I still gotta buy my copy of Crusty Demons so I can come over and play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But one of the games I will not be buying is the 10th Anniversary Edition of Tomb Raider because I honestly hate Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know what, it is confirmed though, Eidos has come out and said they are remaking the very first Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's supposed to be arriving on the PlayStation 2, PSP, and PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: No word yet when, but it's coming soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: for all you fans of Tomb Raider out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why, but it's coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, one way that Tomb Raider became ultra-famous was because it had a movie made out of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And usually movies are made out of famous games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this game was a little more B-list or C-list even.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was more of a cult game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Clock Tower.
[SPEAKER_04]: You remember Clock Tower?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Clock Tower was kind of cool because, you know,
[SPEAKER_04]: Gory, gory murder and the scissors and all that scary stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, what's interesting about it is that it is being made into a movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jorge Oguen is heading up the Clock Tower movie project.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, what's happening is that the person who wrote When a Stranger Calls is writing a script for this movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe Jason Wade Wall is the name of this guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And production is going to start on the Clock Tower movie this fall.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully, the movie will be better than When a Stranger Calls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why do people have to pick all this really non-mainstream stuff to make movies out of?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's about the source material for some people.
[SPEAKER_04]: If a good movie can be made out of this, and I think it can, I think a real scary movie could be made from this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's a pretty scary game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've only played a little bit of Clock Tower.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a bunch of sequels.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't there at least a Clock Tower 3?
[SPEAKER_00]: You were playing Clock Tower 3, weren't you?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it was somebody else that I knew, but I've seen the whole first part of Clock Tower 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, the last time I touched Clock Tower was...
[SPEAKER_03]: I want a Contra movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a Silent Hill sequel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you may get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they broke box office.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_00]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_00]: But at the very least, for the July 8th opening in Japan, they actually have a Silent Hill haunted house called Shocking House that's up from July 2nd with hours 11am to 6pm for our listeners in Japan.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the movie, like I said, opens on July 8th.
[SPEAKER_00]: There was actually a big press conference out where they had someone dressed up as a Red Pyramid and a bunch of nurses sort of slumped over.
[SPEAKER_00]: And there's also, though, a nice quote from Akira Yamaoka.
[SPEAKER_00]: The aim was to make something enjoyable even if the viewer wasn't familiar with the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which actually I think did a pretty admirable job.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm hoping that the movie does pretty well in Japan too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't realize that the movie hadn't come out in Japan yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was kind of the most surprising thing to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought they got it the same time we did so I was kind of surprised they still hadn't seen it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It'd have to have gone through.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because usually I think that it's like a difference of I want to say 1 to 3
[SPEAKER_00]: I was reading about this on some various gaming blogs and I noticed the Silent Hill movie was getting a lot of crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why there's this sudden backlash because it seems like when the movie first came out, these same sites were like, Pyramid Head is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I was a little surprised by this sudden backlash where it's cool to hate on Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't understand what the whole trend is with these movie viewers who are looking for Oscar quality acting in these movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, where are you the judge?
[SPEAKER_03]: What is Oscar quality acting in the first place?
[SPEAKER_03]: Two, why the hell would you go to a movie like that anyways expecting that you know it's not going to be there?
[SPEAKER_03]: You go there because you want to see Pyramid Head slice people in half.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's basically why you would go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which didn't quite happen, but you still got cool Pyramid Head killing scenes.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a horror movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Horror movies are supposed to be campy and bloody.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what they are.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they're not like... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not Casablanca with blood.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's just a movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of feedback in our chatroom, and then we'll get Magus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, Magus, you want to comment first?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_02]: People who expect a lot out of video game movies, just be grateful that it's not like Wing Commander.
[SPEAKER_04]: VXJSnakesV says, Silent Hill was an awesome movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: JeremyTodd1 says, you know, it's because of the hype of the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: When they just got back from seeing it, they were all like, OMG, that was so awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then a month or two later, yeah, that movie sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100Matt says, who are you to judge?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not Oscar quality.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gamerman55 says, Oscars suck.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not what typically gets nominated for an Oscar.
[SPEAKER_00]: You don't really see horror movies up there too often.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think that it was really good.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think that the acting in it was pretty darn good, especially since they had the Borg Queen.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_00]: She was so cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think some people were kind of pissed off by the second half of the movie, which involved the Borg Queen character.
[SPEAKER_04]: But at the same time, you know, a movie is very hard to do with, you know, one person.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if the only movie I can think of that's really pulled it off is like some of the Alien movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't mad by the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Could have been worse.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, all these people being critical on stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: One person, though, that was critical on things would be...
[SPEAKER_03]: Rich Kiyanka of
[SPEAKER_03]: SomethingAwful.com and goes by Lotax.
[SPEAKER_03]: He actually wrote Uebol to see if he could be able to fight him.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, interesting note, he has not, as of writing that letter, he had not written anything bad about Uebol's movies, but Uebol said, yeah, sure, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, he decided to go ahead and officially write a review for House of the Dead, which, or Alone in the Dark, I should say.
[SPEAKER_03]: House of the Dead one's coming later, and
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's just basically a really bad movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's interesting to see though that he kind of bent the rules to be able to fight this guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that is one person that he will be fighting.
[SPEAKER_03]: So maybe I can do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: More people probably read somethingawful.com than actually went and saw Blood Rain, so you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oyebol probably has something to win from this
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of want to see Postal now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of want to see it just because you can't really mess up Postal.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no plot to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just basically violence.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got Gary Coleman in it, which, that's awesome right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's going to have a boxing match with Uwe Boll and a bunch of movie critics at the end.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it could work.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, more people are probably interested in seeing Lotex get his ass beat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And before I say that, I'm not slamming something awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am not a goon yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there are people out on the internet who would love to see Lotex get his ass beat, especially by Uwe Boll.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, I think this is what Uwe Boll needs to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: He needs to get out of the video game movie thing and just start making mindlessly violent or cheesy campy movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because he's got the kind of thing down with, you know, Alone in the Dark and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just make your own source material.
[SPEAKER_03]: That way people can't say, oh, you know, he based it on... It's not even near the game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what he needs to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because he doesn't understand how to make...
[SPEAKER_03]: Good movies, so make crappy movies that have a lot of B actors in it and just go crazy with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Snakes on a Plane is a perfect example of something you can do to that effect, but just go crazy with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of the best movies out there are movies that don't make sense, like Giant Crickets Attacking Earth.
[SPEAKER_03]: That doesn't make any sense, but they're good to watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: GK128 seems to back up what you're saying, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says, Postal will be awful, but at least we'll expect it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guy gets angry, goes kill things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's pretty simple to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know, it worked for, what was that movie?
[SPEAKER_00]: Shoot, now I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_00]: Falling Down?
[SPEAKER_00]: Falling Down.
[SPEAKER_00]: Falling Down was a good movie.
[SPEAKER_00]: If he makes it like Falling Down, then I'll go see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly though, if Uwe Boll's Postal was playing next door to another fucking Keanu Reeves, Sandra Bullock movie, I would rather, if forced to gunpoint, go see the Keanu Reeves, Sandra Bullock movie than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So how fast does the lake house have to be traveling before it explodes?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we need a break now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's cleanse the palate.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll be back very shortly with more of episode 188 of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our fourth birthday.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have to go cut the cake.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcasted to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.