[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of August 22nd, 2005.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Welcome once again to another edition of Orange Lounge Radio To Go, that podcast dedicated to video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining us via Skype tonight, and I know that we say we usually don't do the co-host over Skype, but, you know, we can't help cases of sickness or injury, and that's what the one and only DarkSakura is facing tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, DarkSakura on the Skype tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yo, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_05]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I was covering Classic Gaming Expo for us today, and I guess it was a combination of walking around and the driving and then just sitting still practically with my leg extended, but my hip flared up really bad, so I'm sort of hyped up on Vicodin tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so we can't have her driving over to the studio when she's on Vicodin.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you've got to tell us a little bit about Classic Gaming Expo tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was about the same as it was last year.
[SPEAKER_01]: They had more games that actually worked.
[SPEAKER_01]: Had my picture taken by a millipede.
[SPEAKER_01]: That'll be somewhere on our site eventually.
[SPEAKER_01]: Got to meet some pretty cool people, including the guys who do retro gaming radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: And got to just see all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought Famicom games today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like the original Japanese Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought Final Fantasy 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I got Final Fantasy 5 for Super Famicom.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got Mappyland for Famicom.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got some PC Engine hue cards.
[SPEAKER_01]: We actually got a PC Engine core graphics today.
[SPEAKER_01]: And just some other little bits and pieces that I'll have pictures of shortly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_05]: How did you think this year's Classic Gaming Expo compared to previous years that you've been to?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was really...
[SPEAKER_01]: It was empty.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then again, we did go on second day toward the end, but there was just an emptiness I felt to it, which is probably a good idea they're taking next year off because I'm hoping the one in 2007 is going to be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's supposed to be their anniversary.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, very cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Their, I think, 10th anniversary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm hoping it's big and maybe, you know,
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe if it works out, we can get in on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I definitely want to check it out when it comes back.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they always have a really good show at E3 as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the concept of Classic Gaming Expo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully a year off, we'll just recharge them a little bit and they'll be good to go in 2007.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm looking forward to that, definitely.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, 8-Bit Weapon was back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, how were they?
[SPEAKER_01]: They were awesome as always.
[SPEAKER_01]: And another guy was there as part of the convention playing music on a keyboard.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, there were people who were doing new prototypes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_01]: But nothing, you know, there was the Intellivision people were there again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was a guy, he said it's actually someone in Brazil makes these, but they take the MSX games, like the Metal Gear and the original Metal Gear 2 were on MSX, as was the Guardian Legend, it was called Guardia.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: They were all MSX games, and they have them remade to play on the ColecoVision.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was neat, but there wasn't anything really new there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nothing like what Gradius V was last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, we'll look forward to more reports on Classic Gaming Expo on our website, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura's picture collection will be posted sometime during the week, so we look forward to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I haven't forgotten, four minutes into the show, but I haven't forgotten the one and only TechMassaLoki over there in studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't even like
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: So let DarkSakura do a little report there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why don't you give us one of your stories you're looking at tonight from the hack and crack scene.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, my report, I was just kind of browsing stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of them is a mod for Half-Life 2 called Half-Life 2 Fueled.
[SPEAKER_04]: And because Half-Life 2 is famous for its ragdoll physics and playing with the ragdoll physics, they have some really kick-ass shots from this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like, you know, for example, tons of cars just all strewn about the place and
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like it's going to be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got some ramps in this little demo thing here.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can find out more about it on www.fueledmod.com And they've got some interesting stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well now what I want to do is I want to go ahead and start off tonight's show, even though we had a couple stories there, to start off tonight's show talking about what we like to always start off the show talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: What games have we, the hosts, been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, what have you been playing this week in your gaming world?
[SPEAKER_01]: well seeing as how I started school this week I haven't had a whole bunch of time and I actually am going to be signing back up for Ragnarok Online again it's funny you should talk about signing up for old MMOs you're not signing back up for Final Fantasy XI are you?
[SPEAKER_01]: I wouldn't say I'm not going to I'm going to give Ragnarok a try for a month to see if I really miss it as badly as I think I do
[SPEAKER_05]: That's my philosophy on Final Fantasy as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: But they have like a pay $7 for 30 hours of gameplay, so I'm going to give that a go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just for a month.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hunted down the Vetrex, and then I remembered why I don't play the Vetrex, because it kind of gave me a headache.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the Vetrex was just a cool idea, really.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, true.
[SPEAKER_01]: I also...
[SPEAKER_01]: I tried out a couple of Hu cards at Classic Gaming Expo today.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I also watched Dan try out some of the ones that we bought.
[SPEAKER_01]: We got Sun Sun 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: That game is cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, I don't even think I've heard of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, okay, I have heard of that, but that's a, wow, that's an obscure game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, pretty obscure.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of stuff at Classic Gaming Expo is obscure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Legend of the Valkyrie Loki, what games have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been playing pretty much the same stuff I was playing last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Taiko Drum Master here in the US, of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's got to be weird on the PSP, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: It works really good, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of looked over your shoulder while you were playing it, and it looks really crisp, and it's just like the PlayStation 2 version right on your little PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's really good, and it's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wish it was in English, so I'd be able to understand what menus were and stuff, because it's a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: But someone did make some on GameFAQs, I think, English translations of the menus, so
[SPEAKER_04]: That helps.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's always helpful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those game fact people are always very helpful.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is, but you know what they could help me out with?
[SPEAKER_04]: Some cheats from freaking Burnout 3, because I've got to play through these races, and I'm not liking that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need my fast cars now.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: My gaming week... Is that all you've had?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's all I have.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: My gaming week has consisted of my... Well, I was sick this week, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie has...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: I've had a Japanese one for years to get my music gaming fix out of the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: But since I was living with Loki for such a long time, he had an American PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't have a need for my own, so I finally went and bought one on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought one of the little chibi miniature ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really hadn't seen one because everybody else I know got their PlayStation 2s years ago, so they're huge.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I hadn't really seen the tiny ones up close.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn, those are tiny PlayStations!
[SPEAKER_05]: I could have just loaned you mine indefinitely since I have Final Fantasy X International And you're playing it half the hassle
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry, my headset moved back.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Knowing it's half the hassle.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, also, I bought the PlayStation 2 so that I could, you know, screen new games if we start getting any screeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: I should say additional screeners from, like, you know, media companies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do have demos at work.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't brought them in though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so we'll start taking a look at those.
[SPEAKER_05]: And as well as, you know, just renting some games and checking things out so I can keep a tab on what's going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, other than the PlayStation 2, as...
[SPEAKER_05]: People are cultists.
[SPEAKER_05]: I escaped.
[SPEAKER_05]: You sure did, but you're in Ragnarok, which is, you know, some people would say just as bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, I've been in Ragnarok for like, what, five years, six years?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, well, you're still getting quiet there.
[SPEAKER_05]: My addiction is stronger than your addiction.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're a little quiet there, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: My addiction is stronger than your addiction.
[SPEAKER_01]: My addiction is mighty, and to be feared.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zelda Twilight Princess got the big ol' delay to Spring 2006
[SPEAKER_05]: and of course the question heard around the world what the hell Nintendo what the hell you had this game ready to show us at E3 and we thought you were all ready to go in the fall but now they're saying no we need more time we're announcing a new global launch in 2006 after the conclusion of the fiscal year so no earlier than April 1st we'll provide a specific date at a later point in time while this may come as a disappointment it will absolutely enrich the game and make it a multi-million seller
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would have been that anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that means Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: Birthday present for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, hopefully it's released around your birthday.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the reason why they say they're doing this is because they're adding extra things to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: The game could be buggy as hell.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who really knows why this game got pushed back?
[SPEAKER_05]: But what they're saying is that they're trying to add new things to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which I suppose is good news, but at the same time...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not like there's been a flood of GameCube games lately.
[SPEAKER_05]: They really should have been working on this double time a while ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: What we've got is a bunch of game testers going, but I haven't beaten it yet!
[SPEAKER_01]: Delay!
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be a good news thing, though, because that means the game is long.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully, it'll be a good thing, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does it affect your feelings about the game at all, this delay?
[SPEAKER_05]: for me, I will probably still pick it up but I'm not I feel like by the time it comes out I will feel like, oh, this is yesterday's game
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: yes, a game is only as good as how it plays
[SPEAKER_04]: Another delay that pisses the hell out of me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy Advent Children is not coming out until the end of November, November 30th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not many places have actually, no one's really said anything about this delay, but I have the inside info, being that I work for a video distributor.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that's straight from Sony, folks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gotta hate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope I'm wrong, and I hope that data is just pulled out of thin air and Sony doesn't know what they're talking about, but
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm afraid it's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: and some in Europe so probably not a whole lot of Japanese listeners we've got but if you are listening to us and you're interested in going you need to be registered with the Shinra Company online fan club and I'm guessing if you're not already signed up you might have lost out because I don't think they're accepting new club members anymore so um
[SPEAKER_05]: They will randomly select people if they get too many people that want to get in.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be happening September 10th through the 16th in Tokyo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nagoya and Kyoto will be the three cities that will be showing Final Fantasy Advent Children on the big screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, you're going to have to wait for the UMD and DVD formats.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here in America as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: One other story, I know the big news this week, the game we're all excited about is Nintendogs is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm very excited about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the interesting thing about Nintendogs, they're actually going to be getting a special holiday edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, okay, it's kind of a rumor right now, but Nintendo of America did file some papers with the ESRB that indicate something called
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendogs Holiday Edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we all know how Nintendo loves to get you to buy the same crap in new packaging over and over again.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this really wouldn't be a surprise if this is something they are actually doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendogs Holiday Edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are they being premature with this though since the game hasn't even come out here?
[SPEAKER_05]: It could be a massive failure here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I doubt it will be.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it could be.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's not going to be a failure.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's coming out right after my wedding, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that a hint?
[SPEAKER_05]: You're already going to get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't have to buy it for your wedding.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're already going to have it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I think, honestly, I see the game being a big success because if there's one thing Nintendo understands, it's a formula.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, we have Pokemon as our big example.
[SPEAKER_01]: They know what's going to appeal, and there's already been so much hype from the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's already so widely popular.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't see any way for
[SPEAKER_05]: The Game Boy Micro is going to be coming out here for $99.99.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now the Game Boy Micro, for those of you that were sleeping during E3 coverage, it's like the Game Boy Advance, but really freaking tiny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like palm of your hand tiny.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little bit bigger than the Game Boy Advance cartridges.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you go look on our E3 pictures, they have a pretty close up image.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do have that in the gallery.
[SPEAKER_05]: Four inches wide, this thing is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's tiny.
$99.99.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be coming out September 19th is the day this is coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, faceplates.
[SPEAKER_05]: The faceplate changing is a big thing they're doing with this.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can have a Game Boy Micro that matches your purse or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Flame, camouflage, or just simple silver.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, yeah, they come with...
[SPEAKER_04]: The Silver or Black Faceplate, depending on whether yours is silver or black.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Japanese release will be September 13th, and it'll be coming out for 12,000 yen.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's about $109, so it's a little more expensive in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: But get this, for our European friends, we're paying $99, they're paying 99 euro, and the euro's worth a little more, so that's $121 US.
[SPEAKER_05]: November 4th.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they get pink.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, but they get pink.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not that, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to take a minute to open up the old mailbag here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember, you guys can send in your questions for Orange Lounge Radio at our address.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's togo, T-O-G-O, at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we have a couple of letters this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first letter I'd like to read comes from SithSpawn is the name of the
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have any kids and I don't ever want them.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, I do have a few words concerning video game violence and ratings.
[SPEAKER_05]: The main problem originates with the many groups pushing for stricter ratings and or the banning of certain games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Brian from Michigan is suggesting there are two simple steps to deal with this problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Know your games.
[SPEAKER_05]: As a parent, you need to know about the ratings and actually play these games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, take the ratings with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_05]: The opinions of the ESRB aren't necessarily your own.
[SPEAKER_05]: Instruct your child.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only way to prevent your kid from playing the games you do not want them to play is to ensure that they do not want to play them.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's exactly the same as saying no to drugs.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all about the child making decisions based on input from the parents.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give your kid the tools he or she needs to make educated decisions when you are not around.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like his steps there that he offers there.
[SPEAKER_05]: A very educated response from our friend SithSpawn.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was very impressed with that letter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it was very nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: We also have another letter here.
[SPEAKER_05]: This letter is from another Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: It actually could be Jaime, but we think it's Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie's been listening to the show for two months now and says it's really interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a reason you guys won the podcast award, partially because of my vote.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very kind.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know exactly what you mean about the misspelling of your name in talking to our own Jamie here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have the exact same problem, but in reverse.
[SPEAKER_05]: This person spells their name J-A-I-M-E.
[SPEAKER_05]: So very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: We were talking about Evercrack's economy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Jamie actually sent us a link to an article about the economy, and it's a really good link to a story that has more information on the economy.
[SPEAKER_05]: http://mu.ranter.net theory economy.html And actually what this is, this is kind of like an opinion piece about the economy inside video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a really well-written piece.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you guys have some time, check that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Jamie wanted to point out a website called stopstopkill.com Jamie, did you have a chance to check out stopstopkill.com?
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, this is one I knew about.
[SPEAKER_01]: At the time, it was more of a placeholder, but it actually looks like it's gone full active.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's about the truth about violence in video games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Someone else, you know, trying to get the word out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, any type of research that's being done in regards to video games, they're putting this up on their site.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, you know, also putting out...
[SPEAKER_01]: Trying to give the whole broad spectrum, but also trying to say, hey, this is where you are wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a pretty awesome site so far.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm pretty impressed with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, there's a forum on here that says Gamers Against Jack Forum.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's about Jack Thompson.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, it links back to Jack Thompson's site, StopKill.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: which is basically more of Jack Thompson talking out of his ass.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's true.
[SPEAKER_01]: The man, I hate to say, well, I don't really hate to say it, but he's a freaking idiot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jack Thompson, if you're listening, you're a moron.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: He'll appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, moving on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, moving forward.
[SPEAKER_01]: But this site is pretty cool, and we need more stuff like this.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm actually going to, as soon as I get an opportunity to send this guy a link to that article I found on Game Revolution with the information provided from the FBI and Department of Justice showing the crime rate in youth going down since the release of the PS1.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that he might benefit from that.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, it's funny that we got an email from somebody named Jamie because we also got an email from somebody named Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm actually going to start with Rob's PS because he said kind of a nice thing here and I just want to repeat it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob said something about sorry for delaying a podcast and listeners inquiring what went on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I appreciate your contribution to the video game media.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since it's free, I don't think I have any right to demand it.
[SPEAKER_05]: People should be more gracious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's really nice, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: We try our best.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: We do, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, he actually had a response to an article about virtual ethics, which I thought was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, did you have any reports on ethics going on, like the mugging that's going on in games or anything?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, just to give sort of a bit of a paraphrasing from this one article that he linked me to, a man was arrested in Japan on suspicion of carrying out a virtual mugging spree by using software bots to beat up
[SPEAKER_01]: and robbed characters in the online game Lineage 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got to try that at E3 a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what you do in that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: The stolen possessions, the virtual items, were exchanged for cash.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a Chinese exchange student that was arrested for this in Kagawa.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: Several players had their characters beaten and robbed of valuable virtual objects.
[SPEAKER_01]: It names items called Earring of Wisdom and Shield of Nightmare.
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess they're pretty big things in Lineage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the items were fenced off through a Japanese auction website, according to NCSoft.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the company that makes Lineage 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he did it by using a software bot.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it couldn't be beat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's always a way around this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I want to read Rob's response to this.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you feel your character and stuff are worth paying blackmail, you seriously need a real life.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe the virtual mugging sent the victim home from the internet cafe early to inadvertently save the lives of himself and or his neglected offspring.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blackmail in real life is a serious crime.
[SPEAKER_05]: Virtual ethics had nothing to do with the perp's arrest.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: In regards to the virtual ethics thing, sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_01]: I weep for society.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I did have another email that was linked to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll just go ahead.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was an article that was within it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unfortunately, I couldn't find the original one, but it's a little brief one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Going back to the game addiction business.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was moved to a hospital but died a few hours later due to what the doctors are presuming was a heart attack.
[SPEAKER_05]: I swear I've heard this story before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, maybe not this exact same person, but I swear I've heard this exact same setup, internet cafe, person there playing their game too damn much, and dying from it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I swear I've heard this before.
[SPEAKER_05]: That happened a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody didn't get the hint the last time, apparently.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, actually, when I got the link on this, it was earlier within the week, and the time says five hours ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it was fairly recent.
[SPEAKER_01]: They also said that he'd been fired from his job because he kept missing work to play computer games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's like instead of drinking, he gamed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, and you know, if you look at it this way, for the people who are those, you know, hardcore addicts to booze, they're trying to escape from something that's gone wrong in their life.
[SPEAKER_01]: These people are using, you know, games in return to escape from the, you know, the bad that's gone on in their life.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which sort of goes back to...
[SPEAKER_05]: How would an internet cafe allow you to be there for 48 hours straight?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I know there's 24-hour cafes and everything, but isn't that unethical business?
[SPEAKER_05]: I realize we're talking about another country, but... Well, I know they're making money, but at some point, don't you have to draw the line?
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got to sleep at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you go to a bar and the bartender sees that you've had one too many drinks, the bartender has a... I don't know if it's legal.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm almost positive it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they have an...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care where in the world you are, why didn't somebody stop this guy?
[SPEAKER_01]: This man was ultimately responsible for himself.
[SPEAKER_01]: By all rights, it's not their place to tell him how to live his life, basically.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was a paying customer.
[SPEAKER_01]: If he chooses to pay with his life for that...
[SPEAKER_01]: It really isn't their... I mean, this may sound cold, but it really isn't their concern.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand that point.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is ultimately his fault, but why didn't anybody, his friend, a loved one who noticed he was missing for 48 hours, a worker at the place who must have seen this going on, nobody intervened?
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's, like, not good Samaritan.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody should let anybody play StarCraft for that long anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw that coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's exactly what my point is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eventually,
DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: You seriously gotta question your priorities.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, once in a great while, it might be okay because, you know, you're not feeling up to it or whatever, but if you notice yourself, you're doing it repeatedly over and over again, you're not going out and having a real life because you're staying in and playing video games of any nature, really, not just MMOs.
[SPEAKER_05]: You gotta get outdoors once in a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why we do our advice column, which I guess is a good segue into that portion of the show, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, Rob, you know I did that once when I was in high school.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I stayed out of school for a week to play Final Fantasy 3, which was 6.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you didn't do that all the time, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, and I actually did legitimately develop the flu within that week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, see, it's still a little extreme.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still might kind of raise my eyebrow at that and go, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_01]: But this is to the point that I was in high school.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm an adult now.
[SPEAKER_01]: That man was an adult.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was no excuse.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, hell no.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just bounce uncontrollably at work until I get to go home and play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No time to live!
[SPEAKER_05]: So DarkSakura is here to give us her advice column.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, what is your advice about tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Today's bit of advice is how to survive if you are in the line of fire, if you are the primary target.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, that means like everyone else is wearing camo, you're wearing white.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number one, get as far away as possible, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_01]: run like hell.
[SPEAKER_01]: An untrained shooter is not likely to be accurate at any distance greater than 60 feet.
[SPEAKER_01]: 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Run fast, but do not move in a straight line.
[SPEAKER_01]: Weave back and forth.
[SPEAKER_01]: The average shooter will not have the training necessary to hit a moving target at any real distance.
3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Turn a corner if possible.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, duh.
4.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do not bother to count shots.
[SPEAKER_01]: You will have no idea the shooter has more ammunition.
[SPEAKER_01]: Counting is only for the movies.
[SPEAKER_01]: My final bit of advice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shoot back.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's basically this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Run like a bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's my favorite final piece of advice you've ever given on this program.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're getting shot at, freaking shoot back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Real nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: Taunt them as you run.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what else you got?
[SPEAKER_05]: Perhaps they
[SPEAKER_05]: Now go away before I taunt you a second time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what's going on in the hack and crack scene?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's tons of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, there was a nice cell shading demo that was released, kind of showing what homebrew stuff can do right now, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then also on top of that, looks like SanDisk was announcing that they're going to be releasing their 2GB memory stick here pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: TI-MIDI
[SPEAKER_04]: or Miditty, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a MIDI playing program that's on the PSP, which was kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a rhythm composer program being made, PSP Rhythm Composer, and that's kind of like a drum machine type thing, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, there was a program that was released called PSP Tune, which helps you tune your guitar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's helpful.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the DS end of things, there was also an update done to the ColecoVision emulator, which is called ColecoDS, appropriately.
[SPEAKER_04]: And version 0.2 is released, and they've got some interesting screenshots on ndsupdates.com, so go check those out if you have some time.
[SPEAKER_04]: OrangeLoungeRadio.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Dance Dance Revolution Xtreme 2
[SPEAKER_05]: including La Copa De Vida from Patrick Victorio, that's a cover of the original Ricky Martin one, Look At Us, the Daddy DJ remix by Serena Paris, and Cartoon Heroes from Barbie Young.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even some old songs, Boom Boom Dollar, K.O.G.G.3 mix from King Kong and D-Jungle Girls, Captain Jack, a Grondale remix from Captain Jack, and Butterfly, the Upswing mix from SmileDK.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spin, Spin, Sugar
[SPEAKER_05]: by the Sneaker Pimps, Silence by Delirium with Sarah McLachlan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, we have Block Rockin' Beats by the Chemical Brothers and As the Rush Comes from Motorcycle.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's just a short list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, also Get Busy by Sean Paul.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of a neat little song.
[SPEAKER_05]: The full list, of course, is available on our website, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also making an announcement this week, Karaoke Revolution Party.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whole lot of songs in Karaoke Revolution Party Edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: My gosh, Take On Me, Material Girl, Me and Bobby McGee, Flame, Do You Really Want to Hurt Me, Call Me, American Woman.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could read this list all day.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's huge.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check it out, orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to be Karaoke Revolution Party Edition coming out a little later this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Konami's also announcing Suikoden Tactics, which is going to be coming out for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, you could think of this as kind of like Final Fantasy Tactics, but Suikoden Tactics!
[SPEAKER_05]: The official announcement came out this week that it will be coming out for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're looking at a spring 2006 release date for this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Advent Rising
[SPEAKER_05]: Due to too many bugs going on with the game, or basically I was going to say too many bugs, too many things going wrong in the system, they have quietly canceled the million dollar giveaway.
[SPEAKER_05]: That happened earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Instead, as kind of a consolation prize, each person who participated in the Race to Save Humanity contest will receive two free games from its recent catalog.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: of a consolation prize when you consider that the games you can choose from, BloodRayne 2, Guilty Gear X2 Reload, Psychonauts, Rays as Hell, and Phantom Dust.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's quite a few good games in that catalog there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Too bad though about that million dollar competition because they stand to be paying that much out in all these free games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how many people were in this contest.
[SPEAKER_05]: This really wasn't a game that appealed to me personally, but I just think it's interesting that the contest had to be called off.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a cool game, but it did have its fair share of bugs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, I want to point this out, World of Warcraft, you know this, the MMO, the most popular MMO which none of us play here on this program.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually have a friend that's really trying to get me into it, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've tried to install it, and my computer won't accept the installation for some reason, which makes no sense to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, no!
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't want this.
[SPEAKER_05]: You already put enough crappy MMOs on me.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm trying to make it work.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we will soon be reporting from inside World of Warcraft at some point, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we did want to point out Upper Deck Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is Upper Deck well known for?
[SPEAKER_05]: Cards.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cards, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are making a...
[SPEAKER_05]: They are making a trading card game based out of World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: The quote from Jerry Benton, Senior Vice President of Upper Deck Entertainment, The World of Warcraft trading card game will perfectly capture all of the action-packed combat and furious competition that online players have come to expect.
[SPEAKER_05]: Will there be a slash... Oh wait, no, that's EverQuest 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Slash pizza card, that'd be sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: XBOX 360
[SPEAKER_05]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: $299.99 US for the basic unit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why they just don't say $300, because that's what you're going to be paying after tax.
$300.
[SPEAKER_05]: So for $300, you're going to get the Xbox 360 console, the controller, which is a wired controller, but it has an extended 9-foot cable.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't understand anyways because there's no freaking controller ports on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So where are you playing it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now a new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Find the controller port.
[SPEAKER_05]: A USB port maybe?
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe?
[SPEAKER_05]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: An Xbox 360 faceplate and an Xbox 360 standard AV cable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Composite.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's the first one.
[SPEAKER_05]: XBOX 360 CORE
[SPEAKER_05]: 400 bucks, console, hard drive, 20 gigabytes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, ladies and gentlemen, the Xbox 360 will not have a hard drive built in by default like the original Xbox did.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I'm doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to take that freaking hard drive and rip it apart and put a 120 gig hard drive in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Screw that 20 gig crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: For the $400, you get the wireless controller, the faceplate, a headset, a component high-definition cable, so you... Well, let me... I'll get to that thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Xbox Live...
[SPEAKER_05]: Xbox Live Silver Membership Bonus Media Remote
[SPEAKER_05]: is kind of trying to soften the blow of the fact that the system really costs $400 for everything you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm thinking what people are going to do is be buying that when the third-party stuff starts coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you don't have to buy a hard drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can buy this stupid little 64-meg memory card thing, and you don't have to buy a wireless controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's just nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you don't have to have a headset and
[SPEAKER_04]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Xbox Live Silver package, that's free.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's not really a big... Well, that actually is packaged on the regular one, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know it didn't make the story here on the site, but I read it somewhere else that the Xbox Live Silver will be on both sets.
[SPEAKER_05]: So at least you get that.
[SPEAKER_05]: What would you do?
[SPEAKER_05]: What strikes me as interesting though, okay, I maybe understand why they omitted the hard drive from the Xbox 360, because honestly, how often did you use it with the original Xbox?
[SPEAKER_05]: Granted, you could load your own songs, but how many games really supported that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, we put on a bunch of Initial D soundtracks from, what was it, Midnight Club?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but how... but not a lot of games supported it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, a few, but not a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um, it's not like you could... a lot of games use the hard drive for their data.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's saved, but nothing that a memory card wouldn't be able to fit unless you're a real hardcore gamer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: But now I'm thinking, okay, but now you're also talking with Xbox 360 that Final Fantasy XI is one of your big titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to have a hard drive for Final Fantasy XI because of all the freaking patches they do.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you want to play Final Fantasy XI...
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, most likely.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, just very interesting there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really, to play all the really big games, you're going to have to chuck down the $400 anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: I suppose maybe if you just want Madden, you're just a light gamer, maybe the $300 one will do you.
[SPEAKER_05]: But most people that listen to this program probably consider themselves hardcore enough where that $300 set just doesn't cut it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, any other thoughts on that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, I know I'm going to have to get the premium.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want the HD cables and I want the wireless controller and the hard drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I have to check down the $400.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm just kind of... Well, in the end, it's a better economical decision anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I guess, but $400 is still a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I suppose most systems were around $400 when they first came out anyway, so...
[SPEAKER_01]: They lost a lot of money when the Xbox first came out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think this is a way for them to make something that looks a little bit more affordable and attractive for the casual gamer or for someone who doesn't have a lot of money or doesn't have the high-definition setup you or I have.
[SPEAKER_01]: It makes it a little bit more affordable, makes it a little bit more attractive.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then for those of us who have all this stuff, who would lay down that kind of money...
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, they're like, hey, we've got some goodies for you, we'll save you some money.
[SPEAKER_05]: I suppose what makes some of us angsty out there is that we're looking at this going, oh man, you mean we gotta pay $100 for the stuff we need anyway?
[SPEAKER_05]: As gamers?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's where we kind of feel like, oh jeez, we're being nickeled and dimed again.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I understand what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: By having the $300 set, it makes Xbox 360 more accessible, so to speak, to a broader game audience.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those folks that, you know, they just want the new Madden game or, you know, whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's a really smart move on Microsoft's part.
[SPEAKER_01]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we shall see when the sales figures come out, shall we?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will be paying attention to that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I read a really neat article in Time about the 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: This article came out about the time that we were all at E3.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just saying about how much money they lost on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: With the design of the system, they designed something that would be attractive...
[SPEAKER_01]: to the Japanese market as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, I'd love to see if they're going to be doing the same thing there that they are here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_01]: About having the multiple packages.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: The with and without package, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: OriginXbox360.com
[SPEAKER_04]: What's interesting is there's a timer counting down.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what's also interesting is that the domain was registered by Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_05]: So is it another one of those big, like, you know, we like bees or whatever that site was called.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love bees.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, viral campaigns.
[SPEAKER_04]: Possibly the website by, you know, people looking at it, they figured out that it's going to end on September 27th, I believe, at...
[SPEAKER_04]: 12 Eastern and no one really knows what the hell it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just know that it's a countdown thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got this kind of a picture of a tree and it's cut out of a bunny and it looks Xbox 360 will have bunny love?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's their answer to Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Micro bunnies.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm laughing now but
[SPEAKER_04]: You know something like that could actually happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know something like that could actually happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be their answer to Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be Microbunnies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Microbunnies.
[SPEAKER_04]: You turn around, you walk away, you get something to drink, you come back, there's 400 of them on the screen.
[SPEAKER_01]: And what are we going to get next?
[SPEAKER_01]: Playcats?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, so there's some weird site, and it's basically you can access it at www.
[SPEAKER_04]: Origin, and this is O-R-I-G-N Xbox360.com And you've got the countdown here.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can go check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Figure out what it's about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then on to the subject of something else, which would be the Nintendo Revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: There has been a comment made by Peter Mullenux at Lionhead Studios, the studio behind Black and White and Fable.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's basically quizzed at some European games convention about the revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's basically said this, and this is his quote.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a line at the end of the book, Game Over, and it is, Never underestimate Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is all I can say about the controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Things that make you go, hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, basically, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been the same thing from all these other different publishers I've been looking at.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're like, I can't say anything under strict NDR, but don't count them out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll have to wait until the end of the year to find out.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know that Nintendo's kind of been...
[SPEAKER_05]: With the DS, they kind of changed the controller a little bit, because the controller is a pen, and you never really saw that in a gaming system before, so Nintendo's kind of been on this kick lately, so it'll be very interesting to see what happens.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're bringing back the U-Force!
[SPEAKER_05]: No, God, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: No!
[SPEAKER_05]: How about the Power Glove?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Activator!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything else you got for us tonight, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: And finally... Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Happy birthday to you!
[SPEAKER_04]: Happy birthday, Mario, you're 20.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, he's still youngin'.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, he's a youngin'.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's got a lot to learn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo has officially launched the Mario's happy birthday site, nintendo.co.jp slash mario20th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And on behalf of Orange Lounge Radio, we'd like to apologize to Mario.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are sorry, but your cake is in another castle.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a mushroom cake It'll actually be coming out
[SPEAKER_05]: In September.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you know a release date for this?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's mid-September.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dig Dug is armed with a collection of weapons such as rocks, lava, and quicksand to defeat the baddies that are in his way.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Junior assistant Mr. Driller.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are saying multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Two players in this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: That'll be really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you have any other stories for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: I have that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Core Hotels.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a hotel chain in Southern California and it's one of those really swanky hotel things.
[SPEAKER_05]: They offer a PlayStation 2 and PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically what it is is that if you stay in their rooms you get free use of a PSP handheld or a PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Each hotel has a resident game butler who helps you install and use the systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: How would that be for a job?
[SPEAKER_05]: Being the game butler at one of these hotels?
[SPEAKER_05]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, if you're...
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're thinking that this is a good way to check out one of these systems, think again, because staying at core hotels will cost you well over several hundred dollars per night, so you might as well just buy yourself a PlayStation 2 or a PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can top that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, what do you have?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just been announced that... I've got one more story.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, I want to save mine for last, because mine's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: You read yours.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, Nokia will just try anything to get their product out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Nokia, to combat the PSP being a hotel, they have the Nokia N-Gage Deck Chair.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, folks, the N-Gage Deck Chair.
[SPEAKER_04]: What you can do, basically, is they're going to be putting these out at different venues out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: What's going to happen is they're actually going to be sitting in a chair with a crappy umbrella attached to it and this crappy end gauge attached to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be touring a number of festivals including Carleen Leeds and Reading Festival.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never heard of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, folks, it's going to suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even the deck chair looks uncomfortable.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like the deck chair was put together wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to IHOP today and I saw somebody playing an N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's probably only the second time I have ever seen somebody playing an N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_05]: Their parents don't love them.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it was like an adult.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like an upper 20s looking guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's probably only the second time I've ever seen somebody playing an N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like not in a GameStop demo or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: In the N-Gage's defense...
[SPEAKER_01]: A system is only as good as the games that are on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unfortunately, it doesn't really have any good games anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, now, DarkSakura, you tell me which story was better, Loki's final story or my final story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Linda Carter will be joining the cast of Elder Scrolls 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, Wonder Woman!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Linda Carter, best known as Wonder Woman, or should I say Wonder Woman, is going to be joining the cast of this game, Elder Scrolls 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: And
[SPEAKER_05]: What else do you really need to know about the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously, it's got Wonder Woman in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is freaking awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's, you know, a role-playing game, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're in this fantasy realm of Tamriel where the gates to a hellish underworld are going to be opened.
[SPEAKER_04]: But never fear, Wonder Woman is here.
[SPEAKER_05]: But never fear, Wonder Woman's here with her golden lasso.
[SPEAKER_01]: With her golden lasso.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, directed by?
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe... Written by Joss.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't send me hate mail if I'm wrong, but I believe it's written and directed by the one and only Joss.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you puffy fans.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then that means it's going to be done fabulously well.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was also writing X-Men for a little while.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well...
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll save that to the Buffy fans podcast, if there is one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would think there's got to be a Buffy podcast out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to go look for one right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sounds like a waste of time.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's time for the final thoughts before DarkSakura jumps through the sky blind and strangles Loki for knocking Buffy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did that guy actually come up with the really retarded concept of an invisible flying jet?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why couldn't you just make her fly?
[SPEAKER_04]: An invisible jet is retarded.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because she's an Amazon or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, so she can't fly.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's a woman.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why she can't fly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_04]: She has to fly a jet.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's going to punch you next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: my final thought is my final thought is Nintendogs you are mine this week finally oh god it's gonna be a really bad show next week it's always a really bad show what are you talking about but you guys listen anyway we love you DarkSakura your final thought um reject false icons alright that's gonna do it for another that's gonna do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio to go thanks you guys for subscribing and listening have a great night
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio To Go edition.
[SPEAKER_03]: This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: See you next update.