[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, November 12, 2006, Microsoft unveils movie and television downloads, PlayStation 3 games get some new dates and some postponed dates, and can you really install Linux on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello boys and girls on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome to another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are that video game show dedicated to video games, gamer lifestyle, gamer culture, and all that other stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it's about two and a half to three hours of just chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: We like to think of ourselves as sitting around the table at the local diner, just bitching about video games while we're waiting for our food.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the service is very slow tonight, hence why the show is about two and a half hours long.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Jamie Summers, ROAR
[SPEAKER_06]: Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, I didn't hear most of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, maybe if you were listening to the show and not playing on your computer while we're trying to get things started here, maybe you would have heard my really bad comparison.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just trying to look up to see if anyone had commented on a certain story that ran earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I think you should be focusing on the show now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's show related.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need your full attention, Mr. Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: and also say hello to our old Orange Lounge Radio favorite, Drew Nami.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, if I don't get my French toast soon, I'm going to go kick someone's ass.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: Bad service.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I get it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I left the comparison.
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone needs to pay attention to the show, Mr. Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, here we are and another week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're sitting just before the brink of madness.
[SPEAKER_06]: Video game system releases.
[SPEAKER_06]: PlayStation 3 and Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really quickly, who's getting what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's getting what system?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, I'm getting a Wii but not a PlayStation 3 just yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm getting a Wii and a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm getting a Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, Tiara?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm getting nothing because I am poor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aw, sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Junami?
[SPEAKER_06]: I can send you a Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have lots of love for Tiara.
[SPEAKER_06]: She can watch us all unpack them on YouTube because apparently that makes for riveting game news this week is, you know, watch me play my Wii and rub it in your face that you don't have one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is such horrible blogging news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, like every single blog I visited this week, I guess Nintendo loves everyone else more than us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm over it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But every other website is like, hey, look, here's a video on YouTube of us taking the Wii out of the box and showing it all in front of the camera.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then here's me playing Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like I'm reading the same thing on every single blog.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, isn't there like Real News this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know it's still early in the week, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: But as far as I'm aware, Jessica Chobert has not licked the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: I may be able to beat her to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakra, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_10]: I played Guitar Hero 2 quite a bit last night.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, quite a bit last night.
[SPEAKER_10]: We played all the way through Easy and then through a bunch of Medium.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will let the almighty unlocker of Trogdor tell you about that later.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I got inspired and left the room so that I could make the pre-show with a bunch of stuff that was in Guitar Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was going to put Thunder Horse from...
[SPEAKER_10]: Venture Brothers.
[SPEAKER_10]: What was the band?
[SPEAKER_10]: Deathlock.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I was going to put that in the show, but I decided not to.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you want to hear Trogdor, you have to stay and listen to the entire show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, if you're on the podcast, it won't do you any good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's copyrighted.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, kids.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I looked at Trauma Center and haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then Dan started playing Final Fantasy XII for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm a little bit upset at him.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I played some more...
[SPEAKER_06]: Samora, PSU I'm only level 3 Slowly but surely, making your way That's right, leveling is slow in PSU I played religiously for several days And I'm only like level 12 So it ain't gonna get any quicker I'm sorry to say I just solo through all the missions Seriously, play single player You level up so much faster Just skip all the cutscenes and play single player
[SPEAKER_10]: It doesn't level your online character.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, sadly, no, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, then.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to level my online character.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're just going to play by yourself.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got PSU to play through the online missions.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just want to start leveling my stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything else, Miss DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was full of stuff, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, I picked up two big 360 games this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gears of War, which I've played for not very long, actually, so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't really played much through it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried a little bit of the single player, got past the first mission, and played a little bit of the multiplayer on one console.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I mean, not a real good indicator of what the multiplayer is, but it's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be honest, I don't think the multiplayer is that great.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: But you're wearing a Call of Duty shirt
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh wait, that's Activision.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have two Call of Duty shirts.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this was on the top of the hamper.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyways, so yeah, I'll play through it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure it's going to be a pretty cool game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there is one good thing about it, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: The co-op is amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So at least they've got that going for it, because there aren't that many good co-op games nowadays.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's almost like Contra, I should say.
[SPEAKER_03]: That kind of reminds me of two people playing through the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which also leads me to Contra, which I played a little bit this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, Contra's Contra, so it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, of course, Call of Duty 3 I bought.
[SPEAKER_03]: That one is really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Personally, I like the multiplayer in Call of Duty 3 a lot better.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been playing it locally with a few of my friends at work, and it's just fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's definitely improved over the last one.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only thing I don't like about the multiplayer in it, though, is that the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Your little HUD radar thing that they have, they do not show the gunshots going off like they used to in the first one.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, playing a 10 minute game, it might be hard to find people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, since the maps don't say how many people they're meant for, which the old one did, so you kind of get an idea of which map is large, which one's smaller, and that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: This one's kind of flying blind.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game's pretty cool, though, because you get to drive vehicles and stuff, and I got a lot of my kills running over people with Jeeps, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the game looks a lot better, so that'll be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Grand Theft Auto's Vice City Story has been playing a little bit more, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really, playing more of this, I'm starting to like the game a little bit more, but also at the same time, I'm frustrated with how lazy their programming is.
[SPEAKER_03]: For example...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: but they didn't because they're too fucking lazy so whatever but the game is fun um just kind of figuring out the nuances of it but still Grand Theft Auto and um I don't know it's a little bit more realistic as far as you know some of the vehicle damage and stuff and then um other than that really uh Elder Scrolls Oblivion I've played through about half of that now and hopefully gonna finish the other half I gotta grind through it so I can sell it back you know that type of thing and um
[SPEAKER_03]: Gears of War Elite Beat Agents
[SPEAKER_06]: Elite Beat Agents is the best music-based game ever for the casual player.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and even some people don't want to play Guitar Hero because they're like, that's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Elite Beat Agents is easy.
[SPEAKER_06]: No one else can see because it's on the DS and it's just, you pick up the pen and go.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the song list is surprisingly really good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know a lot of people were like, oh, it's got a weird combination of songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: But dude, if a game can make Ashley Simpson's La La kind of fun, I think it deserves a lot of credit.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I give Elite Beat Agents a lot of credit.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's funny, it cracked me up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even one stage is kind of sad and a little bit sniffly, but you know, I wouldn't cry because I'm a man.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: But no, the game's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, for those that don't know, the essential element of the game is that you tap.
[SPEAKER_06]: You tap on the bottom screen, but you follow these patterns, and you tap, like, in the beat of the music.
[SPEAKER_06]: For instance, if you're playing Material Girl, your tapping might go along with the words, like, do-do-do-do-do-do-do, and you kind of drag the stylus in some parts, too, and follow a little ball.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's a lot more fun than it sounds, because the animations and things really kind of keep you involved.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only small complaint I have with the game is that, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: It just runs even smoothly, so it's great
[SPEAKER_06]: Other game I picked up this week and played is Luminous 2, which is out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, Luminous was my absolute favorite game that was released this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so I still have a lot of love for Luminous 2 because they didn't really change anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's also kind of my biggest problem with Luminous 2 is that half of the skins were Luminous 1 skins.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't think a lot of people picked up on this because maybe people played Luminous 1 and then forgot about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But seriously, if you think... For instance, those folks that follow music-based games, if you think DDR repeats are bad, Luminous puts it to shame.
[SPEAKER_06]: Luminous repeats...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: There's mission mode involved, and versus involved, and there's a demo of every extent extra.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot of new modes that keep it fresh.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you don't own the original Luminous, there's a lot for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you like puzzle games at all, you definitely need to have Luminous 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a must-own game if you don't have the original Luminous.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you do have the original Luminous, then I would ask you...
[SPEAKER_06]: How important are these new modes to you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you really want to be able to use your own music?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you really want to be able to do this other stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you really want to play the Hollaback Girl?
[SPEAKER_06]: How much of a necessity is that to you?
[SPEAKER_06]: And if the answer is, I must, then sure, go get the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's only $30.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not a bad value.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't know if you would want this and the Xbox Live one unless you are just really crazy about your puzzle games or you're luminous.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of tea, Tiara, would you like to share your gaming week with us?
[SPEAKER_06]: What kind of stuff you've been playing?
[SPEAKER_07]: As Soy said, we played Guitar Heroes 2 last night.
[SPEAKER_07]: She was around long enough to beat easy mode, and then I played through medium, or whatever you call it, normal mode, long enough to unlock Trogdor.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then we played Trogdor, and then we went to sleep.
[SPEAKER_07]: But before that...
[SPEAKER_07]: I played Tetris on my phone for a million hours while we waited for A Nightmare Before Christmas to start because somebody bought tickets for the 12.30 show and we actually got there at like 10.30 so it was like two hours of Tetris joy I thought I was going to get lost she got lost everywhere else, that's all but I got lost in a cool way because we found underneath the Golden Gate Bridge yeah, under but that's it, excitement, the end
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, actually, I want to interview you for a little bit because you haven't been on the show in a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And last time you were on the show was when we were still exclusively talking about music-based games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So now we have a whole new world and more people listen to the show thanks to iTunes and XBStream and all games and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: What kind of games do you enjoy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you a computer gamer?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you a console gamer?
[SPEAKER_06]: What would you say is your favorite way of playing games?
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, my outside of the home life has been so busy lately that I haven't really done a lot of gaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually gave up WoW.
[SPEAKER_07]: which was amazing because I never thought I would do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, I was so addicted and I was like main healer in my guild and everything and one day I was just like, you know what, I think outside is nice too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to go outdoors and play today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where are you from so our listeners know?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm from Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know we have some listeners in Vegas so very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: GuardianLegend
[SPEAKER_06]: Best 8-bit game ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Find it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the best.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the most underrated title ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will not shut up about this game until I get my sequel on one of the next-gen consoles.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care if, like, the rights are somewhere in a black hole right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fucking find those rights.
[SPEAKER_06]: Give me a sequel to The Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not that much to ask.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just write your congressman.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to write Feinstein tonight and say...
[SPEAKER_06]: I want a bill passed that will make them make a Guardian Legend 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Junami, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, similar to Yarrarar, I sort of gave up WoW for a bit even though I'm still freaking paying for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was playing Guitar Hero 2 for most of the week, unlocked everything, everything, beat hard mode, that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't been going outdoors.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been going bar doors.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, you live in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been to Vegas.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's nothing to do outdoors in Vegas except make things out of dirt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everything you do in Vegas is indoors and pretty and lights and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, when you live in Vegas, you hate the casinos, don't you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I hear.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've just passed the law for no smoking in restaurants and stuff, so that should be nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: We didn't pass the law for smoking marijuana, though, because all of those stupid stoners were too stoned to go vote!
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, let's go to our chat room, which is available at chat.orangeloungeradio.com and get some comments from our chat room, because the folks over there, we have quite a big crowd there tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're making some good comments there, except now I can't find any.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a lot of people that are listening tonight that say they live in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Janai, Gilder, both live in Vegas, saying hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, of course, to that press start, says, does not live in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jeremy Todd 1 is shocked that Adrenami is giving up World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: No, yeah, for those that didn't hear, I put out a call the other week because remember when Tack Johnson decided to sue Midway or, I don't know, wrote a nasty letter to Midway or whatever he did over the fact that there was create a character and somebody made his likeness?
[SPEAKER_06]: So I put out a challenge to our listeners to create Tack Johnson in as many different likenesses as you could in different games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I was hoping to see one in Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, FootyMonster put one up from what?
[SPEAKER_06]: What was it, City of Heroes?
[SPEAKER_10]: I believe so.
[SPEAKER_06]: City of Villains.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well, how appropriate.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: The OL Army salutes you, footy monster.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to see more.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what else we need to do?
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: We need to give our special foreign correspondent from the People's Republic of Davis a shout-out.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is Puppy's birthday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, happy birthday to Puppy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy birthday, Puppy.
[SPEAKER_10]: And in dog years, he's, like, going to fall over and die any moment now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: What else do I want to say regarding chat comments?
[SPEAKER_06]: JeremyTodd1 asked me in regards to my gaming week, which game is better, Luminous Live, Luminous 1, or Luminous 2?
[SPEAKER_06]: It depends.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would say if you don't own any of them...
[SPEAKER_06]: But you have a PSP, Luminous 2 is probably the best one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just because it practically has all of Luminous 1 in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you already own Luminous 1, the question is, are these little upgrades and the fact that they're going to recycle half of what you already have, is that enough for you to upgrade the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It depends how addicted you are to the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do think Luminous Live is pretty cool too, though, for those that don't have a PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't go out and buy a PSP just for Luminous like I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Xbox Live one is fine, it's just that the Xbox needs a better D-pad.
[SPEAKER_06]: It needs a better D-pad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please, some third party, I don't know, maybe there's Microsoft issues why nobody's done this yet, but seriously, somebody needs to put out a better D-pad for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, you know, Luminous Live has Xbox Live and all that stuff, which is kind of cool, so I'll say that's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Housekeeping!
[SPEAKER_06]: I will say this, I got served.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you listen to part B of last week's show, I said, we were talking about a rumor at that time that Microsoft was going to be offering movies and TV downloads, and I said, no way, they won't do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they sold HD downloads, it would totally nerf the sales of the HD DVD.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what did Microsoft announce on Tuesday?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that they're going to be offering a movie and TV downloads in HD formats.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I got told.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, anyway, they announced that various shows from MTV, CBS, movies from such places like Paramount Pictures, all this stuff would be available.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, there's some screenshots circulating, and you can see some downloads include V for Vendetta, Poseidon, Cradle to the Grave, Lethal Weapon 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know the TV stuff they're offering, old school Star Trek, but the redone special effects, that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Survivor and Pimp My Ride because you really wanted to have that on the Microsoft 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: So basically in a recent story that was on Joystick, Scott Henson from Microsoft talked a little bit about how things would work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Henson mentioned that the files that you download, they will be stored on the 360's hard drive unit and there's not going to be an option to stream videos from the Windows computer because you can kind of already do that if they're in WMV.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Your average 22-minute high-definition TV show will be about 1 gigabyte, and the standard definition version will be 300 megabytes.
[SPEAKER_06]: 720p is what all the high-def stuff is going to be encoded in.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not going to go up to 1080.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would imagine that's because of space concerns.
[SPEAKER_06]: And 720p is really not that bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have the eye to distinguish between the two, then maybe you ought to just get an HD-DVD drive and do it that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't need this.
[SPEAKER_06]: So are you endorsing underground schemes such as BitTorrent?
[SPEAKER_10]: I make no secret of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I think that it's a good idea in theory for people who maybe aren't so computer savvy, maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or people who, you know, are slaves to MTV's programming content and can't live without, you know,
[SPEAKER_10]: The same mindless stuff that they throw out at everybody on their regular station.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have to infect Xbox Live as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: So more power to them.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I have YouTube.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well technically YouTube's not supposed to have a lot of that content on there anyways and they've gotten in trouble for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I have DVDs as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: to be wanting to download that, but, no, no, no, that show is, it's, I like the show, I just wouldn't pay for the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a fun show, it's just like Mythbusters, I'd love watching, that's something that they didn't have on there, they should have episodes of Mythbusters, because that's an awesome show, but, you know, hey, I noticed something though, I noticed that G4 shows weren't on there, and that's kind of surprising too, I mean, you'd think that
[SPEAKER_03]: A cable network like that would want to, I don't know, sell their shows to make any sorts of money that they can possibly make?
[SPEAKER_06]: Good riddance, I say.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think it's interesting, though, that Microsoft is not embracing yet the online, the huge resource online there is of free videos and free audio streams, such as podcasts and vodcasts and that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or, I'm sorry, blogcasts and vlogcasts, if you are an Xbox 360-only type person that won't call them podcasts.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever, I don't care, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just a word.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, okay, I'm curious, real quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Drew, is this something that interests you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not really, considering I don't even have a 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, then, enough said.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess I asked the wrong person.
[SPEAKER_06]: I won't bother asking Tiara, then.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, what do you think about this, though, the Trojan horse aspect of this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't we – I mean, a lot of people were saying this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't just us, but a year ago when these next-gen systems were first being formed, a lot of us said, oh, these are Trojan horses.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to be put in your living room under the guise of a game system, but they're going to be all this entertainment in a box.
[SPEAKER_06]: And look at it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's coming to life.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would also like to point out that at the Xbox 360 demo thing that they had where you sat on the floor and the thing rumbled on your butt, the big speaker thing, that they said all this.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was part of their thing when they had the Xbox 360 at E3 years ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, so like something that they teased a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course they want to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's
[SPEAKER_03]: Their media center PCs aren't selling that great, so they gotta sell something that's like a media center.
[SPEAKER_06]: So how long before the PlayStation 3 follows?
[SPEAKER_03]: Instantly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, seriously, instantly.
[SPEAKER_03]: As soon as it comes out, it's there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where will Nintendo fit into all this, or do they care?
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo doesn't really have to care.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't have to care yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, after all, they're not even jumping on the online bandwagon yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, so anyways, with most everything that's released nowadays or announced for Microsoft, Sony always has to make a counterpoint to anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: And their big thing was, oh yeah, this download service sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: In that case, I do have to agree with Sony, because, well...
[SPEAKER_10]: Your hard drive is not really going to be able to accommodate the volume you'll be downloading.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, Microsoft's even pretty much said the same thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was Aaron Greenberg, who was the group product marketing manager, actually said that they aren't ready to bring out a larger hard drive yet so that basically you can use your memory card and get your own hard drive and use it to...
[SPEAKER_06]: So in other words, because we're too lazy to put out an 80 gig hard drive right now, you should just buy four 20 gigs to store all this shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and that's basically kind of the same thing that Sony was saying about their content.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, PlayStation 3's content is designed for everyone to enjoy right out of the box, which is...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I think you could do that with the PS2 as well though.
[SPEAKER_03]: With their HD unit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, the hard drive thing that
[SPEAKER_10]: We put like 150 gig on ours.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, for non-online Sony game related stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: But also a lot of games, especially in Japan, made big use of the hard drive because you would load a good portion of a game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, for example, on, what was it, 6th style, 2DX 6th style, you could, with the hard drive, you could load all the songs into the hard drive and then play the...
[SPEAKER_10]: What was that mode called?
[SPEAKER_10]: The marathon mode?
[SPEAKER_06]: Non-stop or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Endless.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you could just play endless until you lost.
[SPEAKER_10]: They even had some games where, I believe, wasn't it Final Fantasy XII?
[SPEAKER_10]: You could load onto the hard drive too?
[SPEAKER_06]: The 2DX Nazis in our chat room are correcting you.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's 5th style, not 6th style.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was one of those.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was close.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you consider there's like, what, like,
[SPEAKER_10]: I gave up after 8th style, which was the last good one, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, I want to make a comment on this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this guy that said I need to buy multiple hard drives?
[SPEAKER_06]: Who was it that said that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, Aaron somebody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aaron somebody, fuck a whole lot of you, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, look, when your two biggest competitors are offering something better already, you got no room to be making this statement about how I should be buying additional 100 gig hard drives.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't get me wrong, 360, I still love ya, but right now, look, I can get an 80 gig hard drive in the size of my hand with the iPod, take it wherever I want, and then with the Sony department, you're gonna be able to put whatever hard drive you want in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's
[SPEAKER_03]: Laptop hard drives are not $100, especially a 20 gig hard drive for a laptop is dirt cheap.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the fact that you can buy a 150 gig laptop drive for probably less than you're going to be spending on whatever their next hard drive that they come out for the 360, which is probably going to be like 60 or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know, it's just retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, let's move on to another topic, sticking with Xbox, because I do, you know, even if I think this whole lack of a larger hard drive thing is a little bit silly, Xbox does do a lot of things right, and one of them is the Xbox Live Arcade, despite the fact that Contra is kind of broken.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are some new games coming out for Xbox Live Arcade, including, before the end of the year, Assault Heroes, Heavy Weapon, Novadrome, and yes, Loki, just for you, Small Arms, all coming out before the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, Microsoft also this week announced a partnership with Atari to bring some classic Atari games to Xbox Live in 2007, as if they didn't have enough retro titles.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen pictures of them, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: They look pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they've got, you know, kind of like the Konami titles on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have their retro mode and their, you know, kind of remastered mode, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the games you'll be able to get, Warlords, Tempest, Missile Command, Centipede and Millipede, Battlezone, and Asteroids slash Asteroids Deluxe.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, yeah, they're going to have, like, the evolved mode is what they're calling it in the Atari games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Supposedly, you can play games like Warlords online, which I guess is kind of cool, but I think like most retro games...
[SPEAKER_06]: It will be thrilling for about 20 minutes, and then you'll be, why did I spend 400 points on this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's pretty much a lot of the games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or if you're Loki, you'll say, are the achievements easy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I need to boost my score, because I'm a stats whore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, that is true.
[SPEAKER_06]: So anyways, another thing with the 360, their last... Hey, would you say when it comes to gamer score that you're a total size queen?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I would not use the word queen.
[SPEAKER_03]: A size king.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, for the 360, the last update they did with 1080p blocked out some of the wonderful 1080p televisions out there, and there's also been other issues with it just not being very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, of course, they are working on a fix right now on it, and it is being addressed, and hopefully it will be fixed relatively soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: CallDuty3 comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: The online is lagged, bugged, and doesn't work correctly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't you learn from the first one?! !
[SPEAKER_03]: Fix the game before it comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or did you just say, oh, fuck, we need to get it out before Christmas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, who cares if it's not finished?
[SPEAKER_03]: No one's going to care.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll just release a patch later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'll be angry, but they'll buy the next one.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, seriously, finish the game before you release it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, at least the boss monster shows up in level 30, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, at least they didn't fuck that up.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be my forever question I'm always going to ask when you tell me a game's broken.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to say, does the boss monster show up in level 30?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because if so, at least they didn't fuck up as bad as somebody else I can think of.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's just crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe they took a page from Rockstar and just didn't play the multiplayer mode and just released the game as is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, do you know what the very first thing I did was when I played Gears of War?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: I downloaded a patch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Non-stop excitement from the moment I hit the power button.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gears of War is currently sitting on the desk in my living room.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if it's been played yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gears of War is like a visual orgasm.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'll have more to say on it next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the gameplay, I'm starting to question a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we'll get to that next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't play games for how pretty they are.
[SPEAKER_10]: I play them for how well they play.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, oh, you need to give this one a shot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it really is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, when they say it's pretty, they fucking mean it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really pretty.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, speaking of things that I guess some people might think are pretty, I don't know, we actually have one person who plays this game in the room right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's news for Second Life.
[SPEAKER_10]: As Junami raises his hand.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sup?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, at any rate, you will be able to sit around with your virtual friends watching TV in
[SPEAKER_01]: This is the kind of thing that I go into Second Life to get away from.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm laughing because this is stupid!
[SPEAKER_04]: This is so stupid!
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, what are you gonna do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, man, wanna come over to my virtual pad and hang out?
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll watch Pimp My Ride?
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do you think I was doing in the, and you can do this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not blaming you, but this is, I mean, I get the like technological, wow, that's kind of neat end of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, hey, I can watch TV online, but okay, seriously, like if you're meeting up with other people online to just sit down and watch TV, you can do that in real life.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that being twice as lazy?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, seriously, because if I'm sitting down playing a game where I'm watching TV in the game, is that like twice as, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: Twice as lazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of which, you can actually do that also in Darkness, which is coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're having a streaming video and stuff in their TV shows, so you can actually stop in the game and watch TV, which I don't know why you would.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, Funnydale in our chat room wants to know, since when was Second Life a game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's an experience.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a way of life.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just to say so, that it is launching in November.
[SPEAKER_01]: What would really be insane would be if your Second Life avatar would...
[SPEAKER_01]: Login to his virtual computer and then play Second Life.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do they have to pay for a virtual cable bill?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because that would just suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just find the second box.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can see the posts on the Second Life forums now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm really going to anger some fans of this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, but take it in good stride, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: I can see the posts on the Second Life forums now, alright?
[SPEAKER_06]: Attention, everyone.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should come over to my house tonight because we're going to be watching on my 62-inch plasma fake screen on Second Life.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to be watching Battlestar Galactica.
[SPEAKER_06]: See you at 7.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: PUNCH AND PIE
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Not for watching virtual TV.
[SPEAKER_10]: I download it and watch it at my convenience.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait a second.
[SPEAKER_03]: Could in this game, could I say have my character watch TV of another character watching his TV of another character watching his TV?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like reality shows in Second Life?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Second Life Survivor?
[SPEAKER_03]: So we can watch somebody in Second Life on the Second Life TV watching their Second Life TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the ultimate in boring.
[SPEAKER_01]: I am positive it can be done.
[SPEAKER_01]: All we have to do is find out how.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on to topics before we get all the hate mail from the Second Life fans.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look, you know, I'll give you... I just got the finger from Doonami.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look, I'll give you this.
[SPEAKER_06]: If the goal of Second Life is to, like, recreate life, then having the ability to just kind of go somewhere and hang out, watch TV, is a big step.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's one small step for man.
[SPEAKER_06]: One giant leap for virtual man... Forget it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, Wii Component Cables, hey, the Nintendo Wii's coming out, and remember the Component Cables, uh, there's this whole back and forth where Perrin Kaplan said, yes, you're gonna be able to get the Component Cables in stores, but then the internet's like, but you lied to us before, lady, when you said that the thing would be region-free.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this is what's up is that there's actually only going to be three retailers that you can get it at for now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Circuit City, GameStop, and Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm assuming when they say GameStop, they mean EB Games as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So those will be the places that you can get the component cables.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you're getting your Wii somewhere else, like Toys R Us, I didn't see them on the list, you may have to go to one of the other retailers to get your component cables if you are a 480p whore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not surprised.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they're running in the shortages on everything for the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Accessories, Zelda, Excite Truck, they cannot produce them fast enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm wondering if they just spent all this time trying to produce the units and cut back on the accessories and other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: As far as my company, that's what we're running into.
[SPEAKER_03]: Allocations on everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Accessories and games and you name it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, limiting it down to three different stores, which I'm sure they paid a fat little bonus to Nintendo for that privilege, makes perfect sense to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: The chatroom's still fixated on the Second Life thing, and there's a good comment here, so I want to read it.
[SPEAKER_06]: FootyMonster says, Second Life does open a way of people who cannot be physically together to actually hang out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give you that, and that's kind of cool, and like World of Warcraft is very similar, and a lot of these MMOs are very similar, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you're gonna hang out and watch TV, that's what you're gonna do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me put it this way, that'd be like, you know, the equivalent of, okay, I'm flying, okay, to the other side of the world to meet a pen pal or whatever, and once I get there, what do I do?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've spent all this money, all this time, you know, building up for this moment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey man, you wanna watch some TV?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, sure, let's watch.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's like a big, like, waste of time.
[SPEAKER_03]: What'd you say, Tiara?
[SPEAKER_03]: What'd you say?
[SPEAKER_07]: I said that just described my trip here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look, if you're going to spend all that money to fly out and meet your pen pal, at least do some fucking, because that's... Actually, actually, actually, actually, actually... Because you know that expectation is there somewhere.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was really... Well, Chris and Megsie met...
[SPEAKER_06]: And what do you think they do when they meet up in real life?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think they read the Bible and pray together?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, they're doing some fucking... Here's the better one.
[SPEAKER_03]: When you have friends that come over and both are on the computer, like Rob, if you and Shane are over here, you'll be playing Phantasy Star Universe or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Both of you playing Second Life and watching TV in Second Life together.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're in the same room, not communicating to each other, but you're still watching the TV in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: My mind has just been blown.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, back to actual, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I just wanted to say, if you can't afford the whole plane ticket thing because you can't get out there and have sex with the person that you've been talking to online, the least you can do instead of watching TV in Second Life is do some cyber fucking because that's as close as you can get.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn straight.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyways, on to actual real uses for your TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's definitely a big thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right now, it's speculated that you're not going to be able to have Rumble in your Nintendo 64 games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because your Nintendo 64 games are going to be using the classic controller, and there is no Rumble for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now...
[SPEAKER_03]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, also when you think about the Nintendo 64, not all the controllers had rumbles.
[SPEAKER_03]: You had to, you know, basically buy the rumble pack for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know if that's a huge thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess, like, in games like Ocarina of Time where that was, you know, important because they rumble for, like, you know, hidden treasure and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, I remember reading somewhere that it's speculated that you're still going to have rumble in the games because apparently on the back of the classic controller you'll be able to snap the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Wii Remote to it, and it will use the Wii Remote to rumble.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know if this is something that's coming later on, or if, you know, right now, of course, nobody that has their Wii can check that out, because, well, the online service for both the Virtual Console and, you know, anything else, the news, weather, etc., is not available, so they can't try it yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I guess we'll find out on the 19th when all that launches, and I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that a deal-breaker, you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: I personally don't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hucked in a Dumpster
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could have, but I didn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm allowed.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know why I threw it away, too?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I'm just going to buy the games on the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still think nothing is as cool as playing on the original system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mario Kart cannot come out faster on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still think nothing is as cool as playing it on the system it was made for.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which is why I have 40-something video game systems taking up a whole room in my house.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which is true.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, of course, that's no secret to anybody because I'm a big nerd.
[SPEAKER_10]: But what is a secret is, well, actually, that's not a secret either because there are no more Wii secrets.
[SPEAKER_10]: If anyone thinks that Nintendo is holding something, no, Reggie says so himself.
[SPEAKER_10]: So saith Reggie, so be it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So my Wii isn't going to be able to secretly print money?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I was really hoping to have this reaction on launch day.
[SPEAKER_08]: $50 bill?
[SPEAKER_08]: $50 bill!
[SPEAKER_08]: God!
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, I heard the Wii was going to print money, so I was excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, only for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we have a story later on that might be true.
[SPEAKER_03]: What, that the Wii prints money?
[SPEAKER_03]: You might be able to make it print money.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_10]: And also, of course, there's the plan about the 4 million unit launch, which...
[SPEAKER_10]: What is... Is that the biggest unit launch, do you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: The biggest launch?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't... I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a big unit.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a powerful Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: What a mighty, mighty Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you say it was a big unit, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not interested in the big unit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you say it's one of the biggest units you've ever seen?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, let's see, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of big units that will cost you big money, GameStop is putting together this big bundle of Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a $700 Wii Mega Bundle.
[SPEAKER_06]: And basically, this is the only way that you can get a Wii through their website early.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because remember, this is the same shit they pulled with the Xbox 360, is that, you know, hey, you want to have the Xbox 360 right now?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, buy our $1,000 bundle that has all these games with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's sold out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know, I was getting to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Goddammit, stop ruining the punchline.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, the Wii is $2.50, you get the SD card, which is $60, an additional Wiimote for $40, six games, totaling $300, a 12-month product replacement plan, and, whoopty-shit, a Game Informer gift subscription.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, the talk online was, don't support this bullshit!
[SPEAKER_06]: This is extortion, in a way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right?
[SPEAKER_06]: They know people want this system, so this is how they're doing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So don't support it and then the damn thing sells out in like five minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were going to band together as gamers and teach these corporate dickheads a lesson that they can't make me buy Super Monkey Banana Ball Blitz whatever shit Wii game that I don't really want.
[SPEAKER_06]: But alas, it sold out in an hour.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I almost bought Super Monkey Ball Banana Blitz.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure there's lots of Super Monkey Ball fans out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just picking on your game for no particular reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm in a mood tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know the 1GB Wii SD memory card for $59.99?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can get one for about $20 at, I believe, New Egg or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely not $60 for a 1GB SD memory card.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, that's a rip-off right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the 12-month Game Informer gift subscription...
[SPEAKER_03]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_03]: Trust me.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's $15 right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going to the chat room and reading some comments.
[SPEAKER_06]: RavensDolphin says, Well, look at the PlayStation 3, Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, zing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the whole fact that maybe I don't want a freaking Blu-ray player.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then again, that's kind of a necessary component, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the games are going to be Blu-ray, so... Let's see...
[SPEAKER_06]: JeremyTodd1 says, but not everyone likes the same games as you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe those people wanted all the games packaged in, and so they bought this bundle so they would save money.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I beg to differ.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't save any money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at the games you're getting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Twilight Princess, Trauma Center, Red Steel, Marvel Ultimate Alliance, Super Monkey Ball Banana Blitz, and Madden NFL 2007.
[SPEAKER_06]: You mean to tell me the same person that's going to buy Red Steel is going to buy Monkey Ball Banana Blitz and Madden 2007?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is interested in all those games together?
[SPEAKER_06]: Madden is poopy Madden for the Wii is not exactly poopy Madden's not poopy Madden's not poopy at all if you like football games but I'm saying that I don't think you like every single one of those genres maybe it's the opposite maybe you're a Madden fan and that's the game you want because throwing the football with a controller is kind of fucking cool even for somebody who may not be into football games but do I really want Monkey Ball?
[SPEAKER_03]: Super Monkey Ball Banana Blitz is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've got tons of cool mini-games, and apparently it's both for kids and people that are really hardcore into that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think we've overlooked, though, the main selling point.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the family pack.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, JeremyTodd1 seems to agree with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the Wii is marketed towards the whole family, so the kids would like the child games, and the older people would like the Red Steel Madden.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then again, all six, and of course, JV Mon says, I pre-ordered Monkey Ball and Red Steel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, but did you pre-order Madden?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that game interesting to you too?
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you say all six of those games are something that interests you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Footy Monster says they are good games in general.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't played them yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Marvel Ultimate Alliance is just a shitty port.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game itself is good, but, I mean, it's just a port.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, all this forced extortion of money and forcing me to buy Monkey Ball when I don't really want it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It ruffles my feathers and it makes me very angry.
[SPEAKER_06]: And as you can already tell, I'm in a bit of a mood tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no particular reason for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think Tiara brings some type of energy with her that makes me more, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's gas from your lunch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: from that yummy pumpkin cheesecake.
[SPEAKER_06]: We went to the Cheesecake Factory today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: But wait, wait, you're going to put me in a good mood and that's not the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is not the time to be in a good mood.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob, they're out of cheesecake.
[SPEAKER_06]: People die.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's time, of course, for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I have one.
[SPEAKER_10]: And one that's the size of an entire city.
[SPEAKER_10]: F you to most of the drivers in San Francisco for being retarded and the whole town for being laid out so funny and getting me lost.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even the power of the double horns did not make the people move out of my way or almost run into me or stop in the middle of the damn, not in the middle of the lane I was in, but between two lanes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, God!
[SPEAKER_10]: Just when I think my road rage might have subsided a bit, I drive in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, it comes back.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I want to kill.
[SPEAKER_10]: I imagine how I'm going to kill them.
[SPEAKER_10]: In slow, painful ways, like using a cheese grater and lemon juice.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm done.
Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: After you do game blog sites that think posting pictures of the Wii in play or posting, I don't know, stupid details like, It comes in a box!
[SPEAKER_03]: With cords!
[SPEAKER_03]: And stuff!
[SPEAKER_03]: That is not news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please stop reporting it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know everyone's excited for this console launch, but I do not need to see...
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, stop motion of you pulling the damn console out of a box.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm exempting Kotaku from this FU because the video of his kid playing the system was so fucking adorable, I wanted to go, Oh, they're so cute!
[SPEAKER_06]: It was so cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm exempting Kotaku from this.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least that's a creative way of doing it, but it... I mean, we had news stories about how the Wii can be used as a whiteboard.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just because it's shiny, you can put, you know, dry erase pens on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big deal, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not news.
[SPEAKER_06]: PooEater agrees with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't give a shit about you playing the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I care about me playing the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: My FU of the week goes to Baskin Robbins because the way they scoop their ice cream, like, all the ice cream comes up at the top and none of it ever falls into the cone.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's like, you know, by the time I eat my ice cream, because they eat my ice cream fast, um,
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no ice cream left in the cone, so it's like I have this empty cone with nothing to do with, and it's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was seriously the best thing I could come up with tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not that angry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eat the cone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, no, then I'll give him this.
[SPEAKER_06]: F you to the fact that still with Baskin Robbins, when you rip off the paper, sometimes, like, some of the paper gets stuck to the cone.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's like, I have to eat paper?
[SPEAKER_06]: You need the glue.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_06]: F you to paper cone things.
[SPEAKER_06]: T-R-R-R-R-R.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have a F you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would just like to say FU to Marvel for taking so freaking long to finish Ultimates Volume 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: The last issue came out last month, and the next issue that will wrap it up, which only needed probably about five pages to finish the entire series, will come out December 20th.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, Drew Nami.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, first of all, shared FU for everyone.
[SPEAKER_01]: FU to MySpace, your site design sucks ass.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your members don't know web design works shit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Give them a quiz before they're allowed to make a profile, please.
[SPEAKER_01]: Please.
[SPEAKER_01]: And F you to people who verb nouns.
[SPEAKER_01]: Verbing nouns suck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stop verbing nouns.
[SPEAKER_06]: And on that note, let's move on to our next story because... Oh, our next story is join our MySpace.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a MySpace profile over at www.myspace.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hear clips from the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Add us to your friends list.
[SPEAKER_06]: Comment on our profile with cute little YouTube videos.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that's what people do on MySpace.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's talk about upcoming release dates.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Loki, I heard Full Auto 2 on the PSP is coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was really surprised to hear that because I had no idea it was in development.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a real surprise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's a complete shocker to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm glad you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone came out and said that because if not I would have had to have said it on every single show for a long time now Well thank god 1UP reported on it because now it's true Because nothing is true until 1UP reports on it It's not necessarily just 1UP, everybody reported on it because they finally put out a press release about it But my god, how many fucking weeks do I need to tell you guys something's coming out
[SPEAKER_03]: and no one picks up on the story until, oh, look, hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Some other website posted about this, so now it's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, poopy on you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: It just makes this show special.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the people that listen to this show, you're like a special club.
[SPEAKER_06]: You get to know this first.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so some other special stuff you get to know first.
[SPEAKER_03]: Full Isle 2 Battle Lines for the PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're waiting for that as a launch title, guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not coming out at launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be coming out December 13th instead.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, ha!
[SPEAKER_03]: That's karma for you, Sega.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, along the same lines, Blazing Angels for the PlayStation 3, also not coming out until December 13th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rainbow Six Vegas, also another game being delayed until January 31st for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Xbox Live Arcade Unplugged Volume 1 Pack PlayStation 2 Demo Disks
[SPEAKER_03]: Jampactus.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, now they have this brand new thing called Xbox 360 Exhibition.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be $5.99 retail.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll feature six demos, including Madden NFL 07, Dead Rising, Fear, Fusion Frenzy 2, Lego Star Wars 2, and also six HD videos, including Halo 3, Splinter Cell Double Agent, Gears of War, Rainbow Six Vegas, etc.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: No, this is meant for someone, of course, that does not have Xbox Live, so they wouldn't have access to this, or they just didn't want to buy the Xbox official magazine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or you just really want to pay for demos.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it is out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's coming out on the 22nd, the one-year anniversary.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have $6 to spend, and I just don't know what to do with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not really interested in a combo meal from a local fast food restaurant.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can tell you what you would spend this money on, and it's goddamn not...
[SPEAKER_03]: 360 Exhibition, Sneak King.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sneak King is which you can spend your money on Sneak King and hell, you have enough money for some fries and a Coke.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wrong because you have to get a combo meal to get the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you actually need more than six dollars.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just got served.
[SPEAKER_06]: You got BK served.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're still hungry.
[SPEAKER_03]: You would spend the money on lunch anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now you get Sneak King.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, this is what I'll do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll get Drew.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll say, Drew, don't you want to go out to eat and make him buy the meal and then I'll buy the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Money saved.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't you want some chicken fries?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so getting back into the swing of things here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, this week actually for games is probably the largest week of the entire year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that said, there's not a lot of good stuff coming out actually, which is really sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for the 360 though, there are some pretty interesting things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dead or Alive Extreme 2 is finally making its way out into the market.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you're looking for a lot of T&A, well, you won't have to wait much longer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, Rainbow Six Vegas for the 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess I'll have to get some chicken fries and some TNA.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eragon is coming out on PlayStation 2, Xbox, the 360, and then the portable systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pimp My Ride on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, no, I forgot that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got delayed a week.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyways, what were you going to say there, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: Something really sarcastic about Pimp My Ride the game, but I really need to shut up tonight because we're going to get angry emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob talks too much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob talks too much on the program.
[SPEAKER_06]: I downloaded this podcast having no idea that Rob would talk so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, his fucking picture is on the little album art, but I never knew he would talk so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: More lesbians.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, lots of PlayStation 3 games, of course, all the launch stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mobile Suit Gundam, Crossfire, NHL 2K7, NBA 2K7, Ridge Racer 7.
Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, of course, a bunch of Wii titles, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Avatar Last Airbender, Red Steel, Excite Truck, Legend of Zelda Twilight Princess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty much everything that you want for the Wii is coming out Red Steel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other than all that stuff, Bionicle Heroes is coming out on PlayStation 2, GameCube 360, the DS, Game Boy Advance, Tomb Raider is finally coming out on the Nintendo systems, Capcom Classics Collection Volume 2 is on PlayStation 2 and Xbox, the Sega Genesis Collection is finally coming out, Guitar Man Lives on the PSP, Final Fantasy 3 on the DS, Gunpei on PlayStation 2 and the DS,
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, there's just so much crap coming out, it's amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, yeah, more than I would even want to list.
[SPEAKER_03]: All your PlayStation 3 launch titles, all your Wii launch titles, a lot of other stuff mixed in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: WWE Smackdown vs. Raw 07.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is just too much shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know the commercial Nintendo should have aired?
[SPEAKER_06]: This Sunday, Sunday, Sunday, come on down and get your Nintendo Wii!
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got Big Twilight Princess!
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got Super Wookiee Ballin' in a Bits!
[SPEAKER_06]: Controllers will move this Sunday, Sunday, Sunday at the arena.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and Sonic the Hedgehog Excite Truck!
[SPEAKER_06]: And Chicken Fries.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sonic the Hedgehog on the 360 is also coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pass.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, how about a little bit different release news?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you play the demo?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it was poopy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it was very poopy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sonic the Hedgehog 360?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it was poop.
[SPEAKER_02]: I talked about that last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Were that all for our U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: release dates?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that all for our U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: release dates?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, there's too much for me to list.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, honestly, Polarium Advanced, I mean, if you really want to buy that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we've got a few releases coming up for the U.K.
[SPEAKER_10]: 14th November, we have EverQuest 2, Echoes of Thadeware for PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: 17th, a good number, Asterix Noble XXXL2, Mission Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_10]: on PSP and DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did I miss Asterix and Obelix?
[SPEAKER_10]: I used to read those comics back in the day.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gears of War on the 17th, Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter Premium Edition on Xbox 360, Heroes of Might and Magic 5, Hammers of Fate, Lumen S2 on PSP, Mind Quiz on PSP, Superman Returns the Video Game on DS, Sims 2 Pets on GBA.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, have fun!
[SPEAKER_10]: Just a little bit of other stuff to look forward to within the month is Rule of Rose, Neo Geo Battle Coliseum, Guitar Hero 2 on the 24th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Instead of have fun, wouldn't that be have a jolly old time?
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a jolly old time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Chyram's asking who fed me sugar before the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie, actually, she brought me a cookie.
[SPEAKER_06]: I brought cookies.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like a coffee cookie, so it was sugar and caffeine, and apparently it was laced with crack.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, I had Tiara's Latte Cheesecake, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: It all comes together.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Japan, how about some release dates?
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys have the PS3 now, so you're getting some games this week, including Mahjong Cocktail Club, which comes out November 16th, Tiger Woods PGA Tour 07 on November 17th, and Need for Speed Carbon on November 20th.
[SPEAKER_06]: You gotta wait till December 2nd for the Wii, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, kids.
[SPEAKER_06]: You do get a lot of PlayStation 2 releases coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: You get Rhapsodia, which is going into the Konami The Best series.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually getting a little bit of a price cut.
[SPEAKER_06]: And let's see, White Princess II is coming out on the 16th as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: That also appears to be going into a collection.
[SPEAKER_06]: This game is also going into a collection, and this might be my import title of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Kashimashi Girl Meets Girl.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I want that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll bet it does.
[SPEAKER_06]: Girl meets girl and much kashimashi ensues.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: We also have on the Nintendo DS Puzzle Series Volumes 5, 6, and 7 from Hudson.
[SPEAKER_06]: Magic Taizen and Akumajo Dracula.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just a bundle there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gallery of Labyrinth comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's the Portrait of Ruin title.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what they're calling it over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not a bundle, sorry kids.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're a PSP player, Metal Gear Acid 2 is going into the best this week on the 16th.
[SPEAKER_06]: You get a Sudoku game from Hudson on the 16th.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Gunpei, oh wait, that's the 20th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, you gotta wait a little while longer for that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's all I got for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, with the Wii coming out here pretty soon, and of course the Virtual Console also launching relatively soon...
[SPEAKER_03]: Duck Hunt, Hogan's Alley, Kid Icarus, Kirby's Adventure, Pilotwings, Pro Wrestling, Punch Out, and Wild Gunman.
[SPEAKER_06]: In other words, seriously, the games I really want.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wild Gunman is like the most simple game ever made.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you ever played Wild Gunman?
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the concept of wild gumming.
[SPEAKER_06]: The person goes, draw, and you fire the zapper gun as fast as you can.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's basically, they could re-release this game as push the button fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's exactly what it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was in Back to the Future, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the game that was there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was it also in The Karate Kid?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I might be on crack.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that was skeet shooting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm on crack.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's kind of stupid, though, that they have Duck Hunt coming out anyways, because, I mean, was it that Wii Play game was pretty much Duck Hunt anyways?
[SPEAKER_03]: So.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, we're not getting Wii Play, because we're the United States, and fucking UK gets it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bastards.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be nice if they would rename Hogan's Alley Hogan Knows Best's Alley, because then I could zap Brook, and that would bring me endless days of excitement.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hogan's Heroes Alley.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hogan!
[SPEAKER_06]: The Hogan Family Alley.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just killed Sandy Duncan.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you caught that reference, you totally are an 80s child.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even Matt's laughing at that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even know why.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't you remember the Hogan Family?
[SPEAKER_06]: Never mind, forget it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember the Hogan Family.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what else I remember?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: When this show was good?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Namco has registered new Katamari Damacy trademarks, so we can get more ball rolling in.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have beautiful Katamari Damacy, Katamari Damacy Tribian, and there was an application filed for Katamari Damacy-kun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ball rolling, and to think I skipped the PSP version of Katamari.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, we talked about man cannons the other week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you roll a Katamari into a man cannon?
[SPEAKER_06]: What would happen?
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be a... A big black hawk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that reference is about 150 episodes old, and people aren't going to get it, and they're going to go, what the fuck is wrong with Jamie?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Drunami knows what episode number, you are sad, you are sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: 29, 29 he says, alright, anyway, sorry.
Oh, my turn.
Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Xbox Live is getting another new game very soon, and this is one I know that's near and dear to at least one person's heart in this room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Worms!
[SPEAKER_06]: You remember Worms?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_06]: Worms HD is coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right now, plans for announcements are being discussed with Microsoft right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game is in final certification stages, so maybe we'll get this by the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be rad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rumor is that the release calendar is full for the year, so this might have to wait until next year, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, here's my thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are we getting another UNO pack?
[SPEAKER_06]: God, that's, you know, if another game gets delayed, I really can't fucking wait for the Viva Pinata UNO pack.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just, God, I'm on pins and fucking needles waiting for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have 100 points saved just so I can buy the Viva Pinata Uno pack.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope one of these games... No!
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course I'm lying!
[SPEAKER_06]: This game could be put in when some other game gets delayed if it's ready to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know one of those other games is going to get delayed because they're going to go, oh, gee, when we do the upscrolling level, it looks completely different on two different screens.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, Worms is the game, of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like Scorched Earth.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Scorched Earth in wormy form.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, you fire bombs and
[SPEAKER_10]: I've actually been quoting lines from Monty Python all weekend, and I was quoting the holy hand grenade thing at the Metreon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh lord, bless this thy hand grenade, that it might blow thine enemies to tiny bits, in thy mercy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, at the wax museum, that's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, something completely different, you say?
[SPEAKER_03]: How about Linux on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say Wii on Linux.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be a little weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but anyways, yes, Wii and Linux.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wheelie, you say?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, that's actually what it's called, Wheelie.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's being done.
[SPEAKER_06]: I see what you did there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so it's actually being worked on, and...
[SPEAKER_03]: Supposedly, they're going to start beta testing this thing as soon as the Wii comes out because it's based on the GameCube Linux as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some things that they're aiming to be able to do with this, surfing the internet using the control, of course, as a mouse pointer, even though you can do that anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wii Media Extender to stream movies and music and stuff from your PC to the Wii and to your TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: They said basically think Apple ITV for free.
[SPEAKER_03]: Write document with a regular USB keyboard and print with any USB printer.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you could print money.
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: See?
[SPEAKER_03]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Email and chat with your friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: $50 bill?
[SPEAKER_08]: $50 bill?
[SPEAKER_08]: $50 bill!
[SPEAKER_08]: God!
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, I was late.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Play classic games using the MAME console emulator.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be irony right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Develop your own programs and games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Control Wheelie from your PC using a Wi-Fi connection and use Wheelie and the Wii as a network attached storage by connecting it to an external USB hard drive and pretty much anything else you can do on a PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: So,
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've signed up to hopefully beta test this, so probably more of the come as the Wii gets launched.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, wheelie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wheelie.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm waiting for the picture of the owl.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now that I've said, oh, is there already, oh, there it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, no, that's a Linux penguin.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not an owl.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's dressed up like Mario.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, that's cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm waiting for the, you know, the famous owl that says, oh, really?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm waiting for the oh, wheelie one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, sorry to encourage that behavior on the internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know you like to encourage mass hysteria.
[SPEAKER_10]: Speaking of mass hysteria, this won't really encourage any of it, but it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: For those five people still playing Animal Crossing DS, which I need to actually clean out my village and start doing that because this is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: With the launch of Twilight Princess on 19th November, Nintendo will be giving away a very special and rare gift in Animal Crossing, according to their...
[SPEAKER_10]: If you connect via Nintendo Wi-Fi during the week of November 17th through 24th, you'll receive a letter from Nintendo, which will show up in your mailbox, and you will receive an attached item.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, it could be anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Accompanied with the letter will be a corrupt item that will erase your save and say, Go buy a Wii, stop playing the DS!
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it'll be a flower that you put in your house and then you can't put anything in that corner of your house.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, wait, they already did that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually went to NintendoWiFi.com just to prove Jamie wrong because I like to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it shows 20 random Wi-Fi players.
[SPEAKER_06]: And look at that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Six people are playing Animal Crossing Wild World right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have...
[SPEAKER_06]: Danny Boy is playing and Phil is playing and IJ and Mike and Christina with a lowercase c because she's poetic.
[SPEAKER_06]: And look at this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob is playing Animal Crossing right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, Rob, this is just for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: There may only be six people in the world playing Animal Crossing Wild World right this moment, but 1.5 million people are playing Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least that's what Square Enix will have you believe, because they sent out a press release earlier this week saying that Final Fantasy XII has 1.5 million units on shelves.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, well, I guess 1.5 million people aren't really playing it, but yet there's that many copies in circulation, so soon 1.5 million people will be playing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Fantasy XII, by the way, for the record, did 2.4 million copies in Japan, so it'll be interesting to see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wouldn't it be interesting if it sold more here than it did in Japan?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we all know Dragon Quest is the bigger game in Japan, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, Final Fantasy XII, brand new record for the total number of units shipped for the franchise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good job, Squeenix!
[SPEAKER_06]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some other interesting stuff... Now, next time, make the graphics less pixelated.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some interesting stuff for fans of Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guitar Hero 2, of course, you may remember with the demo, it actually blocked the Ant Commando's controllers from working with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: and apparently that's the case also if you have purchased your Guitar Hero controller from them before October 1st if you have then it will not work with Guitar Hero 2 unless you purchase an adapter which I believe is free but don't hold me to that and
[SPEAKER_03]: So once you get the adapter, I guess everything's... Oh, I'm sorry, the adapter's $6.99.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, if you want to play with that controller, you're going to have to pay another $7.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the other controllers beyond that will work with Guitar Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: So apparently anything that did circumvent third-party controllers has been broken already.
[SPEAKER_06]: We kind of knew that would be coming, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you know, that's the Ancommando's business right there, so they had to get around it somehow, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Drew, you've been playing Guitar Hero 2 quite a bit, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: I see you posting about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you interested at all in these third-party controllers or any of that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just don't really see any interest in them.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got my SG controller from the first game, and I don't really need another one.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I feel like I'm kind of over Guitar Hero, like seriously, the hype around Guitar Hero has seriously ruined Guitar Hero for me for some weird reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, like you know how like when you were the only person that listened to this band and then suddenly everybody's listening to the band and you're like, it's just not so special anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's kind of how I feel about Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, call me an elitist, whatever, but am I doing myself a disservice by not checking out Guitar Hero 2?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, absolutely yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, very yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Tiara says no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because if you spend all the time that you spend playing Guitar Hero and Guitar Hero 2, learning to play an actual guitar, think of all the amazing songs you could play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, weren't you telling me a story earlier today about somebody that was in a guitar class?
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell me the story about the girl in the guitar class.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, this involves my boyfriend, Adam.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's taking a guitar class at the community college.
[SPEAKER_07]: and there's a girl in his class who was asking him, you know, do you believe in psychics and explaining something about this one particular psychic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, Adam told her, the only psychic I believe in is Professor Charles Xavier.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so her response was, does he teach at this campus?
[SPEAKER_06]: That doesn't have anything to do with Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, but you were telling me, okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, haha, she's stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the other part about this was, wait, what was this, she asked him if he knew Boston or what was this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, apparently all she plays is Guitar Hero because she asked him if he had ever heard of a band called Boston.
[SPEAKER_07]: and the song that she mentioned was the song on the original Guitar Hero and every time that she says that she likes a band and he asks what songs that she likes from that band, it's the song that's on Guitar Heroes and she doesn't know any of the other songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I give her credit though for at least taking Tiara's advice and going to take a real guitar class instead of playing Guitar Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm sure it's a great game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just, there's other games I wanted more.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll get it next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll get the 361.
[SPEAKER_06]: I swear to you I will buy the 361, like launch day.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: I will shove this mic up your butt.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can come to my house and play.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just might.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I heard on a Bobby show tonight that it supports progressive scan.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks really nice on my TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not special.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll get a copy for you and I'll put it on my PlayStation 2 and you can play on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'll get the 360 version.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I said earlier.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't see the point in getting the PlayStation 2 one when we know the 360 one will be better because of its expandability.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I can wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you?
[SPEAKER_06]: I sold mine, so yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, on that note, we're going to go to a little bit of a break because obviously I need a sedative, so I'm going to go take some Tylenol PM during this break and we'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio after a little bit of a break.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.