[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, January 7th, 2007, Xbox 360 upgrade rumors abound, Nintendo partners with an MMO developer, and prepared to waste even more time with Elder Scrolls Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio Welcome back, live listeners, to a new year of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are that radio program on the interweb dedicated...
[SPEAKER_03]: Video Games, Gamer Culture, and the Gamer Lifestyle
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR was fun today.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hello as well to recently upgraded Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now with more anger and angst.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: You going to Macworld?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, totally.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, welcome by the way if this is your first time listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know we got some new listeners while we were off on holiday for a little while.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks as well to all the sites that joined us last week for the New Year's Eve special.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they turned around and pimped us.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, myself, and Loki all met up and we just decided, you know, because DarkSakura and I had kind of known each other a little bit before that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were doing another radio program under Station Live and we thought, hey, let's do a show about video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, you know, Loki joined us for that and here we are almost five years later and
[SPEAKER_03]: Still doing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No life.
[SPEAKER_03]: The show started about music video games, so sometimes you hear Orange Lounge Radio, the Bobani radio station, which, you know, we still love our music-based games, but we like to think that we are gaming fans first.
[SPEAKER_03]: We just love video games in general, so that's what the show's all about now.
[SPEAKER_03]: The show we try to present to you guys here every week is that we go over the news, and yeah, you know, we only do a show once a week.
[SPEAKER_03]: We only do a show once a week, so you're not always going to get the latest and greatest here.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do...
[SPEAKER_03]: I have the fortunate luck of having Loki working in the industry in an area that most media doesn't think to look in, which is distribution.
[SPEAKER_03]: So sometimes we get some pretty good exclusives that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: But otherwise, you know, we're kind of like we imagine one thing we used to do when we were at the arcades is that, you know, remember when we did like the Wednesday night, we'd get together, play DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then what do we do afterwards?
[SPEAKER_03]: We went to Brookfields and just, you know, talk.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we nerd.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we ate a lot and then we nerded out talking about stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of what we are.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're the folks sitting around the dinner table at your local diner
[SPEAKER_03]: Talkin' about games and talkin' smack when appropriate and talkin' about good things.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we like to invite guests to our table once in a while from the gaming industry, hoping to have some good names on in 2007.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we like to invite all of you.
[SPEAKER_03]: We like to fill up the restaurant with our listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: We know that the majority of our listeners catch us on the audio blog, also known as podcast, which is released every Monday and Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we also have our live listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: We tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time on Orange Lounge Radio, orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: We have Pump Up the Volume and then something unannounced that we'll be filling in the gaps on Tuesday in the interim.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Wednesday nights we have Guys on a Show, which is kind of like pop culture, geek culture stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thursday nights, STFU, which is really like fast-paced game talk.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's more like a sports show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Friday nights we have Club OLR, which is just strictly music.
[SPEAKER_03]: And by the way, if you missed this week's Club OLR, you did a fantastic job mixing music this week, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not just saying that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Would you do a rip-off of something else?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, I didn't rip anything off.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought you did a great job.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe you hurried through it or something, but... A little bit of trivia for those folks out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: LiveWire from the first episode was actually the second episode I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I flipped them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I liked one of them better than the other one.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I liked it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, Saturday nights, Travis Donovan Live, Geek, Sci-Fi, Gaming, 360, you know, whatever's on his mind, trying to bring a little dose of reality to you kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, Sunday nights, we're here.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, enough plugs for the Sci-Projects.
[SPEAKER_03]: We want to welcome all of our new and old listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those have been with us for...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: What have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_03]: You made me play DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did, it was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played also some...
[SPEAKER_01]: Beatmania 3 was it the 6th I think yeah 6th mix played some Cooking Mama played some Pinball we got our Whodunit back which is now Trading Potter and I joined Guild Wars this week I didn't really care for it the last time I tried it but I gave it a go this time around it's a lot more fun I don't know if I'm going to stick with it but I figure at the very least if
[SPEAKER_01]: I pay the money for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can just play it whenever I want and don't have to worry about anything.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been playing with my friend Heather.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: More Cooking Mama.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you beat Cooking Mama yet?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I came this close to buying Cooking Mama, but I'm holding out for the Wii version.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get them both!
[SPEAKER_03]: Completion!
[SPEAKER_03]: And to make a rebuttal to Holy Shonen, I think you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: What did Holy Shonen say?
[SPEAKER_01]: World of Warcraft is better than Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_01]: World of Warcraft is just more annoying than Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, it just kind of depends.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're almost exactly the same game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't see what the point is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to be playing them both.
[SPEAKER_03]: I understand, because...
[SPEAKER_03]: Guild Wars you kind of level up to 20 and pretty much the entire game is endgame but World of Warcraft has a little more in the interim because you know you're going all the way to 60 there's a lot more to do in the interim I guess if you're addicted to leveling that's fine but I think that Guild Wars takes a little bit more skill to play I don't know
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're very similar in game structure to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really prefer one to the other.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like the fact that Guild Wars I can go to whenever I want for free, like once I've bought it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know that the game still has not dropped in price.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to get the old school Guild Wars, you have to pay the full $50 for it, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: But keep in mind, you say you're paying $9.99 a month for World of Warcraft, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Isn't it like $12 or $14.95?
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't even remember.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's more like $12.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Final Fantasy is $12.95 and WoW is like
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're going to end up paying more in a year for World of Warcraft than you are going to pay for Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, I did feel like the WoW universe was way more expansive though.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a lot more to see in WoW.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the fundamental difference between the two, here's the fundamental difference between the two.
[SPEAKER_03]: In Guild Wars, the entire game is what you would call an instance in WoW.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's alluring to some people, the fact that they play with exactly who they want and that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: GhostSquad is freaking fun as hell.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, GS68.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was talking about Ghost Squad.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a gun game in the arcades.
[SPEAKER_01]: That game is freaking hot.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't played a good gun game in a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't played it in ages, but Dan and I went and we just freaking played through every mission and it was great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every time I want to play Time Crisis 4, somebody's on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Full of lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to play Season 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um,
[SPEAKER_02]: and so I've played lots of Resistance and that game is far better than Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that game and actually it's very pretty and looking at Resistance
[SPEAKER_02]: makes you actually kind of question, hey, you know, maybe the PlayStation 3 actually does look better than the 360, and it really looks good.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, I found myself literally, you know, between gunfights, you know, standing there going, wow, this looks really good, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: What a fucking change for the year 2007 on this program.
[SPEAKER_03]: You are gushing about Sony tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, hold on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is he drinking?
[SPEAKER_02]: Resistance is good, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: Didn't I tell you?
[SPEAKER_02]: That game is hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the problem, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, that's all that's out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoa, back up.
[SPEAKER_02]: You got a PS3?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I got a PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm the only OLR host without a PS3?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I got mine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got hooked up, okay, for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm the only one without the cool new toys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: God hates me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're just not part of the PSWe60 club, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: I heart my Wii 60, screw you!
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so, no, seriously though, it's fun, it really is fun, and I just, I like it so much better than Gears of War, and the fact, you know, there's so many different difficulties you can play it on, so if you really aren't, you know, hardcore into it and stuff, you can, you know, have a good time with it, so it's very good, I like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ridge Racer 7.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I bought Ridge Racer 7 because Nelly actually wanted to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And to be honest, I've played it and it's exactly the same as Ridge Racer 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: It pretty much is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, now you said earlier, though, that you felt Resistance was better than anything you'd see on the 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: So because Ridge Racer 7 and 6 are so similar, did you think that graphically the PlayStation 3 one was superior?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I remember a while back...
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because folks were comparing the two and saying the 360 version looked better.
[SPEAKER_02]: I shouldn't say the 360 version.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, I couldn't pick up the differences.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only difference I saw was when you hit your nitro instead of the screen kind of turning white on the edges, it did this weird blur thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I do like Ridge Racer 7 on how they have different ways you can customize your cars and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Full Auto 2 was another one I picked up on that as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was a huge fan of Full Auto 1.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which I sold back this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Full Auto 2 is okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like the first game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't really notice any changes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the graphics look a little different, but it's pretty much the first game all over again, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's do some chatroom comments, because the chatroom's on fire tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got a lot of new people in chat, and I think they've got three weeks of comments just penting up here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mike W. says, Rob was also the only OLR host without a 360 for a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't get a 360 until March.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be honest, though... You eBayed it, or Craigslisted it or something and paid way too much for one, and she got the hookup because Dan was working it.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be honest, I wouldn't have bought a PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob says, Hey Rob, you're not missing anything with the Doorstop 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, there really isn't anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, what I would want most out of it right now is the Blu-ray player and fucking Tekken Dark Resurrection.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that looks pretty badass.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't downloaded that because it's in another country and I don't like fighting games that much, so it's not a big deal for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I tried Grip Shift and that blows ass and I would not recommend it at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: MotorStorm is fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the demo from MotorStorm.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did not like MotorStorm at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I love MotorStorm.
[SPEAKER_03]: You didn't think it was slow?
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was slow.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it just maybe the target I was at?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jaded says, next week, Loki takes back everything he said about Macs because he received a Mac and gloats about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Could this be the year of change for Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, listen, if I got a free Mac, I'd be selling that shit back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd actually probably smash it with a hammer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or give it to Nelly.
[SPEAKER_02]: She'd probably want it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Other than... Mac fans, don't turn us off, because I heart Macs, and so does Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's just crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't like them.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, you know... We're building a PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know if anyone's seen the new pictures of the new VAIO, but... My God, Sony's copying Apple now.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so, back in the games, real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, I played that Gran Turismo HD.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually looks better than the one at E3, but not by much.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, thank God it's free, because I sure as hell wouldn't buy that piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like Gran Turismo, so that's just me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks pretty, I guess, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It seems to me, and this is what I've noticed with a lot of the games on there, it seems to me a lot of these racing games, because that's mainly what I've been playing, have the kind of okay foreground stuff, and they have this really high-res background image that's kind of plastered on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if you've noticed that in some of the pictures of Gran Turismo HD and Motorstorm and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to doing that, but I've been too busy playing the story mode in it, and I love...
[SPEAKER_02]: Even with no achievements to unlock, this is amazing to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, the thing that's kind of cool about those, they sort of have an achievement system for that one game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You unlock these skill points, they call them, and it actually unlocks different things like costumes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So like in Excite Truck and Burnout, you get trophies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what's kind of neat, though, is when you play through the whole game, it unlocks more weapons, and you can go back and play through again, and then you can unlock harder difficulties and stuff, and you get more skins for multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do want to try out 40-player multiplayer online with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that'd be crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, is that it for Gaming Week?
[SPEAKER_02]: That is it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and by the way, just real quick, real quick, PlayStation 3, their download thing, okay, fucking sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Balls, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: The fact that it takes like an hour to download something and you can't do anything while it's downloading.
[SPEAKER_02]: That fucking sucks and they need to fix that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, now I'm done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quick comment on the PlayStation 3 from Jared Joe in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love the potential of my PS3 so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't wait for it to unleash itself.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have Resistance and Marvel Ultimate Alliance and both of those games are fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had Genji.
[SPEAKER_03]: Notice I said I had Genji.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a demo, but I haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't sold mine back yet, but that's because I like going in every now and then punching animals.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just me.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Every week, once a week, we play Quake.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we decided to try and bring that back a little bit and be in touch, because now we live all over.
[SPEAKER_03]: My buddy Garrett is in town, but Bill's off in New York City, and Matt's all traveling around the world.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we kind of tried to connect through Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we played Halo this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what's really funny, well, Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were playing Halo 2 online.
[SPEAKER_03]: We all suck at it, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's the fun part of it, is that when you're playing against other people who suck at Halo, it's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what's really funny about what happened during it is that
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and somebody that joined the game was GamerAndy over, you know, because he has a site, GamerAndy.com, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: And he was signing on to kind of say, I'm sorry, we weren't able to, because he was, he got an invite to the New Year's show, but just scheduling conflicts, he wasn't able to make it on.
[SPEAKER_03]: So he was coming on to say, you know, oh, sorry, I couldn't make it, we'll have to make up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we'll definitely have him on the show at some other time, because he's a really cool guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, oh my God, he kicked all our asses so horribly at Halo.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's like, oh, I'm not any good, I haven't played, you know, he's very humble.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's like, I haven't played in a year and a half, I suck at Halo.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he just wiped all of us.
[SPEAKER_03]: My friend Matt's pretty good, so he was giving him some competition.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really need to buy Halo 2 because, you know, I have... I think it was fun when I played, you know, briefly a long time ago, but I really... I'm not that great at first-person shooters sometimes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, when we're playing Call of Duty 3, all I'm basically... All we play now is rocket launchers, sniper rifles... Yeah, that's actually what we were playing was the rockets.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that game was kind of fun because that's easy to kill someone in rockets, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but, yeah, just rockets and just sniper rifles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can we form a clan for, like, I suck at Halo?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I realize we have the OL Army, but there's actually good players in the OL Army.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have some people that are, like, level 21.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can we get, like, level 1 for life, Joe?
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, I... Level 1 for life.
[SPEAKER_02]: I suck completely... I suck ass at Halo, so... When Halo 3 comes out, I'm scared.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm seriously scared.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll just play, because I'll buy Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm getting a Legendary Edition, so I have a helmet at my desk, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then otherwise I haven't been playing a lot I mean the arcade of course DDR and stuff but otherwise I got 200 of 200 achievement points in New Rally X thank you very much which is sadly the first arcade game I've gotten all the achievement points on and I'm the only one on my friends list that has played the damn game and I know that because I'm the only one with a high score on the list and I have like 70 something friends on Xbox Live and not a damn other person has played the game except me
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: The only reason I bought it, I remember from my childhood, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: So don't hate.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember Rally X and the good old days.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now that you're an old man.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: D.M.N.
[SPEAKER_03]: from STFU
[SPEAKER_03]: and don't forget all our other live programming on Orange Lounge Radio again and of course we wanted to say take a moment to thank again all of our New Year's Eve people we had on this week we hope to incorporate guests not just from like the gaming industry but like other gaming podcasts and people you see out there in the gaming media we're trying to think of ways to incorporate that on into 2007 because the New Year's episode seemed to be really well received and you guys seemed to dig that so definitely we'll do stuff more like that in the future it was cool good times
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, how about some gaming news?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk some smack about some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, start us off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, apparently there's a small little convention going on called CES, Consumer Electronics Show, that I completely forgot about.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was like, oh yeah, CES is going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so I'm kind of starting that all off.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's been some rumors coming out about a brand new version of the Xbox 360, now with HDMI.
[SPEAKER_02]: Code name the Zephyr.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently there's been shots floating around from Engadget.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know there was some video on there from Xbox Scene.
[SPEAKER_02]: So definitely something that's probably going to be out there at some point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although a lot of people are bitching saying, oh, what about the early adopters?
[SPEAKER_02]: You screwed all of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, I'm just like, I don't need HDMI.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: My TV doesn't have HDMI.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Nintendo does this shit all the time, no one seems to mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you know, the DS Lite, I mean, sure, my panties were ruffled a little bit at the fact that, you know, the DS Lite comes out not even like a year after the DS is already on shelves, and I bought the first printing of the DS, but what can you do?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, this thing is inevitable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, really, I mean, for me, it's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I guess later on down the line, if I really had an issue with this, I can just
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess buy another one or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I don't know, my TV doesn't have HDMI, so it's no good for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think my TV does, but, you know, I go back and I think about how long I was like, I have to get a component cable for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to get a component cable.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to have like the best video ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then it really wasn't that big a difference.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think like, is it really going to be a deal breaker that I can't, I don't get HDMI right away?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, chances are my 360 will break eventually anyway and I have to get a new one because
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I'll just wait for that inevitability.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a lot of people are saying also that the new 360 is going to... And I don't even know where they're pulling this info from.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, because I believe the HDMI part because, you know, we've seen pictures of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they're saying, oh, it's going to have a 120 gig hard drive and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, it's going to have the 65 nanometer chipsets in there and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, really...
[SPEAKER_02]: The 120GB hard drive will be something that they add on later.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's something that they'll have the offer that you can buy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not going to be probably included with this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: To be honest, all I think they're going to do is add this HDMI port.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not going to be a brand new model of the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just going to be, now the 360s are coming out with HDMI ports on them.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they'll have the cooler processor in there, so lower the cost of the system, but
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think they're going to do anything above and beyond this.
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR Dollar Bill says, HDMI don't care
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, let's see, we have, um, I believe it was Paradox Vincent said, uh, DS Fat sucks!
[SPEAKER_03]: And, uh, NM64 says, uh, DS Lite is only worth it if you need a new DS or never had one.
[SPEAKER_03]: So some conflicting opinions there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the Fat is fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you know the DS Fat is actually louder than the DS Lite?
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is good for games like Elite Beat Agents and stuff when you need to, you know, drown other people out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: They did the top-loading one that looked like a Famicom later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, you know, with, well, I guess not really the Nintendo 64, the Super Nintendo, but the 64, they added Rumble later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then you could add the RAM pack later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and they had the Pokemon 64.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, exactly, the Pokemon 64.
[SPEAKER_02]: They always tried to pull this shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And don't think that they don't know that later on, you know, people are going to buy an extra DS because it's in a specific color.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, come on, it doesn't,
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not that hard to manufacture the DS in a different color.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, ooh, I just thought though, Microsoft does that too.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've done it before.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what kind of Xbox I have?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't have the same Xbox most people have.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a Halo Xbox that's the see-through green.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a Halo Xbox that's the see-through green.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but most people don't have that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Most people have the big black brick, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: My big black brick died.
[SPEAKER_03]: Microsoft is not beyond redesigning their consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't you think there will be a Halo 3 limited edition console?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or do you think it'll just be a faceplate?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sega did it too, back with the Sega Support Streamcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the faceplates are what they're doing now.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a big thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I wouldn't be surprised if we see a black console later.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's something that's very possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We all know the Wii colors are coming.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those are coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Same with the PlayStation 3 colors.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to see those as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is not... I mean, look at the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have silver, pink.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody does it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I need something to match my cabinet that I got at Ikea.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, oh my god, I gotta totally get a pink one for my girlfriend because she's going to totally appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And when you give it to her, she's like, wow, this is so pretty.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the fuck am I going to play on it?
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, people, you know why they keep doing this, you guys?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's because people are retarded and they will buy this shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: They will buy a blue DS when it comes out because it's blue.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll buy a pink DS when it comes out because it's pink.
[SPEAKER_02]: because people are retarded and they don't understand there's websites out there that make custom color DSs that you can order brand new in any fucking color of the rainbow that you want instead of having to wait for Nintendo to put it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, there's a conversation going on in chat right now that has me thinking a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you think the black Wii will be a little bit bigger than the white Wii?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and the yellow Wii is going to be super tiny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can address those cards and letters to Loki at OrangeLawnsRadio.com Hey, you started it, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's just move right along to talking about Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, we were talking about that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the beta testing, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: You had everybody slam that site trying to get into the beta test.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you'll find out this month if you got into the beta test.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you didn't get in that way, there is the Rule of Three.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I don't know why else you would call it that unless you want people to say the rule of three, the mysterious rule of three to get into the Halo 3 beta test.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's going to happen is that if you play three hours worth of Halo 2 multiplayer between Thursday the 1st of February and February 3rd, 2007, if you're among one of the first 13,333 to register at Halo3.com right after that, then you will be part of the Halo 3 beta.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other way to get into it, buy Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was cool when it was like a beta thing and you didn't know how many people were going to get into it and you thought, oh, hey, this is going to be only a couple thousand.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're in the cool club now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now we're, oh, anyone that buys this game will get into the beta.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and this is another way to get into the beta.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why the fuck is a beta test like fucking incentive to buy something or do something?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you're beta testing something and you don't realize that's actually work.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: People will be on their consoles one minute after, play the three hours back to back to back, and then be on Halo 3 immediately.
[SPEAKER_03]: There will be 13,333 people to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know why Microsoft bothered to make such a big window.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to buy Crackdown and play Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm telling you right now, if you want to get in that way, if you're not on there at midnight ready to play until 3 a.m., forget it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Write it off.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're not getting in.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know that's how it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know it.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's some people who got to play it anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, oh really?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's beat them up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take their lunch money.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that they could actually beat any one of us.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh really?
[SPEAKER_01]: Bungie actually flew over copies of the beta to the troops overseas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, they probably could get my SCM.
[SPEAKER_01]: Probably could.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hearts.
[SPEAKER_01]: And basically let them have the free demo for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_01]: Give it a try.
[SPEAKER_01]: and I think that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's something kind of different.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think a very interesting way.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I bet you a lot of our troops are kind of into Halo 2 and 3 and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's a good way, I think, to relieve some of the stress of having to be there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it was a really good thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good job, Bungie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so more stuff for the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how they always have themes and stuff on Xbox Live and they're so wonderful how they don't show you what they look like before you buy them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, thankfully there is a website now that will show you what they look like called DashboardThemes.com and you can go there before you buy a theme and check out what it looks like and possibly save your Xbox Live points.
[SPEAKER_02]: Personally, I would just save your Xbox Live points or the other thing you can do if you have a memory unit
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, from what I remember reading on this site, the people were putting it together with their own money.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, they do deserve some type of, you know, medallion or recognition from the community for putting together that public service because for whatever reason, Microsoft isn't on top of it with their previews.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you can preview some stuff on Xbox.com to be fair, but they're not very current.
[SPEAKER_03]: And these guys, you know, they have it the day it comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I think they deserve a round of applause from the gaming community.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, other surprises that you might find.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's interesting is that this 14-year-old boy who lives in Utah claims that he purchased a factory-sealed copy of Madden 07 for the Xbox 360, and he put the disc in his system, and up came, not John Madden, but hardcore pornography.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a roster update.
[SPEAKER_03]: The boy immediately notified his parents and they're backing up the claim and said this is legit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, Electronic Arts was contacted and they're working with the store that the game was bought from to see if maybe something funny went on here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like maybe a disgruntled employee put some porn in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, because how easy would it be to print out a Madden label like on your computer?
[SPEAKER_03]: and then take a porn disc and put it on there?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a little harder because those are actually silk-screened onto the discs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but if you're 14 and you don't know to look for that kind of stuff, I mean, don't you think someone could get away with that?
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd have to be pretty retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although he does look pretty retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: You would have to be pretty retarded if you're a 14-year-old boy and you get porn and go tell your parents.
I'm playing Madden.
Go away!
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep the door shut.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm playing Madden.
[SPEAKER_02]: Inviting all your friends over to play Madden.
[SPEAKER_02]: Building a shrine to the Madden disc in your bedroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to see the coolest copy of Madden you've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_03]: EA would, quote, regrets any embarrassment the matter has caused the family.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a way to learn a lesson early.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, one other quote that's great here.
[SPEAKER_03]: According to a paper in Utah, the Standard Examiner, when Mahoney looked at the pornographic images, his first thought was, quote, this is definitely not Madden.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's NHL 2000.
[SPEAKER_01]: on Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: JeremyTodd1 says, Loki, wouldn't you rather sue the game company and get millions rather than keep some porn you can find for free?
[SPEAKER_03]: RavensDolphin1 said, I found porn on my PSP memory card from EB, I told nobody
[SPEAKER_01]: Was it a used game or a new one?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a used... Oh, that game?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a new factory-sealed game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fireboma says he notified his parents, quote, under long review, this is porn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quote, hold on, we have to go review... Gotta go to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, speaking of something that has nothing to do with porn... Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, it might have been, but that's not official.
[SPEAKER_01]: Guess who's leaving Rare for more porn?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, for not porn.
[SPEAKER_03]: The pinatas?
[SPEAKER_01]: The Stamper Brothers are leaving Rare.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, didn't they like found it or something?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_01]: They were one of the, well, I guess two of the main folks behind Rare and now they're gone.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_01]: They've gone to, uh, quote, uh, pursue other opportunities.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're like, they're all, fuck this shit!
[SPEAKER_02]: We ain't making no more fucking pinata games!
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck this, we want Killer Instinct!
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, wait, wait a damn minute, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Viva Pinata was the best thing Rare's put out in a while, sadly.
[SPEAKER_01]: They did put out, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_02]: Porn.
[SPEAKER_02]: We promise, just make the pinata game and we'll let you make Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_03]: What I want to know is, Viva Pinata was not that bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's actually quite good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a pleasant surprise of a game, so don't knock it until you've tried it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a pretty fun game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had way more fun with Viva Pinata than Cameo and Perfect Dark Zero combined.
[SPEAKER_03]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_02]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well, Perfect Dark Zero is like balls.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if that's why, yeah, I know, and I'm like, if that's why they left was over Viva Pinata, then bye, don't let the door hit your ass on the way out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, I...
[SPEAKER_03]: What I want to know was, did they leave this voluntarily, or is this one of those nice ways of saying they were asked to leave because the community was not too receptive to some of the recent games?
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't believe Viva Pinata is performing very well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it's reaching the target audience.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, critically, it's doing well, but that doesn't always translate to money.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_01]: There's actually an interview, but I have to look a little bit more further into that, but I think it's willing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you think they'll start a rival company?
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_01]: They should make one called Uncommon.
[SPEAKER_03]: WonderDogHerald says... Oh, I get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: WonderDogHerald says they're just taking the money and running.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Morpheus says thanks to Viva I can't play my 360 right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I think that's because I've seen his woman on there playing Viva Pinata non-stop because she's on my friends list.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could be looking at my Xbox friends list at 1 in the afternoon and look who's online playing Viva Pinata.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what would be hilarious is if you smack that woman enough times that she like locked up your system for like an hour or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I said that'd be funny if that happened, you know, in the game where you smack her.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I thought you meant Travis's woman.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, that's not nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Catamari
[SPEAKER_02]: Although what does suck ass is the fact that it's not coming to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently that was a rumor that was going around, but of course diffused by the worldwide Xbox Live Arcade games portfolio manager, Ross Erickson, who basically said that the rumor is total crap and is not happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: No Katamari.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm sure we'll see Katamari come to the 360 some point.
[SPEAKER_02]: You think?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Namco likes remaking stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at Rage Racer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know yet about what the future has in store for Katamari.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's going to be more Katamari games.
[SPEAKER_02]: They registered trademarks already for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless they're going to do some fucking Katamari cartoon, which would be even more cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: We also have some other interesting rumors going around.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because the Katamari thing started as a rumor.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, now they're saying that Radiant Silvergun 3, there was a report earlier this week, that Radiant Silvergun 3 was going to be on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, Knights is going to be coming to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Knights on the Wii would be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, the Radiant Silvergun 3 did get basically...
[SPEAKER_02]: We still have Ikaruga.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm still thinking about getting that Dreamcast one that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it New Hope or something like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: My Dreamcast is in a box, sadly.
[SPEAKER_01]: We used to have ours in an Xbox kiosk.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of those little demo stations, the old ones.
[SPEAKER_01]: We used to have our Dreamcast sitting in one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever happened to your demo station you had?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never seen it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: How much do those things sell for?
[SPEAKER_01]: I have no idea what we got for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: How much, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like $500, if not more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Were you looking at that on eBay or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I was for a customer.
[SPEAKER_02]: They wanted to bring it.
[SPEAKER_02]: you know those things are so hard to get like for even like Microsoft for example in order to get a kiosk into your store you have to be buying lots of Microsoft product and then you get the privilege of buying one from them for like a couple grand it's like thank you for giving me the privilege to buy one from you you fucking douche but I'm trying to push your product you know and you don't want to give me a kiosk or sell me a kiosk I don't understand it but whatever well
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I guess we don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's kind of one of those things where it's like it's happening, but we're not going to tell you anything else.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, they're saying that they might do a... There's a rumor, at least, that there's going to be a smaller one, either for PC or something on Xbox Live Arcade, but... I mean, like, PC is MMO home, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would be a little silly to not put it out on the PC, especially, you know, when the Xbox 360 is a PC, according to, you know, something I read just before we went live tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, according to what Bill Gates, the Xbox 360 is a PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Being that we put this show out on Sundays, some of the stuff has come out during the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Two of those were brand new Ubisoft games, whoop-de-doo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to say before you start getting this stuff out, we have to get a little disclaimer about sometimes you're right and sometimes you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, listen.
[SPEAKER_03]: New year, new show.
[SPEAKER_03]: So sometimes these dates are right and sometimes they're wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why are they wrong sometimes?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're wrong sometimes because they change dates daily.
[SPEAKER_02]: So stuff changes all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: and a company to announce a date initially and have that date stick.
[SPEAKER_02]: is like a rarity.
[SPEAKER_02]: This stuff shuffles around.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the only reason it shuffles around is development cycles, whether they're in behind or ahead in development or getting approval from like Sony, Microsoft, and Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: For instance, just to kind of give an example, this week, or actually I should say a long time ago, I want to say it was in like episode 195 or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a while ago, a long time ago, about six months ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: You said that Bioshock was coming out in April of 2007.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then this week we heard that there was a 2K Games rep that was posting on some forum that said, it's coming out in June, you heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's kind of like, you were in the right ballpark, but for whatever reason these developers... No, they changed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The same day... Well, actually, I think... Because I don't pay attention to some of these date changes or don't bother repeating them again.
[SPEAKER_02]: But before the guy came out and said, oh yeah, by the way, this is... We had a date change to...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: You knew about Oblivion on the PlayStation 3 six months before anybody ever announced it officially.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whenever these titles drop in, it's always right.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I've noticed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Oblivion on PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember that from last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Full Auto 2 on PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: So is there anything in this list that's new that we don't know about yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do have stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, first off, we mentioned it last week, Driver Parallel Lines for the PSP, which was actually March 14th was when that was coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now it's being changed to Driver 76.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if you remember, Driver Parallel Alliance started off in 1976 and then it comes in the modern time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm guessing this game is going to be Driver Parallel Alliance, but just set in 1976.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know that because the Driver series sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it does.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's just happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, though, I do have a date for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: This will make you happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Enchanted Arms for the PlayStation 3, March 14th as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: We knew that was coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely one that, you know, not a big surprise, but we don't have a date for that yet, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: New games, though, that haven't been announced.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dream Pinball 3D for the Wii, coming out October 10th, so still ways off.
[SPEAKER_02]: And not a huge surprise, but Fantastic Four Rise of the Silver Surfer is going to be coming out on PlayStation 2, 360, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Movie time, mandatory movie time.
[SPEAKER_02]: PS2, not 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: PS2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a lot of stuff being developed for PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 2, though, lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, uh, by the way, those two Ubisoft games, uh, Cosmic Family and Spelling Spree.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cosmic Family, I hear, is meant for really little kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I guess it's based off a cartoon series or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Spelling Spree, um, I'm guessing some sort of, like, DS type of game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It makes me think, like, imagine people driving by in their cars, rolling down the window, and, like, spelling at them to death.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, well...
[SPEAKER_01]: P-R-I-Z-E, die!
[SPEAKER_02]: But remember, we mentioned last week, and I haven't seen this anywhere yet, but Driver Parallel Alliance is on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was one of the ones that they didn't mention.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that I really care to play that on the Wii, but I'm just saying, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Letting it be known.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_02]: We think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, I can't check the whole internet, but as far as I'm aware, none of the
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 2, Arthur, The Shield, New Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_03]: Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have a couple big titles coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Atsumare Pinata is coming out January 11, 2007 on 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the name of Viva Pinata, localized for Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the PlayStation 3, you get NBA 07 over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: GT Pro Series coming out for the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: I recommend you pass on that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Coming out on January 11th for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a lot of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: You do get a couple things going into the best series from Koei, including Warship Gunner 2 and Shin Sangoku Musou 3 Empires and Mushoden.
[SPEAKER_03]: I should note, though, that .hack//G.U.
[SPEAKER_03]: Volume 3 is out next week, so I know a lot of folks are really into .hack//G.U.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's on its way out pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also coming out on the Nintendo DS, Zetai Onkan Training DS and DS Dengeki Bunko, Ira no Sora, UFO no Natsu is coming out this week, January 11th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course... That's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess UFO of Summer?
[SPEAKER_03]: DS Dengeki Bunko Ira no Sora UFO no Natsu Huh That's what it's called Okay But probably most people holding out for Oh, never mind, it's a US release, never mind
[SPEAKER_03]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are any of you really going to import it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't think so.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think I will.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I'm planning on getting it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What was that other game that's not coming out?
[SPEAKER_01]: That one that we played for DDR?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to import that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_03]: The
[SPEAKER_01]: They had the intro.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, oh, Oz.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's an old game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know it's old, but I think I'm going to get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we played the Oz song, the Plovastian dance and chorus.
[SPEAKER_03]: We played that today, and Jamie was like, I want that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Reading from that title, I think it's Ida of Sky something, summer, whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, we have our UK release dates, if anyone's interested, which I am.
[SPEAKER_01]: On the 12th is pretty much what's coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bionicle Heroes, Children of Mana, both on DS, Lost Planet, Extreme Condition on Xbox 360, Tokobot Plus, Mysteries of the Karakuri on PS2, and WarioWare Smooth Moves on Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I can't wait for WarioWare to come out next.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: New game!
[SPEAKER_02]: Finally.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: One new game, though, that we're probably not going to see, at least I hope to God we're not going to see this, is a new RPG based on Tingle, that really annoying gay fairy from Wind Waker.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, he hasn't come out yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just people assuming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, flaming gay fairy from Legend of Zelda Wind Waker.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not that there's anything wrong with that, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's just super homo flaming gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so apparently it's...
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh god, it's possibly going to head to the US in 2017.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say, there is no freaking way this game is not coming to the US at this point.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they're going out of their way to put it out in Europe, you know it's coming here.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know it's coming, because the English version will already exist.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got to come here.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about Mother 3?
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't that come out in the... I don't think it did come out over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It came out in Japan, of course, but... I thought there was one game that got translated for the UK, but never came out over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm telling you, it's not going to be Tingle RPG.
[SPEAKER_03]: It can't.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was Mother 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not with the freaking petition going on and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's people out there that want their Tingle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tingle.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know you're going to want this game, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nellie's going to make you buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: She will not make me buy this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will show it to her and then she'll make you buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to play the Tingle RPG.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, will you play the Tingle RPG?
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_01]: When I'm out of school.
[SPEAKER_03]: NM64 would like to point out, Loki, Tingle was in Majora's Mask.
[SPEAKER_03]: JeremyTodd1 says, fact, Rob tried to try out for the role of Tingle, but Nintendo rejected him.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aw, sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is, you know, it's true, though, that I do have this secret desire.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've always wanted to be a voice actor in a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that would be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be a lot of fun, don't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: A voice actor in a game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, wouldn't that be fun?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not Tingle, God no, but, you know, something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe we could be a soldier that gets shot in Halo 3 or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know what the hell you're doing there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Tingle!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, Loki!
[SPEAKER_02]: You should do it!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not gonna be Tingle.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want someone to create a petition right now on that site, whatever that petition site is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki for Tingle!
[SPEAKER_01]: Does Tingle have a hag in that game?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: Holy god!
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you!
[SPEAKER_02]: Insider Information says, Thank God it's not coming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Holy Shonen says, Tingle funny, but I want him dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think he'd sell well over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Too annoying.
[SPEAKER_02]: People will say, fuck this Tingle shit, we want more Zelda.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, something else that won't come out over here is new music games for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, Sony is denying that a frequency sequel and a new music game called Traxian for the PSP were not...
[SPEAKER_03]: Denied by them, but apparently Harmonix spoke to IGN recently, and the team behind Frequency said, this is what Sony did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sony denied Traxian and the Frequency sequel for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Traxian was killed months ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: Months ago that thing was gone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Harmonix proposed the sequel on the handheld, but Sony said no.
[SPEAKER_03]: On top of that, LucasArts was going to bring that game Traxian.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, it was LucasArts, not Harmonix, bringing Traxian.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was also axed.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know for a fact Sony likes to pass on games they should not be passing on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm shocked that they would... With all the furor that Red Octane is causing right now with Guitar Hero and everything, I...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm shocked that they would deny them to make a music game on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially when you have freaking Taiko no Tatsujin, which is a stupid game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't understand Sony's logic with the games they're not allowing through.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't make sense to me at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bad move, Sony.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, do this enough times to Harmonix, and Microsoft, who's going to probably be a little more welcoming, hey, you want to develop for us?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, great, we want games on the console.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what, that's where that game's going to end up.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: The rumor now is for Tekken 6 on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was the same person, quote, IGN Insider, who was also credited for letting the news out for Virtua Fighter 5.
[SPEAKER_01]: So if it's out, it's not like it hasn't been done before that's come out on a non-Sony system.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've had the Game Boy Advance one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember Tekken Advance?
[SPEAKER_02]: I try not to.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually own that game, and I thought it was okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then I've got the Bleemcast Tekken 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: So.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: What would you think, being a Tekken fangirl that you are, what would you think about this coming to the 360?
[SPEAKER_03]: is that good news, bad news?
[SPEAKER_03]: I do always kind of put Tekken with Sony.
[SPEAKER_03]: Think about Sony's version of Soul Calibur 2 had Heihachi as the bonus character.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tekken's always been a very Sony thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: The timing and everything of this seems a little fanboy to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think this is just the negative Sony ball keeps on rolling and people are saying this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think this is legit.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was also them saying, you remember Soul Calibur for the longest time was a Sony exclusive.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yet we had three releases of Soul Calibur 2 on various systems, each with their own bonus character.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not going to say yay or nay, but I don't think it's far-fetched.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's just there's not a lot, even though despite what Sony says, oh, we're meeting our numbers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they're lower numbers that they keep saying.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you want to get your Tekken fix on the PlayStation 3 right now, you can definitely if you're in Japan because Tekken 5 Dark Resurrection is out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you're in another region, fear not.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a workaround just like they have for the Xbox 360 for their demos.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can actually do this.
[SPEAKER_02]: First, what you need to do on your PlayStation 3 is create a new user account for your PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It cannot be an existing user or a sub-user.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has to be completely from scratch.
[SPEAKER_02]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: roughly at, I believe, $40 in Hong Kong twice.
[SPEAKER_02]: And once you've done that, I guess that it's just under the radar for confirming your address or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once you've done that, you're able to purchase the Tekken Dark Resurrection game from Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: You better hurry up and do it now because you know Sony's going to close the loophole on that within days.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you really want it... So do that now or just wait for it to come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's talk about the top purchased arcade titles according to Major Nelson's list.
[SPEAKER_03]: Starting off with the number 20 was Luminous Live, which I thought was kind of low on the list.
[SPEAKER_03]: 19, Cloning Clyde, 18, Small Arms, 17, Feeding Frenzy, 16, Bejeweled 2, 15, Texas Hold'em, 14, Zuma, 13, Contra, 12, Smash TV, 11, Bankshot Billiards 2, 10, Frogger, 9, Gauntlet, 8, Galaga, 7, Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3, 6, Doom,
[SPEAKER_03]: 5, Pac-Man, 4, Marble Blast Ultra, which seems a little high.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although it's a good game, don't get me wrong, just I didn't think it would be that popular.
[SPEAKER_03]: 3, Geometry Wars Evolved, 2, Street Fighter 2 Hyper Fighting, and 1 was Uno, which isn't very surprising.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a big duh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they gave it out for free.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus, it was one of those ones that had porn and stuff, so not a huge surprise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_03]: As far as the top Xbox 360 titles, 20, Splinter Cell Double Agent, 19, Battlefield 18, Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Vegas, 17, Need for Speed Most Wanted, 16, Dead Rising, 15, Madden NFL 07, 14, Texas Hold'em, 13, Dead or Alive 4, 12, Geometry Wars Evolved, 11, Saints Row,
[SPEAKER_03]: 10, EA Sports, Fight Night Round 3, 9, Uno, 8, Call of Duty 3, 7, Perfect Dark Zero, 6, Project Gotham Racing 3, 5, Oblivion, 4, Ghost Recon 3, 3, Call of Duty 2, 2, Hexic HD, because, you know, it was on all the hard drives, which is surprising because they left that off the arcade titles list.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought that was an arcade title, but never mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: And number one, Gears of War, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: No big surprise there.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: PhotoshopSupport.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, tutorials, tools, resources, there's a good link with lots of brushes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, lots of just good stuff on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's even, uh, free, uh, stock photos.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, there's, uh, flash resources, Dreamweaver resources, fonts, textures, you name it.
[SPEAKER_01]: This site is really, really freaking cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, um, I, I'm going to, to vote, uh, PhotoshopSupport.com as my, uh, website of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So surf there right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: One more time, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: PhotoshopSupport.com If you can't spell it, I ain't spelling it out for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, one thing that we're not spelling is lawsuit for L-A-W-S-U-I-T lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm dead!
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it spelled by?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, lawsuit between OverGuitarHero with, of course, guitars and
[SPEAKER_02]: RedOctane, Activision, and the Ant Commandos
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everyone's kind of going their own way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which makes sense since, well, you know, Red Octane, they've fucking made third-party guitars for a long time now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, come on, this is like, I don't know, what's... It sounds to me like they kissed a mate up somehow, one way or another.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone blew somebody, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyways...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so all that's better now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't really matter anyways, because if you wanted a wireless guitar, you can always buy the official one, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you see the Guitar Hero 2 360 box art?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I didn't get to pull that up at work.
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there's a story coming up on it later in Part B, at least specifically what's in the game, so I won't spoil that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the box art's very interesting because it's all white.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's so weird because you're used to thinking, you know, you see the Guitar Hero boxes, they're black, but of course, this is more the Xbox 360's color scheme, so it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: They just look different to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Will Wright is kind of performing that role.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, SimCity DS is not based on the old SimCity, but it looks like it runs on, I think it's either the 2000 or the 3000 engine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's SimCity 3, not 2000.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks a little too in-depth, or they might have enhanced it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: But either way, it's that more 3D ISO type of view than the old school SimCity was.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how much we're going to agree with this.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Eurogamer posted their top 50 games of 2006, and I've got the top 10.
[SPEAKER_01]: So if anyone would like to know, I'll read them off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess one more best of 06 list to close us out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number 10 is Professor Kalashima's Brain Training, How Old Is Your Brain?
[SPEAKER_01]: And number 9 is Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number 8 is Viva Pinata.
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess I need to actually play that, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: 7 is Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_01]: 6 is Lego Star Wars 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Those games are actually pretty fun, but I got really pissed off at the one that came out a year before.
[SPEAKER_01]: 5 is Dead Rising, because there's something really awesome about running over zombies with a lawnmower and cutting their heads off with a scythe.
[SPEAKER_01]: 4 is Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_01]: 3 is The Legend of Zelda Twilight Princess, which Dan and I are currently playing through.
[SPEAKER_01]: 2 is Elder Scrolls IV Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the number one game is... Your mom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cooking Mama.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, Guitar Hero won number one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, because that just came out in Europe this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, okay, okay, I can see that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And to quote one of the folks from Eurogamer, Keza, it says, if you don't like Guitar Hero, you have no soul.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to admit, though, I'm getting a little... I'm a little burned out on Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm a little burned out on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's not God's gift to video games like the media is portraying it to be.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really not.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love Guitar Hero, but I found out I can't play it drunk.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel like I've been playing music games for years, and not to sound elitist or anything, so I'm sorry if I sound that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I understand Guitar Hero made the music game genre more accessible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I do think it's a good game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's a great game, in fact.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't think it's like, you know, aww.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sound the chorus of angels.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fucking Guitar Freaks 2DX, basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel like I've kind of seen this before.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's so freaking great about it?
[SPEAKER_03]: But I guess it's just that it made it more accessible through the fact that as much as we have loved Konami's Bomani title, they've never really fully been Americanized, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: So whenever they try to Americanize them, it doesn't always work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I think they're letting the Japanese teams Americanize the games, and that doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of top 10s, I never posted mine to the site, so I'm going to read it for you now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Would you like to know my top 10 games of 2006?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, too bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to tell you anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did like Eurogamer's List, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know why I like Eurogamer's List?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because I like their reviews over there, because they will tell it like it is over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that was interesting to hear that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But now mine, and here's the ones that I thought were the 10 best games of 2006.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number 10, I said Sneak King on the 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know you might think I'm crazy, but get this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was an original title, the game was four bucks, and it was probably better than most of the games that Xbox released in arcade for five or more.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you think about it, it's one of the best gaming values of the year, and it absolutely deserves recognition.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it came off better than anyone thought it would.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, Sneak King, I know it seems weird to put it on a top ten list, but I felt it needed some type of recognition for kind of what it did.
[SPEAKER_03]: It did something really, really original.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number 9, I said Phantasy Star Universe
[SPEAKER_03]: and the reason why I said that is because you have massive replayability over previous versions of Phantasy Star Online in my mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have single player mode and that would be the type of game that usually you'd think would be sold by itself but on top of that you have the online mode, rationed unlocks that kind of keep the game going and makes the world ever expanding, keeps online mode fresh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number eight, I said Kingdom Hearts 2 which I think far too many people overlooked amongst the 2006 releases.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was an epic game in every sense of the word.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make improvements to the original, kept a fresh storyline, and even if you consider that some of the old worlds from the first game return, I mean, they kept it fresh.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it has a three-hour opening, but the fact that it's got, like, the year's probably one of the best soundtracks of the year, amazing visuals, and fucking Tron World.
[SPEAKER_03]: Enough said.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tron World.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the best games of the year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number seven, I said Trauma Center Second Opinion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo certainly knows how to milk its retro franchises for all they are worth.
[SPEAKER_03]: but New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: takes this old formula gives it a kick in the pants this is the game people wanted on the GameCube everybody wanted to see a game like this on the GameCube and for whatever reason Nintendo said now we'll put it on the DS and it's like people read our minds and they got it when you know we say that the next generation of gaming you don't have to make everything in 3D you can make visually appealing 2D games and New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: was it so definitely it was one of the best titles of the year
[SPEAKER_03]: Dead Rising Dead Rising
[SPEAKER_03]: Having a fresh story, and the battle system is phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it feels simple in the game's first hours, but as you play more, it gets so engaging, and it's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: 16.99 widescreen support in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: helps the game kind of keep up with the next gen of gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, I think it was maybe released a little too late for enough people to notice this title, but it's definitely worth your time if you enjoy role-playing games at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Elite Beat Agents Elite Beat Agents
[SPEAKER_03]: Elder Scrolls 4 Oblivion The Legend of Zelda Twilight Princess
[SPEAKER_03]: CookieMama!
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, I'll read them off and you can explain your picks if you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you should read off what I put on there because it was funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine, hold on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do we got?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have... Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki picked Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the number 10 best game of the year.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure somewhere in the video game top list guidelines it says we are required to put at least one Final Fantasy game in any top 10 list.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this year it's Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's sexy, new, and everyone wants to be it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be its friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is until Final Fantasy XIII comes out, all 50 different versions of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think these are in no particular order also.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just my top ten.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, too bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm assuming this is the order.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't realize Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: 3.5 could be so much fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess you can't beat the old 2D platformer days.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just hope we get some more like this on every system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number 6 was Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_03]: The killer app before Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: A very intense and albeit hard game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number 5 was Twilight Princess.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've waited so long for a new Zelda.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's everything we could have wanted.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number 4 was Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess that's why you said this is no order.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who in their right mind would put Excite Truck above Twilight Princess, you idiot?
[SPEAKER_03]: Me?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, read.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like Nintendo's BEA to the punch for a burnout off-road.
[SPEAKER_03]: A great launch game for the Wii that converted at least two non-gamers, my wife and extrovert, into full-fledged gamers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, that's a good point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number three, Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like Grand Theft Auto 3.5.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've spent countless lunches hurling grenades and rockets at cops while speeding away in my riced-out minifan.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll be playing this game until Saints Row 2 comes out, or Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: According to Loki, the number two best game of the year was Elder Scrolls IV Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to give props to a game that would let me rob a guild bear, punch a deer, and set fire to civilians in the course of one day and wearing nothing but a loincloth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well said.
[SPEAKER_03]: and the number one game according to Loki in 2006, and I totally disagree, Grand Theft Auto Vice City Stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: Despite its incredibly flawed targeting system and rather frustrating glitches, Grand Theft Auto Vice City Stories is the most fun you'll ever have on the PSP ad hoc multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can only hope that GTA 4 is up to this level of fun, just for the love of God, beta the multiplayer more than five minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think exactly for those reasons, the fact that it had some bad beta-ing, you should not have put that game anywhere near your top ten.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was in no particular order, that's why I put it there.
[SPEAKER_03]: so, whatever alright, there you go and then NM64 says Loki admitted his wife's a gamer JVmon says Rob, I would put Excite Truck before Zelda I don't know you guys it's a good game I think Excite Truck is horribly underrated and it probably would be in my top 15 but the worst part about Excite Truck is it was too short that's it that's the worst part about it alright, Jamie has a list she'd like to share my number 10 is actually DDR Supernova
[SPEAKER_01]: Just because it's bringing DDR back to the arcade, giving everybody what they want.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I think that's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's sort of helped rebuilding the whole community, and that makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_01]: And 9 is the Super Mario Bros., just because it's Super Mario Bros., and that game's actually kind of hard.
[SPEAKER_01]: 8 is Resistance Fall of Man, because it's pretty, and you explode heads and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: and I actually like Guitar Hero 2 so it's on there for my number 7 and number 6 is Trauma Center because that game is fucking frustrating and evil and has people screaming loudly at their DS's and then 5 is Wii Sports because it's actually kind of fun 4 would be Zelda 3 is Pirates of the Caribbean Pinball What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay
[SPEAKER_03]: You really thought outside the box for your picks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you are a pinball whore, I'll take it.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I'm married to a pinball whore.
[SPEAKER_03]: I understand, I understand.
[SPEAKER_01]: Two is going to be all the Flash games on the Doctor Who website.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, you loser.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your list just lost all credibility.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_01]: I like the game where he's the drawing and you have to walk him through the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Failed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Clank.
[SPEAKER_01]: And one is Cooking Mama.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't worry, Mama will fix it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're the only gamer girl I can think of that would put Cooking Mama at the top of her list with pride.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very well done.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's great!
[SPEAKER_01]: Cooking Mama is awesome!
[SPEAKER_03]: Next year, her number one game will be driving training.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?!
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, you're a woman.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is good radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: and on that note we should probably go to break while DarkSakura kicks my ass out in the parking lot so we'll be back after this with we'll be back after this with Orange Lounge Radio Part B Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio