[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_13]: And we are back here on Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 215 for this January 7th, 2007.
[SPEAKER_13]: And what's going on actually right now while we're doing tonight's program and taping here live on this Sunday night is that actually Microsoft is giving their keynote speech right now, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Over for CES because Consumer Electronics Show is going on?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, you've got to start us off with Part B, talking about what's going on at CES right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, there's a couple of big announcements.
[SPEAKER_12]: made about, you know, during CES and the keynote speech here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course, as we mentioned earlier, their big announcement, of course, was partnership, I guess, with Microsoft TV, which is an IPTV service.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you're going to be able to watch TV, I guess, streamed over the Internet, as well as record TV while playing games, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: and no clue yet when exactly that's going to go into effect, but it's something that they're going to launch this year.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's going to have digital video recording capabilities for gaming movie viewing and even voice and video chat.
[SPEAKER_12]: It says we're really going to need a big hard drive for that.
[SPEAKER_12]: It says live chat while watching television.
[SPEAKER_12]: So people can watch Lost or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, that's a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_12]: Playing over Xbox Live while recording TV live in the background.
[SPEAKER_12]: And this isn't a huge surprise, because I remember they were talking about something with DirecTV before.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: The other thing which is going on right now that they were talking about was...
[SPEAKER_12]: I believe Halo 2 for Vista
[SPEAKER_12]: But that is not the only game that you can play anywhere.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which just was announced a few seconds ago here.
[SPEAKER_12]: The one live anywhere game that's going to be able to be played on Vista, on 360, and everything else.
[SPEAKER_12]: But not only than Uno.
[SPEAKER_13]: Uno Anywhere.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my gosh, wow, interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really, you know, I always thought you could play Uno Anywhere anyways because it's cards, but...
[SPEAKER_12]: That's just me.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can play the electronic version anywhere you want.
[SPEAKER_13]: Draw4Bitch everywhere across multiple platforms.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I think it's interesting because it's not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_13]: It doesn't seem like anything that would be too difficult to do.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, cross-platform gaming is not unheard of.
[SPEAKER_13]: And even with 360, I mean, Final Fantasy XI, you play against PlayStation 2 and PC users on Final Fantasy XI, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Which is on the 360.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it's not like this is unheard of.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just kind of, I don't think anybody thought that they would do this.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it's not really anything anyone was expecting.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's really, truly a kind of pleasant surprise, if you will.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: For once and for all, they will be able to settle the debate.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is it easier to play with the keyboard and mouse or with the 360 controller?
[SPEAKER_13]: They'll be able to finally settle that debate.
[SPEAKER_12]: Great.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, the chat room seems to be agreeing over at chat.orangelonestradio.com.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can play Uno with anyone anytime you want.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just buy a deck of cards.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's very easy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have an Uno deck.
[SPEAKER_13]: But you can't get the Cameo cards and the Project Gotham Racing cards.
[SPEAKER_13]: So?
[SPEAKER_13]: But I believe you can get, in regular traditional card form, you can get Pokemon cards and the clear cards so you can play Uno in the pool.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you know, you can play World of Warcraft cards, too, once those come out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hooray, hooray.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I guess that's all we have coming out of CES right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: There is one other thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sony's saying that they've hit their target amount of units shipped for the PlayStation 3, which was 1 million by the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although, if memory serves me correctly, I believe that target was a lot higher, and then they lowered it down.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the other thing, too, is they've shipped 1 million units worldwide.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not sold, shipped.
[SPEAKER_12]: They'll sell it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know we're all seeing the big pictures of stacks and stacks of PS3s on block.
[SPEAKER_13]: They'll sell them.
[SPEAKER_12]: Their next target is 6 million by March this year, so.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now that's ambitious.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: One thing I wanted to ask about, too, and you showed me this during the break while we were alive.
[SPEAKER_13]: You have this Impossible Mission ad, and I want, it's Impossible Mission on the Wii, like the old school Commodore 64 game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, it's one of the games.
[SPEAKER_13]: I remember hearing Epyx was coming back and was going to redo games.
[SPEAKER_13]: What the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_13]: I want it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's being released in the UK right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: System 3 is putting it out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Basically, this is an ad sheet that they had on GoNintendo.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just an impossible mission.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's 2D.
[SPEAKER_12]: It just looks like a visually updated version of a possible mission.
[SPEAKER_13]: So they're only getting it in Britain and not here?
[SPEAKER_12]: So far.
[SPEAKER_12]: It might end up coming over here.
[SPEAKER_13]: The one game I want.
[SPEAKER_13]: They do this to us.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't say you folks over there don't get some love.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe you should import a Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not going to import... Well, I can.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're on the different TV standards over there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Component.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not going to import a Wii just to play Impossible Mission.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll just... I'll write nasty grams to whatever company... System 3.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll write nasty grams to them until they put this out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sure it'll come out over here at some point.
[SPEAKER_13]: It better.
[SPEAKER_13]: At least it's a budget title if nothing else.
[SPEAKER_12]: So... Well...
[SPEAKER_13]: E for everyone!
[SPEAKER_05]: I love games!
[SPEAKER_13]: They're so pretty!
[SPEAKER_13]: Can I have a hug?
[SPEAKER_12]: The Entertainment for All Expo... Jamie!
[SPEAKER_12]: Cuddle!
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Entertainment for All Expo, as it suggests, is open to the public if you have $100, because it's going to cost you $100 to get into it.
[SPEAKER_12]: So... Well, what?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's going to cost what?
[SPEAKER_12]: $100 to get into the Expo.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess that's not too bad.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, if E3 wanted to charge you $100 to get in... Actually, from what I remember, any schmo could really get into E3 for, what, that $400 fee or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: You really didn't even have to have ties to the industry to get in that way.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, you know, this is, I guess, cheaper than that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I imagine this expo will still be letting in, you know, media and all that type of stuff for a different rate.
[SPEAKER_13]: Probably not the same $100.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_13]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_12]: But yeah, it'll be interesting to see how it ends up going down.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it's going to be this year, 18th through the 20th of October.
[SPEAKER_13]: And good point, we got several people starting with Blackboy saying, except it isn't E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you know, I understand, but...
[SPEAKER_13]: It's kind of, for all we know, all we got otherwise.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they say they're trying to fill the void, so I realize it's going to be a little different because it's going to be targeted at the gamer as opposed to the industry, but it should be interesting nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I should be able to still go to the E3, the actual E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, that's true, because it's not going away.
[SPEAKER_13]: It would be interesting to see what happens.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't fucking take me to E3, bitches.
[SPEAKER_12]: I need this.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's my high.
[SPEAKER_13]: I need that E, man.
[SPEAKER_13]: I need to cuddle.
[SPEAKER_13]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, just a few months ago, we were talking about all that fear.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, you know, I know it's easy to want to, like, jump on Sony and be all like, ha-ha, Sony's not selling systems, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_13]: But you kind of have to think about, too, Christmas is over.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I think more people are willing to wait, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess then again, the Wii is still seemingly selling out, and the 360 at this time last year was still selling out too.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'd be very interested to see it on a graph, like how many systems Microsoft had out there at this time last year, and how many Sony has out there now.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it's just because I'm a visual person, I want to see everything on a graph.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I'd be very interested to see how it really compares.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because you could say that the 360 was still sold out, but from what I remember, they weren't coming out very often.
[SPEAKER_13]: Whereas Sony seems to be doing a pretty consistent weekly shipment.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, according to this was the big thing that they were pushing, they were saying that we outsold the 360 because we put out a million units before the end of the year and they only had 600,000.
[SPEAKER_12]: So... Yeah, but... Interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: But here's the thing, Microsoft was like, yeah, but bitches, we were out the year before you, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: We're ahead of you by a couple million.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, so Sony's saying they're on the track to outsell the 360 is what they're saying.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're still convinced that they're... Microsoft's saying, we lapped you, bitch.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're just like saying, oh, we're meeting our numbers.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, well, when you drop your numbers like six times and then you're like, oh yeah, we met our numbers fucking six months late.
[SPEAKER_12]: and we lowered them a bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: But we met them.
[SPEAKER_12]: God damn it, we met them.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, no, you didn't technically meet them because, well, you only ship less than 400,000 units at launch in the U.S., so, whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: DDR Dollar Bill says, this is Sony math.
[SPEAKER_13]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember, it's the math of those who eat crayons every day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we have a little bit of something flying around on the rumor mill.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um,
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: To where we were at that last Konami event that they had in, what, August?
[SPEAKER_13]: And I remember they were showing Coded Arms on the PSP, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: But they never showed us Coded Arms on PS3, but I remember some of the other journalists were asking about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: They were really dodgy at the questions at the time, huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: If I remember right.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like they didn't want to say much about it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, at E3, I think it was only a video.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, this other press event we went to was after that, so... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: But they still were not really saying much about it, huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess we'll find out in a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I guess it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to say I heard that the game was really buggy and crappy from the beta or whatever state it's in right now, alpha or whatever
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know, it's not coming out anytime soon either way.
[SPEAKER_13]: Mystic Gohan says, well, Coded Arms sucked, so I'm not getting my hopes up yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Legend of Zaku says, only thing that can save PlayStation 3 is Metal Gear Solid 4.
[SPEAKER_13]: Mike W. also agrees, Coded Arms sucked ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't really think you need to save the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: The only thing you need to save the PlayStation 3 is put more games out, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_12]: And put more games out that haven't been out for six months on the 360.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, that's what they need to do.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, why the fuck, seriously, like, games that are supposed to be launch titles, like
[SPEAKER_12]: Rainbow Six Vegas or something like that and they haven't even put it out yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the problem.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyways, so as we were probably talking about here, Metal Gear Solid and how Metal Gear Solid 4 is going to be coming out on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, Metal Gear Solid Portable Ops just came out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not a huge surprise that they're talking about getting a sequel done already.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, you know, since the game
[SPEAKER_12]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, I hope not.
[SPEAKER_13]: But maybe it'll come with cool 3D glasses.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was actually... I don't think your acid is like what happens when you program a game on acid.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_13]: The 3D thing I actually thought was kind of cute.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have to admit, that little, you know, the little paper glasses or whatever they're playing acid 2 on, it's actually kind of cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it was cute watching Dan play it.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what the best part about the 3D glasses?
[SPEAKER_12]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_12]: Were the videos of the hot Asian chicks wearing the camo bikinis that you would unlock from playing the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: In 3D.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, I thought you got laid on a regular basis.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do not even talk about Asian girls in bikinis and things because... Yeah, how's Dead or Alive Extreme going?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually referring to a video that one of our listeners, I don't know if he wants to tell me about it, he just laughed at it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got sent Aparapara videos with really ugly, way too skinny Japanese girls in bikinis.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ganguro Makeup.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you can't say those words together in a sentence without me freaking out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: We had some weirder stuff with the Asian girls on the Wednesday show.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not even going there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's move on to one other way that listeners can interact with us and give their feedback is our voicemail.
[SPEAKER_13]: Our 800 number, it's 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_13]: and we got some voicemails this week thanks to those of you guys that left the voicemails that number is toll free in the US and Canada but I want to point out it's not toll free outside of that which makes this first voicemail all the more special this actually came in on the Skype part of that because if you are in the UK or Australia, New Zealand wherever the heck you are in the world you can use the Skype to leave us a message for free you can just call Orange Lounge Radio when we're not live and leave us a voicemail that's what this first voicemail is from let's take a listen
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey guys, this is Sosha from the UK.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just wondering, you mentioned every Xtend Extra on the show a couple of times, so I looked it up, and it's not coming out in the UK until like the middle of February, and I was wondering if you were importing it off eBay, and also is DDR Supernova worth the wait, because it's coming out in like February as well, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, guys, keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love listening to the show, especially when I'm on the bus because bus rides are so boring.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I do get funny looks when I start laughing at all the weird stuff you come out with.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, guys, see ya.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for the voicemail.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_13]: As far as Every Extend Extra goes, check out... You can actually play for free on the internet.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can download Every Extend...
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: And the game's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's no Luminous.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't hold it up to that same high caliber.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it's a little more action than it is puzzle.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it's more of like a fast-paced puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's definitely a lot of action element involved.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: As far as DDR Supernova, it's kind of hard to tell because the game varies from region to region because of licenses.
[SPEAKER_13]: But here in America, I did think Supernova was probably...
[SPEAKER_13]: about on the same level with DDR Extreme 2, if not a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I'd say it's worth your time if you're a DDR fan, or if you've never played the series before, it certainly is a good enabler.
[SPEAKER_13]: And from what I remember, the UK, in my opinion anyway, typically gets better licenses anyway than we do, so I'm sure it's going to be even more worth your while.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd have to say the last Stepping Stage had a... Not Stepping... Yeah, is it... What is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not Stepping Stage, it's a...
[SPEAKER_08]: Dancing Stage, that's what I'm trying to think of, had actually a really, really good track list.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd hope that some of those would be incorporated into some of our releases, but unfortunately, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, yeah, it's always like a licensing issue, and you know, the music that sells over there isn't the same that sells over here all the time.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, some of the hits are the same, but for instance, you know, take an artist like...
[SPEAKER_13]: Robby Williams
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, this is Razorburn2021.
[SPEAKER_13]: You'll never see me in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_13]: You'll probably never see me around.
[SPEAKER_13]: I happen to be in
[SPEAKER_00]: Offline Listener.
[SPEAKER_00]: I listen via my PSP and Bleaching Connections.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just wanted to thank you for a very nice year of episodes.
[SPEAKER_00]: I listen to them at work and they really provide me with the news, albeit it's generally kind of a week late of stuff, but it's a way I'm able to keep up on what's going in the gaming world.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've kind of jumped back and forth between a lot of podcasts.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're one of the first ones I've picked up and I've stuck with you.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm
[SPEAKER_00]: Just really happy with your show and I want to wish you a happy new year and say thank you and please provide me more in the future.
[SPEAKER_13]: Aw, thanks for the warm fuzzies.
[SPEAKER_13]: We appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_13]: We like the little compliments to keep us going.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's very nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you know, all things considered, there's a purposeful reason why I played this one because he said that he listened to the show on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I think last week on the New Year's Eve special, I was a little bit harsh on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_13]: I do really like the PSP as a multimedia device.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is an incredible multimedia device.
[SPEAKER_13]: It plays videos, MP3s, and games and all the movie stuff on top of that.
[SPEAKER_13]: The problem is, as a gaming device solely, I don't think it's up to par with the DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's my own personal opinion.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think the library of games that the PSP is offering is quite up to par with the DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I think the fact that people do listen to the show on the PSP kind of speaks to why the PSP is a pretty good system.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because of the fact, hey, not only can you listen to these RSS feeds on the go over the internet, but you can play Luminous too.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, that's what's great about the PSP.
[SPEAKER_13]: and why if you don't own one you should think about it I mean they are they really are pretty decent systems they're just not if you're only looking for gaming and maybe you already have an iPod you already have a laptop to get your podcast on the go or whatever maybe you don't need it you know but if you don't have any of that stuff I think the PSP is a pretty good buy to get a lot of that crap on the go if you haven't bought one yet you might want to hold off anyways because you know what the rumor mills been saying is that they're going to redesign it anyway so
[SPEAKER_12]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_13]: Silly, I'm talking about portable devices, obviously.
[SPEAKER_13]: Laptop.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, but laptops are thousands of dollars for a good one.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they're not that, I mean, they're portable, but you've got to whip this thing out.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not that portable.
[SPEAKER_13]: PSP.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, but PSP goes in your, but sidekick.
[SPEAKER_13]: A PSP is better than a sidekick, I think, except for the fact you can't make calls with a PSP.
[SPEAKER_13]: I already have a phone.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think the PSP is a pretty cool little pocket system.
[SPEAKER_13]: How big are your pockets?
[SPEAKER_13]: Big.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can fit PSP in my pocket, no problem.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can fit PSP in my pocket.
[SPEAKER_08]: My DS fits in my purse.
[SPEAKER_08]: That little micro thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Your PSP could probably fit in your purse, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I can barely get... I have no idea what happened to my Sonic screwdriver.
[SPEAKER_08]: It fell out of my purse.
[SPEAKER_08]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't even that fit.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: And there was another comment in here somewhere I wanted to read.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I guess that was it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't find the other one, so there you have it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Chat.OrangeHouseRadio.com if you're listening live on this Sunday night and you want to join or entertain your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_13]: And of course the chat room is open all week long and it gets kind of dead when there's no live programming.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to agree with Ranma on this.
[SPEAKER_13]: What did Ranma say?
[SPEAKER_08]: A laptop may be thousands of dollars but it is more useful than a damn PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: But...
[SPEAKER_13]: If you're a 14-year-old kid, you may not have a need for a laptop.
[SPEAKER_08]: They make very small laptops, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those new Vios.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just think, yes, a laptop you get a lot of value of, but you have to ask yourself, do you really need all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, how easy is it to turn on your PSP, click, have the headphones in, and listen to the show, as opposed to, I better whip out the laptop, fire up iTunes, da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_13]: A laptop serves a very useful purpose.
[SPEAKER_13]: I heart my little Mac laptop, and it's one of the best purchases I made last year.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, you know, I still also like my PSP for those types of things.
[SPEAKER_13]: I need a bigger memory card, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can also interact with us by sending us emails to mailbag at orangelauncher.com, and we will get to the mailbag a little bit later in the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: But first, more news.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to start off with this story coming from Korea.
[SPEAKER_13]: Korea.
[SPEAKER_13]: Game censorship, a hot topic worldwide, not just Korea, but worldwide.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course, you know, in 2006, we had Rule of Rose causing the problems in Europe and Tack Johnson getting his head into everything over here, which we just go away.
[SPEAKER_13]: In South Korea, things are actually going kind of,
[SPEAKER_13]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_13]: But what just recently happened, the Game Reading Board of Korea actually said that they are going to lift the ban, and in 2007 these games will become available.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the head of the rating board, Kim Ki-man, said in the Korea Times, quote, the reasoning behind the decision was said to be to allow freedom of expression.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's pretty cool, I think, that, you know, I...
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: I would hope.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would really, really hope.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I'm all for expression and it looks like there's another way to express yourself.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's by turning your Wii into a vibrator.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your Wiimote into a vibrator.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, it can be done with the Res Trans Vibrator.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can have the Hello Kitty and I found a Doraemon vibrator on eBay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a program that's put out by KAKO.
[SPEAKER_13]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_13]: K-A-K-O.
[SPEAKER_08]: You download it to your PC, hook it up to your Bluetooth, and it vibrates on command, I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, I want to say, though, there was an easier way to do this.
[SPEAKER_12]: Someone was posting before there was some sort of flaw in the Opera browser.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess it was a URL that's too long or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: The tag will cause your browser to crash, and I think it causes the remote to vibrate as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that might be an easier way to do that.
[SPEAKER_13]: So something easier than using your Kako?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking at the guy's site, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a Wii Remote Test, Wii Saber, there's, um, okay, I can't read this, a Wii Braider Test, Wii Mice Test, um, Wii Fall Detect Test, a Wii Remote IR Sensor Test, um, Wii Pointer Test, uh, Wii Nunchaku, I guess Nunchaku Test, um, a bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is crazy.
[SPEAKER_13]: SithSpawn in our chatroom says, set Wiimotes to orgasm.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm linking this though in the chatroom so that they too can enjoy the Wii Braider.
[SPEAKER_12]: The joys of the Wii.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, a couple websites out there want you to enjoy the Wii as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Especially when it comes to porn.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, a few websites out there are making their porno...
[SPEAKER_12]: WeFriendly.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wait, this reminds me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Jamie, did I tell you about what we did on New Year's Eve?
[SPEAKER_13]: Orgy?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: We had about 12 people over here.
[SPEAKER_13]: You called me drunk.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, we had about 12 people over here.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we had this, you know, somebody that we know had said they'd never seen a porno before.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we decided to use the internet browsing capabilities of the Wii to surf to Pornotube.com and bring it up on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: And by the way, if you're under 18, don't do this.
[SPEAKER_13]: But yeah, we looked up, let me just say the first thing we clicked on, because we couldn't resist, said pterodactyl porn.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, it really is what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's something to behold, I'll give it that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Again, don't go to that website if you're under 18, kids.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry, Loki, I had to share that.
[SPEAKER_12]: You did use the Wii for pornographic purposes already.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh yeah, we've done that a few times.
[SPEAKER_12]: um anyways um so yeah it was a apparently a free one of the free adult sites out there and if you're curious on um wondering what site I'm not really gonna go give them free advertising but it's uh listed on arstechnica.com uh if you go to the free site apparently so you're giving free advertising by proxy yes you make no sense it's a free porn site out there one I have never heard of by the way um
[SPEAKER_12]: and doesn't look that good, by the way.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, so it's free and apparently it's Wii friendly.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, it's kind of neat that they're, you know, and usually, you know, it's kind of funny, porn studios are usually ahead of the game for the most part with technology.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know porn studios were the first ones to actually have, I think, DVDs and recordable VHS stuff as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: And now that they're, you know, kind of making content for the PSP and the Wii and
[SPEAKER_12]: God knows what other browsers out there.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, not a huge surprise.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's kind of cool, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just think of all the porn sites that are going to use that play on the Wii name.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just think of all the Fox News stories we're going to see about how the Wii is a gateway to porno for your children.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wah, evil.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sometimes I wish this next guy would just go away.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a story about Uwe Boll.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry, couldn't help myself.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because this is already a big franchise for them and they want to keep it going.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think they will be more involved in the whole process than the other companies before.
[SPEAKER_13]: We always want to make a good movie.
[SPEAKER_13]: In the past, the game companies never co-promoted the movie or even had a new game come out with a movie.
[SPEAKER_13]: Uwe, those guys could have promoted the movies all they wanted to.
[SPEAKER_13]: They could have had the money pouring out their butts, but if the movie sucked, that's not going to suddenly make the movie better.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's probably a reason they didn't promote the movie, because when they saw it, they probably said, why did we ever sign over the rights to this god-awful man?
[SPEAKER_12]: I could fart a better movie than he could direct.
[SPEAKER_12]: They included free copies of the PC version of Blood Rain, and it's still in that cell, Blood Rain, the DVD.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, actually, I guess the BloodRayne DVD sold okay, but that's because no one saw it in the theaters.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because everyone heard that one chick was naked.
[SPEAKER_12]: I bet you that's why they sold two million copies.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, you know, do like the rest of us and just see it on a website for free.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, you know, it's kind of funny that he mentions Far Cry and stuff, because I really hope they don't kill that franchise.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, they can go ahead and kill all these other ones that have been dead for a long time, but just stay away from any of the good franchises.
[SPEAKER_13]: Whenever Uwe Boll manages to make its way into our show script for what stories we're going to read, I feel a little dead inside.
[SPEAKER_13]: That makes me very angsty, so I think it's an appropriate time for us to bring on the FUs of the week, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: FU goes towards money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn having to pay for everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know, I am an advocate of working hard for the things that you want.
[SPEAKER_08]: But damn the fact that I have to shell out $415 tomorrow to pay for my first deposit for school and my books.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I have to do another $285 and another $285 and another $285 until I'm done.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which I'll be done at the end of March.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know, a $1400 gamble to make an extra $17,000 a year working less hours is awfully nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: But at the same time, that's a lot of money right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I got a few rents.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, fuck money.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blackboy says, boohoo, DarkSakura has to pay for school.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, I've been paying for school.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been in college now off and on over the past 10, 11 years or so.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I finally found something that... That's a lot of off and on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I found something that I really, really want to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think that it'll pay off.
[SPEAKER_08]: But for right now, you know, I'm entitled to sit back, look at this and say, how the hell am I going to steam this?
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I'm going to make it work.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be worth it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But at the same time... Now you just got called a career student.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am... You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: My theory is to never stop learning.
[SPEAKER_08]: Honestly, the moment that you stop learning and let yourself fall into stagnant ignorance is the day you should just shoot yourself in the head.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, it's a good thing we fill your head full of news every week on this program so you can consistently learn something new.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am proud to be a career student.
[SPEAKER_08]: No matter how long I work, no matter what I do, I'm still going to be learning something.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm a teacher, kind of, so did I get props?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Go to school.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: One lesson I hope that was learned today was...
[SPEAKER_12]: The kids out front of your apartment complex, fuck you them for being dumb enough to leave their remote-controlled car parked in an empty space.
[SPEAKER_12]: So when I pulled my car in there, I crushed the car and the kid cried.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's just like, my car, it's crushed!
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, you're a dumbass and you left it in the space.
[SPEAKER_12]: I feel no remorse for you.
[SPEAKER_12]: That'll teach you to put away your damn toys and stop playing in the goddamn streets.
[SPEAKER_13]: If I went to stripping school, would that count?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'd be learning a skill.
[SPEAKER_13]: A necessary job function.
[SPEAKER_08]: They could eventually make you, like, a dollar.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would probably make more money doing that than I do what I do now.
[SPEAKER_13]: I gotta lose my little pooch here.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you do exercise, if you do exercise, and you get free drinks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe I should look into it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just don't want to have to grow my hair out to look like Thunder Down Under.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to wax.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're talking about that over a bagel this morning.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why is this on our program?
[SPEAKER_13]: Um,
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to say an F you to these kettle chips that are Tuscan three cheese flavor because I've almost eaten the whole freaking bag sitting right here and that's not healthy.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love how I'm talking about exercising and working out and I'm like, and I just ate a whole bag of potato chips and I wonder why I'm fat.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're like really good chips though.
[SPEAKER_13]: An F you to having no self-control.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kill me now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, thanks.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're really good chips though.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're like the best chips in the world.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kill me now.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to die.
[SPEAKER_08]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: There is actually, they were actually saying that they were, that it was going to be written by Neil Gaiman, but he's actually said on his blog that he actually doesn't really have any involvement in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: From what I understand, I think he might be a consultant, but I don't think he's actually involved much in the actual thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: But hey, Silent Hill, happy.
[SPEAKER_13]: You probably like the movie more than anyone else I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've seen it four times in the theater.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm going to be buying the Blu-ray disc soon.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I can turn off all the lights and go... Worship Pyramid Head?
[SPEAKER_13]: Build a Shrine of Fire?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know why everyone thinks that I'm this big Red Pyramid fangirl.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because you are.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love the entire story, the entire feel of the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love the whole mythology behind it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But Pyramid Head, Red Pyramid, whatever, symbolizes all of that in one fancy little hot body.
[SPEAKER_08]: Red Pyramid is the guy in the second game's repressed sexuality.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because he goes around raping all the female monsters.
[SPEAKER_08]: OMG, spoilers!
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: The game's been out for, what, five years?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think people should know by now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Red Pyramid kills Dumbledore.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're done.
[SPEAKER_13]: Speaking of jokes that are years old, thank you for that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyways, so something that doesn't have to do with rape or Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nintendo was... All of them, forget it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't want to hear it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nintendo has partnered up with MMO producer Nexen, and really there's no news other than just that.
[SPEAKER_12]: They don't really know why they partner up, but it seems to be that the general consensus is they're working on new MapleStory, MapleStory DS, or possibly MapleStory Wii.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm always for more games, and especially if it's going to be an MMO, that would be pretty cool too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why am I not surprised that if Nintendo was going to partner up with any MMO maker, it would be the folks that made MapleStory?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: What do you think we might have in store for us on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_13]: I've never thought of an MMO on a Nintendo system.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it's never really happened before, with the exception of Phantasy Star Online on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_13]: But let's face it, Nintendo really didn't support that the way they should have.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that fluke aside, there's not really been MMOs on Nintendo systems that I can think of.
[SPEAKER_13]: So this is very interesting to me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was surprised that they weren't actually partnering up.
[SPEAKER_12]: What was that one wiki?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because that kind of looked very similar to Wind Waker, so that would be kind of funny if they took that over and made a game based on that.
[SPEAKER_12]: But MapleStory, based on the graphics of the game and stuff, I think that it would fit on Nintendo console pretty well.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would like to see it as a Wii game because I think you might need a little bit more
[SPEAKER_12]: Processor Power to actually put out the graphics and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Plus, I don't know how well a DS MMO would work.
[SPEAKER_12]: Especially if you've got to pay for it.
[SPEAKER_13]: You don't know unless you try.
[SPEAKER_13]: True.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, who knows what they could come out with.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would think a game like Ragnarok might actually work really well in the DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sad but true.
[SPEAKER_13]: Be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyhow, one thing we resolved to do in the year 2007 is that we're not showing PC gaming enough love on this program and some folks have brought that to our attention.
[SPEAKER_13]: PC Gaming Stories
[SPEAKER_13]: and this actually was recently announced by PC Gamer and PC Zone Magazines.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's a new Oblivion expansion on the way called The Shivering Isles and it only has been confirmed, well, through this, for the PC so far.
[SPEAKER_13]: We don't know if this is going to come out on 360 yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I think it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: I imagine it would.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, Oblivion does very well on the 360, but
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyhow, for now we know it's probably going to make its way to the PC.
[SPEAKER_13]: It will let players explore the Isles, which are divided into northern and southern areas titled Mania and Dementia.
[SPEAKER_13]: Boy, this sounds like a fun place to go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Then you'll be able to go to a door on this... The way you get there is you go through this door...
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Some of the new monsters in the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Gatekeeper.
[SPEAKER_13]: A collection of body parts that have been stitched together.
[SPEAKER_13]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the Knights of the Order, which are made up of three roots.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm surprised you're not playing more Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because you can set fire to anything in that game, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Play more Oblivion?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I mean, I know you haven't even played it really at all.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm surprised by that, because I would think you'd enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But maybe it's just me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I'm not going to have any time over the next three months, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye-bye life.
[SPEAKER_13]: As if your life hadn't been sucked away enough into Oblivion as it is if you've been playing this game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now they're just going to have this, which is even more hours gone away.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's amazing the types of things that people made for Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's an Oblivion wiki out there, a Google Map style thing for Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Excuse me, it's crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bless you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Live radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: We sneeze.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I have some news.
[SPEAKER_13]: PC related?
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, yep, Sony Online Entertainment is releasing, they actually have the open beta for Vanguard Saga of Heroes.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was available on the 5th, and they also have a pre-order campaign that's given to anyone who is given access to the open beta.
[SPEAKER_13]: Some of the websites have had a lot of coverage on this Vanguard game, and it looks like it could be pretty interesting if you're into those types of PC MMOs.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I might check it out if I have some time, if I can pull myself away from Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of pretty.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, one game I'm looking forward to, especially even on the PC, and I know they're making a 360 version, which is awesome, but Command & Conquer 3, Tiberian Wars, they're going to get a special edition called the Kane Edition.
[SPEAKER_12]: And for those who may not have played Command & Conquer...
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: and exclusive in-game content, which is kind of cool, as well as strategy guides, deleted scenes, and bloopers from the game's live-action sequences.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, of course, some of the exclusive content, you'll get exclusive multiplayer maps, three exclusive unit skins, and a limited edition poster.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, that'll be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Going back to something I said earlier, because I'm reading the comments in the chat room right now, ShadowsLiar says, Sky, how is that crazy?
[SPEAKER_13]: Many games have their own wiki, in reference to what I was saying, that Oblivion has all that crazy stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, there are a lot of fan communities, with wiki being open source and everything, many fan communities throw up their own wiki.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I guess I felt like the Oblivion one just felt so vast.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, because there's so much in that freaking game.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's not a lot of games I can recall playing that...
[SPEAKER_13]: The PC version can get them all run around topless.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, you did the mods and everything on the PC one, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: I really should be playing Oblivion on the PC, not the 360, but I'm such an achievement points whore, I can't help myself.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, I really do want to get the Oblivion now for the PC.
[SPEAKER_12]: You should.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think you should put it on my laptop.
[SPEAKER_12]: Might be.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can put the mods in.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what I'm all about, is mods.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, so PC gamers, don't say we don't love you.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, you know, another thing maybe we need to resolve to do is give a little love to
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_13]: But unfortunately, the only mobile story we got for you this week is a little bit of a downer.
[SPEAKER_13]: Microsoft is being sued by a French company, Infusio, for the wrongful termination of a $2 million contract.
[SPEAKER_13]: Infusio is claiming that Microsoft was refusing to approve their game designs, wrongfully withholding the second of four $500,000 US dollar payments.
[SPEAKER_13]: And this is all in regards to the Halo mobile game that I suppose is in development, so...
[SPEAKER_13]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: The first email comes from Tim Surugi.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, LLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, loving the show and hoping it never ends.
[SPEAKER_08]: Never.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's always nice to hear y'all's charming personalities shine every week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm terribly sorry for bothering y'all, but Sky's suggestion got me thinking about gambling games for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: If Nintendo ever decides to get on the ball and make some Wii DS connectivity set up,
[SPEAKER_08]: You could very easily expand the playability of Wii gambling titles, such as playing poker or blackjack.
[SPEAKER_08]: Combine this with online capabilities, and I believe there could be a fulfilling Wii title.
[SPEAKER_08]: Heck, Wii clubhouse games, why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: The point is Nintendo's stubborn lack of celerity in grasping the online world is mind-bogglingly nonsensical.
[SPEAKER_08]: Given Xbox 360's success through live, Nintendo could really take a hint.
[SPEAKER_08]: On a side note, a four-star sequel utilizing Wii DS connectivity would
[SPEAKER_08]: JustPlainRock.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for being so awesome and putting up with my annoying emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: You think Nintendo could reach out to the older community with games like Wii R Old?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd like to get some mad shuffleboard action going on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wii Old!
[SPEAKER_13]: To give credit where credit is due, wasn't that your idea, Loki, for the gambling games on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't remember saying that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe I did.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I never said anything about gambling games.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, well, I guess I did.
[SPEAKER_12]: They have, was it World Series of Poker Tournament of Champions?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I think they're talking, we're talking like real money being gambled.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, you know, I think that would be a gray area that Nintendo, you know... Technically, gambling is illegal in Japan.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, that and that, think about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Usually those online gambling sites, you kind of associate that with shadiness.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, like, you know, there's so many of them out there and you always kind of see the pop-up ads and you go...
[SPEAKER_13]: That's a little shady to me.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know if I want to get in.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not to knock it if that's what you're into, but I'm sure you've done the research if you're going to spend money on it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But you have to admit, there's a lot of crap out there that seems really shady.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I wouldn't think Nintendo would want to damage their reputation with that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, along the lines of what you say, like clubhouse games and those types of very casual games, I think Xbox Live hit a goldmine with Uno, and I think Nintendo, if they were smart, would be quick to get out a version of clubhouse games on the Wii or something like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: That kind of latches on to that where people could really do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But at the same time, I don't know if Wii is set up for that same type of online greatness, at least in what we know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, there might be unannounced things we don't know of yet, like there was on DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: We didn't know that we'd be able to talk on the DS in certain games.
[SPEAKER_13]: But Microsoft really has this rock-solid thing set up with Live, and Nintendo is being a little slow about competing with that.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the longer they take, the further ahead
[SPEAKER_13]: The next email says,
[SPEAKER_08]: Just thought I'd add to the anecdotal evidence that the PS3 is not selling as well as Sony and the mainstream media would like you to believe.
[SPEAKER_08]: In my continuing search for the Wii, I stopped into the usual big box stores, as well as GameStop, EB Games, locations in my area fairly regularly.
[SPEAKER_08]: This Saturday morning, I got up early and made my rounds once again.
[SPEAKER_08]: At every stop on my journey, EB Games, Target, Walmart, Circuit City, Best Buy, there were PS3s to be had, but not a single Wii in sight.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Best Buy still has PS3s in stock from last week's flyer announcement.
[SPEAKER_08]: I find this quite interesting and have to believe that the way too high price point, lack of killer apps, and mounting bad press is really affecting the PS3 sales, while, at least at this moment, the Wii has all the momentum necessary to sell every single unit put on the shelf, with people clamoring for more.
[SPEAKER_08]: Two other small tidbits to note from the Saturday trip.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was not the only person scavenging the stores for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: At several of my stops, I saw the same early 40s lady and her mother also hoping to score an early morning Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pardon the pun.
[SPEAKER_08]: The other tidbit is that while I was wandering aimlessly through the Target, a woman came in, purchased an Xbox 360 system while bypassing the two 60 gigabyte PS3s on display.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, Sony.
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep up the good work on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your show is one of the two or three I look forward to every week as it makes my daily grind that much easier to bear.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks and take care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boston OLR fan.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Again, we kind of got into it a little bit earlier on the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think now that Christmas is over, I don't think the demand for the PlayStation 3 is so much there, and I think the media fear has a lot to do with that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, the Nintendo is still going.
[SPEAKER_13]: But again, I'd be very interested to see.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think we know that Nintendo has more systems out there at this time than Nintendo or Xbox did this far out.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, than Sony or Microsoft did this far out after launch.
[SPEAKER_13]: But
[SPEAKER_13]: I just think it would be interesting still to see the comparison there.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I do think it is pretty obvious that Nintendo's kicking some serious booty right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it's price.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's all about the price.
[SPEAKER_08]: This one's a quickie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just a random wee question.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do they call the nunchuck attachment in England?
[SPEAKER_08]: I believe it's still called the nunchuck.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which I still think is a... Who is that from?
[SPEAKER_13]: Same person?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, different person.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't signed.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't read out email addresses or names through email, so if it's not signed, I won't say your name.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello, OLR, I've been an avid listener of your show ever since I heard my friends talk about it around episode 175.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Once again, it's me, Neki.
[SPEAKER_08]: The New Year show was great, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Has anyone heard the news about the PSP Lite?
[SPEAKER_08]: I was also included a link from NewstechSpy.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: The rest of the URL is articles06, sonypsi.html.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Wii is very hard to find over here at the moment and is a right pain.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't find any store with any in stock yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: for 180.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to say, though, I was very tempted to get an Xbox 360 after playing Saints Row yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe I should get a 360 now and get a Wii later when there's better games out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm enjoying my DS at the moment and hoping to keep doing so.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you haven't already, check out Metroid Prime Hunters on DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Talk to you later, Neki.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for the email.
[SPEAKER_13]: There was something in there I was going to say, and now I forgot because I got sidetracked.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just buying a 360 now and get a Wii later?
[SPEAKER_13]: 3.60s are really good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Again, it all comes down to, and if you've been listening to the show for any length of time, we always say this, the golden rule of gaming is a system is only as good as the games that are on it.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's the golden rule of gaming.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it's really about what types of games do you want to be playing right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you want to play Zelda, you want to play Trauma Center, you want to play WarioWare, you've got to go for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you want to be playing, I mean, you said you played Saints Row, and if that was fun to you, and you want to play other types of sandbox games like that that are on their way to 3.60s, such as Grand Theft Auto later this year, you've got to go for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: and some of the other Gears of War whatever else 360 has to offer Oblivion, Pinata, whatever maybe that's the system for you and if you're an online gamer
[SPEAKER_13]: 360 is where it's at.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you have a soft spot in your heart for the retro classics, Wii is where it's at for the Nintendo stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it's really about what you want.
[SPEAKER_13]: But be careful.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know how sometimes money burns a hole in your pocket and it makes you make rash decisions, and I've done this many, many times, especially with game purchases.
[SPEAKER_13]: But you'll thank yourself if you take five minutes to really think about what you buy before you buy it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Saka's last email Hi guys, hope your new years was good and either peaceful or eventful in a good way that's a nice way to phrase it um
[SPEAKER_08]: I had a long thought to state, but considering my throat is coughing up furballs and other dryness, I figured just to get into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Playing OEB Agents, I've managed to get to the third difficulty level and noticed something.
[SPEAKER_08]: The final songs in particular, Without a Fight and the Jumpin' Jack Flash cover, I noticed how it just matched the mood of the scenario, even getting goosebumps when the songs were being played.
[SPEAKER_08]: It got me to think about some of the boss slash climactic battles in video games over the years.
[SPEAKER_08]: How listening to the music just adds to the battle to make it more memorable.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I was wondering what were some of your favorite songs used in boss battles?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's all for now as my throat is causing me to my head to be cloudy right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: See you guys at the chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's a DDR dollar bill.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've actually become one of my good Doctor Who fandom buddies.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, uh...
[SPEAKER_13]: And what you say there, again, is another great... I actually agree.
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought those songs fit the mood so well in Lead Beat Agents.
[SPEAKER_13]: And yet another reason why I think it is a travesty that that game is not ending up on more best of 06 lists.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it was seriously one of the absolute best games.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry, it's better than Guitar Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is.
[SPEAKER_13]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess that's my opinion, take it or leave it, but I think the game is being horribly underlooked, and I think people are passing off the song list without really sitting down and trying it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I'll tell you what, if you got turned off by the fact that it has Ashley Simpson, La La, or Avril Lavigne, Sk8er Boi, trust me, the music fits better than you're giving it credit for.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, give it a try.
[SPEAKER_13]: Give it a try.
[SPEAKER_13]: And yeah, those songs really fit the mood.
[SPEAKER_08]: One Winged Angel.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I was going to say, hello, Final Fantasy VII, One Winged Angel.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, who doesn't remember, you know, the Sephiroth?
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, we still use that music on this program today.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the Advent Children version.
[SPEAKER_13]: That is like the epic boss battle music.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, yeah, this is the Advent Children one in particular, but, you know, who?
[SPEAKER_13]: What a badass music.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember, though, because how long that took, because I did the Knights of the Round Quadra magic combo, just casting it, going and making a sandwich, and hearing one Wing Angel in the background.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was really cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: If I want to go way old school, think about some of the 8-bit games that had some great final boss music.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I don't know, one that sticks out in my mind for whatever awkward reason, I think just one of the first songs I remember, was Remember Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_13]: 2, when you finally made it to Wart, and you fought him, and it had some pretty cool final boss battle music.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: It sticks out in my mind for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: I also do have to say...
[SPEAKER_08]: I really... Oh, and it's how ironic Junami actually just mentioned both of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to say all of the Wily stage musics in the various Mega Man, Rock Man games.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was noticing that.
[SPEAKER_13]: DMN said that too, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I fully, fully agree with... Especially two... The first one actually was even decent, but the Mega Man games just had awesome music, you know, at any rate.
[SPEAKER_08]: I also...
[SPEAKER_08]: The Genova Battle in Final Fantasy 7
[SPEAKER_13]: ShadowCharlie says Final Battle Music for Sonic 3 GS68 says Destination Blackout from MT2 Ranma says Bowser Theme from Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_13]: 3 GS68 says the Final Battle Music from Final Fantasy 4 Lots of different suggestions there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do have to agree with the Chrono Trigger ones, just the Lavos battle.
[SPEAKER_08]: I especially love just going after you've beaten the game a few times on New Game+.
[SPEAKER_08]: Going back and just doing it right away, and then you get the Maker's ending.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or even better, The Legend of Max.
[SPEAKER_08]: No!
[SPEAKER_12]: For DDR?
[SPEAKER_12]: Kinda.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kinda.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, Guitar Room Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: The last level music in Guitar Room Man was pretty hardcore.
[SPEAKER_13]: To me, those songs don't invoke that same emotional response that I think was alluded to in the email, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Any more emails?
[SPEAKER_13]: One more?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, we do have one more email.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this one comes from Holy Shonen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dear OLR, I'm a huge fan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have enjoyed your show greatly for the past year and a half.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just recently started being in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't call me a noob.
[SPEAKER_08]: We call people noobs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Noob!
[SPEAKER_08]: With the biggest of affection.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I know, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: We say noob less than three.
[SPEAKER_08]: Less than three, that's a heart on its side.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, I was wondering if you could help me with a problem I'm having.
[SPEAKER_08]: My desktop just died and I need a new one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since my desktop would be for gaming, music, movies, etc., I was thinking of getting a PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, since I love my MacBook so much, I thought I could get a good Mac with two operating systems so that my PC-only games actually run on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not sure I need advice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Always weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: Holy shonen.
[SPEAKER_08]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, I love you, but I cannot support your hatred of Mac computers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Smiley.
[SPEAKER_13]: Smiley, Loki, smiley.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is something that I was going to do, except it was a little cost prohibitive for me at this junction in my life.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, given that I have a massive library of PC-only stuff, and we've got the parts sitting in my garage to actually build me a new computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to get the 24-inch widescreen iMac and dual-formatted PC and...
[SPEAKER_08]: and Mac.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can run virtual PC as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't know how well it works on the new builds and what is my laptop doing?
[SPEAKER_13]: For me, it's a little early for that whole dual format thing for me.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's still kind of a new technology in my mind and I think
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not ready for that, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the same as having Linux and Windows on the same box.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the same.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I wouldn't do that to my machine.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the same as having two different versions of Windows.
[SPEAKER_13]: Look, let me just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_13]: Me, personally, I have a... I don't even know the name of my frickin' little... What is that, an iBook?
[SPEAKER_13]: The laptop?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you have an iBook.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have an iBook.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have an iBook, and I just call it my Apple laptop.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have an iBook, and I have a PC desktop, and I love it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love that setup.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have the best of both worlds.
[SPEAKER_13]: I recommend folks do the same.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's great.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a great combo.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only real reason that I was really wanting the Mac stuff myself is being a graphic artist.
[SPEAKER_08]: But honestly, I've done great quality work on my PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: At this point in my life, it's really a matter of your preference.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think if you are doing graphics professionally, video editing professionally, Mac is the way to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if you're doing it for yourself or casually like me, then I don't see
[SPEAKER_08]: as much of a point in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they're great systems.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it just depends on what you want to do with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I like how much space they save.
[SPEAKER_13]: I got a private message from someone that said, you know, it's just doable booting.
[SPEAKER_13]: What's what's the big reservation?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just I still, you know, maybe I'm being stupid with it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you're right that, you know, folks do Linux and Windows and that stuff all the time.
[SPEAKER_13]: So what's the big deal?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just I don't.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: One thing I do use my Macintosh for a lot is I author DVDs.
[SPEAKER_13]: My really good friend John takes a lot of pictures and I make DVDs out of them.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Mac is awesome for that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love it compared to anything I've tried on the PC.
[SPEAKER_13]: Little things like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: But see, I get all that out of my laptop.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I don't have the need for this whole dual boot thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: And to me, it's kind of a waste of resources.
[SPEAKER_13]: For me, personally.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not criticizing anyone else who wants to do it, but I'm just saying for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jaded in here runs for operating systems.
[SPEAKER_08]: And actually, what I was thinking about...
[SPEAKER_08]: about doing myself, because I actually want to learn Linux a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_08]: When we rebuild my new computer, I'm actually going to have two... My plan is to have two 20 gig hard drives in it as my boot drives.
[SPEAKER_08]: One with Linux, one with... My new system is going to be... I can run Vista on it, so I'm taking out my 250 right now, putting it in a USB case, which ironically, the one I'm looking at is called Metal Gear.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: and having that be portable between my laptop and my PC so that anything that I want, anything I need to do, there it is and 20GB will easily store the programs I want to run.
[SPEAKER_13]: Any more emails?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, but this proves that we're big dorks.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, if you have more emails you want to send, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com is the place to send them.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we also offer and welcome interaction through our Skype line, which will be open very soon after another little chunk of stories here.
[SPEAKER_13]: So you might want to get your Skype fired up.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's username orangeloungeradio or 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll let you know when those are open.
[SPEAKER_13]: But we have a couple quick final stories here for you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course, big one.
[SPEAKER_12]: GameStop purchased Rhino Video Games
[SPEAKER_12]: So, lots of good stuff there.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it is official, the Blockbuster-owned company, Rhino Video Games, has been bought by GameStop.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, you know, this isn't really huge news, I think.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, for you it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, for me it's not, because we've kind of known that something like this is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really?
[SPEAKER_12]: Blockbuster's been entertaining offers for a while now for Rhino Video Games.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know because we sell to them, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: It's kind of a disappointment to see them being bought up because I hear they're a very good store chain, but
[SPEAKER_13]: Where do they exist mostly?
[SPEAKER_13]: We don't have them here in California.
[SPEAKER_12]: The southeast, no, the southern east, over, you know, north, south Carolina, Georgia, Alabama.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know, I know right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, that's pretty much where, you know, they were located.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, yeah, they had about, I want to say they had like 72 locations, if I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_13]: See, here in California, we've always had...
[SPEAKER_13]: GameStop, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because previously we always had Software Etc.
[SPEAKER_13]: and Funkoland.
[SPEAKER_13]: Babbage's.
[SPEAKER_13]: They all got absolved.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't remember Babbage's here in California.
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep in mind, GameStop is also owned by Barnes & Noble Inc.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they're a fully owned subsidiary.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Babbage's, since Babbage's was Barnes & Noble's arm for games and tech.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Barnes & Noble's craze, from my recollection, did not really start here in this state until about 10 years ago.
[SPEAKER_13]: and that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Those stores did not start going up until about 10 years ago.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was always Walden Books, which is Borders, essentially.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, apparently the whole thing's supposed to go down on the 14th.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's when I guess it's going to become official and they're going to start... I don't know if they're going to either convert these stores over to GameStops, which I hear that might be what's going to happen, or if it's going to be like this whole GameStop EB thing where
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think so, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been in a movie gallery.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_08]: My dad used to flirt with the lady behind the counter.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just go to Video Clearance Center.
[SPEAKER_12]: They have tons of porn there.
[SPEAKER_12]: In fact, they carry more porn than, I think, actual videos now.
[SPEAKER_08]: They actually said, I went into one and they said they had a green door that you could go behind to buy the porn.
[SPEAKER_08]: They actually had to paint their door.
[SPEAKER_08]: Paint it green?
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody raised a stink and they had to paint over the green door.
[SPEAKER_12]: With what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's purple now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, so now it's the purple door.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Going behind the green door to buy, never mind.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, anyway, forget it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Look, let's... This is so horrible that we have to follow up that topic with this, but hey, look, it's just the way it was scripted, folks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's talk about charity.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll go to the opposite end of the spectrum from buying porn to donating to charity.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course, one charity a lot of gamers know about is Penny Arcade's Child Play charity.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they raised over $1 million this year.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was posted on the Child's Play website this week that, quote, You guys did it.
[SPEAKER_13]: You broke a million dollars in just over two months.
[SPEAKER_13]: Child's Play started as a way to show how good our community can be, but it's turned into something greater than we could have ever imagined.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're making an impact on lives.
[SPEAKER_13]: See you next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're at $1,024,400.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's a damn shame the media won't ever cover that in the same capacity that they cover, I should say, you know, because I'm sure they get a nice, you know, story here and there, but in the same way that, you know, Game Boy Electrocute, Small Child, you know, kids go and shoot up their schools because of video games.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's never going to get that same.
[SPEAKER_12]: Documentary and...
[SPEAKER_12]: Not really a document, but that documentary on video game violence called Moral Combat.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think you'd find better quality behind the beaded doors in a movie gallery.
[SPEAKER_12]: Behind the purple door.
[SPEAKER_08]: At any rate, speaking of quality, and I vote this for quality, Guitar Hero 2 360 is going to have additional content.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're not really saying much about it,
[SPEAKER_08]: Rumor has it that it might be new modes, downloadable content, probably for new songs coming out, sort of like how Karaoke Revolution goes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Putting out the original Guitar Hero songs with extra bass or, you know, rhythm guitar.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that'd be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it does say, though, right on the box, that there are additional songs and downloadable content.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sweet, I knew there was a reason I was holding out for this game on the 360 and this is exactly why.
[SPEAKER_13]: And yes, I do realize I was saying things that may seem a little anti-Guitar Hero earlier in the show, but I'm really not.
[SPEAKER_13]: I really do like Guitar Hero a lot, I just don't think it's God's gift to gaming.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think there were better games that came out in 06 and so on, but
[SPEAKER_13]: I've been holding out to buy this.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've played it on PS2, and sure, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I've been holding out for 360, and I knew this was why.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm also going to link in the chat room, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is a picture of this up on a Team Xbox site that has what the box art is.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm posting that right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: The box art was very interesting looking to me, I have to say.
[SPEAKER_13]: But very cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know I'm going to get it anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know you will.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's Nim.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, Nim.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, Nim.
[SPEAKER_13]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_13]: Not much, really.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't expect to get through.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, you did.
[SPEAKER_13]: You don't have anything you want to share with us tonight?
[SPEAKER_13]: Why'd you call?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was making a TV show.
[SPEAKER_11]: You were making what?
[SPEAKER_13]: The computer.
[SPEAKER_13]: You were making what?
[SPEAKER_13]: A new game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, you're the one that messaged Loki earlier and said you're making this game called Kibi.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: What is this all about?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, um, it's going to run off of a modified version of Step Mania.
[SPEAKER_02]: A couple of the real army is going to help us with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um,
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's pretty much all we're doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're looking for artists and such.
[SPEAKER_13]: Have you made a post in our forums about it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: Right now it's pretty much underground.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, now you just outed it to all the folks that listen to the program, so go post on the forums.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sure you can get some help.
[SPEAKER_13]: And good luck to you on the project.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: So what is it?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's supposed to be a Beatmania-ish game, but with DDR's interface, or...?
[SPEAKER_13]: Turn down your radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hold on a second.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, that's what I thought.
[SPEAKER_13]: See, I can hear myself in the background.
[SPEAKER_13]: Turn down the radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: When you call radio programs, turn down the radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We should have you sing death metal for us, Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's because I love GWAR.
[SPEAKER_13]: Damn headphones.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, no, that's right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, so, anyway, what was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_13]: So this is what, DDR, it's based on a DDR interface, but it's Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, like, have you seen the videos of...
[SPEAKER_02]: Step Mania.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, and I always thought Step... Like, 99% of people who play Step Mania are just doing Finger Finger Revolution.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very few people are actually hooking up dance pads to the computer.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I think it's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_13]: At least make something that's actually not pretending to be actual dancing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's the point.
[SPEAKER_13]: Great!
[SPEAKER_13]: Then I fully support this project.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll draw you a picture.
[SPEAKER_13]: Good luck to you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll do announcer packs if you need it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, thanks guys Alright, no problem, good luck with your project and keep us informed on the forums or whatever, alright?
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, oh, I guess he hung up If you want to call us, 1-877-GAME-OLR or username is Orange Lounge Radio on Skype, let's go to the phones Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: This is Paradox Vincent Hi Paradox Vincent, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I was picking my friend up a game at GameStop recently, and they had Game Informer at display, so I picked it up and I flipped through the reviews, and I saw they gave Wii Sports a 6.5 out of 5.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wait, they gave Wii Sports 6.5 out of 5?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is that a typo or something?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: How do you give a game a 6.5 out of 5?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do I think they gave it one?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they gave it one because it's not like Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not this hyper-polished first-person shooter that takes years upon years to make.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a simple little sports game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You meant to say 6.5 out of 10, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, but the thing is that every single person that I've showed this game to, they've absolutely loved it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I had a... She was an older woman...
[SPEAKER_04]: A middle-aged woman comes up to my mom and says, Hey, have you checked out Wii Bowling?
[SPEAKER_04]: And for someone of that age to come up to another woman of similar age and discuss a video game with them, I think Nintendo's done exactly what they wanted to do in the first place.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, it's like you're living in Bizarro World for a minute when your parents are the ones talking about Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let me quote the review real quick.
[SPEAKER_12]: Their basic breakdown of this.
[SPEAKER_12]: It says the concept is an uneven intro into the system and its controllers, but at least it's free.
[SPEAKER_12]: Graphics, they say the game uses Mii avatars on your Wii, but that's about the only eye-catching thing about it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sound, the tiny sound that comes from the Wii remote really starting to bug me.
[SPEAKER_12]: It says playability, sometimes there are inconsistencies between your movement and what happens on screen.
[SPEAKER_12]: Entertainment, this is a shallow game by design, but it does offer some occasional fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: Replay, moderately low.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_13]: You remember back in the day if you ever let a non-gamer, or even some regular gamers, would play an old 8-bit game, they'd move their body with the controller, and when they jump, you'll pull back and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_13]: Nintendo made that a part of the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: and when they said they were going new generation, they meant it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's why I think a lot of people that have been in this line of thinking for a while are going to be in for a rude awakening pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nintendo is not making games necessarily for the hardcore gamer.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, you know what, I urge you guys out there who read a lot of these reviews, and it's not just this particular one, but think about all these stories we've had lately.
[SPEAKER_13]: We had EGM bash Elebits when it didn't really, you know, a lot of folks feel it didn't need it.
[SPEAKER_13]: We had GameSpot, heaven forbid, didn't give Zelda a 9 or a 10 and they received the wrath of Nintendo fanboys everywhere.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it is very interesting that the common theme here is all Nintendo Wii games.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the other thing, too, is people need to understand these are critics.
[SPEAKER_12]: They don't necessarily... Exactly.
[SPEAKER_12]: And here's a website I recommend checking out, Metacritic.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's M-E-T-A-C-R-I-T-C.
[SPEAKER_12]: And definitely check it out because they break down, they have a list of all the scores at different magazines and websites and whatnot I've published, except
[SPEAKER_12]: We don't have anything on here.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it does give an average and also has user averages.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's a really good place to look, especially if you're wondering if a game is good or not.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't read one magazine or a couple magazines because certain people have certain tastes in magazines.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, for example, if I were rating a sports game, I'd probably give it a low score because I hate sports games.
[SPEAKER_12]: But that's not fair.
[SPEAKER_12]: But unfortunately, there are biased reviews out there.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that's why you need websites like this or just the kind of...
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, you know, then go out and find another one of the hundreds of video game podcasts that are out there being produced by independent gamers like you and me that have similar tastes.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I think that is where things are headed, and that's why I say that the traditional gaming press is in for a rude awakening very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've been dominating the conversation.
[SPEAKER_13]: I apologize.
[SPEAKER_13]: What do you think, buddy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I agree with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that if they are in for a rude awakening,
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really welcoming that because up until now, gaming has been viewed as a very nerd culture thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that just being able to interact with something that's on TV isn't evil.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not obscure.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty natural for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that if somebody can just sit down and have fun with a game, then
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I think that's exactly what Nintendo wants them to do and that's exactly what I think they are going to and I'm hoping they're going to achieve.
[SPEAKER_13]: Out of curiosity, outside of Nintendo Power, can anyone, whether on the phone or here in the room, think of, is there a magazine out there geared towards the casual gamer?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not necessarily saying that Nintendo Power is like that magazine, but you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_13]: Like something that would maybe give the Wii game reviews the perspective that the big boys are missing out on?
[SPEAKER_13]: Is there any type of publication like that right now?
[SPEAKER_13]: Not that I know of.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe there ought to be.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not specifically to gaming.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe they figure that because they're casual gamers, they wouldn't want to buy magazines about gaming.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: But just kind of.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know, but for a casual gamer, just like he said, Grandma's talking to Grandma about Wii Bowling.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, but see, then these people are also going to say, oh, the Wii's the best system in the fucking world because you swing around in the game and it's more interactive.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's not a really, you know, informed decision.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's just, you know, I see something different.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ooh, shiny.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it's... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just kind of on the other end of the spectrum.
[SPEAKER_12]: Instead of having someone that's really hardcore into a game, you have someone reviewing a game that knows jack shit about games and they're reviewing it just, you know, because...
[SPEAKER_12]: Nintendo Total, it's an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, it's an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, any other thoughts you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_13]: Paradox Vincent?
[SPEAKER_13]: Shadow Center is amazing.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is great.
[SPEAKER_13]: Horribly underlooked.
[SPEAKER_13]: And if you own a Wii, you owe it to yourself to at least rent this damn game and check it out.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's pretty I'm spoiled by the 360's graphics and what little I've seen of the Playstation 3 The graphics in Trauma Center, not that thrilling, but that's not the point That's not the point of Trauma Center Oh yeah I'm not surprised, once again I'm sure the mainstream gaming press kind of missed that But the game is more fun than a lot of games I've played in a long time
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, we've got to let you go, Paradox Vincent, so we can take other calls.
[SPEAKER_13]: But thanks so much for inspiring the lively chat we've had here.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_13]: You too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's go to another phone call, shall we?
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's go to this call.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is DMN.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_13]: You always manage to get through.
[SPEAKER_13]: When are you coming to visit me again?
[SPEAKER_13]: May.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, they're planning something.
[SPEAKER_13]: The rest of OLR's contributors are planning something big for the fifth anniversary of OLR, which, by the way, I forgot to say this at the top of the show, but this episode would mark our third year of podcasting or our third birthday.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_13]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, great.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then we were forced to eat Rob's shoes.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can only celebrate so many landmark shows.
[SPEAKER_13]: So anyway, whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: DMM, what's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Two things.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was one, but that previous call fired up some other things.
[SPEAKER_03]: One, I'm disappointed in the three of you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't do it!
[SPEAKER_03]: You did, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: No!
[SPEAKER_03]: I did not hear Okami out of any one of you three.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't play Okami!
[SPEAKER_13]: Interesting, huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's because PS2 games, late generation PS2 games are being horribly overlooked in this, you know, last push towards the next gen of gaming.
[SPEAKER_13]: And yeah, I guess I'm a little bit guilty of that.
[SPEAKER_13]: But again, it's kind of one of those cases where if I had more, if I had a top 20 or a top 15, probably Okami would have made it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or even it could have been my number 10, but I had to say Sneak King, I had to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, but, I mean, for one, Okami was my game of the year, if anybody listened to SDFU, all three of you.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, we don't listen to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okami was my game of the year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was surprised that none of you guys said it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: And there's probably 500 other people out there listening going, why didn't they rank this game higher?
[SPEAKER_13]: Why didn't they put this game on the list?
[SPEAKER_13]: Why not this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Why not that?
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: That's the whole point of top lists, is it's just one opinion and take it or leave it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not saying Okami's a bad game by any means.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's fantastic, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, good, because if you said it's a bad game, I'd punch you in the face.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, no, I don't feel that way at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: That means you'd have to come here to do it, and then I'd have to catch it on film.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't... Exactly.
[SPEAKER_13]: I did not... Well, I left Gears of War off my top 10, and Gears of War wouldn't even be in my top 20.
[SPEAKER_13]: But that's just me personally.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was severely disappointed by Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_13]: Go back and listen to me supporting Michelle from Video Game Outsiders in last week's episode.
[SPEAKER_13]: She felt the same way I did.
[SPEAKER_13]: It just...
[SPEAKER_13]: It wasn't all that.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was pretty and that's it.
[SPEAKER_13]: To me.
[SPEAKER_13]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number two is Nintendo Power for about the past year hasn't really been catered toward the casual gamer.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've changed their outlook on things.
[SPEAKER_13]: I wasn't trying to say Nintendo Power was a casual gamer's magazine.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was trying to think like what magazine is reviewing Wii games from the perspective of I am not a hardcore gamer.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm someone who just likes to have fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: What gaming magazine could Nelly read?
[SPEAKER_13]: None of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: None of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll tell you why.
[SPEAKER_03]: First of all, you see shitty games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could bring up a big example several years back.
[SPEAKER_03]: A game for the PS2 called State of Emergency.
[SPEAKER_03]: This game was hyped as hell.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is when I knew one of my favorite magazines, Jump the Shark, EGM.
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe they gave the game an 8.5.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was one of the worst games I've ever played.
[SPEAKER_03]: It started making me think that I think some of those developers pay off magazines to give their games good reviews, and if that is the case, I'm very sorely disappointed in gaming media.
[SPEAKER_13]: Look at Atari and Driver 3, that's what they did.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not going to go there because I don't have the proof to back it up, but...
[SPEAKER_13]: Gaming fans are very... I mean, it's a very interesting industry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because, you know, you take the passion that movie fans have about movies.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, go to those big movie websites like, you know, Ain't It Cool News or whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just read the passion that people have for movies.
[SPEAKER_13]: Multiply that by 100 and you have the gaming fans and the games.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, it's something else.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, and the gaming fans will respond appropriately, I think.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think gaming fans are stupid.
[SPEAKER_13]: Look at what happened with All I Want for Xmas is a PSP.com.
[SPEAKER_13]: Case in point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you could also put the Halo franchise in that same limelight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think that they're 10 out of 10s as what a lot of magazines gave Halo 1 and some gave Halo 2 when it came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they're decent, but they're not like, you know, industry-changing games.
[SPEAKER_13]: And what's funny with that, I would actually disagree.
[SPEAKER_13]: I do think Halo 2 is a 10 out of 10 game, but that's just me.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean,
[SPEAKER_13]: And I do think it's an industry-changing game, but that's, you know, again, it's opinion.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, DMN, so you're going to have the guy from VG Cats on your show on Thursday, we hope?
[SPEAKER_13]: Either this or next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what we're shooting for.
[SPEAKER_13]: How are you landing all these big interviews?
[SPEAKER_13]: You just smoozing, writing nice emails and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: I... How much dick are you having to suck, I guess is what I'm asking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you taught me, so...
[SPEAKER_13]: I must have taught you better than myself because we're not landing any of these big interviews, but you are.
[SPEAKER_13]: So no, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: We love VG Cats.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm looking forward to hearing that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell them that they're my favorite webcomic ever.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sure he's going to take the time to point that out.
[SPEAKER_13]: The chick on OLR loves you.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, DMN, have a good time.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going to try to get another call before we leave.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Take care, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you want to give us a call, it's 1-877-GAME-OLR or the Skype line is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's try at least one more call here, maybe more if we're feeling saucy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_13]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_11]: I just want to say that Microsoft did not give early adopters the shaft.
[SPEAKER_13]: They did not give who the shaft?
[SPEAKER_11]: Early adopters.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, early adopters.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because they did not introduce the HDMI port for the Xbox 360 XS.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, they didn't.
[SPEAKER_11]: They didn't even say HDMI.
[SPEAKER_11]: They just went like, okay, this is the Xbox, this is IPTV, this is what you can do with it, this is Uno, now you can play Uno on the road, you can play Uno here, you can play Uno there, you can even play this there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, I'm saying it's super bullshit now.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if it's coming later.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm keeping my mind open to this.
[SPEAKER_11]: One more thing I want to tell you about that, that HDMI hookup in the back of the 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: It ran through VGA.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'll get up to VGA through the TV.
[SPEAKER_13]: True, true, they do.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, we'll see, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, and just want to say they didn't give you the shaft, and I am now trying to get money up for Windows Vista.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, good luck.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know, you're right.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_13]: You too, bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't heard you guys talk too much about portables, like DS games, except like Cooking Mama.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, my favorite game too, by the way.
[SPEAKER_13]: So what were you hoping that we would be talking about?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, it's like, because I just started hearing you guys in November, and one of the games I wasn't sure you guys talked about was in the Castlevania series.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what's funny is that the last time I actually played the Castlevania game, I do still need to pick up the new one on DS, but we did get to play it in August at the little Konami thing we went to.
[SPEAKER_13]: I really enjoyed it more than the previous DS game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I get all the names confused.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dawn of Sorrow, is that it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dawn of Sorrow was the first one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, Dawn of Sorrow was the last one, and then this new one, Portrait of Ruin.
[SPEAKER_13]: Portrait of Ruin I liked quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: I liked the whole fact that you had kind of the two characters, and I liked the fact that you kind of went outside the castle into other worlds.
[SPEAKER_13]: It felt a little more like Simon's Quest, I suppose, in that regard.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or Mario 64, where you jump into the paintings.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, kind of like that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, yeah, no, it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: I do want to check out the final release of the game, although I'm pretty sure what we played in August was pretty close to final, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I've been playing for a while.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's really good.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've never seen a bad... What was the other game we played that Kojima was behind on the DS?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, that hasn't come out yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't remember the name of it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Lunar Knights.
[SPEAKER_13]: Lunar Knights, thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_13]: I liked that.
[SPEAKER_13]: LUNAR NIGHTS
[SPEAKER_13]: Ultimate Ghosts and Goblins
[SPEAKER_13]: The Gradius Collection and those other retro titles are great.
[SPEAKER_12]: Every Extended Extra is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Twin V Collection, which is coming out, and the Salamander Collection.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, Salamander Hall.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, of course, for Game Boy Advance, Final Fantasy VI, first week in February there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Diddy Kong Racing for the DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: We love our handhelds.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just the past couple months have been mostly the systems for me.
[SPEAKER_13]: The consoles, I should say.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, just, hmm, Warriors on PSP, I hope it plays like the Xbox and PS2 versions.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I hope so, because I tried Luminous, like you said, and on the phone, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: I couldn't really hear the music, but the gameplay was actually addicting.
[SPEAKER_13]: especially when you consider the mobile really took some risks with the gameplay I felt that Luminous 2 was a little too much more of the same for it to be justified on the top 10 of the year but it definitely was a very solid release and if you have not played Luminous at all then it's okay to skip Luminous 1 and go right to 2 because it does have some added things and I think the additional skins and the music videos were very cool oh that was the other reason why Luminous 2 lost a lot of brownie points with me is because they recycled way too much for Luminous 1
[SPEAKER_13]: so pretty much pretty much Luminous 2 is like Luminous 1 plus other stuff then yeah but like way more stuff and if you don't have a PSP at all you should get the Xbox Live one but I don't think you need both unless you're really a puzzle game whore like I am well not as much for me but the 360 I'll get later I'm eagerly hoping that the music artist pack and the Heavenly Star song is out very very soon it was supposed to be in January at some point so we'll see hmm
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it'll be a while for me to get it because of money and all that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_13]: Any other thoughts for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_13]: DDR dollar bill?
[SPEAKER_09]: I had a few, but I'm just still a little sick right now, so I just wanted to chime in about the portables because I never hear you guys talk about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, we try to give it a little love once in a while.
[SPEAKER_13]: We do love our portables.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love my DS and my PSP for certain things.
[SPEAKER_09]: Same here.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, thanks so much for the call, buddy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Keep listening.
[SPEAKER_09]: See you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: See you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_13]: Those were some good calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Little rough starts to some of them, but we got our way through them.
[SPEAKER_13]: So thank you guys so much for calling in tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going to go ahead and close the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry to those that didn't get through, but we still love you.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just we're running.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're almost to two hours for this segment, so we've got to wrap this crap up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Any last-minute stories, you guys?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Necronasia is coming to the United States as a game called Escape from Bug Island.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let me tell you this much.
[SPEAKER_12]: The game is as crappy as that new title, so don't pick it up when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's shit.
[SPEAKER_12]: But Eidos is producing it, so that won't be the first time that their games suck.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Then, of course, there was some news also coming from CES about Vista, and this isn't really a huge surprise, that the Xbox 360 controller is going to be able to be used with Vista.
[SPEAKER_12]: In fact, it's going to be kind of like a standard for them, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: Big, huge surprise there.
[SPEAKER_12]: What is kind of cool, though, is this Thursday, January 11th, there's going to be new content for Gears of War coming out, including two free maps, Raven Down, which is going to be a map set around a downed Raven helicopter, and it looks pretty.
[SPEAKER_12]: And there's also a new map called Old Bones, which looks like a museum, which looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Both of those are going to be free because they're being sponsored by, and this is weird, the Discovery Channel.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're also giving away 2 million Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_13]: Doesn't Discovery HD, though, have a game special that's been airing or something?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_12]: It makes a little sense to me.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that's kind of cool, I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: And also there's a rumor that Nintendo is developing a wireless nunchuck.
[SPEAKER_12]: Already.
[SPEAKER_13]: Already.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, you have anything?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, then that brings our show to a close.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks again so much for tuning in to and supporting Independent Radio, you guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just a reminder, we're not live next week.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry, live listeners, but we just have personal situations to be dealt with, and that would include I'm finally going to Disneyland with the girls, so we'll take lots of pictures and share that with you guys in the fan communities.
[SPEAKER_13]: and Loki has that other thing which I'm just now finding out about and I really wish I could go to that so please give those two my old Final Fantasy XI buddies give them my best and best wishes and all that stuff and we will still have a new audio blog or podcast whatever you want to call it there will still be a new show that way so apologies to live listeners I know you've had to deal with a break but we promise after this week we won't be having a break for a long time a long time so if you bear with us we'll be good
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you guys so much for your continued support of our program.
[SPEAKER_13]: You guys are awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going to go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_12]: My final thought is there's this laser pen advertisement on this one page here, and it's cool because it shoots a giant laser.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want a laser.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lasers are awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess it's shiny.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dark Sakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, I really, really, really, really, really am tired of drinking my own medicinal tea to make my throat work.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I want, um, and I want to cook something, but not right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to cook for real.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bake me a pie.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll bake shepherd's pie.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll make good shepherd's pie.
[SPEAKER_13]: My final thought is that Legend of Zaku says this, yay, that means you OLR listeners must watch 24 next Sunday in the show's absence.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would actually support that because 24 is a show I need to get back into that's really good, and I'm going to TiVo it while we're gone.
[SPEAKER_08]: People should look for us at Disneyland if they're going to be there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, say hi.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can't miss us.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: Orange Lounge Radio is for you guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see you next week with a new podcast here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks again.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_07]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.OrangeLoungeRadio.com See you next week!