[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_05]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are here on this lovely Sunday evening, January the 28th of 2007 for more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we're going to get into part B.
[SPEAKER_06]: My throat is feeling a little bit better, but I'm going to step out of the room for just a second to get some coffee out of my Hello Kitty coffee maker.
[SPEAKER_06]: For those who didn't listen to Part A, my throat's kind of bad tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm going to go get some more hot stuff to drink, and can you guys take care of some gaming news for a minute?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: I would really appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, so starting things off, this week Microsoft had announced their earnings for their quarter, and of course...
[SPEAKER_07]: The profits were down, but at least the 360 revenues were up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, unfortunately, Microsoft went back and revised their earnings statements, basically saying that their expected 360 shipments for 2007 and spring, they reduced it down from $15 million to $12 million.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is due to unsold inventories in stores.
[SPEAKER_07]: So basically, you know, that big tower of 360s that you see in your Best Buys and your Game Stops,
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, because of that, they are dropping their shipments amount because, you know, who needs to ship more units if there's tons in stores?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, and because of that, all these stocks from other companies have dropped a little bit as well because of that news.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's not a big, you know, big surprise.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, the PlayStation 3 is kind of in the same boat right now where they have a ton of units in stores and no one's really buying them because there's not a lot of games out right now or it's too expensive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Either way...
[SPEAKER_07]: One of the analysts, PJ McNeely, said video game publishers will be under pressure today after Microsoft cuts its life-to-date shipment.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is investor concern about reset of expectations around both the Xbox 360 and Sony PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: So pretty much just, you know, I guess they're playing it safe.
[SPEAKER_06]: I missed all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Could you repeat it?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically Microsoft shipping or they're reducing their amount of shipments that they're going to be... No, I heard Microsoft's goal went down a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I can see the impact that's having on things as a whole.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's only down to me a few million, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of bad, but they just have to sell the units that they have right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: And trust me, those units will be gone once Halo 3 comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And even maybe Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, Crackdown might sell a few... I don't know about selling units for beta, but
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, this is a report coming from QJ.net, speaking of the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is a little bit of a hack.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can use this at your own risk, but apparently a hack has been released, the HDD hacker, that will allow you to use your hard drive, your own hard drive, with the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, keep in mind there are some limitations.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can only really use a Western Digital BEVS series and only a 20-gigabyte hard drive.
[SPEAKER_06]: But keep in mind, if you do it that way, a 20GB hard drive through Western Digital is going to be a hell of a lot cheaper than a regular Xbox 360 hard drive through Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, I'm thinking... Actually, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: The site goes on to say that once bigger Microsoft-certified hard drives come out, then you'll be able to use those with the tool.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm thinking, no, you won't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Microsoft's very good about patching this shit as soon as they find it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I bet you by this time next week, we'll see a patch roll out on live that'll prevent this.
[SPEAKER_06]: The next patch that goes out live will shut this thing out.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: The reason why this does is actually there's information on the hard drive sector that's the same on all the hard drives because they have to be universal since they're working with all these different systems.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically some sort of identified device type of thing that's stored in one of the sectors.
[SPEAKER_07]: So all they do is basically mimic that on this hard drive.
[SPEAKER_07]: So all it thinks is that it's a legit hard drive.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there would be no way to patch this.
[SPEAKER_07]: because it's a peripheral.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'd be like if I took a controller for the 360 and I made it look like that's an official Microsoft controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no way for it to tell between whether this is real or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well you follow the hack stuff more than I do, so I'll take your word for it, but this just seems like the kind of thing that Microsoft's usually all over.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'll take your word for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not like modifying firmware or anything like that, so I think that they wouldn't be able to patch this.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well,
[SPEAKER_03]: Going into things that have, well, I don't know, not quite yet having to do with the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, sort of.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me just rephrase this.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're all familiar with the Unreal Engine, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's been some good games coming out of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, guess who's just licensed it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been licensed by Squeenix.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're basically, there's a manager, I'm all tongue tied now, thank you, I blame you.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a statement put out by the general manager of R&D at Square Enix that's Taku Murata saying that it will speed up the creation process and allow developers to spend
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like this thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Drew Nami says, Kingdom Hearts 3 using the Unreal Engine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wouldn't that be hot?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a boner just thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just kidding, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Still, that's pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Unreal Engine's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's actually a little bit more information regarding the Unreal Tournament itself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unreal Tournament 2007 is now renamed as Unreal Tournament 3 and is going to be on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was confirmed at Midway's Gamers Day in Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be developed with the PC and PS3 versions.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has a release later on this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Unreal.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know one thing I do like about Unreal?
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't played a whole lot of it, but I did play it on the original Xbox because I bought it when it was like $20.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's fucking fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is like one of the fastest shooters I've ever played.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's amazingly fast.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even just the first Unreal tournament was crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was a game that gave me some freaking motion sickness right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I was going to say, you probably are not having much fun with those games with how fast they move.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's also a little bit more as far as, not necessarily just the graphics, but different multiplayer modes.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is a voice-controlled AI and player-controlled vehicles.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's also a conquest mode that will be a battle for eight teams on a map that's three times the size of the Deathmatch and Onslaught maps.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking about Square Enix here, NCSX has reported that Square Enix is going to be producing a collection of replica weapons called the Square Enix Master Arms Collection.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically going to be some of the weapons from the Final Fantasy series and Keyblade from Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately, they are not going to be full-size, so don't get your hopes up there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they're going to range from 15 centimeters for Cerebus to 26 centimeters for Sephiroth's Gunblade.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right now, there's four different blades to choose from.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see, Cerebus, which I believe, I can't remember which Final Fantasy it is from.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Keyblade, of course, from Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Squall's Gunblade.
[SPEAKER_07]: I believe that's Vincent's Gun.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe, I have school to pay for
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, did it already go up?
[SPEAKER_06]: It already went up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have a Playstation 3 so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But apparently it went up and they did this whole little change there is that the Playstation 1 and 2 games now will run right and they'll look fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now you can also, they also did some other little things like you can set an image photo for a user ID and all this other little minor crap Korean keyboards and stuff you can use now.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what's weird though?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know on your PSP how during the months they'll change colors in the background?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well they...
[SPEAKER_07]: PS3 backgrounds will slowly fade from one color to another as time goes on through the month.
[SPEAKER_07]: It might start off black, and now it's yellow.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ew, yellow?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not my favorite color.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, actually, you know, yellow is associated with aggression, so it's not my favorite either.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's actually, though, a little bit more news coming out regarding an animated Castlevania 3 movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the Dracula's Curse movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're basically looking, they're still in the early stages of their production.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're working on the visual development side of everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: So through February it's going to be mostly character creature design.
[SPEAKER_03]: They need background designers, background painters.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're actually looking for artists to work with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they've actually opened up positions in Southern California.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you actually want to submit
[SPEAKER_03]: Your portfolio to them, you can actually email at Belmont at CastlevaniaDraculasCursed.com I think that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're looking for artists.
[SPEAKER_03]: Give us some work.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd like to see that when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, unfortunately, there have been some other bad vampire movies, including Blood Rain, which is up for six Razzies.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's received nominations for Worst Picture, Worst Actress, Worst Supporting Actor, Worst Supporting Actress, Worst Director, and Worst Screenplay.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's, I guess, good news if you really hate BloodRayne.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although if you do hate BloodRayne, you would probably be disappointed to know that he's planning a sequel.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's, I think, already in production, so that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: One other movie that he has coming out, though, pretty soon is going to be Postal.
[SPEAKER_07]: And IGN had some news from that, actually, talking about some of the things that are going to be offending people, including such wonderful things as full-frontal nudity from NewsRadio's Dave Foley.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, he's going to be playing some crazy cult leader.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's one scene... Hooray?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I realize you guys know I'm gay and all, but I'm not thrilled to hear about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: He's kind of old.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, Dave Foley's character in the production is called Uncle Dave and is a twisted cult leader who uses his religious doctrine to keep his subjects in a constant state of servitude.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he exploits this by luring them into orgies and other debauchery.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says in the scenes that they saw, Foley was dressed in an open robe, and they mean open, wandering around the room barking orders.
[SPEAKER_07]: And at the end of the scene, he takes a crap on camera.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the kind of movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Other fun stuff about this movie, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_06]: Talk about your career going downhill after news radio going off.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's got to be made up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other stuff that they have in the movie, it says there's stuff about 9-11.
[SPEAKER_07]: They actually make fun of 9-11.
[SPEAKER_07]: They make fun of school shootings, including, I guess there was one scene that says...
[SPEAKER_07]: This sounds like the dumbest fucking thing in the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a difference between parody that's somewhat amusing and this just sounds like stupid after stupid after stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: It should be interesting, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting's a good word to define it, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll see it, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will definitely go see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: By yourself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless you can talk Nellie into going.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, one thing we didn't go over in Part A were the release dates.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though Loki gave us some exclusives, we didn't talk about what's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I want to start it off talking about Japanese release dates, of which, honestly, folks, there's not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: January was a dry month for us over here in the U.S., and February, at least the beginning part of it, looks to be a bit slow over there in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: We do have J-League Pro Soccer Club Otsukuru 5 coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: on February 1st.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, Zero Shikikan Josentukeni, which is Best Hits from Taito.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm not sure if that's a game that's actually out over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like some type of old school B-52 type bomber game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think this is a game they have over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Twin Cobra?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where's the title?
[SPEAKER_02]: Zero, Shikikan, Josentokini Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just the best hits anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's already out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just going in to be a little bit cheaper.
[SPEAKER_06]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do we have over on the Nintendo DS?
[SPEAKER_06]: We do have a couple things coming out on the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have Monster House, which I suppose is a release a lot of folks are looking forward to, as well as Bokujo Monogatari Kimi to Sodatsu Shima coming out from Marvelous Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nappishitam no Hakko
[SPEAKER_03]: Arthur and the Invisibles for PS2, DS, PC, Game Boy Advance
[SPEAKER_03]: Contact on DS, also Dungeon Siege, Throne of Agony on PSP, Europa Universalis 3 on PC, Ghost Rider on Xbox, NFL Street 3 going to be on PSP and PlayStation 2, Sega Genesis Collection, PS2, PSP, and on the 5th Galactic Civilizations 2, but that's coming out later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dragon Quest VIII Battle Stations Midway PC, Vanguard Saga of Heroes
[SPEAKER_07]: and, um, let's see here, Sonic the Hedgehog on PlayStation 3, uh, Fusion, I don't know, Fusion Frenzy 2 on Xbox 360, uh, City Life World Edition on the PC, and Monopoly Here and Now on the PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, um, that's about it for this week at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, uh, I wanted to mention this, and, uh, this is a little bit embarrassing because the, uh, oh, no, there it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good, we got it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The link wasn't working previously for some reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was trying to hit Blizzard Entertainment to look at this press release that talks about World of Warcraft, The Burning Crusade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, you know that that game just came out earlier this month.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, get this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It sold 2.4 million copies in the first 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was released simultaneously in North America, Europe, Singapore, Thailand, and Malaysia.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then January 17th, Australia and New Zealand, just the day after.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which actually would, because they're on the other side of the dateline.
[SPEAKER_06]: But never mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: Regardless, they came out and sold 2.4 million copies in 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty impressive and certainly shattered any existing PC game records that were already out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lots of World of Warcraft addicts out there in the world, apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they ignoring their babies?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: For those that only listen to us during the podcast, we have a bonus segment we do here live.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mike Moore-Hamey
[SPEAKER_06]: I still have not bought the expansion.
[SPEAKER_06]: I won't be buying it until I hit level 40.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I promised myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well...
[SPEAKER_03]: There are, I think, other MMOs that might be pulling people's addiction.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a Lord of the Rings MMO actually has a date.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a Lord of the Rings Shadow of Angmar to be released in Europe on the 24th of April, according to Codemasters.
[SPEAKER_03]: The price of it actually is going to be a special pre-order rate.
[SPEAKER_03]: for $99.99 that has a lifetime membership instead of a subscription fee.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can either do that or pay £5.99 a month for a six month package.
[SPEAKER_03]: but the advantage of pre-ordering it gives you early access to the game for 10 days you can use a pre-launch character in the full game so basically whatever you make during this little beta is yours to hold on to you get a unique in-game bonus item six Lord of the Rings online stickers and a special window sticker yeah it seems kind of interesting I don't know it's
[SPEAKER_03]: There's so many MMOs out there, really.
[SPEAKER_06]: Amen!
[SPEAKER_03]: Also though, just to let you know, I'm on the US site for this Lord of the Rings game.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the pre-order special that they're having on that one, I'm trying to scroll down on it, it's still loading.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me read a couple of comments.
[SPEAKER_03]: When you pre-order it, you have $199 for the lifetime thing, or $999 monthly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Early Access, you keep your launch care.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the same thing, really.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get an enchanted Cloak of Regeneration and a Ring of Agility.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like regenerating.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had to read some of these other interesting comments.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100Matt says, Dear Blizzard, since you have all this money, you wouldn't mind putting StarCraft on DS, would you?
[SPEAKER_06]: And Michael Doy is going to make a fan with Jamie here saying, I want a Doctor Who MMO.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hell yeah!
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw that coming.
[SPEAKER_03]: I might sign up for the beta for this, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, so before Doctor Who MMO, you're going to see something else coming from BBC.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be CBBC, their kids' property.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to be creating an MMO based on that called CBBC World.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be aimed at kids ages 7 to 12, and it's going to kind of just be your online MMO for kids, just like Toontown, Disney thing over here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's gonna have a bunch of, like, you know, custom avatars, you know, minigames, music videos.
[SPEAKER_07]: Completely lame for anybody over the age of 12, but Jamie will still be signed up to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's gonna be, like, what, Gaia Online or something, which I quit in, you know, a day, because it was boring.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll still play it, because, like, if it's BBC related, it might remotely have a Doctor Who reference in it, and you'll be like... If someone tells me for sure there's a Doctor Who reference, I'll sign up.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chat room, lie to her.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: But I only want our UK listeners to tell me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, on a completely unrelated note, that doesn't even have to do with video games, but I think it's kind of funny regarding the BBC.
[SPEAKER_06]: I read on some reality TV news site, don't ask me what I was doing reading it, but I was, that the BBC is doing like a Harry Potter reality show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not called Harry Potter, but they're sending kids to magic school.
[SPEAKER_06]: and it's going to be like a reality show for kids in magic school and they actually have to do magic tricks.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's magic school.
[SPEAKER_06]: You mean devil school?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I get it, I get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I see what you did there.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no, it sounds really cheesy.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I hope they bring the show over to America because it would be a hoot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Magic school.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because they get a lot of shows from Britain over here.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it should be hosted by David Copperfield because he's washed up anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell ever happened to David Copperfield?
[SPEAKER_06]: He just disappeared.
[SPEAKER_06]: He just made himself disappear.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, one game that disappeared but made a hell of a comeback moving into some non-MMO PC gaming news, Sam & Max.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, they were gone for a long, long time, and then they came back.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're getting new life thanks to GameTap and, you know, some of the other distribution methods they're doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Episode 1, Culture Shock for Sam & Max came out in October of 06.
[SPEAKER_06]: Episode 2 came out December of 06, and now Episode 3 just came out on GameTap just this past week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's titled The Mole, The Mob, and The Meatball.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be the third part of a six-part series.
[SPEAKER_06]: From what I understand, I have yet to play these games myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really need to.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a GameTap subscription.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to put down the WoW and get into these games.
[SPEAKER_06]: From what I understand, none of these episodes are really long.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe you'll play them for four hours, depending on how much you play.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have to explore every nook and cranny or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it sounds kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: You often hear about these episodic gaming, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: They kind of produce one or two episodes, then that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's kind of nice to see Sam and Max keep going at it and being very successful.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I've heard nothing but raves about the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I promise you I will play Sam and Max at least part one, maybe all the way through part three, depending on how I enjoy it, before the month's over, which doesn't give me much time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully that series will run a little longer than the cartoon series that they had.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you can see the cartoon series on GameTap, for whatever it's worth.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well...
[SPEAKER_03]: For our PC gamers, there's a bit of sad news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Age of Conan has been delayed even longer.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will be out in October.
[SPEAKER_03]: It actually will ship October 30th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Xbox 360 version is going to be in 2008, so it'll be after that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks pretty, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: What the fuck did that have to do with anything we were just talking about?
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw an ad for a Tycoon game and I was thinking PC stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: There could be some major money made there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then it should come out in the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any more curveballs you want to throw at us?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if, you know, you're not into porn Tycoon or, you know,
[SPEAKER_07]: Age of Conan.
[SPEAKER_07]: You might be interested in Ghost Recon Advanced Warfare 2 for the PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be coming out day and date with the Xbox 360 version which is March 9th.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to feature some more multiplayer stuff as well as up to 32 players online and more game modes including the standard deathmatch co-op and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Plus it's just going to have a whole new storyline.
[SPEAKER_07]: To be honest the game looked originally kind of like the first one a lot but
[SPEAKER_07]: The storyline sounds pretty interesting, almost like they're going to do, I want to say there's like Mexicans invading Texas or something, and some sort of, like they have to stave off some civil war over Mexico and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, it was a fun game the first time around.
[SPEAKER_07]: I cheated the whole way through it, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Surprise.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was fun, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Infinite grenade launchers are awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, I knew you and your random porn tycoon outburst would stir chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's going on in our chat room?
[SPEAKER_06]: TheRobD says, Loki just had his what if it snowed in San Francisco moment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meklar says, porn tycoon.
[SPEAKER_06]: First off, build a fluffer room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the fluffers are an important part of pornography.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then DarkTetsuya says, I thought they made that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was called Playboy Mansion.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Playboy Mansion was lame.
[SPEAKER_06]: How would you improve on Playboy Mansion for Porn Tycoon?
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually make it cool and not Playboy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because Playboy, to be honest, just sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: They just want to be X-rated, but they're too classy for that shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, if it was like, you know, Penthouse Mansion or something like that, that'd be a little step in the right direction there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Joshi16 says, Neverland Ranch Tycoon.
[SPEAKER_06]: One person buys it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guess who?
[SPEAKER_07]: Peter Pan?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: So, have you guys seen this list already?
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, Jamie, have you guys seen the list already?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, Loki, Jamie, have you read this list already?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, what would you think would be on this list?
[SPEAKER_06]: Besides Tomb Raider, which is up on the screen right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: What games do you think, number 7 is Tomb Raider, what series do you think have just been run into the ground?
[SPEAKER_03]: Remakes of Final Fantasy 7.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, well let's see if it shows up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, number 7 is Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number 6 is Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_06]: because, I mean, really, I mean, there's been all those stinking Battle Network games, but there was, you know, there was never really a Mega Man 9.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mega Man X games kind of ended in 2004, and so, you know, Mega Man's just kind of been done to death.
[SPEAKER_06]: They need a resurgence of Mega Man, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Beautiful Joe is at number five, which I think is an interesting selection.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had, like, two or three games for that series.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's hardly running for the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: But were any of them as good as the first one?
[SPEAKER_07]: But they, you know, to be honest, though, they may have not been as good as the first one, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, you have to kind of take off to run it into the ground, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: GamesRadar cites Red Hot Rumble, which was a Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: type fighter game that had beautiful Joe characters in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number four was Dynasty Warriors.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every single Dynasty Warriors game is exactly the same as the one before it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then they keep doing this fucking Empire shit, which is exactly the same game all over again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number three is Tenchu, and they cite the PSP version, as this has just been done too much now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, that game, there's still not that many games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number two is Spy Hunter.
[SPEAKER_06]: I agree with this.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's been like three games in that series.
[SPEAKER_06]: But seriously, it was gone for the longest time.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had Spy Hunter and then a forgettable sequel in the arcades, and then it was gone forever, and then suddenly Midway decided to make this resurgence out of it, and it's not been anything to scream about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's why they say they run into the ground.
[SPEAKER_06]: They cite Spy Hunter 2 and Spy Hunter Nowhere to Run.
[SPEAKER_06]: 3 games by 3 different developers the number 1 series they say has been run into the ground Sonic the Hedgehog the number 1 series and of course they cite the GBA port of the original that was god awful in 2006 Rivals and Riders which weren't that great of course this new one that's god awful they say the last truly good Sonic game according to GamesRadar Sonic Rush back in 2005 was the last good one you know what I think is interesting though
[SPEAKER_06]: I know a lot of folks out there think we're Nintendo fanboys and girls here on this program, and to some extent, you know, we are a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hasn't Mario had some pretty shitty games, too?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you ever play Mario is Missing?
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a PC game, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, there was a version on Super Nintendo that was pretty awful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Luigi's Mansion, not that great.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of people didn't like Mario Sunshine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was pretty good myself, but a lot of folks didn't like it for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the re-release over and over.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why is Mario getting a buy out of all this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I guess...
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario 64, Donkey Kong
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that Mario vs. Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, those games are okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I meant, like, just Donkey Kong stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, the Donkey Kong Country... Donkey Kong Country got ran into the ground.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was okay, but then, like, they had the stupid fucking bongo shit, and then... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, the bongo games were interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but then they have those other ones where you had to, like, you know, use the bongos to, like, move up a, like... What was that one where you had to basically just use the L and R buttons on it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think...
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of the franchises out there kind of suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, Ranma made a good one that these guys left off the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't forget Spyro.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a great one that should have been on the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good catch, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or Crash Bandicoot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are both really good ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see, what else do we have?
[SPEAKER_06]: TheRobD says, yeah, but the last real Mario game came out 11 years ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that would depend on what you consider a real Mario game.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about Rampage?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's a good one, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, we should come up with our own list.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, JeremyTodd1 says Metal Slug.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: What about Contra?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been a while since we had a Contra game, hasn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, last year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, besides the arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I meant like 2005.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, we had Shattered... Wait, not Shattered Soldier.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn, I don't remember the last one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Vinpower says, I admit, I had a blast with the Mario is Missing games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm glad someone enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ninja Turtle games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, we got some really good ones here.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the list wasn't so bad as it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, another thing that's not so bad is reading your emails that we get every week.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, we rather enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And DarkSakura is queen of the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when you send your emails to mailbag at orangelaunchreader.com, DarkSakura will read and often respond to your emails and pick some of her favorites to read here on the program.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, because we do get quite a few letters, we can't read them all, but we can try.
[SPEAKER_06]: So DarkSakura is going to open up the mailbag and dive on in and see what we've got to read this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, what's in the mailbag this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Two emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, let's do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: First one, SalutationsOLRCast, I just had a question about the Nintendo Wii, and if its games contain region coding, thanks for reading this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, I don't know if you guys heard about this article, but someone tried to electrocute themselves with an arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Their Pac-Man high score was beaten, and he claimed that he had nothing left to live for, so he attempted suicide with a Pac-Man machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty weird, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: He just comes from Zenith.
[SPEAKER_07]: He should have just tipped the machine over on himself.
[SPEAKER_03]: That wouldn't kill anybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've had an arcade machine fall on me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, first of all, um... Did it hit you in the head?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that might explain some stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Teasing, just heart?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm letting you buy me dinner.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can make it up to me with potato pancakes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fat chance.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, my car's dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, um, as for the, the, uh... Would you like, would you like a nice cup?
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you like me to bring you a cup of wah?
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, I'm trying to do emails, so you can shut up, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: All own...
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie So at any rate, the Nintendo Wii is definitely region coded So yeah, but they're working on it, they're working on it And also about someone killing themselves over a score Darwin loves them Sorry, that type of person should be removed from the dream pool
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving forward to the next and last email, pretty long one, coming to us from someone who has not signed the email, so I'm just going to say JCK.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey guys, great show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just wanted to give some feedback to two news items on last week's show.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Dallas Area TV Network's WFAA has reported on the PS3 and Wii as a giveaway to porn.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, gateway to porn.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the New York State bill... Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're giving away porn on the PS3?
[SPEAKER_06]: Now I'll buy one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey Rob, shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the New York State bill A00547 and later the A02024 prohibiting the sale of certain games to minors.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you want to read the email though if you really want to talk?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to go get more coffee for my Hello Kitty maker.
[SPEAKER_03]: They are the ones who seek to censor and control every content distribution chain.
[SPEAKER_03]: The problem is that the world cannot be made safe, even if we could agree on what safe is without oppressing sub-subculture somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is impossible for any of us to remake the world in our own image.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have to accept that...
[SPEAKER_03]: that we don't like exist, that our children will stumble onto them if we don't shelter them or otherwise prepare them for that initial contact.
[SPEAKER_03]: I may not agree with the religious conservatives who homeschool their kids and filter their TV, but at least they're active parents.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are legal issues that surround the New York bills.
[SPEAKER_03]: First of all, who decides what is objectionable?
[SPEAKER_03]: The ESRB and MPAA are private industry bodies.
[SPEAKER_03]: We cannot pass a law that deputizes these private bodies to rate things
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: and PAA ratings and the gaming industry chooses to submit to the ESRB.
[SPEAKER_03]: The public pressure is on retail distribution chains to comply with what forces the content creators to adhere which is why every major game retailer already checks ID.
[SPEAKER_03]: The system works and there's no reason to change it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's the end of the email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_07]: I got nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to say that that's pretty...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd have to say yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I agree with... If the government really... And see, this is... I have a whole problem with the government being way too involved in our personal lives.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that it is unreasonable to expect somebody else to protect their children from...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: The reference to the homeschool religious fundamentalist, a friend of my friends that I met here when I moved out to California, she had been so sheltered homeschooled.
[SPEAKER_03]: She actually didn't go to school until she was in high school and thought that oral sex was talking about sex.
[SPEAKER_06]: I knew someone who thought the F word was fart.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so when confronted with the reality of their ignorance, you know, who's to blame but their parents, you know, keeping them from the stuff that's going on in the real world.
[SPEAKER_03]: And to go back to the statement regarding needing a governmental body to participate with a government-controlled law.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I guess it's the government-controlled.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not redundant.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I understand the logic in that, but I still think that if we have a private party that is not involved in the government, we are likely to get less, I would say, bias.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, our government is bought and paid for.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, for every...
[SPEAKER_03]: Person that you elect into government positions, there's a lobbyist behind them paying lots of money for them to say, you know, I think that cigarettes are okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that why Travis is running for president?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know either.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just putting that out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I actually think that it is better for us to have that separation with those facilities and the government.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the law is unnecessary, and I agree, unenforceable.
[SPEAKER_03]: The way it's current incarnation.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I read through the email while you were ranting there, and it was well thought out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like getting those thoughtful emails.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love when people with brains email us.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you should email us to mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: And please be smart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, dude, we got another email just as I was closing the box.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're already smart because they listen to this program.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to read this now.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is by Nintendomaniac64.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: WorthOfThousandWords.com, an entry into this Internet Porn Tycoon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've got a picture of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody had already done this on this WorthOfThousand.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody photoshopped Railroad Tycoon and says, Internet Porn Tycoon.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, thank you for sharing that with us, Nintendo Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Too bad it's not real.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I can only hope.
[SPEAKER_03]: By MicroProbe.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, MicroProse was the one that made it originally.
[SPEAKER_06]: I see what they did there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay, Photoshop!
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, so in the past, PlayStation Portable Firmware has been defeated by Grand Theft Auto Liberty City stories.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, you know, Sony went and apparently fixed the hole, or so they thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, people have found another way using Grand Theft Auto Liberty City Stories, one of the original copies, that you can once again break the firmware.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what have they done?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep, they've done it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They've made their wonderful Hello World proof of concept thing, and even today, which just got released, a downgrader for firmware 3.03.
[SPEAKER_07]: So try as you might, Sony, you'll just never win.
[SPEAKER_07]: Never, ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: This is why consoles shouldn't have firmwares.
[SPEAKER_07]: They should just be good to go instead of having to upgrade.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's the big deal about homebrew on the PSP anyway?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it really that bad?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it really killing families across America?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it really something that has to be prevented at all costs?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, they're encouraging it on the PlayStation 3, but that's still when people are going to pirate the, you know, they're going to break the firmware to pirate shit, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was reading somewhere else that HD DVD, of course, you know, they finally had to admit that, yes, it's been cracked.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: This kick to your ass is courtesy of DMN.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell DMN to go suck on a... Anyway, I wanted to just say really quickly, and then we're going to get into the Skype line and hear what you guys have to say and play a voicemail.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got one voicemail this week that's pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want you guys to hear it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say this real quickly.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might remember...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and Stingus.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they die when they sting you.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you love bees, check out the site.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's ilovebees.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to get into the Skype line and take some of your calls here live on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: But first, I want to play a voicemail that came into our line this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, of course, we always invite your voicemails on any topic.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can always give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR when we're not live.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or for those of you guys outside the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: or Canada where that number is toll free, you can always give us a call on the Skype line at
[SPEAKER_06]: Just download Skype and call username OrangeLoungeRadio.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's us.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you can leave us a message throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: But keep in mind, if you call right now, you're probably going to get on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll take you live on air.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you're the type that likes to formulate your thoughts first and then leave us a voicemail, you can do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or sometimes we get other craziness on our voicemail line.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I mean craziness.
[SPEAKER_06]: So check this out because this is pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you might have to listen kind of carefully because they talk fast because you can definitely sense there's a lot of excitement in the room.
[SPEAKER_06]: So check this out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey Rob, it's me, I just finished on the Freezpop concert, it was awesome, I have a little surprise for you, hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yo Rob, this is Sean from Freezpop, what's going on man, I'm just chatting, we're like, wait, is he going to show up tonight, we don't know, is he going to fly in, I don't know, is he going to fly in tonight, I don't know, we're looking for like helicopters, you're not here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, this is Sean from Freezpop, hope you're doing well, rock out, good times, guitar hero, fun times, anime, good times, all around you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Freezpop, here's Adam again, he's got something he has to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, let me translate because those guys talked faster than the Micro Machines guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: That apparently was Sean from Freeze Pop leaving the message because Ranma went to the concert in New York City the other night and got them to leave a message.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, sometimes we get craziness on the voicemail line.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I encourage you folks, program the 877-GAME-OLR into your cell phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when you come across internet celebrities such as this guy from Freeze Pop, then you should have them call in and leave us crazy voicemails because, you know, that's fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to open up our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's 1-877-GAME-OLR or it's username Orange Lounge Radio on Skype.
[SPEAKER_06]: We want to offer up you guys to interact with our program here on Orange Lounge Radio because, you know, it doesn't have to be all about us.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, to some extent.
[SPEAKER_03]: It could be all about me.
[SPEAKER_06]: To some extent it does have to be all about us, but we want it to be about you guys as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So give us a call right now on the Skype line and we'll take some calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's start off with this call tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is DMN sans really crappy microphone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, DMN sans really crappy microphone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I'm going to kick your ass next time I see you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bring it, motherfucker.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, wow, I'm just reading in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, 2DX Gold is supposed to be at Konami Gamers Day, which we're going to next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know where the hell that came from.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody just blurted that out in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can somebody back that up?
[SPEAKER_07]: I wouldn't doubt it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, no, I see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meklar, oh, and 2DXGold is going over to America.
[SPEAKER_06]: Left the UK a day ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not sure where it's going, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys got any big conventions or game shows soon?
[SPEAKER_06]: And Jason put it together that it must be coming over to Konami Gamers Day.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming to SakuraCon.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's where it's going.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so playing the Ghostbusters song.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to have a full report on Konami Gamers Day next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And keep an eye on our website.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thursday and Friday.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the news that we get there is embargoed until a certain time, but the minute that embargo's up, we're going to post a ton of shit from the show, so we're really excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, DMM, what's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Three things.
[SPEAKER_04]: One, huge STFU announcement.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is your Thursday night program, yes?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not this week, but next week, we're going to have MC Frontalot on the show for five good minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate you!
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I knew Jamie would be pissed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell him to say something for me and record it, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about we Skype you in and you can talk to him?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have school.
[SPEAKER_04]: When are you guys taping it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you don't do it live.
[SPEAKER_06]: When are you guys taping it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll keep you posted, but I'll kick Jimmy to the curb and you can interview with me.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have school every night this week, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's not this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't your people talk to his people and see what you can come up with?
[SPEAKER_03]: My people will talk to your people.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, maybe we can get them on this show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, anyway, so that's exciting news for you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys are getting more celebrities than we are.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all Jimmy's fault.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've been around for five years.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys are on like nine weeks, and you're having freaking... Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Love you too, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you just call to rub it in, or is there anything else you want to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I actually had two things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a review of Bookworm Adventures.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, Bookworm Adventures is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty much the greatest casual game ever made.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what Xbox Live needs.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's $30 for the full version.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds kind of steep.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I have a keyboard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but not everyone does.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's $30 for the full version.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a bit steep, but very much worth it.
[SPEAKER_06]: exciting is there any particular reason you love Bookworm Adventures?
[SPEAKER_06]: is it the smarts you get to use in constructing words?
[SPEAKER_06]: is it the graphics?
[SPEAKER_06]: what is it about the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: it's that and it's the charm and the game makes this really crazy deep voice like a voiceover guy if you beat the crap out of an enemy it's like CRUSH it's pretty cool can you do that one more time please?
[SPEAKER_06]: CRUSH that's pretty awesome
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anything else on your mind tonight, DMN?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, bonus segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted to talk about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know the podcast listeners didn't hear it, but I actually can totally sympathize with that one lady because I just broke up with my girlfriend over WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember calling her or you or the both of you during Guys on a Show one night.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it wasn't Guys on a Show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was this show when I was really fucking plastered.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's right, when you called in here drunk.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you guys broke up?
[SPEAKER_06]: Over WoW, what happened?
[SPEAKER_04]: Over WoW?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, one, I came over to visit her several weeks ago, and she decided that playing WoW and raiding was more important than spending time with me, and that kind of pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I called her earlier this week to see if she wanted to do something, and she's like, no, I'm playing Burning Crusade.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to get 70.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, okay, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm done with this shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you want?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want level 70 or cocked?
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to make a decision.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that what you told her?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like, you know, you find WoW more important than, you know, hanging out with me and I care about you and I do all this shit for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look, that's how I would break it down.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would say, you know, if I was having this problem in a relationship, I would say, look, do you want level 70 or do you want the cock?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you can't have both.
[SPEAKER_03]: I game and I get laid when I want it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's because you married a nerd.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: DMN, anything else you want to share?
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got to let some other people on.
[SPEAKER_03]: You need to tell Rob he parks like an asshole.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Rob, your parking sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why does my parking suck?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, when I was down... Oops, we lost the connection.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you would like to call us, our username is Orange Lounge Radio on Skype.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or you can give us a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's toll free in the United States.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, Rob can't hang up on me.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but I can unplug your mic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and I can steal yours and beat you in the head with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was that, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_06]: Ow, ow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn, it hurt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mike is like hardwired in that fucking mix board.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's because my powerful, awesome voice has fused it there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I totally owned Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry if I broke your arm.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll just have to give me a free massage.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll just have to give me a free massage from MassageTheRapist.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: I take my profession seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lodge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nah, you, uh, all that 2DX stuff that I've been hearing from, from Over the Pond.
[SPEAKER_06]: Over the Pond, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that whole Ghostbusters thing that kind of shocked us last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah, okay, what about it?
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: You also know that Bettson mentioned in a press release that they're supposed to be having, you know, one of their top guys said that they're supposed to be having a content update for Supernova.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're supposed to add 200 to 300 more songs into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: 200 to 300 more songs in DDR Supernova in the arcade?
[SPEAKER_01]: Show Bettson press release.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: This could be something they're announcing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think Konami's gearing up for lots of announcements this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've been kind of quiet, so I think we're going to get just blasted with stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think if that is true, you'll hear about it Thursday.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't hear about it then, or Friday, I don't know when the news is embargoed, but Thursday or Friday, if you don't hear after that, it probably wasn't true.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I could do it right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Watch.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll post it up on chat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, okay, but how often are things talked about that don't necessarily happen, such as Link Mode?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, that was never Konami or Benson's fault.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was because they got shafted by the people that were supposed to make the part for them.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so, you know, I was disappointed at first, but I let that slide because I have faith that Konami might find another way.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if they don't, so be it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, they'll eventually find an alternative.
[SPEAKER_01]: It won't be now, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably in the next... Alright, you been playing anything else besides Bomani lately?
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, more in the Groove R21, and I just played Drum Mania today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, let me rephrase.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you been playing anything that is not a music game?
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, Initial... I started playing Initial D today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's something.
[SPEAKER_06]: And in the arcade?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought the card and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: How is that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there a lot of competition in your neck of the woods?
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually traveled out of state today.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a tournament, so I managed to play, you know, in addition to other stuff, I just played, you know, I managed to get into Initial D while I was at it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it wasn't that much, but it's really hard to find an Initial D machine in Chinatown anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know one place, but I will make efforts to follow up on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, Zaku, your voice is breaking up a little bit, but thanks so much for calling in, as you always do, and we'll talk to you another time, alrighty?
[SPEAKER_06]: have a good one if you want to give us a call it's 1-877-GAME-OLR or it's username Orange Lounge Radio on Skype if you're sick of the same old people calling in week after week then you're not helping because you're not calling us so you should get on your telephone and give us a call right now it's 1-877-GAME-OLR otherwise it's going to be the same people get through every week or you can always leave us a voicemail because I know some folks can't listen live on Sunday and so they want to you know interact with us in other ways so
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess we'll do one more call.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll go over to this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you guys doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've already been on the show today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your voicemail.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I do what I can to help the show out.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love you guys and girls.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's fun to... You know, we had Freeze Pop, at least we had a casting from Freeze Pop about a year ago on the show, and it was very nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish them a lot of success.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're a good bunch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sweetness.
[SPEAKER_08]: I also hope you liked the voicemail I left you on your personal line.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: It cut out.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was it supposed to be?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I heard a couple notes.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were playing a song.
[SPEAKER_06]: It sounded like they were starting to play a song, but you were obviously indoors because it cut out.
[SPEAKER_06]: What were you trying to leave?
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's talk more rock.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, all I could hear, this is the voicemail.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like, this is for you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then that's all I could hear.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then it went, you know, cell phone drop.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might need to switch carriers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because when we played that, there were a few people that showed up with their Guitar Hero controllers.
[SPEAKER_08]: They moved towards the front and started, like, freestyling on the song.
[SPEAKER_06]: People showed up with their Guitar Hero controller to the Freeze Pop concert?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, one of my friends, Aaron, he got them to sign his controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty hardcore.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like that, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's rad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, anything else you want to share with us, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you have a good time at the concert overall?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I did, and I also picked up another video game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got Elite Beat Agents.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, Elite Beat Agents, one of my favorites from 06.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did you think?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not as easy as O and Don, but I'm enjoying it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait until the difficulty really ramps up as you go through it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I believe it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to finish the last song on easy.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, Ranma, thanks so much for the call, and thanks for the voicemails.
[SPEAKER_06]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: My friend Patty agrees with you, what you said about the whole Wii incident.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just letting you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, thanks for the support.
[SPEAKER_06]: Later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, thanks so much to all of our callers tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you didn't get through, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can always leave us a voicemail.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's 1-877-GAME-OLR when we're not live.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now I'm going to open it up to any last minute stories we have here in studio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any last minute stories from anyone?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, some interesting stuff for the PSP, including a brand new game coming to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: This should get Jamie happy, or very happy here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Happity.
[SPEAKER_07]: Happity, yes, very happity.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dracula X, Rondo of Blood.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is coming to the PSP, according to UK-based game magazine Play.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other stuff, though...
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're expecting Final Fantasy XIII this year, sorry to disappoint you, but that's not happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dream on.
[SPEAKER_06]: We all knew that.
[SPEAKER_07]: According to Tetsuya Nomura himself, he said it's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: He says, hopefully going to be out in 2008.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and that's even that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll probably get it late 2008 in Japan, and then we won't get it here until like 2019.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that'll be when I get a PlayStation 3, it'll be 2009.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: According to Midway, because I know they've had their Midway's Gamer Day, was actually last week, they had some info regarding the Midway Classics that are going to be on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, some of the pricing for that, Demon Slayer,
[SPEAKER_07]: is going to be $4.99 and should hit the PlayStation Store in the next few months.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it doesn't really say what are the other costs on like say for example the Mortal Kombat games or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they look good though.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have some screenshots actually online now of like Mortal Kombat and Rampart and Super Sprint and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what the hell this is but apparently there's this homebrew program called Mini VMAC for the DS where apparently they're running Mac OS on a DS which is so wrong but okay and then of course a PlayStation 3 ISO loader is being worked on right now and hopefully it'll be done soon they're in testing phase so Piracy on the PlayStation 3 coming soon
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure Sony's thrilled to hear that news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, you have anything for us last minute?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I just have my usual awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well then I guess that's going to do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey guys, thanks so much for tuning in to us, downloading it, and supporting independent internet radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We really appreciate it, and it is that support that keeps us going week after week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see you back here next week with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do believe there's some football game on TV, but we're not watching, so we'll be here Sunday night live, 6 o'clock Pacific to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Talk about more games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So until then, this is Rob Roberts for DarkSakura and Loki saying see you next time here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next week.