In the latest misreading and misapplication of the European Union's GDPR, Ubisoft has
an inactivity period for Ubisoft Connect where you may lose your account irretrievably. It's
a good thing my entire Ubisoft library exists in Steam because we've learned that Ubisoft
can't be trusted to manage reasonable accounting. At least Google had the consideration to refund
software and hardware charges. This is the latest death now for Connect. Now it's time
for your hosts, Rob Roberts, Jamie Summers, and Loki to tell you more about this story
and the rest of the week's gaming news. Starting right now on the show where every gamer has
a voice.
Hello, my friends out there on the internet. Welcome back to another week of the show where
every gamer has a voice. It is Orange Lounge Radio. We are live once again, July the 23rd,
2023 with episode number 968. Excuse me. No, that's wrong. The number's wrong. It's
episode 969 of our show. Wow. Whoever did that is totally fired. My name is Rob Roberts
and joining me as they do every single week here on the program, say hello to DarkSakura
or Jamie Summers.
Hi.
Hi. How are you?
I'll be fine when my meds kick in.
Yeah. Well, I've been there, done that, but I hope you do feel better.
Yeah, I'll be fine. It's just been an incredibly busy week and you know what? Incredibly busy
weeks yield me sleeping until 1.30 in the afternoon on my first day off.
I tried.
I still got up and did my ballet stuff.
I tried to sleep in yesterday and it wasn't happening. I don't know if it was the cats
or my natural body clock or what, but I could not. I needed, as I call him with Alan, I'm
out of salad pills to help me sleep. So I needed a salad pill to help me sleep and I
didn't have one, unfortunately.
I have my own things that I take for sleep that I'm actually thinking about finding something
better just because part of my condition is hypersomnia and I can have cataplexic moments
during the day. For anyone who doesn't know what cataplexy is, it's when your body just
kind of stops responding and loses its tension. You know, like people who randomly fall down
when they walk. You know, I'm not that severe, but it's been a lot worse and I have a suspicion
that part of the heat is to blame for that. But it's just a little bit like not good when
you're in the middle of working on something and suddenly your hand doesn't want to work
and then five seconds later, it's okay.
Well, let's also say hello to the one and only tech master, Loki.
Hello.
Hopefully you're doing a little better this week. Hope all is going well. I notice in
the background tonight as we do tape live every Sunday night at the voice geeks network,
twitch.tv slash vog network. That's VOG network. Nine o'clock Eastern, six o'clock Pacific
right after the Bobby Black Wolf show. I noticed behind you, you have the, I think that's the
original fallout or fallout to playing fallout. Yeah. All out. That's pretty good. What, what,
what made you think of the OG fallout tonight?
It's the closest thing I could get to Oppenheimer. So I see, I see. Will you be, will you be
flipping over to Barbie halfway through the show?
We've already done Barbie, but yeah, we could. I mean, it would be fair.
It would be fair. Yes, it would.
It's too bad. I can't like do like half Barbie half.
You that's what you need to set up. You need to set up OBS or whatever you're using on
a split screen and you're going to fall out on one side and Barbie horse adventure is
on the other. And there you go. You got your barb and Heimer.
My, yeah, my brain just went to Barb and Heimer as like this new, uh, uh, gestalt creature
that you have to like fight as an enemy where everything is, you know, you've got the Oppenheimer
on one side and then you have the Barbie on the other. So they're like a combination.
I can't make brain happen. That's fine. It's you, you can appreciate this though. As somebody
pointed out on the book of faces to me this week is that, um, the Barb and Heimer thing,
um, that already happened in the nineties. We've already been there. They called it tank
girl.
Oh, tank girl. Tank girl proceeds. I mean, tank girl, the comics. Yeah, no, I don't.
I know. Yeah. Although I love, I, I personally thought the tank girl movie was fine and I
was already a fan of the comics. Apparently. I don't know if this is true or not, uh, somebody
who's in tune with the movie news, like tire car, somebody in our discord needs to correct
me or whatever. I heard that Margot Robbie, of course, Barbie, and you know, lots of other,
um, really legendary characters in movies right now, including what else she's been,
been Harley Quinn, she's been Tanya Harding, Harding. So, uh, Margot Robbie apparently
has the rights to tank girl or has some sort of like, I mean, I can see that he doesn't
work directly with Hewlett. I would be pissed. I'm, I'm sure it would be respectful. Margot
Robbie's been pretty, pretty good for Hollywood. Honestly, I really can't complain. And then
bring iced tea out of retirement to play the ripper again. Yeah. Um, I, I, I, shockingly,
I have not seen Barbie or Oppenheimer. I probably, I doubt I'll see Oppenheimer, but I want to
see Barbie really bad, but I was hosting a show last night here locally. One of the burlesque
troop was doing their thing last night. So I just didn't get to the theater this weekend.
Did you go, Logie? No, I, I, I thought my wife wanted to see Barbie, um, which I would have
been fine with. Um, no, we didn't end up going. I'll probably go next week though. See, um, Ninja
turtles, but Oh, there you go. I want to see Barbie rub. I do too. So the problem, if you
want to go like for serious, we need to go Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday night, because remember I'm,
I'm flying to Atlanta on Thursday, so I'm out next weekend. Yeah. Well, Monday I don't have ballet
and I can always, I said I was going to stream at my normal time, but I can always switch stuff
around. I mean, um, for Barbie. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, for Barbie. And this is a perfect tie
into some streams I've done recently. I don't know. Have you, have you seen the cast of final
fantasy 16 on Twitter? Are we quick? Cause it's like, um, originally the Clive's voice actor,
Ben Starr did one. And now the guy that did, um, uh, Sid did one where they're going like one
ticket to Barbie, please. They're doing it in the final fantasy 16. I don't know why I don't know
who put him up to it. I don't know. Heard though that there are, there's like one
message that seems to have been slipping over people's heads. And that's that without spoiling
anything. Cause I had to go look up some context for this is that it reiterates this, um, narrative
that there has to be one group in charge over another group. And, uh, apparently I haven't
seen that coming from anybody else, but from what I know about it, that has actually seemed fairly
apt, uh, observance. Um, and so I really, really want to get the context out of it by seeing the
whole thing. Well, that's, I'm also waiting for cinema therapy to do an episode on it.
I was going to say, uh, I had a few friends see it and basically they said that it,
it ruined them. Um, in the sense that like they were extremely emotional afterwards and like
ugly crying and that type of stuff. Um, which is interesting. So I was like, Oh, okay.
But going, you know, piggybacking on what you said, dark soccer though, is that it,
it kind of makes this Barbenheimer phenomenon more interesting because usually you would expect
a lot of, you know, Oh, the movies are going up against each other, which movie is going to be
number one, which one's going to flop at the bottom. But this one's very much like, like
literally the two movies are uplifting each other. And like this whole, it's this wild phenomenon
that's happening with this thing, even though we've had counter programming or whatever you
want to call it before it's and people are already looking ahead. Now they're talking about, uh,
Saw Patrol because, uh, Saw 10 and Paw Patrol come out the same day.
Mike makes a good point out that it's like with Animal Crossing and Doom Eternal.
Yes. Yes. That is, that is a great point. Animal Crossing and Doom Eternal,
somebody else. I will say this right now. I will not see any Saw movies,
but I will in solidarity play a few pig matches in Dead by Daylight.
Perfect. Um, I was going to say there was also a great meme about, uh, the Dark Knight
and Mamma Mia also come, came out the same day. So, uh, the, what did they say? The Dark Mama
walked so Barb and Hymer could run. It's pretty good. I love it. I love it. It's great. Anyway,
at some point I'll get out and see the movies, but you know, just other stuff going on and
video games to play, but I do hope we can go see Barbie. The hot stuff also is very much a,
but I mean, I get going, the air, the theaters are always air conditioned and quite comfortable.
Usually. Usually. And practically have beds in them.
Yeah. Yeah. So it is nice. My problem these days is trying not to fall a fucking sleep
while I'm in a movie. Just put in massage chairs and I'll just die there. Okay.
Yeah. And by the way, just to, uh, follow up, uh, somebody in chat about the Margot Robbie
tank girl thing had said, Questbuster said, Margot Robbie's company has the rights.
So here's hoping, hoping so interesting fingers crossed.
All right. I just don't think that a proper tank girl movie can be done without Jamie Hewlett's
involvement. Um, and I was glad that there was a lot of, at least the artwork, I don't know if it
was him that did the art or artwork just in his direct style in the Lori Petty movie. But I mean,
if you want to know what else he gave us gorillas. Well, and a Lori Petty cameo would be mandatory
in whatever they do. Like mandatory. I love Lori. Unless she says no, but why would she say no?
Yeah. Anyway, of course, nothing is happening if they don't resolve that SAG-AFTRA strike as
well as the writer's Guild strike. So, um, obviously here's hoping that, um, the studios
will fucking cave on this bullshit, especially regarding AI and all this and give the actors
the fair contract they're looking for. So, you know, solidarity with those that are protesting.
We'll get some exec thinking he can write or, you know, hiring someone on Fiverr.
Yeah. Which by the way, I, I want to, um, you know, it is a gaming show and I want to get
into video game news, but all this stuff is important. Well, number one, if you didn't
already know, video game stuff is not part of the SAG-AFTRA strike. So like, for example,
I've been talking about my trip to Atlanta Southern Fried Game Expo, and I'm going to be,
lucky enough to moderate a panel with Nintendo voice actors from some of the recent Nintendo
games who voice act Bowser, as well as Princess Peach, Princess Rosalina. Um, and it's not the,
don't confuse it with a movie. These are the games, you know, dating way back. Um,
and some people are like, can you even talk about that? Yes, we can. I do not know if these folks
are members of SAG-AFTRA or not. I am assuming they are because I think voice acting merged
into that some time ago. And that's also why SAG and the voice actors already negotiated a strike
a couple of years ago. You may recall that there was a video game strike that I want to say was
threatened. I think it did go through, but only for a couple of weeks. I don't think it lasted
very long. Um, so, uh, video games are not part of what is being struck right now. So with
conventions and stuff, they are allowed to promote and talk about games. They're just not allowed to
talk about any movies that they may be affiliated with. So, uh, there's that. Yeah. Bobby Blackwell
says SAG has a separate voice actor contract. There's many, many, many different, um, types of,
you know, contracts and so forth. And so, uh, but obviously, you know, we, we hope by the time
Dragon Con rolls around or, cause you know, San Diego Comic-Con has already had to deal with it
this weekend is that you can't ask actors about their projects. Um, which, you know, is
understandable. You want to support the strike, but at the same time, it's like, Oh, this is,
this is a difficult line to walk. So hopefully in the next few weeks, uh, the studios will cave in
and, um, you know, get this AI bullshit out of here along with the other it's, I know AI is the
only thing I'm kind of laser focused on, but there's many other elements of the contract too.
And there's, you know, all the information out there on the internet, if you want to look it up.
Um, so yeah, uh, be interesting to see what comes of all that. Um, okay. I really do want to get
into some gaming news though. I want to talk a little bit about the recent Diablo four patch.
And the reason why I want to bring this up at the top of the show is that this really goes beyond
just one game. Um, this is more about the reaction to this and everything that's going on as well as
the patch itself. Loki, I don't know if you want me to talk about this or you want, you want to
do this? Cause I'm not familiar with it. Okay. That's fine. I'll talk about it. Other than
patch, bad walk back patch. Yeah. Uh, I know Diablo four is a little more of my camp and
that's fine. So I'll talk about this. So here's what's happened is that there was a patch that
went out this week in preparation for season one. Keep in mind that seasons are not new to Diablo.
They exist in Diablo three and Diablo two remastered. Um, it's all about kind of restarting
the character from scratch that everybody's on the same playing field. And usually there's unique
rewards to the season. It's kind of, kind of a reason to start playing again. It's kind of
a different way of doing like prestiging, if you will. Um, controversial with Diablo four is the
fact that they're doing a battle pass, uh, with the seasons, but the battle pass is a hundred
percent cosmetic. There's nothing in the battle pass that is, you know, actually affecting game
mechanics. Well, I take that back, but there is something in it, but the rewards are on the free
tier that affect, um, the season specific mechanics, but those rewards are on the free
tier. So the paying for it will not change that. Um, but, uh, either way, whether you wanted to pay
for the battle pass or not actually, and if you got a limited edition version of the game, you
already have the battle pass, which you can redeem in any season technically, but I don't know why
you wouldn't redeem it in season one. I don't see what's going to be better or different about
season two, but it is your choice. At the end of the day, you do, you do you. Um, but the pre-patch
before season one, so season one started Thursday and a pre-patch went live earlier this week.
And people did not respond positively to this patch because some of the things that they were
doing in this patch were a lot of character nerfs. They were doing a lot of, you know,
different powers on, uh, different characters who were being nerfed and rolled back. And one
of the biggest things that they were nerfing was experience. They actually were rolling back some
different types of experience. Um, I want to actually see if I can get the patch notes
actually up here. Unfortunately, this article I thought would have them didn't, but let me see
if I can grab them real quick here. Um, sorry. I'm, uh, should have had that up beforehand.
Uh, but in the pack, cause I want to cite some specifics here if I can. Okay. Yes, this is it.
So I'm going to go over to, for those of you watching live on Twitch, we're going to hop over
to the other screen so you can see these with me here. Okay. So they set up some things for the
actual, you know, season that this whole mechanic that's unique to the season. Okay. And then they
talk about, all right, they're doing, you know, some things with the items and so forth and,
you know, bug fixes, the usual types of things you would expect. But then when you really start
to get down into it, you start to get some interesting updates. Um, for example, there's
some renown value upgrades. This is good because it actually up the amount of renown you get from
doing side quests, which is, um, helps you get rewards that are locked behind that. Okay. But
this was one of the big things level scaling in dungeons was adjusted. Um,
monsters start to trail behind the player and level at a certain point. And this change does not
affect this, but what happens is that let's say, uh, at world tier three, if you are below 55,
the levels 55, that, uh, the experience, this is what I wanted to get to pre season. If the
mobs were one level higher, you get 15% extra three levels higher, 25% extra. They change this
now you only get a 1.5% bonus. So the amount of extra experience you get for the mobsters being
higher level than you is kind of not worth it. And one reason they were trying to do this is
they were trying to actually make it so that if you are playing with your friend, so if you're
level one and your friends want to bring you right to the end game to power level you, that trick is
not going to work anymore. So now you're only going to get, so before you would get level 100
monster XP, which is a lot and a 25% bonus on top of that. Now you get an 11 monster XP and
a small bonus on top of that. Now, Mike Defton chat says, this one is fair. I agree. They're
trying to avoid a situation here. Like what happens in Diablo three seasons. And what happens
in Diablo three seasons right now is that people just the first person that gets to level 70 power
levels, all of their friends. And it kind of takes away the leveling experience. A fundamental thing
you have to understand that is a difference between Diablo three and four is that the word
Paragon means something very different. In Diablo three Paragon levels were basically like boundary
breaking levels. You were at the max level and Paragon levels go on and on and on for infinity
and boundary break. People want to rush into that stage of the game. In Diablo four, that is not the
case. Levels 50 to 100 are Paragon levels, but they're just extra levels. They're not exactly a
boundary break. Most people see level 100 as the boundary. Blizzard does not really play this any
differently, because they keep talking about the race to level 100, the first hardcore character
to 100 and all of this stuff. So you have to remember that Diablo three and four are set up
differently. And that's why I don't find this such a big deal because Blizzard is basically trying
to say you're not going to cheat your way to level 100. You need to play your way through the game.
But what's a little weird to me is that the way they did this, like a normal way I would level
playing solo would be to do nightmare sigil dungeons three levels above where I was at,
because that's about you know what you can do solo and you would get a 25% bonus. But for some reason
you can't do that anymore. I'm not sure why they changed that because I mean that doesn't really
affect the power level game. But all right, I mean, I'm gonna respect their decisions and so
forth. And I'll just say, okay, well, then you just do, you know, nightmare sigils that are around
your own level and so forth, whatever. It's just an interesting way to play the game. And then they
talked all about these other balance updates. And there's a lot if you want to look at everything
they changed with, you know, barbarian and so you can go into the patch notes look, but overall,
people were not pleased with all these nerves. But I also understand why they made some nerves
because you got to go all the way back. This season mechanic that they're putting in
the season of the malignant, malignant hearts are being added to the game, these are going to give
you extra power, they needed to do some nerves to accommodate for the extra powers that are going
to be coming with malignant hearts, so that you can't just raffle stomp your way through the game.
And again, people burning their way all over the level 100 right off the top. So I'm not going to
say that like there are some things in the patch that didn't quite make sense. But I don't think
this was really the OMG, the world is ending thing that some of the Diablo community made it out to
be. Disclaimer, I'm also not a level 100 player. So I can imagine that there are a lot of people
that were in end game theory crafting the numbers playing end game, not happy to see these nerves,
because it's going to feel like a setback before they really have a chance to experience the
malignant hearts and all of this stuff. So I thank you, Dr. C says I'm by no means a Diablo expert.
So I definitely appreciate my the perspective from folks that know better. I am by no means
Diablo expert either, but I'm a fan. And I'm trying to take a step back and go okay,
as in most cases, is this as bad as the internet is making it out to be on social media?
And the answer as far as I'm concerned is not quite. There are some question marks and there
are some weird things. But I don't think this was the worth the meltdown that people were having
over this. But nevertheless, when I say meltdown, I mean review bombing. So of course, here we go
with the Metacritic review bombs again, as if Metacritic user reviews should mean a goddamn
thing at this point, because this is what always happens to Metacritic user reviews. Don't read
them, don't trust them. They're, they're nothing. So Blizzard then also actually did a little round
table with associate game director Joe Paporia, game director Joe Shealy and community chief Adam
Fletcher, they did, they threw this together, really, they did a live event on Friday,
to try to address what happened. And they actually said in a quote here, Adam Fletcher said,
it's not the greatest play experience for players out there. We don't plan on doing a patch like
this ever again. We hear you loud and clear. Joe Paporia followed up, we know that reducing player
power is never a good experience. Sometimes we just don't get it quite right. So they went on
to detail some of the things that they're going to change. And part of that is the XP adjustment.
So the road from 50 to 100 is not going to be quite as rough as it was before. There's going
to be you know, there were some things that they're going to fix with hot fixes that were
unintended, like world tier level changes, they weren't supposed to change. And so they were able
to hot fix some of that and all this stuff. As you want to Matt and chat says seems like part
of their strategy is trying to slow the burn a little bit. Some of those balances did make sense.
Yes, there is a part of this where they're trying to slow the burn. Absolutely. And so again, I'm
not saying that like, the player base that got angry had no reason to be upset. I think it was
just maybe a little blown out of control. Anyway, in chat from quest Buster says I was not happy at
all after making it to 100 and then stacking hours on top of that to farm gear to perfect said build
and then have this patch disrespect the time I spent was not a great feeling. I was upset,
but then I just walked away from the game and I'm taking a break, which honestly,
is probably the best thing to do in this scenario. Like when it's affecting your mood like that.
I think that's very smart to recognize I should take a step back away from the game and do all
this thing. And I can see where it gets frustrating needing getting to 100 and having all this change.
But I'm kind of curious if you see yourself coming back to play the season at some point
to see what the game looks like at level 100. With this new season mechanic thing in there.
I'm kind of I just I'm kind of would be curious about this. So anyway, that's in a nutshell all
that's going on this week with Diablo four is just again, I see this as bigger than just Diablo
because again, you have the user base the fans making so much noise about this that they they
caused the community to really jump and do a unplanned roundtable about the patch after the
fact. And then you know, basically admit to we need to communicate better in the future, which
I would say that's better than most gaming companies are doing Niantic right now when it
comes to some of this feedback. So Zen monkey 11 and chat says all this season stuff games do now
is just annoying and stupid to me. Well, thank fortnight. Because now you have a lot of games
that are doing this. And to be fair with the season stuff again, season play existed in Diablo
three, but it didn't exist at the beginning. They did add it later on. There was no battle pass,
though. So that's also another thing that felt very different about Diablo three. To my follow
up question, he doesn't cost 60 $70 either. That's true, too. And that's a fair point.
questbuster and chat says I'm on the fence. I've been toying with playing a necro, which I should
have done from the start, which got off relatively unscathed. Plus, I like minion classes. You know,
what's funny is I am playing a necromancer in the season, but I'm doing the bone spear build where
you you don't have any you sacrifice all your minions for bonuses. So kind of kind of a
different way to do things. So anyway, I thought that was kind of interesting. And, you know,
we'll see how this develops and the Blizzard communicating with their player base. Again,
I know some people are still angry about stuff, but I still feel like they're doing more here
than most game companies are doing right now. And you know, again, a lot of that is probably things
they've had to learn from the past and some of the missteps with Wow, Overwatch, etc. Pretty much all
the Blizzard games have had a problem patch at some point for sure. So Zen monkey says I just
like four seasons once they go past four and get into season 25. I'm like WTF This is dumb lol.
Diablo threes on season 28 right now. So speaking of which, so I don't know what season Fortnite's
in. Fortnite hides it though, because don't they reboot don't they reboot the world and then they
call it like chapter four or something? Well, they have they have seasons in like, chapters,
I think or something like that. So there's different like events that go on throughout
the year, but then they like do like a like a massive reset and stuff. But it's usually
progressive, like a storyline and they have a big finale and then it's like the brand new season.
And Dark Soccer and I talk a lot about Dead by Daylight. And essentially, the tomes are season
events in that game, you know, so it's it's what's present in a lot of games these days and a lot of
genres. So but you don't, you also don't really have to buy anything to redeem them, you can use
iridescent shards that you run by playing the game. So it doesn't necessarily require real
money. Yeah. Not that I'm not gonna spend real money to do it. And the iridescent shards can
take a while depends how much you play. I mean, if you play a lot, then yeah, you probably will
get enough. So well, I don't know I use mine for blood points like all the time. Ah, here.
All right. Well, speaking of our gaming weeks, whether it be Diablo, DVD or otherwise, let's
talk about our gaming weeks in our kickoff segment. How was your gaming week? Dark Sakura,
how was your game? Mine was actually fairly eventful. So I did switch to going back to
retro games on my Saturday stream. And so I am playing live live. And I'm playing the original
and playing the Super Famicom version. I have a translation of it. And I am absolutely loving it.
I made it through the caveman scenario and pretty much laughed the whole time. I also played
Oh, gosh, what was the Kirby game on Super Nintendo? The one that was multiple Kirby
games. I always forget the name of it because there's so many different Kirby games. But I
played the Japanese one of it. Superstar. Yeah, I played Hoshino Kabi played through a little bit
of it got through the wispy woods fight. You know, it was pretty fun. Basically, I was just
I was testing out my new controller. I played Strider two for PlayStation. Super deluxe. Thank
you, Mike. If anyone knows this mic. But I played through a couple of stages of Strider two. I played
through Jackie crush for also for Super Famicom. I played super fantasy zone, which was the version
of fantasy zone that came out on the Sega Mega Drive aka Genesis. Just about a few other things,
I was trying to just make sure the ones that said were translated were actually translated.
And some were some were not played a little radiant silver gun. You know, I tried to get
bots a gun working and I couldn't get it to work. So I'm back to the drawing board on that.
But, um, I also of course, played a significant amount of dead by daylight. And I words we had
some pretty fun things happen. Um, we, I had a peekaboo with with a Bubba.
It was actually really cute. And I did make a clip of that one just because it was so cute.
Um, like Bubba surprised me most of the time you expect to be face camping, basement camping,
trolling, you know, tunneling shitheads. And then you find the one Bubba who's just like,
I'm gonna fun Bubba fun. Yeah, fun Uncle Bubba. Oh, nevermind that I'm wearing somebody else's
face. It's no one you know. Isn't it cages Tuesday? Yes, I think that's fun. I'm definitely
gonna be every every match is gonna be for Nick cages for a bit. Well, three Nick cages and the
person who didn't want to buy the DLC. Well, um, I am not going to be playing him right off the
bat, I think unless I'm just going to go ahead and get the adapt out of the way. But his perks
are pretty Mimi. Um, like, I don't even know I think I'm gonna have fun. But I'm also looking
forward to his red carpet cosmetic that's coming out the studded jacket. And the 50 bajillion
voice lines. I watched a video that was all of his voice lines. I guess I should say I listened
to the video. There's a lot of shits and fucks out there. Lots of them. And not at the same time,
by the way, but usually in the same sentence. Um, I played with some word scapes, you know,
my usual little, you know, what I play when I'm not doing anything else game.
Excuse me, that's, that's that. Um, my, my schedule for the week is changing a little
bit because I don't have ballet on Monday. So I'm going to be able to go a little bit
later continuously on Monday, and then I'm doing a marathon on Sunday when we should be doing a while
are good times 1130 to 1130. I'm gonna just pass out when I'm done, I think.
All right. Oh, and apart from gaming, my eye infection is healing. Finally,
it's hard to play games when your eye is like constantly watering. It's kind of gross.
Uh, Loki, how was your game week?
Um, it was all Minecraft again. So I went ahead and was working more on my final three episodes.
There was a lot of like other work to like do infrastructure stuff for later on the season.
So I had to do a lot of that this week. But I'm hoping to get I was hoping to get it done today,
but it's probably going to be early next week. And then we also checked out MCC Island,
because there's this whole thing for so let's back up a bit. So MCC is minecrafter
or Minecraft creator clash. It's a event that they do every I don't know how often it is
pretty often at least once a month with like really popular Minecraft creators, like the
biggest creators out there. And then last year, I think it was last year, maybe two years ago,
they did this MCC rising where they they're like, Okay, plebes out there, we're gonna,
we're gonna let you play with the big boys a little bit. So you just submit your application.
And maybe if you're lucky, you'll, we'll let you in and you'll do your own event. So that's what's
happening. So we created one of our new members for season three on channel 64
was enticing us to, you know, get involved. So he put together a application video. So we did that
we have a team of four now. And we went and checked out MCC Island and I suck at everything
on there. It is not my style of gameplay. So like parkour PvP stuff, like it's just,
I always have to play more of it, I guess. But yeah, basically, you had they're gonna
pick 10 different teams out of these application videos. Last time, I think there was like 3200
videos submitted to them. So obviously a lot but assuming you get in everything, you know,
you may eventually get involved with the regular MCC as well, if you place pretty high in the MCC
Rising stuff. So it's a good way to, I guess, get your foot in the door, some of these people,
you know, end up on like empires and stuff like that. Some of these big things because you have,
you know, hermitcraft, the empires folks, dream, I mean, they're all like involved with MCC. So
it's all the biggest, the biggest creators in that space. But I suck at all of it. So it'll be great.
I had such a horrible time in MCC Island, but apparently it's harder than the actual game too.
But it's just different. I'm just not used to playing that kind of stuff. But it's also
a super long shot. Anyways, we had fun making the videos. So that was fine. I don't really hear
either way promoting it. So I was a little more curious what that was all about. So yeah, thanks
for elaborating. Yeah, yeah. So yeah, it's usually pretty fun. I mean, I don't know, like, they,
assuming you get in what they do, they have a coach that they'll give you. So they'll be one
of the MCC players will actually coach you through the games and stuff like that and get you ready.
The actual event takes place at the end of next month. So it'll be a very short turnaround. I
don't know how they go through 3000 some videos. I suspect that a lot of it's not the video and
some amount of subs you got because looking at the people from last year, it's like, Oh,
these small creators with only 1 million subscribers are going to participate. It's like,
come on. Like that's a little Do they really need help? I don't know. But we'll see. We'll see what
happens. I gotcha. All right. Well, good luck. My gaming week. I already kind of talked about
Diablo four. I am playing the season in Diablo four and I'm playing necromancer and up to level
38. I think just I just cleared the season quest today because there's a whole little quest that
goes to the season. Some of it's level gated because you have to clear some strongholds.
You can't really do until level 35. So it was gated a little bit, but I just got through that
whole quest. So that was, uh, it was neat that, you know, they didn't have that Diablo three
where you would have unique storylines in the season. So I thought that was good. I mean,
it wasn't in depth, but it had voice acting and a movie at the beginning. So I was like, okay,
that's kind of neat that they went all out with that. So, uh, that was cool. Um, I'll probably
keep playing the season for sure. I don't know if I'll get all the way up to level 100, but I,
I'm through a good chunk of the battle class pass. Granted, I use, you know, cause I had
limited edition. I got my free accelerated battle pass, which gave me 20 levels,
but I'm up to like tier 39 or 40. So, um, you know, kind of gone a long way through.
So I'll probably keep going. They have the season journey, which they had in Diablo three,
which were kind of like steps and they help get you like big chunks of battle pass, uh, stuff.
So I'll, I'll probably work on that a little bit. So that'll be something that I do in the coming
weeks. And, um, other games I've played, uh, I also played, um, Overwatch randomly,
a friend of mine, um, when it wanted to play games together. And it was one of those things
where we realized this is a game that we have in common. So I played a little bit of Overwatch.
We had some really good matches, uh, last week, but, uh, today we played some more and had some
not so great matches, but that's okay. Cause I feel like I'm not as big of a flop as I thought
in Overwatch. Um, especially when it comes to support classes, like I find that like playing
Lucio and mercy kind of like the, you know, the ones that have been there. My friend is kind of
forcing me to learn Ana, which I'm not very good with the snipers, but I'm kind of forcing myself
to learn Ana cause her toolkit is really useful. So, um, that's been interesting. I never thought
I'd get back into Overwatch, but, and I'm really only doing it for my friend, but, um, it's, um,
it doesn't suck. So there's that. Um, and then the other game, I feel the need to talk about
this week is something that got released that a lot of people are talking about this week.
Cause it's kind of game adjacent, but it's not really a game. It's an app. It's a little thing
called Pokemon sleep, uh, came out and, uh, you know, we've been kind of, this has been on our
radar a little bit because, you know, we like Pokemon and there's been a lot of like WTF,
why are they doing like a sleep thing? Like why, why, why is Pokemon sleep like a thing? Um,
and so Pokemon sleep finally came out this week and, um, I'm gonna review it here on the show by
saying, um, I don't fucking get it. And, uh, I've, I did it twice and I don't plan to do it ever
again. Um, I, I don't understand the point. I failed. Maybe I'm just old. Um, but this,
this is really, I, this is pointless. It's absolutely pointless. If you want to track,
not true. If you want to track your sleep, there are plenty of ways to do it
through Android or iOS. And if you have a smart watch, whether that be an Apple watch or, you
know, whatever watch it is you have, I guarantee there are sleep trackers that do it better than
what Pokemon sleep is doing with your phone, sitting on the corner of your bed and this whole
thing. But, but they, they're, they're able to, it's very important data that they're collecting.
They're collecting the sound of your loud farts. That's right. Apparently also get picked up by it.
That's right. It records you while you're asleep. Now you could turn that off. Cause
that is very creepy. And it's actually, it's very easy to turn that off. So in all fairness,
like the recording thing, cause a lot of people look at that and go, what the fuck? But you can,
you can turn that off like real easy. Like the game kind of goes out of its way really to have
you, this is how we're going to make the next Wario game that much better. They're forcing the
fart noises. I guess. And Mike Deaf says, Pokemon sleep is not there to replace whatever you use
already for sleep tracking. It's there to incentivize people who want to improve their
sleep. That's, that's what the existing sleep trackers are supposed to do. I'm sorry. I just,
I'm going to tell you why there's again, like a lot of Pokemon games that come out, I feel it's
very messy. There's a lot of stuff like all over the place. Like, okay, you got to cook things for
Snorlax. And when you have the Pokemon, you'll get these random Pokemon that show up while you're
asleep and you can choose one of them to give a biscuit. Cause you're trying to make them your
friends so you can add them to the party and then they collect things in your party. And they, you
also have photographs that go on and then you want to check in three times a day, not just when you
sleep. Cause you want to cook the curries for Snorlax to gain the power. Everything I just
named is an actual thing in the game. And it doesn't make any goddamn sense. It doesn't.
And it's just, it's just one of those things where it's like, I w well plus also, okay,
so you get all these Pokemon. Why it doesn't connect to the other, is it going to connect
to Pokemon home at some point? If it does, then I, then I will shut up because then that makes a lot
more sense because it actually ties into the rest of the Pokemon universe. But otherwise it doesn't
like, like I've heard like, Oh, you can get shinies through this. I'd be fucking pissed
if I got a shiny in this game and I couldn't transfer it over to Pokemon home to actually
use in a real Pokemon game. So I don't know. Mike Deft says, it's really simple for me.
It's not that convoluted. I'm sorry, Deft. You know, I love you. I'm bringing the receipts.
I'm bringing the receipts because I just, I I'm bringing it. I still have it on my phone,
although I plan to delete. Is it going to yell at me for not tracking the last couple of nights?
Probably. But okay. So yeah, I got, I got power for doing something and now Snorlax is like,
yay, I'm gonna, okay. I guess I went up a level. I did something, whatever. I got rewards. I have
no idea what these do. Here's, it's another rating. I have no idea what this does. Okay.
So there's that. And then there's another rating for your Snorlax there. So there's all the Snorlax
and then there's all these other Pokemon. So like I somehow have a Pichu and a Pikachu in my party.
And now look, you have all these buttons that do shit down here in the corner, the main menu. And
when you go to the main menu, look at this. God damn it. Now I'm getting more tips. Okay. You go
to the main menu and look at this. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine,
10, 11 buttons that all do different things. I heard you. Nevermind. I misheard what you
just said. What did you think I said? I thought you said you got tits.
Well, maybe I did. No, I did not. But anyway, my point is, is it a sleep tracker or is it a
micromanagement game? Because I'll tell you, it's a micromanagement game. And there, and again,
I want my micromanagement game to have somewhat of a point. There is, I guess, a friends feature,
but I connected it to Facebook. Nobody added me as a friend. And then when I went back in to see if
any of my friends were on it, it said, you need to reconnect to Facebook. So I was just like,
I'm, I'm over this. I'm over this already. I don't get the point. I have a sleep tracker.
I've been running it for quite some time. If you want to see how horribly I sleep,
it's this lovely little thing that I have that shows me. So last night I got some pretty decent
sleep, but actually shows me like how it went and all that good stuff. So that's what I use.
Here's the thing. Maybe I would feel a little differently.
If the game would just tap into the existing data that my watch is already giving it.
Why does it need to do its own separate thing by lying on the bed and inferior way of tracking
sleep as opposed to something that can measure your heart rate regularly? I don't understand
that. And I do realize there is a separate device that you can also buy and all this,
I'm still not going to track your heart rate. So it's just, it's wild. So I'm not a fan.
If you're a fan, congratulations. I hope you catch all the Pokemon and then won't be able
to do anything with them. But you'll feel really good. And that's the point. That's the point.
Yeah. We didn't even touch on monetization. There is monetization.
Oh, of course.
I, I can't tell you what it is because the minute I saw it, I was like, I'm, I will,
I will never give this game money. So I didn't even look into what it did anyway.
So that's, that's, that's my thought. So, okay. My dev says the dev say they would like to connect
with other existing apps or devices for sleep tracking. Great. I will be happy to amend my
review at that point, as it stands now, hard pass. In fact, it's coming off my phone. So that's that,
that little bit of me playing it right there is the last you're going to get for a little bit.
I love what SSU100Matt said in chat over at twitch.tv slash vog network.
S2 100 Matt says bigger menu than the cheesecake factory. Yes.
But no complimentary bread. What's up with that?
All right. That was my gaming week. Let's get into some gaming news and what's going on around
the industry. We will start off with, Oh, and real quickly, just I've plugged it a lot, but I'm
legally required to say I will be at Southern fried gaming expo this weekend in Atlanta.
It is running the 28th through the 30th of July at the Marriott Renaissance Waverly hotel.
That is right by the Atlanta brave stadium, if you weren't already aware. So if you are somewhere in
the Atlanta area or even a little far, I encourage you to drive in, say hello. I'll be doing a panel
Sunday at one o'clock featuring Nintendo voice actors. I'm really excited to be there,
play a hell of a lot of video games and just have a good time. It's just going to be a fun weekend.
And then I'm looking forward to going right back in five more weeks for dragon con. I'm racking up
those frequent flyer miles, except I'm taking two different airlines for some reason. Well,
I know the reason why this trip I used reward points. The other trip, Alan and I are going,
so we bought Southwest. So yeah, anyway. All right, let's move on into some other
gaming news and what all is going on. So Loki, we'll start with you.
Yeah, so the end of the show last week, we talked a little bit about how game pass cores and be
replacing Xbox Live Gold. And we got some more details on that shortly after our show ended.
So basically, the four different tiers that they have now, they're all going to be game pass. So
game pass cores, basically what Xbox Live Gold was the main difference being that you're not going to
be getting the two games a month that they had previously. But instead, it's going to be kind of
a catalog of 25 high quality games, they say on console. So it's kind of like a smaller
library that you would have with the normal game pass. And that's $10 a month, they have the console
game pass, which is $11 a month. And then of course, you kind of know what that is PC, of
course, the PC game pass for 10 bucks, and then ultimate for 17 a month. And what games are going
to be coming with that collection? Well, they we do know what those are. And they said new titles,
and they said new titles we added two or three times a year. So some of the things in there
Among Us Dishonored 2, Doom Eternal, Fable Anniversary, Fallout 4, Fallout 76, Forza Horizon
4, that's awesome. Gears 5, Grounded, Halo 5 Guardians, Halo Wars, Psychonauts 2, Ori and the
Will of the Wisps, State of Decay and The Elder Scrolls Online, Tamriel Unlimited. And then of
course, there's some other stuff in there as well. Among Us, for example. So not a bad library.
But yeah, so obviously, I think they're trying to entice people to just spend the extra dollar
and just get game pass. But if you don't want to, you don't have to and if you are an existing
Xbox Live Gold member, your membership will convert to game pass core on September 14.
Um, so some real talk for a minute, the free games they've been given away on Xbox Live Gold have not
exactly been scraping that bottom of the barrel for a while, some decent indie titles in there.
But let's be real, there is no showstoppers. Let's usually use that word. There's no showstopper
like get like attention grabbing giveaway they've done on Xbox Live Gold in a long time.
This allows the system to pivot to something where they can have some big names. A lot of
those names you just read right there can have some big names that are available. And of course,
are they available on cloud too? When you do this? I think that's a huge question. No,
because core is not cloud ultimate is the only one that has cloud play. So yeah, if you want,
I mean, I think the argument is that you would want to probably just have the regular game pass
if you're playing on console. It's only $1 more a month. Yeah, I mean, really for, you know,
25 versus hundreds of games and all the brand new like Microsoft games coming in there as well. Like
it just, it makes sense to do that. But I mean, if you're really looking not to spend that extra
dollar a month, I mean, it's already $10 a month. You just want quite a bit. You just want Madden
multiplayer. That's all you want life. You don't want anything else, then you there you go. You can
save the extra buck. Yeah. But yeah, I mean, the sj 100 match in chat says Yeah, I haven't touched
the games with gold games since pre game pass. I keep forgetting to download those people echo and
say same, same, same. The sometimes the only reason I remember the PlayStation ones with the
PlayStation ones have actually been kind of better like Alan Wake remastered I was actually really
excited about that. So like, but but PlayStation if you have the app will send you a push notification
and remind you, hey, it's not too late to grab Microsoft does not do that. Yeah. So it is kind
of nice. So but yeah, I this doesn't really surprise me. I'm surprised that the term Xbox
Live is going away. That is a little bit, you know, weird and like, Oh, wow, that was such,
you know, especially when that rolled out. If you think about it, this show has I mean, I don't like
to toot our own horn too much. But to to folks for a minute. This show has now seen the birth
and the death of Xbox Live. And that is wild to me. We were here when Xbox Live started,
it wasn't that long into the show was like six months after we started our and now here we are
at the end, which is wild to me. So but I mean, everything that game pass is doing and especially
when we talk about you know, the cloud gaming and the Netflix style model of video games,
it makes sense. It is the future of games. So I'm not surprised. So online multiplayer is not
quite the name brand future feature, even though they all charge for it, the name brand feature
that it used to be so I get that they're, you know, compiling it all into one program, but it
does it feels a little weird with Xbox Live. But such such as life things change things rebrand.
It happens. All right. Well, speaking of things change, you might remember last week on the show,
we were talking about towards the end of the show that like, hey, by the time we kind of get to
the show next week, we're going to be looking at emerged activism, Blizzard, Microsoft,
psych, here we are. It's been a week that did not have years later. I know, right? Well,
apparently an extension has happened, but it's only a two month extension. Here's what happened.
So they were supposed to hit that target of July 18 to merge the companies. But because of the CMA
over in the UK, the competition in the markets authority because of that block still being in
place, and they have not found that workaround yet, even though now they are past all the hurdles
in the US. So you know, even with the FTC turn up, it's done. It's going to happen in the US,
the UK CMA is the sole holdout. But because they haven't worked that out yet, they have
made an agreement. So Microsoft, Activision, and the CMA have actually basically extended that,
you know, it's going to take, I guess the extended of the deadline for the final decision is now
August 29. So because of that, Microsoft and Activision are going to extend their completion
deadline further out. There's big penalties if the companies do not merge. And I don't think that's
because of a court thing. I think that's because if Microsoft pulls out of the deal, there'd have
to be a huge fee paid. I don't see us going down that bridge. This is now about what is the UK
going to do and what does Microsoft soon to be Activision Blizzard do in response?
Because if the CMA does not reverse their decision, I think we're likely to see
some pullout in the UK, which could be very, very, very interesting.
But as of now, nope, no merged company. And now we may have to wait till the end of August. So
maybe by the time we get to Labor Day, we'll finally be talking about this. Goodness.
All right. Well, speaking of decisions in the UK that are a pretty big deal,
Dark Soccer, what do you have for us?
Well, the UK has been deliberating over what to do about the whole loot box situation. Is it
gambling? Is it a gateway drug, slippery slope, blah, blah, blah. Some countries have already
flat out banned them like Belgium and the Netherlands. But their culture secretary,
Nadine Dorries, said that because they were still gathering evidence,
they said direct government intervention may risk unintended consequences. And that's a quote.
So they've actually agreed on some principles. So the first is a commitment to make available
technological controls to restrict anyone under 18 from acquiring a loot box without consent or
knowledge of a parent or guardian. So a lot of the controls are already there, but they're not
used very widely. So these would basically set up a best practice for parents. And then a second is
to make people more aware of these controls of the public information campaign and setting up a panel
to share, again, those best practices. Basically, game companies will have to disclose the presence
of their loot boxes before someone chooses to buy a game. And the games will have to show clear
probabilities before they buy a loot box. So basically, they also are working to enact more
lenient refund policies for these. And then they also want to tackle the black market that's around
loot box purchases. They are going to be monitoring it for the next 12 months
and seeing what the results is.
Interesting.
Apparently, there's people who already have an addiction to loot boxes,
who have taken out loans to get content in games via loot boxes.
Yeah.
And it really, for them, it is the same as a gambling addiction.
Interesting. I did not realize, I mean, I was gonna say I did not realize there was a black market
around loot boxes. But yes, of course, there is because I do remember years ago, you got to way
back when everybody was getting their Xbox 360s hacked. That was all part of loot boxes on the
black market. They were buying EA FIFA packs, and doing shady stuff with that and selling those
accounts. So interesting. I just never thought of black market regulation as a part of it. But I
guess that's some good news in that.
Or even people selling, you know, their systems with save files on it, because it has
out of print material on it, like the PT thing with PlayStations.
Or a flappy bird on a phone. Yeah, it's true. It's true.
Which came back. I mean, people are gullible. But I mean, it's just more or less opening the door
for exploitation. And people are always going to jump on it.
Yeah, it's true.
You can't regulate greed. You can only curb it via regulation.
Good point. Comment from message when I'm 100. Matt in chat says, got to be honest, I kind of
missed the loot boxes in Overwatch, not the buying part. But getting the boxes and getting the random
skins and so forth were a lot more fun than the battle pass thing. I might agree with that,
actually, is that like the battle pass is kind of meh. I think it really depends on the game,
though. It really depends on the game. Like I if they did loot boxes and dead by daylight, I'd be
annoyed. So but Overwatch, it doesn't bother me. So I would, I would wish they had they'd have a
system similar to among us. I, you know, I had just started playing that last week. And I like
the progression system where you earn points. And then you kind of like, it's almost like a skill
tree, the unlock stuff as you go along. So it's like, Oh, I can get this skin by to unlock this,
this, this and this person, but you're still getting stuff along the way. And they reward you
But you're still getting stuff along the way. And they reward you for playing, which,
I mean, I think that's kind of really easy to get in that game.
Yeah, exactly. So like, I, I wish it was like that type of system. But,
you know, they need, they want the money. But like, even with that, though, like there was
skins, like, isn't what you're talking about very similar to the combat crypt in Mortal Kombat with
like 1000. Maybe I don't know what like, there was like, and I wanted those from among us.
So I bought the pack for it. And then it gives you like a new skill tree thing that you can
unlock stuff in. And I think that's cool. Like, that should be the way it's done. At least that,
you know, it's like, okay, I want a thing. I know what I'm getting with that thing. But they're not
giving me that thing right away. You still have to earn it through like gameplay, but at least
it's like stuff you can unlock. So the other awesome thing about it is that you can pick
which set of skills or items you're unlocking by choosing which path you're walking on at that
time. And I think that that's great, because it can let people focus on, you know, I want
stuff for my healer, let's have a healing tree. I want stuff for, you know, melee, let's have a
melee tree. That would be great. Yeah.
All right, well, let's move on. The UK is really dominating gaming news this week,
because this next story is about them too, right? Logie?
Yeah, so there is a, basically, I think, like a regulation, that's a mandate that's passed the
European console, or council that is basically requiring that all batteries that are in appliances,
light transport vehicles, I'm assuming, like they said, electric bikes, electric scooters,
that type of thing. And other devices should be removable or replaceable by the end user.
I think it's to basically eliminate some of the waste that goes out there. Like so for example,
like if I have a controller for my PlayStation four, something like that, the battery dies in
it, I got to replace the whole controller. Unless you know, I go and take it apart. But now they're
saying, oh, well, yeah, we'll just have, you know, a replaceable battery, then you can put a
new battery in there. And it's good as new. So if this goes into effect, the thought is, well,
maybe then if it's a regulation that now game consoles, like, namely, the switch will have to
put out a version that has a removable battery, or whatever the switch Pro is that comes out,
we'll have to have a battery that is removable or serviceable by the consumer. Which is good,
I think they should do that. I remember old cell phones used to have that is is good,
because I bet a lot of these devices with the batteries embedded, you know, even though
s 200. Matt says I had to replace a bunch of my handheld batteries because a bloat or not not
being able to hold a charge lately, Nintendo makes it more or less pretty easy to replace batteries,
just a few screws, and you're done PSP even easier mobile phones are more of the problem.
I bet in any of those cases, people just throw the shit away. And I don't think that's particularly
great. So I think this is good that they're gonna make make it very easy to flip out the
battery that it needs to be sure. Yeah, my PSP is I had a few of them. And I think I had to throw
all the batteries away. I hope I've thrown all the batteries away for those because yeah, they do
blow up after a while. And same with phones. I think the phones for sure. You may be it wasn't
even that long ago where we had stories about Apple throttling their phones because batteries
wear down. And so it was causing the newer operating systems are causing, you know, battery
usage to be greater. And so they would throttle it to allow, you know, the older phones, I guess,
to be able to work along or whatever the case may be. But it's kind of almost like a planned
obsolescence at that point, because there's no such thing. There's no such thing as planned
obsolescence. Pretty much. It's just the way I don't think so. There's certainly there's
a lot of things that you buy now that don't last as long as they used to if you were to buy them,
you know, several decades ago, it's just several decades ago, they didn't have as delicate
technology as they do now. Yeah, but not even necessarily delicate technology stuff like we're
talking like dishwashers and you know, major appliances and stuff like that, like a lot of
that stuff last. I'm sure there's a lot of people that have like an old refrigerator that is you
just kick it away. Whereas you buy a new refrigerator craps out after like a few years.
So it's it I think there is obviously there's companies are going to say, Oh, yeah, we're
planning to make something obsolete. But at the same time, there is planned obsolescence. I mean,
with even like, not talking even hardware, like looking at, you know, a lot of phones,
after a while, they stopped receiving updates for their operating systems. And so basically,
it's like, okay, we got to buy a new one if you want those new features, because we're not going
to support the old one anymore. And I get it because it is processing power and all that type
of stuff. But I actually think of I think the most egregious example is not in the in the
universe. I think it's the K cups is what I think of. Yeah, that's the one that I go, Oh, no, that
was that was dirty what they were doing there. You know, because at least at least with phones,
or whatever you want to name, you can technically still use those devices, you can play whatever
games time on them. With the K cups, they were literally trying to say like, if you have an old
Keurig, you're not even going to be able to buy new coffee cups to use with it. That's kind of
what I would put in there. So tell me do cars today take the same tires as a 1969 Mustang?
No, no. And why? Because the way the cars are built today are built better with different
tires in mind. So I mean,
things are going to change and move. It doesn't mean that it's planned to fail.
There's also not designed to last though, like there's there could be precautions or like steps
are taken to make a product last longer, but it's not in their best interest to have a product last
longer, they want to last a decent amount of time. And then you'll buy a new one from them is
and Rama said it said it exactly right. As OS is get more advanced, older hardware can't support
it exactly. And I have seen what happens when people try to hack their systems. To put will
put like hacked versions of operating systems on and then see them struggle. See the the firmware
for it cause all kinds of problems with their system because it's not built to accommodate it.
I mean, it's just the nature of technology, it's going to move on past the hardware.
They can also design the hardware to be able to be upgraded. Like for example,
there are phones and laptops that they have very few that have replaceable parts,
including the processors, how long those base last before the new parts aren't going to work with
them. I think I thought of something very important with all of this because my brain
was thinking about well, okay, I mean, you have PlayStation, PlayStation two, PlayStation three,
PlayStation four, and by the time PlayStation, you're not making original PlayStation. But
here's the thing that is making that all different now, the cloud. Because why did something what was
a big selling point of stadia in the first place? Oh, even on this oldest Chromebook,
you can run Google stadia and run the newest games on this because it's all in the cloud.
So I, in a way, this this cloud direction that we're moving in, in a way I think is
actually kind of an obsolescence breaker in an interesting way.
Not necessarily, because even so, even playing it in a browser,
there's still going to be some limitations on you say that the base game to play it effectively,
even in a browser requires eight gigabytes of RAM, and you're on the system that only has four
is not necessarily going to run, say that playing through like, actually, I'll put it right now,
say that on GeForce, say, if you have, you know, very weak internet, you're going to get that pop
up that says the game is shutting down, your internet connection is bad, you won't be able
to use the service, there's still going to be a technological requirement, even for cloud based
gaming. Anyway, I was somehow we hopped over to this from the replaceable battery thing in game,
I think, or in consoles, I think at the end of the day, I'm, I think for the environment concerns,
I think it's probably the best because there are too many people. What all of you are saying in
chat is true about how easy it is to replace the batteries and some of them that is still too
difficult for a lot of people that would just throw the damn thing out. And so I think this
is a really good way to help ward off electronic waste at the end of the day. But we'll see. I mean,
but we'll see. I mean, maybe it's just buying time too, because inevitably, I get the rest
of the conversation we've been having. Inevitably, these devices will get probably thrown out anyway,
as they become obsolete. But I think it buys a lot of time. I don't know.
Well, I think that more companies to go along with that need to adopt the same kind of policy
that the place I work for has where, by 2030, there's going to be a zero carbon footprint.
Every piece of technology that's put out there is able to be brought back in and recycled
for zero waste in production of new materials. Because now there's so much out there that any
of these items can be turned back in through a native recycling program. And like, hey,
we'll give you a gift certificate for the value of whatever you're bringing back in,
for the value of the parts of what you're bringing back in, recycle the parts, put them into the new
machinery. And that way you keep operating at a lower cost, one thing, because you're not
needing to buy new materials, just the whatever it's going to cost to recycle them. And I think
every company needs to have a mandatory recycling program. Like, hey, you done with your Xbox,
and you don't want to sell it to a kid down the street? Send it back to us, and we will recycle
it for you. And it will become somebody else's Xbox, which Microsoft is, is there's several
companies have signed on to that Microsoft was one of them too. So yeah, of course, the name.
So um, but Oh, damn, what was gonna say with that? I'm very curious. I would think some states
are probably trying to pass laws around that too. I don't know to what extent they can,
I have to admit. But I do think about like, you know, the infamous California electric car law,
right, where like, all the cars sold in California have to be,
to some extent, electric by a certain year, which is going to be very interesting. So anyway,
I'm just curious, any new purchase of a car, right? No, yeah, it's not going to get rid of
old cars, but it's still gonna, you know, there's gonna come a point where gas stations are a thing
of the past. And so, or a niche, I say niche, there'll be a niche, like like diesel pumps,
or well, that's not that's, I was just reading an article where Switzerland and I think Norway
are doing the induction charging roads. They're starting to do them. Oh, that's cool.
Yeah, which I think, I mean, if we incorporate that, just I mean, it's going to be expensive.
But if they implement that, you know, let's just say California wide, since we have that law,
then it's, I mean, first of all, I think that they're also using more durable materials than
simple asphalt. Yeah. And the fact that the charging system is going to basically
remove so many different sources of emissions. And not just that, but those charging stations
won't need to be as necessary and, you know, have people take up space parking and all kinds of-
God, could you imagine- There's more to it, but I'm sleepy.
Yeah, no, so I was like, could you imagine if I5 was just a giant charging through all the
poo poo cow farms that you try to throw the way to Disneyland? Or yeah, or the 99?
It's like F zero. Yes, it is. It is literally like F zero.
Maybe they were onto something with that. All right. All right. Let's move on and talk about
something that you may not want to replace if it inevitably ends up getting rid of it. And that is
your Ubisoft account. Apparently Ubisoft is going to be suspending inactive accounts. This could be
very bad if you have games that you've purchased attached to it. Some emails have been spotted
going out. There's a Twitter user that posted a screenshot of an Ubisoft support email that said,
your Ubisoft account has been suspended for being inactive. If you don't log in in 30 days,
it will be closed permanently. Yikes. That's very bad if you have purchased games on it.
Now it's important to note, this doesn't mean that not playing it for 30 days makes it go inactive.
In fact, the official time period, we're still trying to figure out exactly what that is. Some
people were saying it's like up to four years or something like that. But still just that whole
fact that Ubisoft is looking at possibly closing inactive accounts, even if games are on them.
That is a little bit weird to me and kind of, I feel like it's gonna scream class action lawsuit.
And yet I know, I know, when you agree to buy games digitally, you have this, I know,
you don't have to, but I'm telling you, do you think that's going to stop a class action lawsuit?
If somebody loses their, you know, five year old copy of, you know, Rayman or whatever, you know,
they bought on Ubisoft some time ago. Go back and play Assassin's Creed 2.
Yeah. But I know Italy for you. I did sign into my Ubisoft account just so I was like,
Oh, maybe I should do that because it's been a while. But then I realized it actually hasn't
been that long. Because I if you have PC game pass, and you've played anything on Ubisoft,
such as Oh, Assassin's Creed Odyssey, through that, you're gonna have logged into the Ubisoft
thing relatively recently. Or in tried and chat says, Yeah, I just threw it away. It didn't look
like you were using it anyway. Yeah. dark to see it says I know they had a bunch had a bunch of
freebie giveaways that I just have sitting there. Yeah, I think a lot of people probably built out
built up free stuff on their account. And it's probably an Ubisoft's best interest to get rid
of those accounts that are just sitting there. It still seems a little bit shady to me. Whether it's
legal or not, it just seems shady. So it is shady and end of it. But I have a feeling that they're
doing it for I mean, it's it's, I don't think they're doing it as any sort of like malicious
action or anything or to. I mean, it would be a good way to promote people to go back and and
give them their products more more views. But at the same time, I'm sure that these accounts with
data storage are taking up space. Yeah. I mean, I'm trying to give them a benefit of a doubt. But
typically, I don't because it's Ubisoft and we know what has happened. Yeah. And to be fair,
that Ubisoft said I wouldn't even call it up forward, whatever the fuck they call that thing
to be soft forward. Okay, whatever it's called has probably seen more users on it in the last
two days since this news story came out than it has in the last two years. Because everybody's
logging in to make sure they don't lose their account. So I don't know, maybe the whole thing
was a genius evil plot. Who knows? sjo 100. Matt with a with an excellent point I agree with in
our chat room saying should delete eavesgimaw for being inactive and caring about Ubisoft's employees
preach. Well said, well spoken, agreed, cosigned. Yes. All of that. Let's move on to some news that
could potentially be a little more exciting dark soccer. Well, this is news from a leaguer. So take
it with you know, an entire salt lick. But there is a rumor that Sega is bringing back altered
beast and Gunstar Heroes, which I mean, first of all, that's going to make my husband really giddy
because he loves Gunstar Heroes. But altered beast is, you know, wise from your grave.
But yeah, they are looking to go back into their back catalogue and see about making new projects
out of it. There's not really a whole lot about that. But there is a player survey out and about
for gathering feedback to see what people would like to see more of and mention among them is,
of course, the Sonic series, Yakuza, Valkyria Chronicles, Phantasy Star, and a few more. In
fact, one of the questions I'll just read the entire list. What games do you want to see more
new content for? Sonic the Hedgehog, Yakuza, Super Monkey Ball, Bayonetta, Gunstar Heroes,
Shinobi, Jet Set Radio, Phantasy Star, Phantasy Star Online, Sakura Taisen or Sakura Wars, Shining,
Altered Beast, Retro Fighter, Streets of Rage, Valkyria Chronicles, Puyo Puyo,
Project Diva, Shenmue, Football Manager, Total War, Golden Axe, House of the Dead,
Virtua Tennis's Crazy Taxi, Other. So hell yeah, Other.
Yeah, I'm totally down for Other. That's right.
But Other too. I think that the Gunstar Heroes one though is pretty good for this house.
I think the Altered Beast concept is pretty cool too though. We haven't seen that series in a long
time. I'd be jazzed to see Altered Beast may come back. But I'm also very much, and I'm sure we all
are on the same page and start to see it in our chat, who says, Dear Sega, do not, and I can't
stress this enough, fuck up a new Gunstar Heroes. Truth. Do not. I mean, I still want to see
like a treasure delve, you know, back into their old stuff, like bring us out a
modern cleaned up version of Silhouette Mirage or was it Doki Doki Mischief Makers?
You know, I think that our Chameleon Twist or, you know, actually re-release
Radiant Fucking Silver Gun, and not 50 bajillion copies of Ikaruga, please. That'd be nice.
I really love the idea of an offline Phantasy Star game for a change, you know, and we've seen
Phantasy Star single player games that were kind of modeled after the online ones because they
had that PS Vita Phantasy Star game. Now, of course, I can't remember the name of it,
but of course, Phantasy Star universe was kind of in two parts. There was the online mode,
and there was an entire single player mode as well in that game. I'd dig a new offline
Phantasy Star to be honest. Not that I dislike the online ones. I just would be curious what
they do with it. It'd be very interesting. Yeah, and I agree with Rama and Quest Buster,
basically like going back to the roots of Phantasy Star 5 would be badass, I think.
So we'll see. All right, Loki. All right, so we talked a while ago now, I think we mentioned that
basically Epic is opening up Fortnite to allow folks to create their own games within Fortnite,
kind of like Roblox a little bit. Well, now we have word of a veteran FPS dev that's forming
a new studio to actually do that. They are going to be making games within Fortnite.
The game that they're talking about is Outlaw Corral, which is like a Western 1v1
FPS game. Doesn't sound that great, but you know, that's fine, I guess.
But yeah, you can check it out. They have like an island code that you can look at the game, but
I mean, cool. This doesn't look very good, you know, in my opinion, but I mean, it's neat to
see like people actually adopting, you know, that platform. But yeah, the fact that they have a code
to look at the game instead of like a direct link or something like that kind of makes it difficult
to discover things in my opinion, but neat. Yeah. Very interesting that I think it's more
interesting that we are seeing commitment to Fortnite as a game development platform.
I guess I'm not surprised, but it's kind of one of those things where it's like, oh, this is
happening. Oh, this is, we've got commitment. This is something, this is not something where it was
a flash in the pan we talk about at one time, like, oh no, people are going to make games for
this. So we're going to be talking about the future, which is interesting to me. So we'll see.
Yeah. And while this is an interesting story, as far as like this game being in there,
what's actually been more popular recently, which is, should be no surprise is a clone of Only Up.
And I'm going to tell you, like, if it's anything like Roblox is, clones of other games are
basically what you're going to get a ton of in these things. It's just going to be, it's rife
with copyright infringement, left and right. Like just blatant free for all.
Yeah. All right. Well, moving on to another story here, before we get to something classic,
I want to talk about a very interesting future for Blizzard games. You know,
Blizzard has historically had its own launcher for games, the Battle.net launcher. Remember when
they tried to change the name of that and the users made them change it back to Battle.net?
Well, Blizzard has announced that some of their PC games are going to be going to Steam.
That's right. Overwatch 2, which is, you know, probably a game that needs a bigger audience,
will be coming out for Steam on August 10th, although they have not committed to anything
else for the platform yet. In a press release, President Mike Ibarra from Blizzard said,
we've heard players want the choice of Steam for a selection of our games. However, something
important to note, even though Overwatch 2 is available on Steam, you have to have a Battle.net
account in order to play the game. Buy stuff in it. Battle pass. Hello. But also cross-platform
play. So to be fair, we've seen Blizzard do a lot more cross-platform games with things like
Overwatch 2, right? That was a big deal, is that unlike Overwatch 1, Overwatch 2 is all
cross-platform now, as is Diablo 4 versus Diablo 3. So I can see why this is happening now,
because Blizzard has that more infrastructure in there for that cross-play. So it's interesting.
But yeah, if you're trying to do this to avoid Battle.net altogether, for whatever reason you
may have, I don't think this is going to work. But maybe you want it on your Steam deck. That I could
see. Now Blizzard did not officially announce Steam deck support, but that doesn't mean people
are not going to do whatever they need to do to get it running on that. So that part is going to
be very interesting for sure. Overwatch 2 is also getting a big update on the same day, August 10th.
That is the day that PvE missions are supposed to start, as well as the new PvP mode and a
new hero. It's all called Overwatch 2 Invasion. So that is on the way. What is less on the way,
unfortunately, it looks like there's been about 50 esports staff at Activision Blizzard that were
laid off around the Overwatch League. The OWL, or Overwatch League, may be changing significantly.
It may be ending the city-based franchise format. Nothing is confirmed yet. But employees were
informed of layoffs on Tuesday, and a former member of the team told The Verge in an interview
that layoffs are out of nowhere, and that a skeleton crew might close out the current
Overwatch League and World Series of Warzone seasons. But in a quote saying,
in my eyes, they are completely unequipped to internally support anything esports after that.
Yikes. So this all also is on the piggyback of Overwatch League waving the franchise fees for
teams. Yeah, it looks like they may be trying to consolidate some teams and maybe not do so much of
the city-based format. It was at a strong start, but I kind of think the pandemic really kneecap
this thing, among other decisions. It went off of Twitch, it went to YouTube, and it kind of
keeps moving around. Some were aired on ESPN. I think the grand finals are on ABC at some point,
but then COVID-19 happened, and it changed a lot of that. And I don't think it's been able to find
its footing ever since, quite frankly. So we'll see. We'll see what happens for 2024 and beyond.
But does it end up going the way of Heroes of the Storm? I hope not. That would be very bad news
for Overwatch players. It's very sad with Heroes of the Storm. Heroes of the Storm still exists,
but if you look at the map for BlizzCon, there's nothing Heroes of the Storm on it,
which isn't surprising. But Overwatch has two halls. When SG100map points out,
going to be honest, Overwatch 2 being kind of lackluster also hurt it. And that is very true.
People did not respond to Overwatch 2 the way that I think Blizzard expected them to.
Changing the feature set probably didn't help, but that all plays into it as well. So
we'll see what happens. I mean, I've played a little bit of Overwatch and it's fine,
but I also haven't given Overwatch any money since I bought the original game when it was
the more traditional model of a $50 game to buy. And that was how many years ago at this point?
So I'm going to be honest, I'm not going to buy the battle pass. I'm not really interested in any
of that stuff. So we'll see. We'll see. All right. Anyway, let's take a trip down memory lane in our
next segment to a time when we didn't have to worry about season passes, battle passes,
esports, none of that. It was a very different time. So let's roll the bumper.
And now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where I'll dive into the vault and pull
out a classic and tell you about it. It's time for the classic game of the week.
And what did you pick this week, DarkSakura?
Live Alive, the original from 1994 for Super Famicom. It was developed by Square
and it's a very interesting game. I had started playing it back in the day and never
really made it that far. So now I'm officially playing it and have made it through
the prehistoric part of it, which we're actually watching right now. This is actually what I
streamed on yesterday, Saturday. But anyway, it came out in 94. It's a role-playing game
developed by Square for the Super Famicom. Yes, there is a remake that was done by Esquenix
for the Switch that came out last year and also then PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, and Windows.
So it follows seven different scenarios across different time periods with two other unlockable
scenarios that link all of these narratives together with this reoccurring antagonist named
Odio. You explore for a little bit and have different story twists and then there's
turn-based combat that's played on a grid and it's kind of weird. I'll just tell you right now.
It took a little bit to get used to and it's really frustrating when you're trying to move
into position and then somebody attacks like someone else and you have to wait to make your
move. It's ridiculous. But the game was really well received. The unique gameplay and the narrative
was also very highly lauded though the game is not a very long game. The remake was also brought
in very well. Although some people are saying that there are some gameplay elements that did not age
well. The original sold 270,000 units and was considered a failure. However, the remake sold
500,000 copies. Also, the director Tokida Takashi went to use his time from Live Alive
into other games. The brief run-through on some of those other games we are looking at
Final Fantasy III on NES, Final Fantasy IV, V, Chrono Trigger,
Parasite E, Chocobo Racing. I'm trying to find some more recent stuff.
Final Fantasy IV DS, Final Fantasy IV The After Years, Dissidia Final Fantasy Theatrhythm Curtain
Call, The New Live Alive, Future of the Final Bar Line, Octopath Traveler 2. So, those are
other things he's been involved in. At any rate, you basically take a role of one of eight different
protagonists through nine scenarios. So, each narrative does have the same basic mechanics.
Each of the story has different gimmicks. One can use stealth. One can use telepathy.
With all but one scenario, you are navigating through themed environments from an overworld
area to dungeon environments and the battles are triggered differently for each scenario.
Some are random. Some have sprites you can avoid and others are very well scripted. For example,
do you see, well, I mean, for those who are watching how you see these little
clouds poke around, you actually sniff to find out where your enemies are and so you
have an idea of how to go right into a battle or how to avoid one.
For the record, the cave people speak in thought bubbles and grunting and smelling.
Yeah, they have smell-o-vision. It is a turn-based system for the fight and you're on a seven by
seven grid where you can move around, perform different actions like attacking or healing or
different ranged works. Your skills can use without limit, though some do take multiple
turns to charge. And some of the abilities can give you extra properties such as
dealing elemental damage or healing or increasing your power.
You also gain skills with experience points that unlocks new abilities. Some of the progression is
locked away behind story events. Sometimes the techniques are learned by watching other people
use them. And then you can also equip and use items and have accessories that boost your attack
or other items to recover health. And if your character or the party is defeated, the game ends,
of course. So the remake has the basic gameplay carried over, although it's a new graphic style.
And some of the changes are just there for ease of use. You have like health bars and whatnot,
but honestly enough, I kind of liked getting the alert right at the beginning of the match
and then just trying to mentally keep track of it. So the different chapters that you have,
and I know I've kept mentioning the prehistoric, but you also have ancient China, feudal Japan,
the wild west, the present day, the near future, and the distant future.
And the protagonist has to fight an enemy whose name is or incorporates ODIO. Like the last one
in this one was O-D-O or IO or something. It was like that. There is an eighth chapter set
in the middle ages, which in turn will unlock a final chapter that brings all the narratives
together. So in prehistory, you play as Pogo with his ugly ass gorilla friend named Gori.
And you have to rescue a girl named Belle. They say Beru here. I've always just known
to this Belle. But she was supposed to be sacrificed by the rival tribe to their
dinosaur god, Odo. Get it? So all the same names. You have an Oloshihu in the imperial China,
looking for a successor. The Edo Japan, the infiltrator, you have a ninja, a Boromaru,
having to rescue an important person and kill the captor.
And the wild west, you have the wanderer who has a showdown. You have the strongest who is
in the present day with this guy who wants to be the strongest person in the world, thinking
that defeating enemies in each fighting style will help them get his goal. The near future is
the outsider with a psychic named Tadokoro Akira. You have the distant future, the mechanical heart,
where you're on a ship called Cognito Ergo Sum, I think therefore I am. And you play a maintenance
robot named Cube. And then in the middle ages, you play the knight Orsted. And I won't go more
into that without going into spoiler territory. Anyway, it was developed by development division
five of Square, also the folks who did the Final Fantasy series, and was the directorial debut of
Tokida Takashi, who had also worked as a designer for Hanjoku Hero in Final Fantasy IV.
And the concept was born from when they make an RPG where people could experience multiple stories
at once instead of the smaller stories going into a grand narrative. And it was made by expanding
the storage capacity of the Super Famicom ROM so that players could finish each part during the
day. And for the record, I finished the caveman in basically two and a half hours. That's even
with having to start over on part of it. The designer for this was Inoue Nobuyuki and the
programmer Fukuye Fumiaki. They had also worked on those other games with Tokida,
and they began development December 1993. And the whole thing took a year and a half and was
produced for a Super Famicom 16 megabit cartridge. But Tokida had to adjust to being a director. He
was more used to being hands-on for graphic elements. And so the hands-off approach was
a little bit hard. And originally the scenarios had a graduating difficulty scale, but it was
abandoned so that players could tackle the scenarios in any orders that they wished.
And basically, the battle system in there was intended to be a strategic experience,
and Tokida described it as real-life shogi. So that's kind of cool. And they wanted to not
show the hit points, but have the characters act like they had been injured or looked weakened as
they took damage. And then, of course, after it was done, the team split up to do other projects.
And I'm not going to go too much more into the characters on there, but some of the
characters were based on pop culture figures. Like, for example,
one of the characters was based off Oda Nobunaga.
One of the characters was also working on Basara and lended her work to the character design.
And Orseb was directly based on the Warrior of Light from the Final Fantasy series. So,
anyway, we also had influences by Devilman, Dragon Quest IV, First Human,
Giatris, and also some nods to Stanley Kubrick in there. So, anyway, the music in this game was also
done by the amazing Shinomura Yoko, who had left some of Capcom's projects after working on Street
Fighter II and moved to Square to do music for RPGs. And Live Alive was her first major RPG
composition, which I believe I mentioned in a previous episode. So, of course, there was also
some input by Uematsu Nobuo, as in the Final Fantasy composer who helped her out with
getting everything laid out. And some of the songs in the game were available as downloadable
content for Theatrhythm Final Fantasy Curtain Call, and some of the songs were included in
a tribute concert. So, Live Alive was released on September 2, 1994, meant to be released before
Final Fantasy 6, but there were delays, and so it was released after that. But there was
a prequel manga that preceded the distant future scenario, and that it was actually
done without Square's permission. The game was re-released on Nintendo's Virtual Console for Wii U
on June 17, 2015. Virtual Console port to 3DS was November 28, 2016. And then more people were
demanding the title, so they had to get permission from the guest illustrators and make sure the
re-release could happen. And the characters from Live Alive were featured in the 20th anniversary
crossovers with the mobile game Holy Dungeon and Final Fantasy Legends The Space Time Crystal.
So, the remake, I'm not going to go too much on the remake because that's not classic yet,
but the remake was built using Unreal Engine. Everything was updated in it. It had in-game
radars and maps, and the character designs were redrawn by Ikushima Naoki. And, of course,
Shinomura came back to orchestrate and rearrange the soundtrack. The original MIDI sound files were
lost, so basically she had to copy from the original and remake them. There's also the New
Future chapter had a vocal version of the theme Gogo Buriki Daioh, and it was done by Kageyama
Hironobu, who is best known for performing the Dragon Ball Z opening, Cha La Head Cha La, which
is actually one of my favorite anime openings ever. But, anyway, you know, like I said, not the best
received, but it was generally favorable. I can already tell just from playing through the
caveman scenario why it never got a US release, you know, between gorilla humping and eating
people and the naked man who wears a thong made out of a lizard, a live lizard, and explosive fart
jokes. Yeah, probably a reason. But, yeah, that's the game. Live Alive. I will, if anyone's interested
in seeing it on Tuesday, I will be starting. I think I'm going to do the cowboy, so be there.
All right, yeehaw. There it is. Not yeehaw people, but just yeehaw.
Classic game of the week, Live Alive, which is, yeah, I keep meaning to check out the remake
at some point, and I just haven't gotten around to it because, you know, endless backlog of games.
It happens. Yeah. Hey, Rob, real quick. Yeah. I found out that there are now analysis applications,
one of them by Intel, that's meant to search for deep fakes.
Basically, it's combatting AI rendered video. Perfect. Perfect.
But I've thrown that in since that's been a point of contention.
Yeah. By the way, before we get into rapid fire news, you know, I know we've been talking about
that I'm going to this convention this upcoming weekend, and I got Dragon Con. I should also point
out, and I was going to ask, because Alan and I got our TwitchCon tickets this week. Did you pick
yours up yet, DarkSucker? I assumed you were going. Maybe I shouldn't assume.
I did.
Okay.
I did, and now that's why I'm doing marathons so that I can actually eat
while I'm there and do my cosplay. But yeah, I bought my tickets.
Nice.
I believe it or not, I've actually made enough this year so far that I could buy my tickets
flat out.
Oh, that's great.
I was very happy.
Congrats. So that's awesome. Well, TwitchCon Vegas is coming up in October,
so that will be another opportunity to see myself in DarkSucker, although we don't
really work with it in any official capacity or anything like that. So it's what it is.
All right. And Bobby, no. So moving on, let's get into rapid fire news.
So, Loki, we'll start with you.
All right. So Death Stranding DLC, or I guess bonus content, is coming to Fall Guys.
So I really like the Sam Bridges costume that they have with the teeny tiny little bean baby
that's in there. That's pretty awesome. But yeah, you can get the standard issue Bridges
SDT suit that's in there. And yeah, looks cute. When is it coming? It's already come out.
It's part of the July 18th update. So nice.
Great. By the way, Loki, I completely see what you did there. You switched the game behind you
to one of the many Barbie video games there at some point.
It's Barbie Horse Adventures.
All right. Perfect. Perfect. All right. Moving on, DarkSucker.
So if anyone is a fan of the Google Doodle, there is Space Invaders World Defense, actually, which
is an augmented reality version of the game and has worked with Taito for mobile devices.
So this is actually being put out by Google for the 45th anniversary. This is basically
much bigger than just having the doodle to commemorate it.
But you basically can go around shooting Space Invaders in real time using your phone. Huzzah.
Good times. Yeah, I downloaded that to check it out. But it didn't look like it actually
used like landmarks or anything. It was just more of an AR Space Invaders game,
which was cute for a minute.
I mean, that's what it was described as. So I guess it did the bill.
Yeah. All right. And then one more thing to talk about. And that would be, do you remember a few
weeks ago when we were talking about the surprise that the Dolphin emulator was going to be coming
out for Steam and we were like, Valve's going to allow that? And as it turns out, LOL, JK,
Valve is not actually going to allow it at all. What happened in this case, there was no DMCA or
anything like that. But Valve's legal department did contact Nintendo. And there was, you may
remember this, they did reach out proactively to see about this whole thing. Valve forwarded
a statement from Nintendo's lawyers to the Dolphin team and said they could only launch the emulator
if Nintendo approved. So the part of the legal letter said, we specifically request that Dolphins
coming soon notice be removed and that you ensure the emulator does not release on the Steam store
moving forward. And does that surprise any of us? Probably not. I think more of us were surprised
that it ended up on the store in the first place, but it will not be coming to the Steam store.
On a related note, Nintendo has still not done anything to address the lack of backwards
compatibility and playing some of the old games on these systems. But I guess some people just don't
care about that. Moving on, let's check out what is coming out around the world in a segment we
call world release dates. So Loki will go to you. All right. So we've got a few games. So starting
off with Mr. Run and Jump on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, Xbox Series,
and the Atari VCS. We have the Queen's Gambit Chess on iOS and Android,
Remnant 2 on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series. And This Way Madness Lies on Nintendo Switch.
Then we're getting Ratchet and Clank Rift Apart on PC, Zuan Yan's Sword, Miss Beyond the Mountains
on PC, Arcadian Atlas on PC, Cry Machina on Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation
5. Dragon Ball, or I'm sorry, not Dragon Ball, Double Dragon Gaiden, Rise of the Dragons,
that's on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series.
The Expanse, a Telltale series, episode one on PC, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One,
and Xbox Series. Koa and the Five Pirates of Mara on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation
5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series. Surprisingly busy week considering the time of the year that it's in.
We've got Let's School on PC, Pixel Junk Scrappers Deluxe on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4,
and PlayStation 5, Psychic 5 Eternal on Nintendo Switch, Puzzles for Clef on PC,
Radiant Tail on Nintendo Switch, Return to Monkey Island on iOS and Android,
Sword and Ferry Inn 2 on Nintendo Switch, Yagra Union, We Will Never Fight
Alone on PC and Nintendo Switch, Disney Illusion Island on Nintendo Switch, Hello Kitty Island
Adventure on iOS and Android, Natsuman 20th Century Summer Vacation on Nintendo Switch,
and I believe that is it. All right, well going to Japan,
love this on the Nintendo Switch, You Suck at Parking comes out this week on the Nintendo
Switch. Oh man, that's the game that all the Americans play. I know, several people that
need that game. Well, you could, it's a multi-language edition, it isn't limited to
Japanese, but yeah, You Suck at Parking is coming out from GameSource Entertainment,
and yes, it is not a racing game, it's about parking, so. Anyway, also coming out on the
Nintendo Switch this week in Japan on July 27th, Cry Machina is out in a regular and
limited edition, Deep One also in a regular and limited edition, Hanasaki Works Spring,
regular and, you guessed it, limited edition, Psychic 5 Eternal in a regular, and
Esper edition because it's Psychic 5. Hayarigami 123 Pack is also out this week,
Yuoni, and those are the Switch releases in Japan this week. Heading over to the PlayStation 5,
guess what? If you want to get You Suck at Parking on the PS5, you can do that as well.
Cry Machina also out on the PS5, that Hayarigami 123 Pack is out as well,
all that in Japan this week. Pretty busy week, all things considered.
S2100 Matt in chat says, remember you park like an asshole. I used to have those fake
ticket printed up to put on folks' windows. No, but, and I know I've told this story on
the show before, I'm going to tell it again, I remember the first Live 365 Awards that we went to
when we parked next to some guy that parked like an asshole and Dark Sakura left them a note on
some Hello Kitty post-its that I had in my car that let them know you park like an asshole.
Do you remember that? I remember that too because I thought it was the funniest thing
because I just, I happened to have Hello Kitty post-its.
I remember, you remember my friend Julie, right? Of course. I saw her a year ago at a Pokemon ride.
Really? Well, I just remember that she and I were taking the same Japanese class
and someone had just parked completely impossibly bad, like really bad. And she took out honey
packets and poured them all over the handle of their car door. And then put salt on it.
Yeah, I'm passive aggressive notes. I can't get sued.
Don't piss off Julie.
Yeah.
That's, that's, that's Julie anger.
All right. How about the UK release dates, which hopefully don't lead to anger.
All right. On the 25th for PlayStation, Xbox, and PC, we have Remnant 2.
On the 27th for PlayStation Switch and Xbox, Double Dragon Gaiden, Rise of the Dragons.
Also on the 28th for Switch, we have Disney Illusion Island, PlayStation Ghost Song,
and for PlayStation and Switch Cuphead limited edition.
All right. All right. We just have a few more news stories for you, and then we'll see if
anyone wants to give us a call tonight over on our Discord server over at vognetwork.com
slash discord. But first we do have some more news and this game keeps trickling out the news
to keep it as a headline every week. Pretty exciting. Yeah.
Yeah. So there was a whole rumored story about Homelander joining Mortal Kombat. Well,
that's not all. So they finally made the announcement of the Mortal Kombat, their first
DLC pack that's gonna contain well, Homelander from the boys. And then a really awesome matchup
with Homelander's Omni-Man, who is from the show Invincible. And, you know, also voiced by JK
Simmons. So it's gonna be amazing. Then we have Peacemaker, Quan Chi, Ermac, and Takeda.
Oh, well, that's cool because I kind of missed having him in the last Mortal Kombat,
in Mortal Kombat 11. There was a lot of talk of him.
Yeah. So there's a whole like there's, I remember like with like Invincible and the boys and stuff,
there was all these like kind of like fantasy matchups like, well, this Superman type character
versus this other Superman type character and they're both evil. Who's gonna win? So we're
gonna see a lot of, you know, Homelander versus Omni-Man. It's gonna be amazing.
And I don't know when it's coming out yet, but it looks fantastic. Oh, September 14th
is when Mortal Kombat 1 releases. And then the combat pack, not sure when that's coming out yet.
I would feel like it's gonna be there the day it comes out, but maybe it will be.
Maybe. Yeah. And it comes with the collector's edition or premium edition as well.
Yeah. So, but that's right around the corner, but that's how they do those games. NetherRealm
just announces it like three months before it's gonna come out. And then they just,
they hit it hard with the announcements leading up to the release date. They actually do a really
good job of teasing and releasing their games. So I would love to see like a whole versus series
with all these different superhero shows. Like let's get, let's get like Invincible versus,
you know, the boys versus, I don't know, whatever else. Throw them all together. Hey, hey, you know
what? Let's just bring back heroes. Why not? Let's have heroes come back in too. And then just have
a big fighting game with all these different superhero TV shows. I'd be down with that.
Def points out, we'll probably get more news at Evo, which yeah, that's coming up
first weekend of August. So that is a very, very good forecasting as well for sure.
Yeah.
All right. Well, I think this is, this next story is really funny to me. Dark Sakura.
Neopets. I had them. You had them.
I had them. Yeah. All the omelets for my Neopets.
Neopets are going through a reinvention and I don't know how I feel about this artwork.
In fact, I don't really care for it. I liked the old artwork. So anyway, the,
the new management behind that is looking to reinvigorate the world of Neopia. On July 18th,
they they had the world of Neopia which had a lengthy blog post by the Neopets team that was
talking about the future of the franchise, the abandonment of Metaverse and NFT plans.
So yeah, I'm not interested the moment that NFT got brought in.
Well, good thing it's leaving.
They basically fixed the flash problem.
Yeah.
Oh, good.
And wow, $500 Neopets NFTs are no, no thank you. But basically after fixing the flash thing though,
is that they're two big initiatives were pretty much hated. The thing that they had released
didn't line up with the things that made people like Neopets. And so they're dropping whatever
that was. And they're going to do a mobile game called World of Neopets, which is a social life
simulation game where you live your ideal Neopian life from the perspective of a Neopet.
They're still leaving though the old Neopets
are intact. And they're going to do some things with the old style one. The new site
was actually should have launched a few days ago, July 20, to be a one stop shop for all
brand announcements and all the stuff. So I don't know how I feel about it. You know what?
Well, it's, I'm happy that evil was defeated with NFTs. So that's, you know, and it's it,
this is not the first time we've seen the gaming companies retreat from NFTs now recently. So I
feel like this, like this NFT thing was a flash in the fucking pan. Like it, it's, yeah, it's
going as far as leaving as fast as it came in. So don't let the door hit you.
All right. Rest in pyramid heads lasagna.
Loki.
All right. So apparently there's been a leak of some of the developer data on Roblox. So there
was about 4000 developers who had their personal identifiable information leaked to the public.
These were folks that attended the Roblox developer conferences between 2017 and 2020.
And it had everything basically all of their personal information that you could imagine
that would be in there. They said even they kind of brag about the ridiculousness of it,
even t-shirt sizes. So apparently they have notified everybody that has been affected by it,
but you know, it still sucks. So they pledged to continue to be vigilant. But you know,
all the vigilance that you can possibly muster is not going to help it when all their personal
information is leaked out. SSJ 100 Matt sums up the
comments on this article perfectly by saying, Oof.
Exactly. That comment's really funny. It is pretty good.
It's pretty good. All right. That should really just be the headline. All right.
Moving on to one more story. Another one of these things that, you know, is showing up in our
industry more and more is AI, or machine learning, if you will, but we all know everyone's calling
it AI. I think this is really funny. So some Redditors have ended up trolling a content farm
to report on a fake World of Warcraft feature that doesn't actually exist.
Okay, so there's this website called the portal, which is a blog that publishes gaming content
powered by z league. That is basically all just cover for machine learning AI generated bullshit.
But what's funny is that so so a Redditor noticed that the portal website was taking discussions
from gaming sub subreddits and turn them into blog posts. So what they did is that they made
a fake post and other Redditors played along, as did Blizzard developers in this whole thing.
And sure enough, article gets posted World of Warcraft players excited for Glorbo's
introduction. Glorbo is not anything that actually exists. So um, but now of course, now this is the
big joke. Now everybody's talking about Glorbo. And now here we are talking about Glorbo. And
guess what it doesn't fucking exist. So a Blizzard has actually been contacted to see if
they will actually address the hype for Glorbo and bring the feature into Wow, it would be a very
funny like they can't actually do it as a feature but it would be a really funny like pet flavor
text or something like that like something just a little wink and a nod I think or an item like
Glorbo's ring of sorcery or something would be really funny to put in the game at this point.
Didn't they do that with like the sword that was supposed to be in that South Park episode?
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. No, they do that. They do that shit all the time. All the time. Bobby
Blackpool points out that the article actually references the AI bot. So this is a great way to
break AI bots. And I think it's funny and we should keep doing it. CNET had to correct AI
generated finance posts because errors were found. Gizmodo, Geo media had that forging ahead with AI
generated blog posts, even though they got things wrong, like a chronological list of Star Wars
movies and TV shows wrong. AI is not ready in the way that companies want it to be ready. And I think
they're going to find out the hard way about this for sure. So Bobby says they then made another
post on Reddit worrying about AI bot news sites. And the same site made a post about wow players
worried about AI bot news sites. This is so good. It's getting so meta. Yeah. They just,
then they need, what they need to do then is reference that site and discuss about that.
And then it'll go one step deeper and they just have to keep going with it. Yeah. So,
it doesn't seem to be going anyway, away anytime soon, but some, some folks are believing, you
know, if you want to, you know, believe in the future of AI, some believe that AI could help
combat misinformation by, you know, assisting newsrooms with fact checking, but, you know,
I'll believe when I see it, cause right now it's not there yet. So, but we'll see, we'll see what
can come of it. I think it just depends, again, it depends on how the machine learns. It's very
clear that this thing got its pants pulled down for pulling all of its information from Reddit
and everything that was generated from there. So, Bobby actually links us to the article.
Oh yeah. This is great. So, this is from an archive cause obviously I'm sure the article
got pulled at some point, but this is actually at the portal where Glorbo is introduced into the
game. And again, it's, it's the most generic thing where it's just like, wow, players are buzzing
with excitement because this introduction it's there. Here are the key takeaways like,
like an AI bot would do. Some players have reservations about the mandatory item,
kick clack. That's gotta be a rearranged letter word of something. I don't know. This is really
funny. Glorbo's impact on the game. Honestly, this new feature makes me happy. I just want
some major bot operated news websites to publish an article about this.
Oh, it's funny.
Ah, it's so good.
Keep it up. Keep it up, Reddit.
But it really isn't good.
No, the prank is good. The prank is good.
The prank is great, but I mean, and it really does bring attention to it,
but at the same time, the fact that it exists, that it's trying, you know, that people have
programmed it to basically try to beat a human reporter to the punch.
No, I think it's great that it catches this company with its pants pulled down and just
shows how this can be exploited. Big issue with machine learning and learning. You can exploit it.
That's what this shows right now. So just food for thought, food for thought.
All right. Anyway, with that, let's get to the list of round table where we invite your calls
over at vognetwork.com slash discord. We also invite your emails every week to our mailbag,
participate at orange lounge, radio.com. And we like to read those emails on the show.
Dark soccer. Did you want to do that now? Or you want to finish eating while I bring on a collar?
Okay, so let's get to it.
It's got pepperoni on it. So now it's making me kind of meh.
All right. First email. Would Silent Hill 3 be the first of what we refer to as mascot horror
games? Or is there a significant predecessor? That's from Robert M. Kinda. I mean, it's not
really the first. We had splatter house. Oh, good call. And of course, I mean, any of the
games that were based off the movie franchises, you know, I mean, even Halloween had a game.
Nightmare on Elm street had one. There was a Friday the 13th game. Not that they were any good,
but. But yeah, I mean, I think splatter house is a great call out.
Yeah. Splatter house was the first one that comes off of my head. I mean,
you also think about early Diablo. Oh yeah. Yeah. Think about.
What about like phantasmagoria? I don't know if that's not really,
I think that's phantasmagoria. Really have like a mascot to it. Although I love phantasmagoria.
That's a great game. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. There was. Well, I mean, doom kinda.
I was trying to think if there's anything from that PC, like CD rom point and click era,
you know, when I think about things like seventh guests, but I guess, I guess it's, you're right.
It's not really like the brand is the kind of the mascot. They're not really any particular
character. Like I couldn't tell you what the main character's name was in that game at this point.
In golden acts, death adder. Oh, okay. But that's not, that's not
horror though. I don't know. Well, I loose interpret it loose.
Medieval horror, I guess. But I mean, but yeah, splatter house would be the first one
that came to mind. Yeah. No great call. Great call out.
All right. So next email. Hey yo, O L R doing my part and emailing the show
with a fun question and also sent us doggos. Thank you for the doggo. Doggo is cute.
Lego has been venturing into gaming theme sets in recent years. Most notably they have themed
playsets of super Mario brothers, as well as scaled builds of actual consoles like the NES,
the Atari 2,600, and recently a Pac-Man arcade machine with moving functions.
So my question to you all is what gaming series or gaming inspired set would you like to be
seen, uh, would you like to see be made into a Lego set? I personally really like the console
builds with the movable actions, like the NES TV. So I would like to see maybe a classic game
boy build with a small crank function, granted the beauty of Legos that one could make their own set,
but I just prefer throwing money at Lego whenever possible. Haha. Anyways, thank you for the show
as usual. Be well and stay awesome friends. SSJ 100 Matt. Um, great question. Um, I went a
Silent Hill diorama. That's a good one. I'm going to be predictable and say Metroid. I think for me
that's pretty predictable. Um, but you know what, you know what random like thing popped into my
head was Faxanadu. Um, that is very random. I know, but like, remember like some of those,
like the trees and the way the stages were built. It was, if you remember the, the Lauren that game
was about like climbing these trees and things like that. I don't know why. Like, I just think
that would make like an awesome Lego set, but you know, you want it obscure. Here you go.
I think we're gonna, I mean, I would be really surprised if they didn't do a Legend of Zelda
set at some time too. There is, there is supposed to be one, it leaked out. It was the, uh,
great Deku tree. Um, that was going to be the thing they have like product shots of it. They
just haven't announced it yet. Um, so that is coming. And remember there was Overwatch,
there is Super Mario Brothers stuff. There's also Sonic coming very soon. So they've done a lot in
gaming recently. I would like to see something along the lines of, um, I'd like them to do a
pinball machine, like honestly like a functioning pinball machine. Yeah, they could do it. Get some,
like, uh, they're like, not technics stuff. I mean, it would be some technic stuff in there,
but like some of the stuff that they have with like the robot creation sets and stuff
where you could really get it to be functional. Well, I know people have made them, but like,
I mean, I want to see Lego make one. Um, I think it would be really cool, uh, more practical,
like Mega Man or, um, you know, Zelda. It was actually themed around their, uh, astronaut
made with 15,000 bricks and this thing would be pretty damn expensive, but I'll,
I'll link it in the chat room for whoever wants to see it. Um, it's pretty cool.
I would love to have like there, you know how they did do the, the Pac-Man one, like it's,
it's fun as the crank stuff goes with that, like team up with one of those, like console,
like the tiny little console makers and make like you build the cabinet, but it's an actual
full functioning little mini cabinet or something like that would be really cool.
That'd be great. As big of a fan of the cabinet ones. I mean, I think that they're neat looking,
but I would rather have just like a nice diorama. I really would like to have a nice diorama.
Um, so, uh, next up, um, come on, open up. Um, hi, OLR. I have just been a podcast listener
for a very long time. The live show is just too late for me. You have been a part of my
podcast rotation for 15 plus years. I'm not sure how long, but I found this show back on all games.
10 years ago in 2013, my wife, Tracy died. That time I did call in. I remember that.
Now I have the best news ever. Last month, my daughter brought my first granddaughter
into the world. I'm so happy for the addition to the family. I'm not really gaming right now,
but I do keep up on the news with OLR weekly. Thank you for all you do. I don't know if I
should say the full name, so I'm just going to see Steven. No, I definitely, I remember that call
because, um, that was, I'm sure an incredibly difficult period, um, for you to go through. So,
um, you know, I'm, I'm glad to hear things are, are great these days for you and that you have,
uh, the family continuing to grow. That's great. Thanks for reaching out. Cause I believe this was
the only emailer that actually listened to my pleas for lurkers to email us. So Steven,
you get the gold star email of the week award. Yay. Although I appreciate the other emails as
well. We do hear from those individuals, uh, somewhat frequently. So I appreciate
a lurker, uh, un-lurking to, uh, send that other email. I want to say that we made friends through
live journal. Oh, I'm sure. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. With this person. Yeah. Um, I'm pretty sure I see them
on the book of faces too. So, um, and for the record, I have started the disentangle my
entanglement process and I'm taking the bird with me. Oh, oh, the bird app, which actually is not
going to be the bird app as of, you know, tomorrow. It sounds like, cause now it's, you know,
X marks the spot for the term has become a generic. Yeah. It's ingrained. It's like
Xeroxing. I'm always going to call it bird app. Here's the thing it's for, as far as I'm concerned,
it's Arco arena. And if you live in Sacramento, you a hundred percent know, like we all do,
you a hundred percent know what I mean when I say it's like Arco arena, because
where the Kings used to play, not their current place with the beam and all that shit,
but where they used to play, uh, in, in a little bit more of a suburb area of Sacramento,
though it's still considered Sacramento proper, the big arena. Yeah. The big arena that they
built there was called Arco arena was actually the first sponsored name arena in history.
Fun fact, because what happens there? I think, uh, no, cause it's now a pile of rubble. Uh,
it is going to be a hospital soon. Yeah. But, uh, so Arco arena, they lost the naming rights.
Fun fact, it was going to be the seven up arena. And at the last minute, the,
the naming deal changed. I know somebody who was on the deal for that. I learned all these
useless facts about it, but anyway, the name like Arco is gasoline. If you don't already know,
cause I don't know if that exists nationwide, terrible gas. Yeah. We Alan and I call it PP gas,
but it is it's cheap cause letting your car run on PP, but it is cheap. Very, very cheap gas.
I don't know if it's nationwide or not. So that's why I wanted to give that explanation.
So, um, yeah. So the arena was called Arco arena, but then they lost the naming rights after like
10 years or something like that. And it was called, I think, wasn't the name after it,
power balance, balance. Pavilion. Wasn't that the next name, which was after those
fucking wristbands or something that were like, it was terrible. And then I think it became this
like, and what happened was that everyone refused to call it that it was still Arco arena,
even though they would welcome you to, we'd say, uh, yeah, it's Arco arena. Yeah. Nice try. No,
we're not calling it that. And then it was sleep train, which ended up getting an amphitheater.
Yeah. Which, uh, which was train amphitheater was something else. No, it was both. They had
both. That's what made it confusing. They had the amphitheater out in Yuba city, rural area.
And then they also had the arena. So you had the sleep amphitheater and the sleep train arena.
And then mattress firm bought sleep train, but they never changed the name.
It was still the sleep train arena. No, it was Arco arena. Yeah, exactly. No,
it was always a forever Arco arena. And they finally bulldozed Arco arena
last year because it is now going to be a hospital Arco arena hospital.
People are going to have babies born at Arco arena.
Are they still going to do like the monster jams in the hospital?
It's going to be their big fundraiser event is having that out in the parking lot.
No, all the monster jams and shit happened at the golden one center, which is the new and that
funny enough, people don't call that Arco arena. No, that's the golden one center
because that's downtown. That's just the downtown Plaza.
Actually, I do know plenty of people that still call that the downtown Plaza.
I still call it downtown Plaza and I'm not even from here.
Or is it the K street mall? Like, I don't know what they call it. All of it. All of it is
acceptable. And I'm just like the mobile old sack. So a non Sacramento version of the reference that
I think more people would understand would be candlestick park. Exact same thing happened
with candlestick park. Remember when candlestick park was like monster.com park? I think at some
point, do you remember that? I've purged that from my memory.
Exactly. Cause nobody fucking ever called candlestick park, anything but candlestick park.
They bulldozed candlestick park. Yes. I know you mentioned it. That's why I brought it up.
They bulldozed candlestick park like several years ago. Like Paul McCartney was last play
there. I heard they were going to put houses or condos there. I don't know if the pandemic
slowed that down or what, but they still have it. It is just a bunch of empty land. Do you know
what that empty land is called? Candlestick park.
Candlestick park.
All right. Yes. As you're 100 Matt, you got your sports ball, but it should look,
here's the thing. Was the last event at candlestick park sports ball? No, it was not.
It was a Paul McCartney concert. Fun fact. Uh, what was the last event at Arco arena?
It wasn't sports ball. I think it was also a concert of some sort.
Hold on. You know, Arco arena has its own, um, Wiki page and it's under Arco arena. It's not
It was really brothers Bardem and Daley. Really?
It was, it was, yeah, it was the circus.
Of all the things they could have done there. Sleep train arena.
Oh, you know what else though? That became the makeshift hospital. They, it had a moratorium on
the bulldozing because they made it. Remember when they were really worried about tons of
people being hospitalized, that became the overflow hospital. Arco arena was the overflow hospital.
So ironically, ironically, yes, Arco arena was a hospital. And from what I understand,
one person used the services. One person. But I, you know, I don't give it too much shit because
they were preparing for much worse. And I think we need to give that credit, you know, that they
were ready to go. Um, but that now that I think about that is ironic. Arco arena kind of foretold
its future by becoming a hospital there at the end, didn't it? Right. Anyway.
Well, I know that they had, um, a, uh, a goodbye thing like last March.
Yeah. That's what it was. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. They had a goodbye event,
but the last official event to hire out the arena was, um, the circus.
It's kind of disappointing. I don't know why. I think the circus is kind of silly now that I'm
in my forties. Maybe if I was a kid, I'd be more excited. But
anyway, uh, DJ says, what's the, Oh, nevermind. That's a response to something in chat. Cause
I was like, we went over this it's for when it, when it's a hospital, it would be Arco arena
hospital. All right. Let's get some calls. They've been waiting patiently for a long time. So I want
to get them on the air. Hi, you are on orange launch radio. Who's this? Hey, it's the one and
only Ron. How's everybody doing? It is so good to hear from you, Rama. And I just want to make sure
we're clear. It is always, what, what do we call the new hospital? Go arena. That is exactly right.
Good job. We're we're fast learners here at orange lounge radio. Appreciate that.
What's on your mind tonight, my friend stuff. But first thing first, I want to thank Loki.
He, there's something he did on his YouTube page. That was a big save for me a couple of
weeks ago when I was on vacation. What's that? I was, I went down to South Carolina and visits
a friend of mine and I'll help her with her kids and all of that. Her kids had a, um,
leap over and they were bouncing all over the walls. And I'm like, I got to get them to calm
down. And I spoke to my friend's son. Like, what do you like? And he goes by crap. Haha.
Well, they'll put our channel 64 out of peep out of them for hours. Nice job. Good. That,
that is a true fan right there because you are living the spread the word part of that there.
Okay. Nothing to put kids asleep to me rambling for like 15 minutes at a time about things that
I'm doing. Okay. So I'm about to derail this entire fucking call right now, but you did call
into orange lounge radio. Rama. I just noticed the cup you were sipping out of is a raising
Cain's cup. Have they fucking infected New York city? Like the plague as well. Those things have
showed up everywhere in the last like two months everywhere. My brother in Christ, they have a
global flagship location in times square. Of course they do. Of course. How long has it been?
How long has it been there though? A few weeks. And I went by there a few weeks.
Let me tell you, I went by there cause I'm like, I went to the healthcare. I went to Zach's bees
and then I'm like screaming at friends on Facebook talking about this is not the chicken y'all were
telling me about. So y'all need to shut up. So I went to raising Cain's with a friend thinking
we'll grab some takeout and then go to the bus. There was a line going outside and around and
the place has been open for a few weeks. I'm like, I'm going to go, I'm going to order online,
pick up my food, then go home. And that's what I did. And now they're opening another location
in, I think around 14th street union, um, near union square later this year too.
I've never had it, even though it's ever, I drive by it all the time, all the time. And they,
they just bulldozed a fucking Walmart and they're replacing it with Raising Cane's apparently.
That's a big Raising Cane's. I know, right? I think something else is going there too,
but like Raising Cane's going to be the parking lot or something wild.
I think, I don't remember if I saw one in Alabama or I might just be thinking of Zach's bees.
Well, anyway, I know you didn't call in to talk about chicken, but you know,
uh, more chicken talk. What's on your mind tonight?
A couple of things. Um, I want to talk about something that you brought up
earlier tonight and something that I mentioned last week. Okay. Now we talked about loot boxes
and addiction. Well, I got a story for you. I'm going to change the names on this to protect
people. Good idea. I noticed how you said that you did not say the innocent.
You just said, well, this person is far from innocent.
Aren't we all down? So two friends of mine were going to get married and all that. And the wedding
was, was postponed, canceled, whatever that down with my friend, me and Marco, she tells me that
her now ex fiance slash roommate got addicted to loot boxes. I'm talking, he would not pay his own
bills. He just kept throwing money into loot boxes or in this case, gotcha games, you know,
game over. Would you like to contain you $5 for, and that's what he was spending his money on.
Oh no. And the addiction got really bad. And my friend's father had sat down,
had a talk with him about it. And he said he got better. Evidently he did not.
He's I know he's better now, but basically his relationship is gone. Everything he works hard
for. It's everything gambling edition. It's everything that you see play into that playing
out there. That's that's unfortunate. I'm really sorry to hear about that. I hope, I hope he
got the help he needs. I borrows. I know he's in therapy for it, but I do not bring it up because
he doesn't know that. I know that's for the best then. Yeah. Now,
this is something that came up in a topic last week about the whole
Microsoft acquisition and so forth. I had mentioned that while everybody I see on Facebook
talking about the whole acquisition, nobody has said anything about the shit Bobby Kotick has done
because, and I'm looking at it like, what's really sad is nobody in your friend group has said it,
right? Because I'm like, you've listened to this show, right? Okay. Just making sure we're clear
on that. Okay. Outside of y'all only like maybe 1% of people are talking about it.
Okay. And it's more, the thing is more people is concerned about, they don't want Microsoft
taking quality. That's what they're more concerned about as opposed to what's going on with Kotick
and the harassment and so forth. Well, at least you underscore why the court case seemed to be
all about call of duty. I mean, there, there was a reason for that and you, you kind of underscore
that. Right. And the thing is, I'm thinking about if I'd never listened to OLR, I wouldn't know
really check the game blogs as I used to. So even if I did, if I read an article about it,
probably go through one ear and out the other where y'all y'all bring this up every day,
because I think I'm saying things because it is something that needs to be discussed.
Like I have a couple of friends who work at Ubisoft and they talk about how great things are
for them. And I'm just sitting here going, Hmm, I say something or just mind my business and just go
about my day. Respectfully mind your business and go about your day because maybe it is for them,
you know, and even though the culture tends to trickle down from the top, because the company
is nationwide and split up into smaller studios, it could be that wherever your friends are at in
the infrastructure, maybe is a little more insulated from other places. So if there's
if they are happy, there's no need to poo poo on the parade. Yeah, it's not
that. It's more like, I just want like, whoever is to know what's going on just be informed.
Maybe the way I know myself, it's going, I just wouldn't know how. So I'm just like,
what about like, hey, I heard like there was a you I don't know if this is actually true. I have to
there's a union starting at Ubisoft. Is that something y'all are getting in on, you know,
or something that that might be the way to address it instead of like, wow, I heard your CEO is a
total shitlord who hasn't been accountable for the last four years. Like what the fuck's going on in
that place? That's not going to work, you know, but maybe just kind of hint dropping at some of
the ways employees are pushing back might be an interesting way to gauge it. Basically, yeah,
for right now, as long as I see it, they're happy. I'm I'm not going to say anything. Yeah,
but it's sort of like, it's like, it's like seeing two sides of it. It's like,
you know, this is going on. But when you look at people who are discussing it, nobody's talking
about like, it's a nonsensical thing, which in actuality, it is not, you know. Yeah. And I think
God forbid you depending on what for what group you're in a page, you bring that up. It's like,
hello. Well, no one you know, I'm just like, come on. Maybe maybe you should care.
Sure as hell do. I know you do. I know you do. Well, Rama, I hate to wrap up,
but we got one more call I got to get on. So any last minute thoughts for us tonight before I let
you go? Oh, I am running out of space for Funko Pops, because I just bought one. That's my basic
one of my TV crushes. So yeah. Okay, you know, I'm like, you're not gonna say that not tell us
who the TV crush is. I'll tell y'all. Let me go grab it and well better. So Pena Lawrence from
boy. Hold on. I love it. Oh, I shall tell you later. I have a nightcrawler this this big.
As long as you didn't say gambit then mako child won't be knocking on your door.
It was never a gambit fangirl. It was always my blue fuzzy elf.
I don't have any pop vinyls with crushes. But I do have Richard Simmons.
Was I something for you, Rob? Oh, I have a mini Richard Simmons bubble bubble head. Yay.
But um, talk to me later on Sean. I got some organizers on Etsy and I will link you to them.
Appreciate it. Appreciate it. Because all I do now I just haven't been protective.
Bad things that just keep them stacked all over my room on my little studio apartment.
Shoot what happened? There we go. Okay. Anyway, Rama, I'm gonna let you go so we can get another
call. Thank you so much. Take care of my friend. anime jam session. Listen to it or else. All
right. Bye. Bye. All right. Let's get another call here on the air. Hi, you are on orange
launch radio. Who's this? Hey, this is deaf. Hey, deaf. It's good to hear from you. What's up,
my friend? Well, I wanted to talk about a recently released game that last year was
released and didn't have that critical price. Which is choco Bo GP. Oh, yes. Oh, yeah. Oh,
did you Okay, is this about the purchase of the new version of it? Yeah, I actually got the
physical version. Though it's a it's an import. I actually have I think it's a
yeah, it's a European version. Because in America, you cannot get it physical,
a physical version on the digital. The thing the switch is region free. So you can buy
the Korean version or the European version, it will work fine perfectly. But yeah, last year,
if you remember, it's like, yeah, you can buy the game. But it's filled with microtransactions.
It's filled with battle passes. It's, it's like not good. So heavily. It was so heavily into the
into putting it more money that it needed to. So it's like, it was really a disappointment. But
right now, it's like, okay, it has everything, you can unlock everything with the currency the
game gives you. It is a grindy game, I will say it's like not it's not, you cannot get everything
like really easily. But the game is fun. It's a really competent card racing game. It has like,
it has the not necessarily easter eggs, but it has those references to Final Fantasy as a whole.
And obviously previous or other chocobo games like Mystery Dungeon,
chocobo racing even and in that. So it actually it is a fun game. It's like I was playing it last
night with with some friends. We were playing the chocobo GP mode, which is like a battle royale
thing. You have us you enter to a 64 party race, but it's divided in eight between eight players.
So if you get to the top four positions or top four places, rather, you keep advancing until
you get to the final round. And if you win, you then you win more points, you win more tickets,
more money to buy more stuff. So it's it's really addicting to and in that sense,
especially with friends, which because it's not that necessarily that the game is not populated
online. It actually, I actually surprised that there's many people playing it. But every time
my friends and I like were trying to group up, we did group up in the same lobby. So it was funny
that we were pretty much hugging the first places. But still, anyways, it's like really
fun. My only gripes with the game right now is two things. Again, it's it feels really grindy.
But again, the fun, the fun aspect is really compensated. But the other thing is that local
multiplayer is only for two players. So you cannot have like Mario Kart or any other racing games out
there that you can have up to four even. So yeah, it's that's really limiting. But at the same time,
you can go local multiplayer via like local wireless and you can play up to up to eight.
So if friends have this, have the game on Switch, it's like, okay, you can play like that. But
but I would rather like have one console and have multiple players
have a playing from one instead of having multiple consoles.
Let me ask you this question because, you know, it's very hard for them to once the game is out,
kind of get people to give it a second chance. You know, it takes it takes a while for that
information to get out there. We've seen it happen with games, you know, No Man's Sky,
Diablo three, etc, etc. List goes on and on. But let's let's make believe this is the game
they had released originally. In your opinion, do you think this ends up being a successful game?
Or is it still just kind of like me? It's it's it's a meh game. I don't think it ever
would have caught on anyway. What happens if this is the game they'd really released originally?
I think at least the perspective would have been different, that's for sure.
But I wouldn't think it would have been like a success. Like, Oh, my, you have to play this
game. No, it would be the same. Because even even a year ago, it's like, okay, you can buy the game
in the game. This again is it is fun. But like in comparison to other card racers, it doesn't
bring anything new to the game. So it's like that you have your your magic sights, which is like
your Mario Kart items, you can combine them like in DBCon racing, you have your drifting you have
and the tracks even though they are buried there, they're not like too many, there's only like
nine or 10 tracks in total. And each one has one or two variations of it. So it kind of gets
repetitive in in a short term. So again, it's it wouldn't been like a huge success, probably
a moderate success. Okay. And more people would have been like, Oh, if it's an if it's on sale,
get it. Yeah, it's like that kind of thing. I would. Yeah, it's like, even right now it's like
it's on sale. So that's that's how I convinced a friend to get it. Hey, it's really cheap right now.
You should get it because we can play it and all that stuff. And yeah, he had we had a really
good time. And we plan to play it more. So it's like, yeah, it's so awesome that that the game
is better now. But it also sucks that it took a year. Yeah, pretty much to get there. Yeah. So
yeah, that's a bummer. Well, depth, I appreciate the check back in with that game because I admit
that again, the relaunch of it kind of fell off my radar. Although I was super interested in
Chocobo GP at first I like you and many other people were just kind of like once we heard
how they really were going to micro, you know, monetize the game and stuff. It's like, ah, fuck
it. You know, if this if that's what this is, nevermind, we should have never had it come back
in the first place. But it's interesting to revisit it now. I'll kind of be curious,
especially when it does go on sale in the future inevitably. Maybe I'll end up picking it up for
myself. We'll see. Who knows? But again, it's it's in sale right now. Don't know how much longer it
is going to be. But it's 50% off. So if you're really interested, you can pick it up right now.
All right. Or relatively low price. Even the physical copies aren't that expensive. Mine was
around $35. So again, if you're interested in that, you can get it that way. All right.
All right. Well, depth, I'm gonna let you go. So we can wrap up the show. But thank you so much
for the call. Hey, thanks for having me. All right. Take care, my friend. All right. That
was great to hear from depth. Appreciate that. Well, with that, I can smell dinner downstairs.
So I'm definitely ready to wrap on up and head on out. So reminder, we're not back next week,
we will be back in two weeks. Bobby Black Wolf will be here next week, though. So just
because the show ends early enough where he's able to get back and do his show.
But I don't have my rig and can't do this show. So but so I'll be gone next week. No,
I however, will be playing dead by daylight. All day, daylight by daylight.
So yeah, if you want to see cranky Jamie, you have open lobbies most of the time.
All right. Um, what's that? I said have a safe flight. Thank you. I'm flying the
plane myself this time. So we'll see how it goes. So I'm just kidding. But hopefully,
yeah, hopefully all goes well. We'll see you back in two weeks. We'll talk about all the greatest
in gaming news at that time. In the meantime, we're gonna wrap up and get on out of here for
the night. So of course, we wouldn't be able to do this show if it wasn't for you all. Thank you
all for checking out the show. Thank you for spending the time with us. We are the show where
every gamer has a voice. But we need more voices to put out here on air. So tell a friend or two
about the show help us spread the word because we are the show where every gamer has a voice.
A nice five star review on a site like iTunes, or wherever it is you found this show goes an
awful long way as well. So super appreciate all of that as well. Final thought time stark sacral.
We'll start with you. I can't brain. Um, but, but pineapple and pizza is delicious,
but pepperoni pizza is terrible. I like both personally.
All right. Have a good stream. Have a good night. All right. Loki will go to you your
final thought tonight. I'm going to go to Santa Cruz next week to visit the homeland
of my DDR machine. It's allegedly it came from Santa Cruz Beach boardwalk. Allegedly,
I don't I can't confirm that. But that's where they said they got it from. So we'll see.
Santa Cruz boardwalk was the first place I ever played Mortal Kombat three.
It was also the first place I ever played laser tag. So we can go back and play that
laser tag to even though it looks like they set up our next week, basically.
Yeah, basically we're going on vacation. Good. Enjoy that. That'll be fun. Awesome.
All right. Well, uh, for my final thought, of course, I look forward to seeing those of you
in the Atlanta area at Southern pride gaming expo. Uh, very excited about it. Uh, don't be shy,
come up and say hi. My understanding is this is a much smaller expo than, um, dragon con. Of course,
uh, I believe it would be more in line with the crowds I see at California extremes. So, um,
please, if you're there, come say hi. Don't be shy. I'm a normal person. I promise. Um, happy,
happy to sit down and play a game. As long as it's one, I like, don't ask me to play
literally anything. It's gotta be something I somewhat like, don't ask me to play Madden.
I'm not going to do that, but blaze of steel. I might, I might, but I look forward to seeing
everybody there. And of course, we're going to have that panel with the Nintendo voice actors
Sunday at one o'clock. And I am jazzed to talk all about that on next week or next week's orange
lounge radio. If not a little sooner, uh, that's it. Have a great week, two weeks. Everybody will
be back then to talk more about gaming. Have fun, stay safe, stay out of the heat. And if
you have to be in the heat, stay hydrated, but otherwise indoors with video games,
sounds like a great idea to me. We'll see you next time. Bye everybody. Good night.
You've been listening to orange lounge radio. Orange lounge radio is a production of OLR
studios to join us for our live show. Tune into vog network.com Sunday nights at 6 PM Pacific
9 PM. The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the
staff of orange lounge radio or fog network, but you know, they were all still true.