Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts? DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
This week 343 Industries does an about face announcing that future installments of Halo
and any FPS they produce will contain a local split screen mode. This is just the start
of tonight's news, stay tuned for this and so much more starting right now in the show
where every gamer has a voice. Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show
where every gamer has a voice. It is Orange Lounge Radio live tonight on the February
of 26th, 2017 with episode number 677 of our program. My name is Rob Roberts joining you
live here at the Voice Geeks Network, vognetwork.com where we tape every Sunday, we tape live
Sunday nights at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
and we are here to talk about video games and gaming culture, the gamer lifestyle too
with me here in studio, welcome back DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
Why hello there
Hi how are you doing?
Better than last week
Yeah you don't sound so great but at least you look good
Well of course I look good
I always look good, I woke up like this
Girl
I gotta say also a big thank you and hugs and kisses to DarkSakura because this was
something she ran and picked up for me after the show two weeks ago when she was here because
she'd spotted them. This is like a Walmart exclusive which I don't set foot in Walmarts ever
If I could have helped it but I went and looked for him for Dan because he had been all hyper
We went to like three different fucking Walmarts looking for him
So what these are and if I do go to a Walmart, I go to the Walmart that they built here
We broadcast live in Sacramento, California and there is a Walmart in the middle of nowhere
Like literally in the back roads, like you're going to go to Elk Grove on the back roads for those that are local
Like there's literally a Walmart in the middle of nowhere, like I don't know who goes there but there's a Walmart there
And sure enough the Walmart in the middle of nowhere had the little arcade classic
You know all those little neighborhoods popped up around that area of Elk Grove
I think it's more built for the future because you know down here by, I don't want to give away where I live on the show
There's developments coming up nearby here too, anyway
So I was going to say these arcade classics, so this is pretty cool
So they're like little tiny cabinets, like arcade cabinets, like tiny arcade cabinets
I'm talking like the size of like a wallet
They're maybe what, eight inches high?
Yeah, yeah, they're not that big but they actually like they have a game inside them
So this one is what, this one's Qbert right?
Yeah, which I honestly think it might be the Colecovision version
It might be, they definitely look like old school computer versions
And then this one is Centipede actually
So I can actually, I can fire up the little demo
I don't know if you guys will be able to hear this okay, but you might be able to hear the little
Let's try
I don't know if they can hear that at all
But you can hear like the little background noises if I try to fire
Well I can hear it across the room
Maybe, it's very very quiet probably, sorry it doesn't come through very well
But yeah, and they're cute, they're like the screens on them are very tiny obviously
But this is something that I've seen like it seems to be a trend in the whole retro gaming thing
Because I guess this technology to make these little screen games is really cheap
Because I've seen now Atari flashbacks are coming on things that look like that
Where it's like a Game Boy micro or something, you remember that? The little micros?
I have a Game Boy micro
I know, they're a little bigger
Remember you used to carry it to E3 every year
I do, I do, but the screens are maybe a little bigger than that
Do you know that got me into a Nintendo thing once?
Did it really?
Yeah
No, I forgot about that
It was I think the last year that we went
Because the last year we went I had a media thing, it was the year before that
When I was like, someone's like, is that a Game Boy micro?
Yeah
You wanna come see this?
Sure
Hey Ashley since you weren't here last week, I don't even know if you heard this news
Did you hear about E3 opening up to the public?
Yeah, I knew about it
I was here when we talked about it the week before that
Oh that's right, last week was the follow up, sorry
Everything's a blur in gaming news you guys, sorry about that
So last week was the follow up that they hadn't sold out the tickets still
So not something you jumped on or are going to be going to
Good point, I'm kinda done with E3
Yeah
I mean it was fun
Stories like that I doubt are gonna happen anymore
If they do and we're wrong, awesome, we'll try to go next year
You know, but I just, you know, maybe
I'm still wanting to go to, I wanna go to a real convention
No
Since we're not having gamer X this year apparently
No, sad, well there's MagWest, that's probably the contender out here
I love MagFest though, and you know what really cracked me up?
I'm gonna go to DragCon
So I know you don't wanna talk politics on the show, but I'm just gonna mention
Me not wanna talk politics
But it was in the news that the guy who happens to reside in the White House right now
Was speaking at an event, right, did this whole speech thing
And the whole thing with that, that thing, he was in National Harbor, Maryland
He was at the exact same hotel where MagFest is at, that whole thing
Was at the same hotel where MagFest is at
So it kinda cracked me up knowing that, you know, the president saying whatever he's saying
I wasn't listening, on that stage, and I'm like
Gosh, that's where like, all these bands were playing
Like Bit Brigade was playing like just four weeks ago
I have to say something to Bob Coffee
Yeah
I'm not going to Anime Expo ever again
You've been before
I used to go, I went like five years in a row and cosplayed every time
My first AX was amazing
And then I went to the one at Disneyland Hotel where we had the DDR third mix
I was gonna say, you got hooked into DDR thanks to Anime Expo, right?
I played DDR and Combat Boots in 1999
It just got to be way too overly commercialized
I mean, Anime now is super commercialized anyway
But it wasn't quite the same thing where you'd go and you'd find
Like the people selling the Japanese laser discs or, you know
All of the, you know, real import stuff
Or the Avextrax CDs because I loaded up on Avextrax CDs
And it's just not what it was
And I broke a wing my last year at AX
Because that was my Angel Sanctuary cosplay
So, I'm kinda done
Fanime is a little bit better
But I haven't been to Fanime in a while
When was the last convention you went to?
GameRx
Oh yeah, GameRx, of course
You haven't gone to a lot though
No, not really
I hadn't even cosplayed this year because I was so mad at the cosplay contest
But I'm hoping I can make it to the convention I've been working on
All of their material for since it just started DerpyCon
One of these days I'd like to actually visit the convention I've been doing the guidebook for every year
That's New Jersey?
Yeah
I think Rama would love to have you out there
I'd like to
Shoot, I just want to go to New York really
Send me to New York somebody
All of y'all on the East Coast
Maybe get 50 bucks a person and y'all can fly me out
Start your GoFundMe
This is my Kickstarter
Alright, anyway
Bask in my presence
I hate to ignore
We had to catch up with Jamie though since she was out last week
But I hate to ignore her over there of course here in studio as always
Techmaster Loki
Hello
Hi Loki, how are you?
Fine
What do you think of these little arcade thingies?
Are these, is this the sort of thing that interests you or are you like, nah it's cheap?
I'd buy one and take one apart
That's a very Loki way of putting things
Actually, well and that was the other thing I didn't mention about these things
These things were only 20 bucks a pop
That's the thing, that technology is like so cheap now
Those Atari flashbacks are what, like 40, 50 bucks?
I don't know, they're not that expensive
And I see these all the time now
I was at the mall yesterday
There's a, what's that new store that's popping up with all the nerdy stuff
BoxLunch, is that what it's called?
Hot Topic?
No, well I think it's the same people that run them
Spencer's?
No, I think it's BoxLunch is what it's called
Spencer's is disgusting now
I don't even think they have that at our mall
Yeah, they have it at Sunrise still
No, there's Spencer's at Sunrise
Who goes there? Anyway
Disgusting people
Apparently I do
But what was I going to say about that whole thing?
Oh, so I was at the BoxLunch
Which sells, they have little sections dedicated to all the nerdom things, right?
There's a little Doctor Who section, there's a little Pokemon section
That's right, they do have one of those places down at the Paladio
They have a BoxLunch there
Oh, do they really? Okay, okay
Or something that is very similar to that
So of course I got a look in the gamer section
Because they have like gamer shirts
And there was of course a lot of Overwatch stuff
But I was like, oh maybe I want a D.Va shirt
And there was a Soldier 76 shirt I took a picture of and sent to Shane
Because he had gray hair at the time because he's in the process of dying it
But they also had, in their whole little gaming section
They had a little like mini, like 100 retro game thing
That was like one of these tiny screens
That was like probably something you'd put on a keychain
That had 100 retro games on it
Except they're all just like, I know they're garbage
Not things you recognize
Like this game looks like Pole Position
But it's not
And you know, they're not
It's Pole Poopsition
Exactly, it's Pole Poopsition
And 99 other games
It's like those old Nintendo carts that are like 250 games in one
Then the joke is, all the games suck
It's like one of those things
But anyway, I saw one of those
And I was like, those were pretty cheap too
So this is like this trend now in retro gaming
Is that the technology is so cheap for these tiny screens
We're probably gonna see even more of it in the coming years
I don't know
I wanna also of course introduce our chatroom over at live.vog.network.com
Again, live on Sunday nights at 6 o'clock Pacific
We read your chat comments
And you can participate along with the show
And sometimes you guys drive what we talk about here on air
I know there's other stuff going on in the entertainment world this evening
But I mean, isn't it pretty clear what's gonna win Best Picture?
No, there's not
About 14 nominees, anyway
So thank you guys for being here even when there's other stuff going on
But Darth Tetsuya is talking about the flashback portable
Kind of looked almost like a PSP or something
But a bunch of Atari classics on it
I think it also supported SD card ROMs
I didn't even realize that if that's the case, that's pretty rad
If you can actually load ROMs on it too
And how big of an SD card do you need for Atari 2600 ROMs?
Last I checked, I mean this was a while back when I downloaded the full ROM
So it was like 6 megs, so it can't be that large
Atari ROMs are like 4 kilobytes
That's what made the programming on that system and the things that they did so fucking impressive
Is that they had no space to work with
With Atari 2600 games
So it's really amazing the stuff that they crammed
I mean, as much of a garbage translation as Pac-Man is versus the arcade
The whole reason why the Pac-Man turned out garbage
Is because Atari wanted it on a 4k ROM cartridge
As opposed to a more expensive 8k cartridge
Which I think when they did Ms. Pac-Man on Atari 2600
Like a couple years later before the big bust and everything
If you ever played Ms. Pac-Man on Atari 2600
It's fine, it's not exactly like the arcade
But it's much more what you would expect an arcade translation to look like on the 2600
But the 4k only ROM on Pac-Man, that's what killed that game
Is that the guy was so limited on what he could work with
It's like, he could only have it
The reason why the ghosts flicker
Is because it could only draw one ghost each frame
It couldn't draw four ghosts
So it draws this ghost, then this ghost
That's okay, it's transparency right?
That's why I always thought it was
It's flickering because they're transparent
Stop Ian Chat says it does support SD cart ROMs
But it's not 100% compatible
Well that's kind of, I didn't even know that
Like I'm learning something here on Tonight's OLR
I had no idea, because that means I could play that homebrew shit
Like Halo for the 2600
Or didn't some guy go in and fix ET?
Yeah they fixed ET
That was the thing we reported on
So you could play Stacks
That game that was part of the Ready Player One contest
Yes, yes
Yes, I don't know why that's so fucking rad
But it is, I don't know
Anyway, let's see
Dark Tetsuya says there's a homebrew version of Pac-Man that's way badder
It was based on the Ms. Pac-Man conversion
Yes, if you've ever played that, it's great
Did he just remove the bow and that's it?
I guess and change the pink to blue or whatever
He had to do to change, yeah probably
Oh thank you, Bobby Blackpool says there was only three ghosts in the Atari 2600 version
I forgot that
I forgot that there was even, they had to downplay the three ghosts
It's hard enough even on that
I know, I know, jeez
I still, I still, even though it was garbage
The thing is, when you're six years old
Which I think is how old I was when I was playing Pac-Man on the 2600
You don't give a fuck
Like you, you just don't, I don't know
Does your six year old care about graphics and accuracy of things?
Yes
Maybe the 80's was just a simpler time
Well they, they will just, but see now they're so
Like they know what Minecraft is
They don't know anything 8 bit or 16 bit
They're like, look daddy, Minecraft
I'm like no, that's just how games look
I'm like, you better be good, I'm gonna make you play the Colecovision over here
Let's see how, you think that's terrible
Well, hold on
Darsakra, how do you view Colecovision gaming as punishment?
I don't
Exactly, but that's the point
Is they play it because they're forced to play it
And then they, they learn to appreciate it
But they won't because
The Colecovision was the best system of its time, seriously
Do you know how many gamer parents I've heard say
I'm gonna raise my kids the right way
And for the first three months that they're gaming
They're not allowed to play anything but Atari 2600 and Colecovision
That's too late, he already has a tablet
Like for example
In the next three months they do Nintendo
Let me just put it this way, okay
Today, alone, today, he must have watched and played
He got up at six o'clock this morning
And watched four hours of Minecraft YouTube videos
He then played another couple hours of Minecraft on the Wii U
Followed by probably what was like another three hours of Minecraft YouTube videos
That's too much Minecraft
Exactly, he doesn't shut the fuck up about Minecraft
All the goddamn time, like dude
I know you like Minecraft
I like Minecraft somewhat
But I don't need to hear Minecraft every fucking second of the game
Just like Daddy, Daddy was the only one that would talk about Minecraft here on OLR for a long time
But I didn't like fill every moment with Minecraft talk
Dark Tetsuya wants to point out about that Pac-Man ROM hack thing
They did redo the mazes
Let's not forget the maze was different in Pac-Man versus Ms. Pac-Man
Ms. Pac-Man had, I don't know if this came over on the 2600 conversion, it's been too long
But I remember the arcade was like four different mazes
As you upgraded through the fruit, you got different mazes
That was the future, Loki, was different mazes
Anyway, let's see
Stoppy in chat pointing out the Coleco Chameleon was punishment
Not the Coleco vision
That's called a scam, I'm sorry
Close, but not quite
SSU100Matt in chat at live.vognetware.com says
Forget going to your room without dessert, play Virtual Boy
Do you want your kid to develop chronic migraines?
Cause the Virtual Boy, that's how you're gonna do it
That is how you're gonna do it
You know it's quite fast, like I watched the Ben Heck tear down of the Virtual Boy
He actually made it better too
But like just learning how that worked, how the whole Virtual Boy thing worked
Was like a spinning mirror and they had just like lights
It literally was like one set of lights blinking on and off
And it just spinning to cover the whole screen
Oh, I always thought it was just one big screen
No, no, it's like lights bouncing off mirrors and shit
It's like, it's crazy
God, no wonder it gave people headaches, that sounds cheap
Alright, anyhow, let's get into tonight's kickoff topic
I wanna talk about a couple things here at the top of the show
Before we get into the rest of the gaming news
But the big thing this week
You know, OLR, we've been around 15 years
When the show first started
We were gaming on mostly the PlayStation 2
And I think the Xbox had just come out
I think we were finally getting Xboxes to play
Dance Dance Revolution Ultra Mix on Xbox
Like that was like back when the show started
When did Ultra Mix come out? Was that like, that wasn't too early in the Xbox
It wasn't too early, I remember when it came out
Because we had that guy that we used to play DDR with
Bring the Xbox over during OLR
That was when you and I lived together at the apartment we had with the pink carpet
Where we had the old webcam that would refresh every 30 seconds
That was when we played Ultra Mix for the first time
That was about the third year of the show probably
So maybe like 2003, 2004
So yeah, that was when that was out, Ultra Mix
But when the show first started it was mainly PlayStation 2
My point is, so we were here when PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 launched
We were here on PlayStation 4 and Xbox One launched
And this week, something that doesn't happen all the time is happening
We have a new console coming out
The Nintendo Switch is finally going to be out this Friday
So we will be living in a world where Nintendo NX is no longer something we speculate about
Over and over again because Nintendo won't say a goddamn thing about it
But we finally will be playing the Switch
And now that the press is getting their hands on the Switch
And more and more people are coming across
Nintendo Switch is out at expo events
I know Nintendo is in San Francisco with their tour
Which, with all respect, I didn't see the point of going to the San Francisco thing when it's out in like six days
I'm like, I'll have it in my living room in six days
So Nintendo Switch is going to be out
And we're finally learning the last few things about the console
Some of our questions getting answered
One of the big whoppers that they dropped on us this week
Virtual console ain't going to be there
No shit, you don't say
Well, now, again, not to inflate my ego too much
I need to be able to fit through the door
But did I not say on last week's show
We need to be prepared, it's not coming
Because they're not talking about it, it's not going to be here
Did I not say that like on last week's show
So, it doesn't mean I wasn't still disappointed in the news
And I gotta say
I really had to kind of like
I don't want to say argue about this
Because arguing over video games is sometimes silly
But I've had to have debates with this
Where I know so many people
That are huge Nintendo fans
Where it's like
If you criticize Nintendo
It's like you attack their religion or something
And it's like, okay, look
I can love video games, I do love video games
And I can love Nintendo, I do love Nintendo
I can still be critical of Nintendo
Question the things you love
Exactly, you can still sit here and go
This is something that should be better
And I do it with all the systems
Sony is not perfect
Microsoft is not perfect
Yes, she doesn't have an Xbox One
You know, Microsoft
And there's things I love about Microsoft
I think the Windows 10 integration is awesome
Personally, but anyway
I think Windows 10 is poop
It is awesome because now I don't have to buy an Xbox One
This isn't about Microsoft
Look, this is about Nintendo
And I think even though I can say I love Nintendo
I do feel like I get disappointed
By Nintendo a lot
Because you feel like there's these things that are like
The low hanging fruit
That's what they call it in the corporate world
The low hanging fruit that you think Nintendo could go for
And they don't
And this has been a battle for forever
It's been the whole online gaming thing
It's been like a low hanging fruit for Nintendo
That they never seem to get
That maybe they're going to get right with the Switch
Now they're going to charge money for it
But we don't know because Nintendo's really
Still not answering a lot of those questions
Although
What? Are we going to find out on Friday?
I guess we're going to have to with the online stuff
Right? Because Bomberman and all that stuff is supposed to be playable online
So we'll start to get some of those answers finally by Friday
But anyway
Virtual Console ain't going to be there day one
And I have to admit I'm a little bit disappointed
And you know
Some folks are trying to needle me on Twitter a little bit
Saying, oh Rob
Do you really have to play Balloon Fight on a
30 year old game on a brand new Nintendo console
And it's like
Well, yes
Actually
Because something that the Switch can do
That the other systems that
Virtual Console isn't available on
Is the whole fact that I could be playing
Something on my TV and then
Pick up my Switch and go somewhere else with it
And I was looking forward to being able to do that with
Yes, the old games too
Or the whole fact that
Perhaps if we're playing a two player game
Like the original Mario Brothers
Not Super Mario Brothers, the original Mario Brothers
Maybe I could have a Switch
And my friend who's over has a Switch
And we can play old school console
Games like that, you know
Like in the same room and be having fun with that
Right? So, yeah
I am a little disappointed that's not going to be there day one
I understand that Virtual Console will probably
Happen eventually
But it's another one of those things
Where I'm like, this launch
Is starting to feel more and more
Half-assed
And then I had one of my friends
Telling me about how, well when you look
At the other console launches
You know, how can you say that Nintendo is half-assed
Because PlayStation 4 had
All these ports when it came out and dah dah dah
And all this other stuff
Here's the thing
I was thinking about that
And this is one of the other key differences
The reason why I'm really feeling
This a lot is of how
Shady
Nintendo is being with the information
At least with PlayStation 4
At least with Xbox
And these other systems
We pretty much knew months in advance
Exactly what was going to come out of that box
We learned the answer about Virtual Console
This week
We still don't know the answers about online
And this is out in five days
Right? That's the shit that is starting
To make this really feel like
We're pulling it out of our asses as we go
We don't have any sort of like
And even the PlayStation 3 or even
Xbox 360, Xbox One
There was no question of how online
Was going to work for those systems
Or even that most of the feature sets
Advertised for it are going to be there at launch
Not, oh hey
Patch it in later
Dartitsuyu in chat says
But to be fair, is Virtual Console really
A huge deal? In the meantime, they're going to get
Arcade Archives, so if you need your retro fix
That would be the way to go
Arcade Archives is cool, but have they said
Witch games in the archives, there's
Kind of a lot of garbage in the Arcade Archives
There's some good stuff, there's some good Neo Geo
Fighters and like Bubble Bobble
Isn't that just Virtual Console anyways?
It's Sony's thing, it's like arcade emulation
Basically, and yeah, it's
It is kind of just Virtual Console, so it is weird
To me that it's, the Arcade Archives
Thing is getting a whole spinoff, but
Whatever, it doesn't make sense
It's probably because
Their networking shit ain't worked out
Because if you think about it
That isn't
I mean, I guess it does make sense that Virtual Console
Is not there, because they're saying that Virtual Console now
Is going to support net play over
You know, over the internet
As you're going to be able to do multiplayer
So because they don't have their net code shit figured out
That's why you don't have the networking
The online networking right now, or multiplayer
For the most part
I mean, at least that paid service
And maybe that's why Virtual Console's not out
Whereas these arcade games don't have
That, or at least I assume they don't have
That internet play
And so that's why they're able to just dump them on there
So anyway, um
Let's see, what's the other thing here
Sj100matt in chat says
I would like a Virtual Console lineup to supplement the inevitable
Dead period between games on the Switch
Yeah, that's true too
And to be fair, maybe there was a part of me
That was hoping that Nintendo was
Going to do it differently this time
With Virtual Console, I know, hahaha
But that they would actually have a
Constant flow of Virtual Console
Releases, which if you look at the Wii U
In the past couple years, it has not been a constant flow
But, you know, God
There's this story floating around the internet
About a guy who just beat
714 Nintendo
Games on his Twitch stream, right?
There's a big story going around about that this week, right?
So there's over
700 Nintendo games
That they could put on Virtual Console
You put one game a week
And that's just Nintendo
And that would carry that system for over
10 years
Like with new stuff
Ok, I understand, some of those games are garbage
Licensing issues
Blah de blah de blah, fine
Get like 200 of the 700 games
Less than a third
Get 200 of them
That's still going to be like one new game a week
For almost 4 years
And that's just Nintendo
That's not even counting
Super Nintendo, Genesis, Turbo Graphics
Commodore 64 they could bring back
Because that's the soft spot in my heart
They did like 4 Commodore 64 games on the Wii
And then that was it
Yeah, I guess I'm just a little bummed
I was just hoping
Maybe Virtual Console would be a little better
This time
Doesn't sound like it's going to be
So it's a little bit disappointing in my opinion
But
I will give Nintendo this credit
Because, oh my gosh, I can be critical
And I can say good things too
And I am very excited to hear
That it sounds like more games are actually
Making the launch day, right?
Yeah, more games are making the launch day
And also with that
They're physical games, you know
If you're like, of course, buying digitally
You're going to have to install everything
But they're physical games, unlike the PlayStation 4
And Xbox One
Do not require an install on top of
The game
It's just going to be whatever's on that
That cartridge
That's going to be cool
At least right now
Can't promise that for the future
Yeah, that's still cool
That more games are going to make the actual launch day
I know I'm very excited for Fast Racing
Neo Remix
Thought that was a very competent game on the Wii U
So I'm excited to see what they do with that
With the Switch
Now that's another game I will have to get on March 3
Because right now, as it was
I was really only going to get Zelda
I'm not really interested in the Bomberman
Thing, which I've talked about before
Maybe when I see it in action, I'll change my mind
But I'm not willing to
Take the leap of faith on Bomberman
The way I'm willing to do with Zelda
But I know Fast Racing Neo, I'm willing to take the leap of faith with that
So I'm excited to get that
And what, Snipperclips
Or whatever they're calling that, that's out
On March 3rd as well
Nippleclamps, that's out on March 3rd as well
You can use your Joy-Con
And explore fun new ways with your friends
To titillate
With HD vibrations
But yeah, Snipperclips
I'm sure will be fun
And that might be a good in the same room type of game too
So I mean, yes, there's positive things as well
I like that
Okay, now Nintendo's coming out swinging out the door
With more than just Zelda
Even though, you know, of course, Zelda's a big freaking deal
But that'll be nice
So, I'm still getting my Switch
I can huff and puff about Virtual Console
I think I'm just
Accepting that
The Switch for right now
Is going to be a Zelda machine
For the first couple months
And Nintendo should really be thanking BioWare
For going to be distracting me
With Mass Effect Andromeda
In these first few months
Right after, you know, I get some good hands on time with Zelda
And then by the time I'm done with Mass Effect Andromeda
Oh, here comes Mario Kart
Splatoon 2
And everything else that, you know, we have to look forward to
Do you have all your amiibo pre-ordered?
Because you gotta get all the amiibo stuff
Nintendo seems to think so
So, yeah
So, I mean, at least
There's that and, you know, by the summer
We get Splatoon 2, which is a big deal
Arms, I'm hearing a lot of
Positive stuff on, I'm still skeptical
But I'm willing to say, okay, well
Let me get it in my arms and play with it
And maybe I'll be sold on it
I'm excited to check it out
And then Holiday will be
The Mario game, I know, Loki
You like to joke that it'll get delayed
I think we all know Nintendo can't afford to delay that
They'll have that on Holiday
Or they'll have some big fucking title for Holiday
They have to, because the real launch
Of the Switch is Holiday
I fully expect Virtual Consoles in place
Probably in October
Star Fox Zero, again
No, they're not that bold
I hope not, anyway
Let's see, JD is in our chat over at
Live.vognetwork.com saying
A couple people I know who went to the demo
The San Francisco thing this weekend
I wasn't sold on Arms until I
Played it. William
Murderface points out Stormblood
Will be a nice time sink as well, that's right
Final Fantasy XIV gets an expansion
Nintendo can thank Square Enix as well
For that, so there'll be things to distract
Me from, you know, okay
I'm done with Zelda on the Switch, now what?
So, alright
Anyway, what else on the Switch?
Anything else we need to talk about with the Switch before
We move on into gaming weeks and
What else is going on? Just most of the downloads are
Pretty reasonably sized, it looks like anything that's
More of just like a digital only titles
Is they're gonna be about 1 gig
Ish, whereas
You know, comparable
Download sizes to the Wii U
Cause I was looking at, they had Mario Kart 8 listed
On there, and it's about the same size as
On the Wii U, which makes sense cause
The visuals are pretty much the same
And then, you know, Zelda of course
Being the biggest one, like 13.6
Gigs or something
Which is like half your storage right there
Yeah, because even though they say 32 gigs
The operating system
Takes up so much of it, and there's gonna be a
Day one patch by the way, so
Expect that more of it will get eaten up
Just don't buy digitally, at least on this system
Cause it doesn't really make sense as far as
Being able to store it on there right now
And because Nintendo's so good
At not dropping prices of their games
So that means your game's gonna be worthwhile
Later on, and once you've finally played out
Zelda to your heart's content
Then you can always sell it back later on
Like Fast Racing Neo, is that getting a physical release?
No, that's not, but like I'm talking about the ones you do have a choice
You know, just buy it at retail
Is I Am Setsuna still a March 3rd game?
I think so
I haven't checked that out on the other platforms yet
So I was thinking about maybe getting that one too on the Switch
Just to buff up the library a little bit
So, yeah, okay
Well, I'm gonna definitely pick up a Switch on Friday
And I can't wait to talk all about it on the next edition of the show
I'm hoping over the weekend, at some point
I can connect with some other people that own a Switch
And we can test out some of the multiplayer stuff
And, you know, get a feel for it
You know, I'm still excited, despite these things
Where I'm like, I have to constantly lower expectations sometimes
I am still excited
I'm excited because everything I'm hearing
About the whole fact that, you know, you play on the TV
And then you pick it up and take it with you
It's super seamless, it's fast
It works the way you think it would based on the previews
I think a lot of that sounds really exciting
It sounds like, if nothing else, as a tech nerd
The technology's gonna be awesome
Even if sometimes I wish Nintendo would do a little more with the technology
That's all it is
So, yeah, and DungeonBuster in chat over at live.vognetwork.com
Says, it's been getting good reviews so far
And ActDeft confirming, iAmSatsuna is March 3rd, yeah
JD pointing out, aren't SD cards cheap and easy to upgrade on consoles?
Yeah, there is that
So, I mean, even though Loki's saying, don't go digital
I still understand, I understand what you're saying when it comes to like that
But does it have expanded storage on that console?
Oh, yeah, you can pop in another SD card, that's it
Are they gonna allow you to save to it?
Yes, yes, no, that's not a problem
They are making that a lot easier than it was on their other systems
So that part's, well, even on the Wii, it really wasn't that bad
But I think it's even gonna be a little better on the Switch
I'm not worried about that end of it at all
But I think you do raise a damn good point
When, and I've always said this, you know, what's the benefit in me buying digital, right?
Because you said Nintendo doesn't drop the price on their games for a long time
So you have more
Or at all, I mean
You have more equity basically in those cartridges
Those cartridges are still worth something
So if you do get sick of the game, you can sell it back
And you make some money back
Whereas with digital games, you don't ever get to do that
Yeah, like, I mean, I'm not saying that Zelda isn't necessarily a great example
Because Zelda's gonna be probably, I mean, that Zelda
I think it's gonna be one that's gonna have a lot of replayability on it
But like something like ARMS or something
Where you may buy it and it may be fun for a while
And it's just like, okay, listen, I'm just not really interested in playing this anymore
That might be something that's worth picking up physically and doing that
I mean, I'm definitely looking forward to picking up Zelda
Just to be picking it up on the Wii U
I haven't pre-ordered it, so I'll try to go pick it up day one
And if they say, oh, it's not available, like, well, fine, I'll just download it
I'm not pre-ordering your shit fucking GameStop
Let's see, a couple of people in chat talking about the whole memory card thing
And a couple of people saying it looks like two terabytes may be the cap on the memory cards
And what the Switch supports, but, okay, two terabytes
Let's not get ahead of ourselves, I mean, there's not that many games coming out for you
I mean, shit
You could probably fit
That's a little much
You could probably fit everything that Nintendo's gonna release this year on that kind of card
Or in the lifetime of the system
But that is low-key
That is good, though, that, you know, yes, it will go that high if people do want to do the digital thing
Because there are people that disagree
And they think that the digital thing is much more of a convenience
Especially those that are gonna be more portable with the system
Fine, more power to you
They are really missing out, though, not having YouTube or Netflix or anything on that thing
I'm serious, like, that's what my son uses before we got his tablet
That's the way he would use it
And he still uses the Wii U for that, is watching YouTube
And I think Netflix on the TV to the portable instantly is a real missed opportunity
We talked about that in a previous episode, I'm not gonna re-hide that
But, you know what, maybe it'll be there by holiday
I think we need to go back and re-evaluate, I think it'll be interesting
I almost feel like I wanna, like, write down every- maybe we'll do this on the next episode of OLR
Tell me if you guys think this is a good idea
On the next episode of OLR, what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna write down the list of my grievances
And things I wish they would do better on the Switch
I'm gonna write it down, and we're gonna put it in an envelope and leave it here in the studio
And during the Christmas episode of OLR, we're gonna open it and see what problems Nintendo addressed during the year to make the console a full-fledged system
Shortest time capsule ever
Yeah, shortest time capsule ever
I like that, that's the segment
Short attention span time capsule
We should just do one of those every year
I think it's a good idea, short attention span time
Well, shit, episodes of this show are kind of- we could just always go back and listen to an old episode of OLR
But that would involve us having to listen to ourselves
I don't wanna do that
No, not gonna do that
I certainly don't wanna listen to myself the way I sound right now
I don't even wanna talk the way I sound right now
Alright, done
JD in a sock
Yes, JD in chat says a mini time capsule is a great idea
Come on, Noel Gus in chat says put your list in a sock
And you know what?
I love it, we're gonna put it in a sock
No, you know, we need a time capsule, you know what that means?
We need to get one of those little containers of the mini Tootsie Rolls
That's actually also doubles as a piggy bank
I gave you one
And there you go
So vanilla ones
I wasn't thinking of the short attention span time capsule
And then on top of that, we get mini Tootsie Rolls
I support this play, okay
And we'll leave one in the time capsule as a present to ourselves
You know what? I should like put in like a clipping of my hair to see if my hair color is like
Is that gonna be like a
Pused by the end of the year or something
Okay, I love it
We're creating a scene in the Christmas story where we're like we're cutting it into three pieces, you know
This mini Tootsie
Alright, this is happening on the next OLR
Short attention span time capsule 2017 edition Nintendo Switch
I actually think I still have one of those containers somewhere
Alright, then bring it to the show and that can be our time capsule
Let's go buy another one
If not, then I'll just go to the dollar store
I will find a sock
Get a plastic bin
We'll paint it silver
Okay, it has to fit here in the studio somewhere
We have to
Alright, I love it
Come on, Noel Gush suggests
Go to the 99 cent only store and put a Lego dimensions figure in it as well
Dude, yeah, like I want to run across those
Like my son got one as like a Valentine's Day card or whatever
And of course he's like, I don't want this
And it was the Simpsons car
I was like, sweet, where do I get more of these?
I like building Legos
Like more than any person probably should
But I like it
Alright, anything else on the Switch we need to talk about before Friday?
No
Alright, there it is
So, Darsakha, will you at least
Will you try playing with my Switch before we
Shove things in a sock?
I'm going to pretend that you didn't phrase it exactly that way
Alright
I would entertain
Phrasing
I would entertain the possibility
Of a demo of the Nintendo Switch
That you just happen to own
Socks not included
Okay, fair enough
JD in chat simply says, whoa
Phrasing
That's Emmison Mansey
You know what, that's going to be our quote
Our word of the year, like Tatiana's choices
Phrasing
That Archer episode was like four years ago
So I kind of think
That's like every Archer episode
I've only watched like one season of Archer
Okay, first off
And What's Your Face was pregnant most of it
First off, Archer is fucking amazing
Like it's got some of the greatest quotes in it
Like I just said, Emmison Mansey
Do you like ants?
Do you want ants? Because that's how you get ants
Why not that?
Lots of great
Archer quotes, anyway
Let's move on
I was ready to move on
Let's move on to our
Too many socks
Alright, that's in the 2015 capsule
Oh god
How was your gaming week?
What types of video games have you been playing this week?
And what socks have you been wearing?
Dark Sakura
I have these very cushy socks that I got at Daiso
In Roseville
They're $1.25 a piece
And their pile, they're very comfortable
They're my new favorite pair of socks
For $1.25?
Yeah, seriously, fucking Daiso
I know what a Daiso is
Cat socks at Daiso, worth every penny
One of those vacuums?
That's Dyson
It's like a Japanese Dollar Tree
It's like the Dollar Tree that everything in there is like
In Japan it's like a Yen store
Where's this? The Galleria
They have one at the Galleria and they're putting one in South Sac
Which is going to be like
Daiso, yeah
Oh my god, I'm going to be so happy
I fucking love Daiso
Anyway, so now that the socks are out of the way
Let's go ahead and get on to my
game I've been playing
Game singular, because fuck
AkumaJP is pointing out it's a 100 Yen shop
That's what I corrected myself
Okay, I was going to say 1 Yen is actually not a lot of money
No, I corrected myself
It's like the Peso store
Did everyone not hear when I corrected myself?
No, we were laughing too hard at the sock thing
Girl, okay
Video games!
But also my Daiso socks are amazing
Anyway, so I've just been playing World of Warcraft
Like, a lot
Dan's probably
Addict
You know what, yeah, kinda
How does it feel all these years later?
Well, I really, though, I like this whole
expansion because
I am an Illidan fangirl
And it's just been
Demon Hunties all over the place
Addict
You should still play with me in VRT
Because it's fun
Are the gameboy.org guys ever on there?
John was on once
To give me
Guild adding privileges
Oh, cool
And then, I actually
I had bad
insomnia one night and played Bust a Move
on my phone, as in Puzzle Bobble
And
I don't know what the hell I did
I was on some fucking streak
And my highest
score had been like 500,000
for a while
I hit 1,500,000
And I don't even know what I did
So, lots of Bust a Move
And then
Pokemon Go, because all the new Pokemans
are out and they're adorable
Except for this one thing
That I wasn't even thinking of Magma being part of its name
And you know how I feel about
Snails and Slugs, I hate them
And it was called
It's Slugma
Slugma, right
I didn't for a moment think about Magma
Do not go to the nastiest place possible on this show
I did go to the nastiest place possible
That's all you need to say
Until someone pointed out that
No, that's fire and it's magma
And not the favorite curse from Red Dwarf
So
Yeah
I caught one and I don't care anymore
So
Um
I have a Furret now
And it's adorable
The Furrets are cute, considering they're the new Pidgeys
And those things, the Centrets or whatever
Are fucking everywhere
And now I have all these Furrets
The Furrets are adorable
I just want to take a nap in a pile of Furrets
You do want a Furret coat for Christmas?
No!
I want them to be alive and scribble
I want them to be pets for reals
But that's really been
Oh yeah, Miitomo
I'm still doing Miitomo
I do realize though, some of the Gen 2 Pokemon
Get really uncreative
Like, there's a Pokemon called
Pineco
Do you know what it is?
It's a fucking pinecone
And his name is Pineco
That I think is the prettiest one right now
Is the Xatu
Oh yeah, the evolved
I caught one on its own
But they're pretty
Like, Mayan and Incan
Design
And I really like the design
Some of the designs are really cool
My watch told me to stand, so I'm standing
Alright, you stand
Catch a Pokemon with your watch
I have been doing Pokemon Go with my Apple Watch
And I have to talk about that a little bit
Sure, go for it
If you can't bust out your phone
But you're going to go for a walk
I don't know how this works on the Series 2
It has the built-in GPS and everything
But I find it really neat
That when I'm doing my walk at work
I just turn it on on my watch
And it actually even has
Kind of like how your little thing blinks
You know, when there's Pokemon nearby
It'll actually show me the list of them
And let me pick which ones I want to catch
It lets me hit the Pokestop as I'm walking around
But the other thing too
Is that the feedback that it gives
For my walking for Pokemon
Goes into my
Workout ring
Or close the rings challenge
That's a big thing
All over the place
It applies to my
Workout ring on my watch
So
I love the integration
It's really fun
Is that like Fitbit? Because when I play Pokemon Go
I still get the credit on Fitbit
I honestly think it's more accurate than Fitbit
And I've read a lot of comparisons and things
And they always are updating it with every OS
I'm still on the iPhone 6 Plus
And the big thing they added into that
Was they put a Fitbit type thing in it
So I know I'm getting crazy
Same with the Success Plus
Or Success, what I have
But the watch will also monitor your heartbeat
And so as you're walking
It will put it into your whole
Workout thing
So every time your heart rate goes up
It counts as workout time
I have the weirdest question about the watch
Does it work if you own two iPhones?
Can it sync to both?
Or no, you have to pick one
You have to pick one, but you can do two watches
For a phone
But pairing, I mean, it takes like
A minute
It's only because
Basically your data is stored on your phone
And syncs to your watch
Because the watch doesn't have that big of a capacity
But I mean
And if you get a series too
Could you imagine swimming for your Pokemon walking?
That would be pretty rad
But yeah, I hadn't played a lot with it
Until this past week
And I was actually really
Delighted by how it worked
Very surprised, very delighted
It just really
Was uh
It made it a lot more fun for me
Because then I didn't have to stare at my
Phone while I was going walking
I could actually just leave it and go
And it was really fun
So it's like
Having your little device
What's it called?
Yeah, it's like having that
But more interactive
And then you get the little thumps on your wrist
When it finds stuff
So that's cool, the whole haptic feedback
So anyway, that's my mini review
Of Pokemon Go on the Apple Watch
Alright, there it is
Moving on, Loki, how was your gaming week?
I played lots of Skyrim
As usual
And then of course also played
Until Dawn Rush of Blood
Because I actually haven't played
Too much of that
I've been demonstrating it a lot for people
But I actually went and decided to play
Some of it myself
And that game is still a lot of fun
I really enjoy that game
But it's kind of funny though
Because everybody else that plays those games
The first time they're jumping and everything
And I'm just like fucking going to town
Killing shit with my guns
But I really do enjoy that game
And I've also been getting lots of peer pressure
To get Overwatch
So I don't know if I'm going to do that though
It's not really on sale too much right now
It's like 17% off
Or something like that on the
Playstation Store
But I don't know
People want me to play it
That's it
Oh well, Pokemon Go actually
I don't have the plus yet
But I've been playing a little bit of Pokemon Go
Mainly just enough to keep my
Streaks going each day
That's about it
Honestly I'll turn on every once in a while
Usually if I need items I'll go get that
When I'm walking around midtown
To catch stuff
I just kind of look around to see if there's anything new
I got one that looks like a cow
Oh the milk tank?
Or whatever it's called?
Those are apparently pretty good
I don't have one yet
So I have one of those
Yeah it's like the same shit
It's like the same shit all over the place
It's like okay well shit I've already got all those
Like I don't want any more of that crow
Witch thing
There's too many of those
And they don't evolve
Yeah they're fucking useless
They're only good to finally get
The fucking dark trophy
For catching dark types
That's what it's good for, that's it
Alright well I guess I'll do that then
Yeah I don't know, just recycle it
And JD points out it will evolve in Gen 4
Oh okay let me just wait until 2020
For that you know
Save those candies
Save those candies yeah
Alright
I have to check my demon hunter right now
On Warcraft? Oh yeah cause the whole app and all that
That's actually pretty nice
I'll tell you what I haven't really played at all this week
Ingress
Because I'm finding
Very little point to do that anymore
I've been burned out too
For me it's the fact that there's no
Like the live event thing
I know they're doing shards
But it's not exciting for me
I could give a shit about shards
The shard thing is too limited I think
And every time I hear shard I just think of shart
It's appropriate
Alright
My gaming week
So pretty much a lot of the same standbys
I've been streaming some of it on my twitch channel
Cheatplug, Rob Roberts on twitch
Please please follow me if you aren't already
I appreciate it, I've been really trying to grow
Things over there on twitch
And I've been doing more streaming
A lot of the old same
Standby stuff, Final Fantasy 14 and
Overwatch which I'm still continuing to play this week
Which by the way Loki, act deft and chat
Over at live.vognetware.com
It's practically screaming in caps, get Overwatch
Loki, yes I know everybody wants me
Everyone wants
Me to get Overwatch
A lot of people that I'm co-workers with
They play on PC so
My PC's not
I don't think it's good enough to run Overwatch
You might want to check
Sometimes Blizzard's pretty good about making sure
I need a new PC anyways
I've been looking at getting either a new laptop
Or a new desktop
But the laptops are pretty decent for the price
And now they have the new Ryzen chips that came out
Which look pretty nice
My out of date monster will run Overwatch
So
This probably will
I don't know
I would use controller though
I guess I would lose that against keyboard mouse right?
Probably
Unless, well play a character
Like Torbjorn or Symmetra where you can set up
Like turrets and robots to do
The things for you that might help
Anyway, so I've been playing some Overwatch
Then let's see I was continuing to play
Skyrim HD which I talked about a little bit last week
I was playing that a little more on
Xbox One and still really
Enjoy the graphics, like I'm like okay wow
This game really does look good you know
It makes me very excited for Elder Scrolls 6
Which I hope they announce sooner rather than later
Even though I think it's going to be a
Fallout game this year
Like a New Vegas 2 or something
Another one? But they just did Fallout 4
Fallout New Vegas 2 or whatever it is
I think is what the rumors say for this year
No
We'll see, we'll see
Other than that I did download a few new things
I did not realize
This was on Playstation 4
But I think it just came out recently
Which was a Chinese rooms
Game that they did
Before, it was only one of their first games
It was the Half-Life mod that there was a
Spinoff game before they did
Everybody's Gone to the Rapture, which you know
I loved that game, so the fact that
It was only like, because they're doing a big sale
On Playstation right now so it was only like 4 or 5 bucks
For Dear Esther even though I think it's new
On Playstation 4, it's not a new game at all
It's been out for like 10 years, but I'd never played it
So I wanted to get in there and play it
And I didn't get super far in it
I didn't really like talk about the story or anything yet
But it is really pretty
I mean, again, the fact that it's not on Playstation 4
Like, you know, walking on these
Barren cliffs
By the ocean and this grey
Very dreary setting
It does look gorgeous
For what it's worth, so I had fun with that
And then another game I downloaded which I played a little more of
Which I did enjoy
Was this little game called Enter the Gungeon
Which I played a little bit of, lowkey
I saw that
Did you see that when I was playing that?
So that was fun, I liked that
It's pretty much like a roguelike
I guess
But with guns, and yes you do
You go through the dungeon, you find stronger guns
To take on more bosses
And find more guns
And bosses based off guns
So I didn't play a lot
But I played enough, I played through the tutorial
And then I was playing the beginning stage a little bit
I got through at least the first floor
And beat one of the bosses
Which is kind of weird
So yeah I was having fun with that
And I didn't realize in the theme song
To Enter the Gungeon, they actually have a whole custom thing
Where they're actually singing about the Gungeon
So that was a nice touch
Props to them
So I was enjoying that
So that was pretty much my gaming week
Alright
I was getting into housekeeping here
But there's not a lot to tell you
Besides please follow us on Twitter
We're also on Facebook
And I do want to mention
On Twitch TV
We not only have our own channel on Twitch
Which we haven't really been using a lot of recently
Admittedly, but we are trying to build up the presence
For VOG Network over on Twitch
If you do follow VOG Network
Over on Twitch
Several of the hosts that do things here at VOG Network
We auto host their feeds
And at a later time we're hoping to bring you some content
Original to the Twitch feed of VOG Network as well
So check that out
We were talking about that a little bit on last week's show
And then Bobby went in and like
Figured out how to get back in there
And made sure it was up and running this week
So he did all that, so thanks Bobby
So check that out
Let's get into some gaming news
Lots more to cover, right Loki?
Yep, and as I was talking about
My gaming week this week I of course played
Lots of the Playstation VR
And apparently it's selling pretty well as well
So they're also
They have revealed that as of February 19th
They've sold about
915,000 units
So they're actually
Expected to hit their estimate
Of about 1 million units by mid April
Originally they were
Forecasting 2.6 million units
But of course they lowered that down to
750,000 which they've
Already exceeded, so
Good for them, apparently that makes the
Playstation VR the highest selling headset
Of the three main contenders
The Vive, Rift, and
Gear VR
Alright no I'm sorry
It's actually the Vive and the Rift
Including the Playstation VR
The Gear VR is actually I think sold
A little bit better
So hopefully this bodes well for Sony actually
Continuing to support it
Because there was some of us worried that it could go down a path like the Vita
I still think
Just everybody show that stuff
They get really
Wowed by it
So I still think it's just getting
It in the people's faces basically
To try it
And once they've tried it
I don't think I've ever had anyone go
Oh that's dumb
Or like this is never going to take off
It's always been like holy shit
Just amazing
That this is
Even a thing
And so it's just getting people to try it
And once they've tried it then they pretty much
Become evangelists for it
I don't know if you guys know
But I never did end up getting one
For Pro which in retrospect
Was probably the wrong decision to be honest
But it's okay
I own it
Well I don't know
I don't know if I'd be using the Playstation VR
The whole time if I owned it
Do you use it regularly?
I have been recently using it more often
I haven't really been playing VR games in it
But I'm always like whenever they have sales
And stuff I'm always looking to see what games are on sale
And I do have some in my backlog
That I get to play
It's funny actually the other day
I was looking through my catalog of stuff
I'm like man I thought I had more games than this
And then I looked and I'm like
Oh wait that's stuff that's been downloaded
And I'm like 187 games
Holy shit
My Playstation library is looking just like
My Steam library
But yeah there's like
Oh I bought Need for Speed
And Dragon Age Inquisition
When the fuck did that happen?
Silly stuff
Not really a game I would play
But I definitely want to try it in VR
I played for just a little bit this week
I played Rez
The new one that came out
The reimagining for the second time
But I don't have Playstation VR
I've just been playing it on the TV
And I still love it
I do kind of
If I had a VR thing I would like to play this
God so many cords everywhere
With that VR headset
My house is already a mess
I mean really
Because you just have the one that combines
The HDMI and whatever
That other thing
So it's basically
Just that and then everything plugs into it
I mean yeah you can kind of twist it up
And stuff but
Just don't be stupid don't spin around circles
Like my son does
Bobby Blackwolf in chat says the PSVR has
Almost sold as much as Eye of Judgment
No Eye of Judgment
Will never sell that
Eye of Judgment is dead
It's gone
That bet is never happening
They stopped making them
It's over
They didn't make a million of them
Unless you could always hope
Now here's what you have to do
Here's what y'all have to hope for if you want Loki in the tingle outfit
You need
And for those that are newer to OLR
And don't understand what this joke is
When the Eye of Judgment
The Playstation 3
There was this game that they were doing
With a game
It was an augmented reality card game
And it was dumb because you played an actual card game
And all it did was
Change the graphics on the TV
And it was like
Wasn't it expensive too?
It was just not a very well thought out idea
I mean I'm sure the game
We went and saw the demo
At E3 and I was just like
I don't see the point
Somebody didn't really think this through
Somebody was like
It's the Ryan Reynolds picture
But why?
But you jump to conclusions
So anyway
The whole bet was
That if they would sell
And Loki was like it's never gonna sell
So I don't even know how it happened
But Loki made a bet and said look
If the Eye of Judgment sells a million copies
I will come to the show dressed as Tingle
From the Legend of Zelda singles
It was a talk like Tingle
I don't know what the hell the thing was
Well at the time we were on camera
We were on Justin TV at the time
And so you would do your little dance on camera
And we'd all have a good laugh
But you knew in the back of your mind that's never gonna fucking happen
No it's never gonna happen
It was a safe bet
It's garbage
So here's what you all need to hope for
If you want Loki to ever dress up as Tingle
Which just isn't gonna happen at this point
And Sony does this sometimes
For a new piece of technology
Cause Sony does this right
Sony said they do the
With the Playstation
Their online magazine thing
They reclaim the name or something
So sometimes Sony will reclaim names
And use them for other things
So maybe they'll bring back Eye of Judgment
And it's like a new game
Or it's a new something
Like something in virtual reality
And it's fucking awesome and sells ten million copies
Now we can sit here and say Loki
That's not the same Eye of Judgment though
Cause someone can make a game called
The Eye of Judgment
Like a free to play game
I don't know like a one penny game
And they'll sell it and say ha ha
See they sold a million copies
No but the bet was Sony has to sell
A million copies of the Eye of Judgment
Anyhow
Not gonna happen
Let's see
Bobby Blackwolf pointing out
That's right
And I think all these years later
Bobby was very protective of the secrets
But I think I'm safe to tell you
If you never found Loki and Flappy Vog
As Tingle, it's in there
And you need to play more
I'll leave you with that
If Bobby wants to just yell it in chat
If you play enough of Loki
In Flappy Vog
Eventually you'll get Loki as Tingle
Yes it was an embarrassing part of my life
But it's hilarious actually
I recorded that
I recorded that in my car
Off my laptop in the rain
In the parking lot of my work
Because there is no quiet place
To make those noises
At my place of employment
Without
Embarrassing myself
He does the voices you guys
It's worth revisiting Flappy Vog
This week and checking that out if you never saw that
Alright anyway
Let's move on
Register participation for this week's episode of
Orange Laundry Radio at vognetwork.com
Use the passphrase, inch
ActDeft in chat points out
It was kind of random
Alright anyway let's talk about speaking of random
Fallout Fantasy 15 has been getting
Updates here and there and they finally released
What like a booster pack this week
Patch 1.05
Released this week which
Supports this new booster pack which has
Some items for fishing
All I know is it tried to download the update on my system
I don't have enough hard drive space for that
Oh gosh is it really that big of a
Hell no must have been
Well anyway there is a new level cap
For your characters you can go up to 125
In levels you can also store
200 Prompto pictures now
And there is also an MP3 player
For Noctis when you are riding on a
Chocobo which you didn't have before
But also the 1.05 update
Is the long awaited
PlayStation 4 patch
Which will allow the frame rate
To go up to a maximum of 60 frames a second
On a PlayStation Pro
I'm a PlayStation 4 Pro
Owner and let me tell you
I haven't noticed a difference
Playing Fallout Fantasy 15 under this new patch
Granted I didn't do a lot
But when I did play
I didn't notice a difference
So good job on that investment
Rob PlayStation 4 Pro
Anyway
Some users out there on the internet
Noticing that some of the frame rates
And the transition between different frame rates
Is pretty jarring
So I guess
Maybe I'm not playing in the right mode
Do I need to actually go into the high mode
Maybe that's why I didn't do right
So maybe I'll go back
And tinker with that a little bit
Just to see if I can get the game to
Look even prettier but
It looked good enough for what it's worth
Anyway
I guess near playlists were added
To the game too
As you're driving around you can actually listen to the soundtracks
Near if you want to hear that
Sure cool
Alright
How about the DLC with Gladio and all that stuff
That's what I'm really waiting for
Cup noodle
Yeah my cup noodle hat where's that
Can't wait for that
Moving on Dark Sakura
What do you have for us
I have stuff
Very sad stuff
A moment of silence if you will
Alan Stone who was the co-founder
Of Nintendo of America
Died
It was reported on February 23
He died at
71 from cancer
71 is still a decent run
But still you know
With current life spans that is
A little short still
He was
One of the people behind getting
You know the original Mario Brothers
And Donkey Kong
To be as popular as it was
Over here and so we actually
I would even say oh the
Resurgence of video gaming in America
To him so
RIP
People probably don't remember that
You know there was a lot of stores out there
That were really tepid
On stocking Nintendo
And Sega after
The huge video game crash and you know
Nintendo of America had to work very hard
To make Nintendo
A success in this country which they did
So yeah I think
We owe a lot to
You know what Alan Stone
Did and fuck cancer etc
Indeed
It's
Also I don't know was he still involved
With Nintendo in later years
Or probably not
Because I was going to say it really kind of sucks
Here we are a week before the Switch releases
I'm pretty sure he would have been excited to see that
But he probably had moved on from Nintendo
Later in his career as you know people come
And go from jobs all the time in different companies
So but anyway a tip
Of the hat there for Alan Stone
And thank you
For everything you did to set up Nintendo
In America
Loki let's change the subject
Something a little brighter please
Yes definitely a little bit brighter because
We're going to be talking about sunset overdrive
And that was a pretty bright game
Yes it was it was a very fluorescent game
So you know
It didn't do as well as Microsoft had hoped
But
They're saying that they still may continue on
Even without Microsoft
So
You know basically you know the president
Of Insomniac Ted Price
Said that while there hasn't been any movement
On a sequel you'd you know
Have asked Microsoft about that
But we're passionate about the franchise
And we own it so you may see more
Sunset in the future from us
No promises and no timeline
To speak of but it's something
That represents our willingness to create
Unexpected experiences
And of course they're working on the new Spider-Man
Right now
I would be totally down for cross-platform
Sunset overdrive game or hey
Sony exclusive
Sunset overdrive game
Oh yeah I know
I know people that really enjoyed sunset overdrive
I didn't I didn't get into it
I kind of tried to play it but I really didn't
Get into it the way I think a lot of people did
But I know there's a lot of people who'd be very happy
To see them kind of continue it because
I don't think it sold to the expectations
That Microsoft had I mean Microsoft
Gave it away during one of those games with gold
Promotions at one point so
You know I don't think it quite had the sales that
They'd hoped for but yet NAC
Still hasn't been given away yet
That's you know what that's a good point and NAC is getting a
Sequel you know what that's a darn good point so if NAC
Can get a fucking sequel why can't sunset overdrive
Get a sequel alright that's well put
Loki well put
Alright
Let's move on I know a lot of you are fans
Of Jim Sterling over on YouTube
You're one of them right Loki? Yes I am
You like to watch this well you're probably happy to hear this
I'm very aware of the situation yeah
So you probably know more about this than I do
Apparently what happened the case dismissed
This week with
Jim Sterling fighting with Digital Homicide
This was where Digital Homicide
Did what basically come out and said that
He
Basically was what slander was that what it was about?
It was a whole bunch of stuff so he had done
A bunch he does a series called
Best of Scene Greenlight where he'll show
Off games that are just garbage
And he'll like make fun of them
And then he also does you know like a let's play
Series that he does with
Different games like that and one of the games he showed
Was the Slaughtering Grounds which was this
Like you know very
Basic first person shooter game that
Used a bunch of pre-bought assets from the Unity
Store and didn't really do anything
And so he just you know
Called it like an asset flip and so
Then James Romain
Who was part of
Digital Homicide
Came out with a video slamming
Him on his review of the game
To which you know he's like this isn't a review
It's a let's play and then
So he decided to do a
Review of a review
And like did that and I think it even
Went another step further but
It came down to like they were saying that he
You know was
Slandering them and he caused them
Financial harm and they were trying to sue him for like
Ten million dollars when in reality he
Probably brought more publicity to their game
Right and then they would have had otherwise
These guys weren't exactly right in the head
Anyways let me get in the heat like
Allegedly don't sue us
He um you know
Also like did like an interview with him and stuff
And it was just it was
Cringy but so to make a
Long story short he went this
Went you know they pursued him
You know sued him and he got
A dismiss with prejudice so he's
Um you know
Free to do whatever on this he's supposed to make
Like a video about it on Monday
Actually regarding this dismissal
Um but yeah I mean these are the same guys
That try to sue steam reviews
You know sue people like
To find you know who's
Leaving bad reviews on their game so they can go off
Through them monetarily and then
Then steam of course pulled their games off of
You know
Here's the thing that I think kind of sucks about this
Is that you know there's the whole you can read
The motion for dismissal it's all public and online
Both parties have to
Bear their own attorney and filing fees
So that means he
Jim Sterling still had to pay for the attorney
And the filing which he shouldn't have to do that
No he shouldn't the other parties should have to pay for that
Here's the thing the reason the thought
Well the thought of it is
That it was more of like
Jim Sterling being nice about it because
He could have pursued it
Further to get those attorney fees but he's just kind of like
Fuck this I just want to be done with them
Using the YouTube
Ad revenue from the videos about it to pay for it
Well it's just like he just wants to be done with them
I think because he had a
Strong case to where he could have gotten damages
From them but it's more of just let's just
Forget about it you know let's just
Leave it and I'm just
Going to still make fun of you but you know
There's not much you can do about it
So you know basically now they just said
Any time that they
They're not allowed to you know file
Complaints regarding this of course
If they do file any additional complaints not
Documented in there they have to make sure
That they're considering fair use and
Some other thing I don't remember
The exact
Wording of it but yeah
I mean that's kind of what's been going on
It's been going on for a few months
Now I think
Geez
Alright well I think this is interesting too
I didn't realize this in order to file
A lawsuit in Arizona the guy
Contributed to the
Patreon a dollar a month to
Say that he does business in Arizona in order to
File the lawsuit there
It's shady shit
That is shady as fuck
Well be careful if you set up one of those
Patreons because I know a lot of people are setting
Those up but there's another great reason
Why OLR hasn't exactly
Jumped in on Patreon yet you know
Legal things like that
So anyway I don't have the fucking money
To pay a lawyer like
Anyway
Let's move on
People need to
Just stop suing everybody over stupid things
Y'all need Jesus
Or whatever
Y'all need
A lobotomy
Moving on
Y'all need to go outside right Darsyra
Yeah go outside and play some Pokemon Go
Well as
We know or may
Have known and forgotten
Or did not give a shit about
Pokemon's 21st anniversary
Is coming up so Niantic
Is doing
An event from February 26th
Until March 6th
For the anniversary
It's going to be Pokemon day
Or in that case Pokemon week
Where you can
Catch a special Pikachu
He'll be wearing a party hat
Just like the Santa Pikachus
And so I am going to be
Going on a Pikachu hunt
I'm just going to hang out in the park by your house
And hunt Pikachu
Yeah I'll have to get one of those
So I can have all the different Pikachu hats
It's all about hats
I have the um
Both the Christmas Pikachu and Raichu
And I want the party hat Pikachu and Raichu
Instead of Raichu there but I would assume Raichu would
Yeah if it's like the Santa hats
Then you should be able to evolve a Pikachu
With a party hat and get a Raichu with a party hat
Party too
But that's really it
I'm excited to catch a party too
Will they spawn more Pikachu so you have a better chance to catch them
Or are you going to have to find
I don't see anything about that
Well here's a pro tip there is some Pikachu nests
Up in Sacramento so you just have to look at
I missed my Porygon chance
You did miss your Porygon chance
They were all over during the Valentine day event
Well I'll just do it next year
That's what they all say
Alright
He's saying in his best Adore Delano voice
Party
Loki what do you have for us before we get to the classic game of the week
So apparently now you have
The ability through Twitch to
Change your name
Now changing your username
Also not only does it change your name
That everyone can view it
It also changes your channels URL
Of course
They're saying that your old URL won't
Redirect to the new one
And then you can use that feature
Once every 60 days
And of course you can only change
The name that's available
I never realized
That you could not change your Twitch name
This seems like one of those
Really obvious things
That I wonder why it wasn't in place before
But okay
Well I know
In the past certain things have been tied
To actual names on the accounts
Like an account number
And so if they
Made that change
Where they assigned account numbers to everything
Then they could do that
Because that was like
I think Sony
Can you change your name on the
Playstation now
No and that's a very
That's a thing that some people have problems with
I thought that was something they were working on
So I think that's the same process
They have to assign your account a number
And once they have everybody to a number
They can go and allow you to
Change those names
Alright
So if I want to change my name to Mob Moberts
I can do that now
Yes, as long as it's not taken
As long as it's not already taken
Don't take it or I'll sue you like that guy
Alright let's talk about this
Before we get into the classic game of the week
And it has to do with Unity
The Unity game engine is
Being used for more than just games
There's other things that are using it
In fact there's a brand new French
Animation show called Mr. Carton
That is now the first
Cartoon TV series
Made in Unity
So now you can make a television cartoon
In Unity, which makes me think
How easy would it be to port that cartoon to other devices
Through Unity
Which also makes me think
Remember when the 3DS was going to get movies
Whatever happened to that?
What happened to Tron or Tangled
In 3D on the DS, what happened to that?
Instead we got Dinosaur Office
Look at Tekken, the Tekken movie was in
Was the Tekken movie out?
Because I think if there was a version of Tekken
On the 3DS
That actually had that movie
Bundled with it
I was going to say
This is something that they've been pushing with Unity
Because they had that whole tech demo
I don't know if it was just for Unity 5
Or whatever the version of Unity was
But they had this big cinematic
Thing that they put out
And they were saying
Yeah, you could use it for making movies
Yeah, Mr. Carton
Has a 13 episode season that is
Premiering on France
Televisions this week
There's also, I guess 6 episodes have already
Aired and you can actually go check it out on YouTube
If you want, they're just short little
2 minute adventures
And I guess the language barrier
Doesn't really prevent you from enjoying it
Because the cartoon doesn't say much
So you can still kind of enjoy it there
I didn't watch it myself to be honest
But maybe I will knowing that
I don't need to know a lot of French to be able to understand it
The creator of Mr. Carton
Found Unity to be very suitable
For the process saying that sequencing was a lot less
Challenging in Unity than it is
With more traditional methods
Storyboarding and mastering were handled with other applications
But set building, lighting
Rendering and so forth
Was done with Unity
So that's pretty cool
A cartoon
All out of Unity
Alright, let's go back to a simpler time
When you can just
Program your own game
You can just create any game you wanted
Unless it was like pinball construction
Set or something
It's the classic game of the week
Where Dark Soccer is going to step into the gaming vault
And find a game that she thinks
Hey, you brat
Enough with your newfangled
Switches
I'll show you a switch
Nipple clips
You'll go out to the yard and pick your own
Which is psychological warfare
Believe me
Dark Sakura
What is the classic game of the week
That the kids should be reading about and playing
The game is Crazy Chase
Or as we had it in the US
Casey's Crazy Chase
Who remembers when I did
Casey Munchkin a while back?
Not me
No, actually I thought you had already done this game
Because you did do Casey Munchkin
And I forgot they were different games
I have to talk about a slight bit
Because there was a big
Casey Munchkin was sued
Well, I'd say Phillips was sued
By Atari
Phillips Magnavox
Because Casey
While they didn't advertise
That Casey Munchkin was
Like Pac-Man
In fact, they were very clear not to say it
So many other people drew the comparison
And were advertising it
That way in catalogs
Even though they said don't do it
That they got sued
By Atari
Because Atari at that point had the home license
For Pac-Man
They
Magnavox won the first suit
But Atari
Appealed and won the
Second court case
So that's that whole drama
In a nutshell
Casey Crazy Chase was a
Sequel and a response
And of course anything that has
The Casey name in it
Comes from the
Phillips electronic president
At the time, Casey Mencken
So, there you go
But this game is a sequel to Casey Munchkin
In this game, it is still a map game
And it actually does have
A lot of the features of Casey Munchkin
They came out
In, let's see
In the UK on the
Phillips video pack and in North America
On the Magnavox Odyssey 2
But this game
It has a twist on the whole thing
So in Casey Munchkin
You had drats
The little monsters living in the maze
And, you know, your little guy
Would walk around
And eat them and eat dots and stuff
You know, kind of, yeah
Pac-Man-y
You know, had
The same plethora
Of mazes in the level editor
But it just changed everything up
So, you didn't have the dots
And power pellet lookalikes
You know, at all
And instead you had the drats
Who were the monsters
Who would walk around growing trees
And you could go around and eat the trees
But you only got one point per tree
Your main objective was the dratapillar
The dratapillar
I would say bears more than a striking
Resemblance to, uh,
Centipede
In its kind of ball-shaped body
So I'm gonna call Loki in the future
The dratapillar
Um, and anyway
The way that you solve
The levels and get points
The big points are by going around
And eating the dratapillar's body
Now, first of all
I love, like, the little
Munchkin guy in here
He rolls around all over the place and grins
And when he wins
He kinda smirks and winks at you
Like, they do like a half smile
It's just funny and clever
But anyway, the dratapillar's head
Will totally kill you
So you have to go and you have to chase
Behind it and eat its body
And so when you have eaten all of its body
Um
You can, um
You can also eat pieces in the middle too
But it leaves those body parts there
The dratapillar
The dratapillar will totally kill you
And you have to eat its body
It's kinda morbid, isn't it?
Coming up next on Casey Munchkin
But, um
But yeah, you can actually even just cut the segment
By its head off by eating it
Which leaves the rest of the segment there
What kind of fucked up things are we teaching children?
It's the 80s, Rob. No one cared
Um, so when you eat a segment
Of the dratapillar, it actually turns the drats
White
And what's kinda funny is like
It's like in those old cartoons, you know
Where the roadrunner would run by the
Coyote and he'd be spinning in the middle of the road
That's kinda what it does, it's pretty cool
Um
And you get 10 points for stunning them
So that's, you know, different ways
To, um, to score
You know, bigger points in the game
But of course, every time you eat a piece of the dratapillar's
Body, it speeds up
So, um
You just have to pretty much be
Fast, think quickly
And, um
You know, run through it. Now, one of the other
Things about this though
Is that it supported the Odyssey 2's voice
Add-on module
Which basically, it, um
It would
Hum, like, background music
Um, through the game
And then you'd get like, oh no!
When you die, or laughter
Or different things
Um, and of course, with this game
You get one life
So, but it's
It's a neat little game, you know
It was definitely
A unique twist on the maze game genre
And one of the better games
That came out for the Odyssey 2
I spent a lot of time
As a kid, well at the time
I had a Colecovision
I'll take that back, this was a house before that
I didn't have a video game system
We had, uh, The Neighbors, uh, Odyssey 2
I have, I have
One now, and I eventually got one
Later, but, um
I spent so much time on this one
And, um, what was that other
Fucking game that had the board game?
I don't remember. I'll remember it
When I'm totally not thinking
About this. I think I've even done
It for a segment too, so my brain's kinda
Too much coding
Alright, well there it is. But yeah, Casey
Uh, Casey's Crazy Chase, also known
As just Crazy Chase elsewhere. One way
Or another. It's Casey's Crazy Chase
Your classic game of the week
You only get one life
And you have to eat the body
You better not let
That Dratapillar fuck you up
And you better eat its body
And then once you've
Devoured that Dratapillar
You're gonna smile and wink and nod
Did you see when- I did, I was watching
This fucking hilarious- This very rudimentary
Little Atari 2600, excuse me
Odyssey level graphics of a little
Winking face. Like, I just ate
His entire body. He's like, hey
Atari, wink
Fuck you
Next time, I'm gonna eat you from the inside out
It's what I think of your centipede
Yum, yum, yum. He's a Dratapillar
Now
I mean, bleep bleep bleep
And Stoppy is helping you out
Quest for the Rings. That was it, thank you
Was the board game. I was like, it was something
And you have done that as a classic game before
I have, but we, you know, we had
Like, it was the full thing. We just said fuck the board game
We just play the game
Quest for the Rings, I mean, I remember
That was a pretty, like, for what it was
An old ass game, that was a pretty
Rich, like, pretty
Big game, you know what I mean? Like
The things that it did going into the different rooms and stuff
We were just like, first graders
That didn't give a shit
For second grade, we're like, whatever, we're just gonna play the game
The other thing I was really good at was
Crypt equip. I think that's what it was called
It's the word scramble game
But I was always really good at this, so whatever
Whatever
Alright, that's it
The word is Dratapillar
Dratapillar
You know what? I say now
That if anyone is a shit in chat
They're the Dratapillar
And will eat their bodies and leave the head
That's kinda weird
Poisonous little heads
That's very weird, you're weird, stop being weird
You know what?
So are you, you hang out with me
What does that say about you?
When I'm forced to
Bitch
Alright, we're gonna take a quick break
Hey Rob, let me do a goddamn break
No, Rob!
What?
Plenty more of this to come
When we come back with more of
Orange Lounge Radio
Right after this
Welcome back everybody to
Orange Lounge Radio
Live tonight with the
677th episode of our show
Already in Progress
I'm here, Loki's here
Dark Soccer is here
And you're here, thanks for listening to us
Be it live, during the
Oscar ceremonies
Which I know has been distracting for some people
I have not even been paying attention
I did see some of the pictures of people on the red carpet though
Even though I don't usually get into all that fashion stuff
Outside of like Project Runway
I'm waiting for the fashion photo review version
The fashion photo review or whatever?
Some of the people on the red carpet look really good
I gotta say, there's been some really good outfits on the red carpet
Did you see what Janelle Monae was wearing?
No, was it a suit?
No, no it was not, it was very much like a
Like a triangular dress type of thing
She looked like she could have been a boss in Final Fantasy
It was great
Go look some of these dresses up
Look amazing on the runway
Anyhow, I wanted to ask you guys about this before we got into
Fire News, before the show, one of our listeners
Tiger Claw sent me a link
And I thought this was an interesting thing to talk about
Since we do like to do classic games, right
And you know, play old games sometimes
And sometimes we have to rely
On emulation to provide
Those games that
You know, might not be accessible otherwise
And that happened to a Super Nintendo
Game this past week, Quick the Thunder Rabbit
Was a platformer for the Super Nintendo
That was never released, it was a port I guess
Of an Amiga title
Oh, did you find the picture?
Yeah, she's got like the whole
Fuck, French Revolution
18th century French
Dress
The hip bustle
Can I talk about the Thunder Rabbit, please?
I guess
Don't talk about our competition tonight
Janelle Monae, she's talented, but she's our competition, Dark Sakura
Stop talking about her
Anyway, so Quick the Thunder Rabbit on Super Nintendo
Was a port of an Amiga title
And I guess it was a platformer
And it would be like one of those auto scrolling shooter
Games and fighting games and what have you
So somebody actually found
A copy of this game, this user
Online, but he altered the game
When he released it, he edited in a
Splash game, or excuse me
A splash screen to the start of the game
And then made some
Small alterations to the game's
Code, I'm assuming to
Make it run better or
Run more appropriately
Maybe on the forum where this was released
SNES Central asked
In the interest of preservation, would it be possible
To upload the unedited ROM image
And the answer was
No
So some people feeling like
This is that horrible
Gigantic TMZ
Watermark on a popular
Photo
Or it's like you own a very
Rare painting
And you decide to paint your initials
Or what was that painting
Where somebody like repainted Jesus'
Face, this is a thing that was like
In the news a couple years
Ago where some gal got a rare
Painting and she painted over the face
Or something, it was horrible, anyway
So some people are saying this like that
But it's funny because I'm kind of reminded
Of like back in the day
On like games on Commodore 64
And like the older
PC games, like the splash screens
And the built in trainers and all that shit
Was par for the course, you would see that
Everywhere
But at the same time I also understand why
It's like dude this is not a
Common game by any means
You have the one copy potentially
Give us the actual game
It's kind of a dick move but hey at least you have a copy of the game now
Yeah
You can play, I mean yeah it sucks that
There were some changes but it's better than nothing
I suppose it's better than nothing
DarkSakura you're big on classic games
Do you think this is defacing a classic
Painting or they have the right to
Do this because they're the only people that have it
I truly do believe that it is
Definitely doing
An injustice
To the game
So
I think that if
It
Well at least, I understand winning it out for preservation
At least in the sake of this
Having an unedited
ROM of the game
Should be still
Distributed for that preservation purpose
In its unadulterated form
It's sort of like
Or how about like this, let me put it this way
Imagine where they found
All of those, you do the x-ray
Of the paintings to see the original painting
Underneath it right
Like for example the beached whale
That was in that one piece of artwork
Or going into Van Gogh's work
And finding
His, that he's painted over other
Works, you know it's kind of
The same thing
Whether or not it's done in
Um
What's the word I'm thinking of
Done out of
Good taste, done out of
Respect, like good intentions
Good intentions, or even if there had been malice
Behind it, there was no malice in this
At the same time
It would still be
A shame
I don't think they would have had a problem if they just like
Fixed it to run or something like that
Like he put a splash screen
No, actually some people believe
And this story that Tigerclaw sent me
Went on into like an interview with some video game
And actually says, even though
This guy doesn't think he's doing harm
Because he's trying to make the game more playable
It actually still is a disservice because this is a piece
Of gaming's history, you know
He's not the guy who created the original game
I can see that perspective
Here's, okay, here's another one
And this is gonna be highly controversial
But I'm gonna use something that's been a point
Of contention in religious circles
The writings of Josephus
Have been altered ever since
Like
Were altered to say that yes
He saw Jesus
The original writings never said that
I see, I see
But it's the same thing where it goes
In and makes an alteration
It's revisionist history is what it is
It's kind of like how you have
The King James version of the Bible
Right, not to get too religious, but
That's also historical
Not just that, it wasn't necessarily
An interpretation of it, it was
Altered
By picking certain
Items in translation and putting
Them into a way that politically
Benefited his regime
And in this case, we don't know
The reason that this guy did this
If it was as some type of
Reflection on himself
Or some way to hold power
Over the community, we don't know that
My thought is, maybe there's
Two answers here, like
Release the original cart the way
It was done if it's broken or whatever
And then go ahead and alter it
Release the fixed one and now put your initials on it
Because you did fix the game
Stope has another good comparison
The Diary of Anne Frank
Her father edited it to remove
Her talks about her
Puberty, sexuality
You know, different things that young women
Go through, sure
But again, it's revisionist
It's, in this case,
More of a patriarchal type of control, but still
But it's the same thing
I look at this as no different
Dungeon Buster, with an interesting
Perspective, though, that I think is worth sharing
Over at live.vognetwork.com, says
On the other hand, a lot of the preserved games
On sites like archive.org
For old PCs, they open with
Cracked screens because they're the
Only ones available
And kind of like I said
You know, even though a lot of us
Kind of see what's going on now
As a negative, what this guy is
Doing was perfectly par
For the course in the 80s and early 90s
It's like a B
It's not an A
Of just releasing it, but hey, you know what
It's working
It's a B movie? What is it?
You're rated on a scale, you know
It's like a B, you know
It could have been better if you released an altered
But at least it's out there
It's like a B
I give it three stars
Out of five
Three out of five
Alright, let's do some
Rapid fire news
Go around quickly and talk about some of the things
That have been happening in the game industry this week
Loki, speaking of something I would give
Three out of five, Irrational
Games, they've changed the name of their
Studio to Ghost
Story Games
Goatsy Games? That's irrational
Ghost Story Games
I hope that you're only making spooky games
Their reasoning before
They said was because
It was irrational
Because ghost stories are immersive, exciting
And steeped in the community
That reminds us of our mission
Really, it's just because you couldn't
You're like, ah crap, we gotta
Come up with something guys
Ghost Stories
I have a ghost story for you all
Knock knock
Who's there? Boo
Boo
Who? Don't cry
I have a ghost story for you
What? The Phantom
Of the opera?
No no no, what was that machine
That we saw at E3
Oh oh
Where's my shade sound?
That was like a C plus
Joke, but it was a little intellectual
For the show
Coleco Chameleon Zero
I give that joke
A two out of five
You know what, if I were to
Roll my eyes any higher, I'd be looking
At your backyard
Actually you'd be looking at a sheet that
That's covering the backyard, anyway
JD and Chaz is
So that's a boot
Are we gonna toot it or boot it?
Alright please move on please move on
We'll keep moving on
So hey, guess what
There's gonna be some more games that are
Backwards compatible with the Xbox One
Toot
So Assassin's Creed Rogue
Borderlands 2
Which is also I think one of the games of the
Gold this month as well
And
King of Fighters 2002 unlimited match
Are now backwards compatible
That's cool
Yeah so
Yeah especially with the fact that
Borderlands 2 they're kind of giving away
For free
Seriously if you have not played Borderlands
My god
Go play Borderlands
Borderlands 2 is fucking awesome
Wasn't one of the big games on Xbox One
Early on and PlayStation 4 to be fair
The Handsome Jack collection
Yes I have that in my library
Fucking haven't played it at all
What's funny about that is that
Half that is Borderlands 2
But they went back
And what HD-ified it
I think it wasn't that board
Handsome Jack collection I was one and two
No no it's two and the
Whatever that
Pre-sequel that one
One is not in the Handsome Jack collection
I haven't played Pre-sequel yet so that might be worth it
Once again though
I'm getting into that groove where like
I buy a bunch of shit I'm never gonna play
It's as bad as Steam
I've kind of stopped that on Steam for the most part
For the most part
Oh YYR in chat says Space Invaders Infinity
Gene that's one of the games
That's backwards compatible now
Hell yeah if that is one of them
YYR
If it is it's not in this release
That was a great game on 360
I love when those games
I bought on 360 just randomly
Show up on my Xbox One one day
There we go call them back to the
Very opening moments of the show
Things Microsoft is doing right
Backwards compatibility
Better than anybody else right now
Isn't that great that purchases you made on a previous system
Roll over to a newer system
Isn't that something?
That's so crazy
It's as if
With Nintendo where Virtual Console has persisted
With the Wii and the Wii U
And now eventually on the Switch
As if somehow
They would have some sort of record that you made
Those purchases
If only they had the forethought to do that
Too bad
Too bad that other companies don't have
A unified marketplace like that
Like Sony
Oh wait Sony
Too bad we can't bring those
Backwards compatibility
The Playstation Pro is just
Not strong enough
To emulate something the PSP can emulate
Anyway
YYR says
The full list is
Borderlands 2, Assassin's Creed, Rogue, King of Fighters
2002, Gyromancer
Moondiver and Space Invaders
Infinity Gene
Which is funny cause
Is Gyromancer that Square Enix puzzle game?
Cause I own that one too
And I had Moondiver so I had like three of those games
I didn't even realize that
I have not fired up my Xbox One games library
Every time I've been firing that up recently
I've just been going right into Skyrim
Ah yes I do see them on the list now that I actually
Cause this is a, wow
That is one extensive list there
Oh what of all the 360
Of all the games that are backwards compatible
I know, if you haven't checked your Xbox One
In a while, like go into your games library
And just look like in your two download list
You might just find like
Surprise, you've got like 12 games that you bought
On Xbox 360 that are now backwards compatible
That's happened to me quite a bit
I mean, they fucking got
Beat and groovy working on Xbox One
Backwards compatibility
Why did somebody waste their fucking breath
Even testing to see if that game loaded
Like that's amazing
That is amazing
That's dedication
Alright, anyway
Ah hey, a follow up
To something we talked about last week
In the case of the
Missing box of Super Nintendo
Games that went missing
I guess it was blamed for the
Lost in transit, yeah, lost in transit
Lost in transit, you know
Pretty quick to blame somebody stealing it
At the post office, because let's be real
That's what would usually happen
But in the interest of fairness
And we should say
Everything's okay, nobody stole it
It was recovered, that's right
They did recover the
Super Nintendo games valued at $10,000
Apparently what happened is
They were found
At an Atlanta, Georgia
Mail recovery center
So how about that, so Bobby was trying to get him redirected
To his house, no he didn't
I'm looking to see what I have
Anyway, so it was at the Atlanta, Georgia
Mail recovery center so they were able to locate the package
Here's the interesting thing
Because this was
Going around on so many news
Outlets and everything
Apparently it was giving the post office a bad rep
Right, because a lot of us were jumping
To conclusions about, oh it was stolen
So this guy was able
To get through and actually get noticed
He says in his
Little statement on what happened
He told me straight up the reason he was
Contacting me was because of the news articles
He'd encountered on the case
So thanks to the coverage, I had a strong
Contact within the US postal service
Who passed me to his employee who opened the
Investigation and then found the package
So how about that y'all, angry gamers
Accomplished something, angry
Chated fucking gamers accomplished
Something, good job
100 Nintendo, Super Nintendo
Games for you, that's more games than you'll
Find on the virtual console at launch
For the Nintendo Switch
I do think I have most of these
I love it
Loki, fuck off but I love it
Maybe that's lost somewhere
Check Atlanta
Check Bobby's house
Bobby, do you have virtual console?
Do you have virtual console in that basement?
Is that where it went?
Bobby Blackwolf
In the conservatory
With the computer hacking kit
Alright, hey
Steam prices are going up soon
Okay, just kidding
That would be the clickbait headline I would try to post
On Facebook, but it's not as bad as it sounds
Because the steam prices are not going up
In the states, so if you do come across
An article about steam prices going up soon
Here's what's really happening
Yes, sales tax is now
Included in the prices
Across new countries
There's new tax laws that are requiring sales tax
Be applied to digital goods
And services in some new countries
Starting in March in Switzerland, South Korea
Japan, New Zealand, Iceland
South Africa and India
April in Serbia, May in Taiwan
And July in Australia
So for example the tax in Australia is 10%
So in July the price of steam games
Will be 10% higher
It is going to pay for this tax
It's not like the US where you get
Charged tax after the advertised price
In these countries
For whatever reason the tax code is written
That the tax must be included in the advertised price
I guess that's like
Buying flight tickets
Here in the US
Now have to include all the other little taxes and things in them
So steam is having to do
It's alright Australia, you're used to getting screwed over
When it comes to pricing anyway
It's not nice
It is not nice
That's alright, wait for the sales
Wait for those sales
Alright, Dark Sakura, how about you?
What do you have for us?
Well a couple of things actually
That make me super happy
And one of them is a huge fuck you
So I like that even better
This one is the first happy news
One of the favorite games of my household
Actually a series I should say
Are the Wonder Boy games
That came out on Sega Master System
Well now
Dotemu has brought out
A remastered version
Of Wonder Boy 3 The Dragon's Trap
And it's just going to be called
Wonder Boy The Dragon's Trap
It has a hand drawn style
And
But it's also
Got the music
And you can swap
Between the new
Hand drawn style
And the original style
So that's really awesome
There is a whole
Trailer up and I would suggest
That people check it out, it's really sweet
Um
Next is something
That
I have to bask in this
For a minute
Humble Bundle, which by the way
I sent you a message on a bundle
I actually knew about this bundle
And I'll tell the listeners about it
Because it's the Humble Civilization Bundle
This isn't what Dark Sakura was going to talk about
But their newest bundle is the Humble Civilization Bundle
And if I remember right off the top of my head
You can pay a dollar
For a dollar
You guys, if you don't own
Now look, Civilization 3 is actually my least
Favorite in the entire series, I'm going to be honest
But Civ 4 is one of the best
So like if you can't be bothered
To pay one dollar
For Civilization 4
Literally, I can't
With you
But you have to also be a fan
Of those types of games
Not for a dollar, you don't really have to be a fan
If you've got a fixed income
Type of thing going on, look, I'm not going to
Break you too bad, but look, seriously, if you have the room
In your budget to forgo a soda
And buy the Civilization
Humble Bundle instead
I would encourage you to do so
As Dark Sakura takes
A big swig of her Diet Pepsi
That she probably paid a dollar fifty for at the store
And says, I don't have time for Civ 4
Actually, it tastes pretty awful
That's blood water, okay
Actually, it tastes like it
Thanks to my nose, but still
But my good news
The Humble Freedom Bundle
Raised
6.73 million
To aid
Immigrants
In response to
The new Voldemort
Immigration ban
You know what, I don't even want to call him Voldemort
Because he's fucking orange
In response to what happened
I'm just going to call him the dump
Because he's a human garbage dump
Anyway
The proceeds are going to charities like
The ACLU, the American Civil Liberties
Union, the International Rescue
Committees, and Doctors Without
Borders
Basically, it offered
Over $600
Worth of gains for $30
Including some pretty
Big ones like The Witness
And they also
Said that they would match
Up to $300,000
Of the proceeds
Totally, that's up to
.73 million
They did
Some of the games finally started running out
Because I'm sure some of the game makers
Hey, I think it's awesome that even the
Creator of Stardew Valley
That game is hot shit right now in the indie scene
And in the gaming scene in general
It's awesome that that guy would contribute
200,000 copies of his game
To this cause, but the reality is
He had set a number
And once they exceeded that number those keys were gone
So in the final hours
I think once they broke it was either
200,000 or 250,000, sorry I don't remember
The number, but some of the games
A good chunk of them kind of fell off the list
Like Stardew Valley I know is probably the biggest name
That no longer became available
At that point, but again
That's not a read because that's awesome
But a game like that
That's still hot shit
Getting $15 a copy is donated to a cause
Like this at all
Even more if you look at the number of keys that were available
Think of how many people
That was
Who gave a
Fuck you
To the establishment
Or just wanted to play some games
But still
It was a big fuck you
And I am so proud of them for doing this
Moving on
Alright that's it for our rapid fire news
So let's talk about
What is coming out in stores this week
Loki, gee what could possibly be coming out in the US this Friday
Horizon Zero Dawn
That's right
That's a big deal too
That is a big deal
Torment, Tides of Numeric
Isn't Horizon getting pretty good reviews too?
It is
I didn't have my eyes on it
Until I started to hear about some of these reviews
I don't always listen to reviewers
But when the feedback is uniformly positive
Like it is for this game
Or majority positive
Or like that movie
That has 100% of Rotten Tomatoes right now
That Get Out
Has 100% of Rotten Tomatoes right now
That definitely grabbed my attention
Like oh maybe this is something I should be paying attention to
And go see
Same thing kind of happens with video games
Yeah
So we had a game called Torment, Tides of Numeric
And that's on PC, Playstation 4 and Xbox One
Constructor HD on PC, Playstation 4 and Xbox One
Musou Stars on Playstation 4 and the Vita
And then of course a whole bunch of shit on the Nintendo Switch
So of course we have
1-2 Switch
I am Setsuna
Just Dance 2017
Human Resource Machine
Little Inferno, Skylanders
Imaginators, The Binding of Isaac
Afterbirth Plus
Super Bomberman R
All those on the Switch
Legend of Zelda, Breath of the Wild on the Switch
Wii U, World of Goo
On the Switch
And that would be your lineup right there
World of Goo, yes
That's not an old game
Does that game date back to the Nintendo Wii?
I think it does
It's an old game
It's like one of the first WiiWare games
Back when it was called WiiWare
Alright so moving on to Japan
And checking out what's in Japan this week
Horizon Zero Dawn gets its release on March 2nd
As well as Winning Post 8 2017
Ironically enough Loki
Borderlands, the double deluxe collection
What they're calling it in Japan
I think this might be a price reduction though
I don't think this is the initial release of the game
This is funny that we were talking about it before
And it's called the double deluxe collection
And it's very clear on the box
Borderlands the pre-sequel and Borderlands 2
Are on that
And that is on the Playstation 4 this week
Let's see traveling over to the Vita
Playstation Vita only has Winning Post 8 2017 this week
Otherwise the Vita kind of has a week off
Which believe it or not
Yes they usually have stuff going on
In Japan
Nintendo 3DS has a release this week
It's a Doraemon game
Doraemon Nobita no Nan Kyoku
Kachi Kachi Daibuken
Comes out this week
And it looks like some type of polar adventure
For Doraemon
Cause all his friends they're all wearing those big
Poofy like
Like Eskimo jackets type of things
That's what they're wearing
I love Doraemon he's so cute
Well then you can check that game out
And now in Japan I get to talk about the Nintendo Switch
Cause the Nintendo Switch is also out this week
In Japan
It is a region free console don't forget
So if you wanted to pick up one of these Japanese
Titles you could
And these are the games releasing on the Nintendo Switch this week
On March the 3rd
1, 2 Switch in Japan
Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild as well
You can also check out Dragon Quest Heroes 1 and 2
Is a release that's available in Japan on the 3rd
And Super Bomber Man R
Is available as well
Puyo Puyo Tetris
Also releasing in Japan with launch
Ikeme Disgaea 5
Is releasing as well
Ikeme To Yoki no Setsuna
That's the I am Setsuna
Releasing in Japan
And then there also
If that all is not enough for you
You can also get a variety of accessories
And all that other good stuff that's also releasing
With the Nintendo Switch this week
And did I mention Amiibo
That's right you can get more Amiibo figures
Also released in Japan this week
Welcome to the release calendar Nintendo Switch
How about the UK Dark Sakura
Okay, so
In the UK we have
On, what's today
The 20, yeah
So today, Stories Untold
For PC, and then
Our guess for them it was yesterday, anyway
It's already tomorrow over there, but yes
On the 28th, Torment Tides
of Numenera
On
PlayStation 4, Xbox One
Mac and PC
For all you people who say games don't come out on the Mac
Fuck you
On March 1st, we have
Horizon Zero Dawn
Coming out for
The PlayStation 4
On the 2nd
What is the weekend?
I can't even right now
On the 2nd
We have Snipper Clips
And Super Bomberman R
On the 3rd, Human Resource Machine
I am Setsuna
Inferno, World of Goo
And of course, the Switch itself
Worldwide release
Yo, for the Switch
I'm gonna go hide in my room
And raid until Mass Effect
Andromeda comes out
Sounds like a plan, addict
Hey, you're the enabler
Dealer
Alright, let's go
To the mailbag
Every week you guys send us emails
Participate at
DarkSockersLoungeRadio.com
Is where you can send us emails
And when those emails come in, DarkSocker dives in the mailbag
Headfirst and reads your emails here
Live on air
So DarkSocker's gonna jump into the mailbag right now
And pull out
Jack shit
Empty mailbag
Not even a crusty poop
Why would you say that?
Because I'm a little high on cough medicine
Right now
Okay, I accept that excuse
Anyhow, there is no emails
For DarkSocker to read this week
And that makes her a sad panda
Actually, it probably doesn't since she is still kinda sick
She probably appreciates you all giving her voice a break
I'm gonna just assume
You all knew
But for next week, you can email us
Participate at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
Guess we'll have to go back to some news
Won't we, Loki?
Yep, and all the things old are new again
343Industry says
Promise? Hey, guess what?
We were briefed with Halo 5 by
Taking out split screen play
But that's not gonna be a problem going forward
We're going to go ahead
And make sure that's included
In all future releases
Because it was incredibly painful
For the community and us
That we didn't include it in Halo 5
So that's pretty nice
That'll be available
That's a staple, so why not?
Alright, so
Nice, I don't know
I guess I was kind of past it
At this point, but I'm excited
I guess a little bit to see it coming back
Because my first introduction to the Halo series
Was a split screen Halo thing
A local area network
I'm sure I've told this story on the show many times before
But it was actually at a wedding reception
My friend had a Halo themed wedding
And they actually had Halo playable
At the reception
And that was my first introduction to it
And it was awesome
It really sold me on the original Xbox
We go back to what we were talking about earlier in the show
So the split screen stuff, that's pretty cool
So I'm happy to hear it's coming back
I think that'll be a lot of fun
Alright
Well, in news of That's Awkward
This week
And where does all the awkward stuff happen?
Live streams, right?
So anyway, there was a live stream this week
Which is captured forever, thanks to YouTube
Where
I'm probably gonna say this name wrong, I'm sorry
I just don't follow a lot of the streamer celebrities
Really
But Kefri, I think is the name of the streamer
He's an Overwatch player
Plays a lot of competitive Overwatch
Plays so much competitive Overwatch
He happens to be the highest ranked Widowmaker player in the world
And Widowmaker is one of those
As I call her when I'm playing the game
Bitch snipers
Because when I get sniped
From across the map
I tend to yell out, that bitch sniper killed me
So, yeah
But I also do like playing Widowmaker a lot
Because sometimes it's really fun to be the bitch sniper
So anyway
Kefri is
The highest ranked bitch sniper in the whole world
And this was interesting
Because what happened is that he was actually
Playing the stream and doing some ranked matches
And came across
Somebody impersonating his gamer tag
So had the exact same name
In the game
Also playing Widowmaker
But as they were playing the match on Twitch
They figured, oh this guy is using an aimbot
He's cheating
He's doing these shots you can't even do
With a normal machine
Basically
Guess what?
The real player ended up winning anyway
So
Even when the guy was cheating
He couldn't beat the team
And what's really hilarious about this is you know how
One of the big things in Overwatch that's pretty awesome
Is that you always get to see play of the game
Which has become this whole meme online
So guess who got play of the game?
The real one and he even typed in chat
I think at the end when all is said and done
He said, can't even beat me with hacks bud
Laughs
You gotta love
Yes, you gotta love it
Usually that level of douchey snark
I'm like, I don't like that stuff
In the competitive scene but in this case
It is completely and utterly warranted
Fuck cheaters in online games
Fuck them with something hard and sandpapery
So this guy got what's coming to him
Embarrassed on video, it's just a bummer
We couldn't see what this guy's real
Gamer tag was
But in other words, if you're gonna go
Fake, then
You're probably gonna get beat
Kaijuto in chat says, bleh
The cheating I don't agree with
But a screen name is a screen name
There could be a hundred Kaijutos, I don't give a fuck
Yes and no
Certainly there's other people out there that must call themselves
Skye because I never get the name on websites
Which I actually usually don't try to take that name anymore
I try to get Rob Roberts wherever I can
But I digress
The fact is
That he's taking the name
And playing Widowmaker
And cheating while he's doing it
Which could be
Giving the impression that when
Other people play against him
It's the real guy
Even though it's a cheater
Does that make sense at all?
So maybe what Blizzard needs to do
And I think they actually do do this
If you mouse over the gamer tag or something
You get to see the numbers that are following the gamer tag
So you can tell if it's the right
One or not
I don't know if the professionals numbers are out there for everybody to find
But
I kinda think intent is a big part of it
And when you're using these cheating bots and so forth
To play the same character
That the hacker does with skill
Even though apparently
He's not skilled even with the hacking tool
I think that's kinda shitty
That's the whole thing
When it's like impersonation with the intent to impersonate
If it's the fact that
Oh I've been using this name for years online too
Well then that I understand
I think I went on Twitter
To try to find
I want the name Rob Roberts on Twitter
And it belongs to a spam account
But when you search for that name
You get these other Rob Roberts that come up
And I think one is like a DJ in Australia or something
I can't be mad at that guy
That just happens to be his name too
I'm not mad at that guy
I'm mad that a spammer took the name Rob Roberts
But if this other DJ had the name
Then I really couldn't be upset
Because it's his professional name too
In a different way
Anyway
Alright let's move on
DarkSakura
Well we are losing one of the writers for Portal
Very very sad
But necessary I'm sure he thinks
That it is
Paul who has been with Valve since 2004
Worked on Half Life 2 Episode 1
Both the Portal games
Left 4 Dead
Has just left the company
He didn't say anything about what's up next
But he was working with Double Fine
On Psychonauts 2
So maybe it's to spend more time on that
Only can speculate
But
Good luck and go get him
Go get him
Yeah
Hopefully he already finished the script for Portal 3
On his way out
Valve can't count to three
I'm not gonna hold my breath
We'll see
But these comings and goings happen
And series can still be strong
Casey Hudson left BioWare
And now Mass Effect is being done by other people
Which
We won't really know if the story
Is still good until Mass Effect Andromeda
Is out we get a chance to play it
But we're hopeful
Did you see the voice list?
I did and I also saw the
Andromeda t-shirt that was on sale
At Gamestop when I was at the mall
So I was like oh the merchandise is out already
I was also listening to
Some of Natalie Dormer
I heard the little interview with her
It was pretty neat
Very excited for the game to come out
I can't wait to fuck all the aliens
Alright moving on
Loki
The question is is Natalie Dormer one of the aliens
He can fuck because you know
She's the doctor
Oh she's the chakwas replacement
Yes she is the asari doctor
I don't need to know what the profession is
That's not really important
No this is important because Dr. Chakwas is like
She's mom
She is the den mother mom of the Normandy
She's very much like you know
Like Kathleen Turner
Like you know
Why don't you come into my office and we'll
Drink a glass of champagne
So uh
The doctor is a pretty big role
Alright
Well um
Let's talk a little bit about
Esports I guess so
One thing
Is coming to TV pretty soon
In the weirdest locations I guess
The CW network
Yes that's who you think of
They're going to be broadcasting
I guess a tournament for
H1Z1 king of the kill
And so with that
Along with the actual broadcast
Which is supposed to air April 20th
At 9pm eastern time
They're going to be doing also a 5 part documentary
Series leading up to the tournament
And it's going to follow the um
Prematch preparations
Of Echo Fox
The um professional esports team
They got rid of top model for that
What the fuck
I've actually watched
A little bit of king of the kill
It's actually pretty interesting
Since I'm sure you guys are probably not familiar with it
It's basically like DayZ
But put into um
It almost like gets a little bit like
Um
Not the Hunger Games
Sort of like the Hunger Games I guess
So basically you're in this environment
You land and you have to find your guns
And then there's like gas coming in
As well and it keeps making the
Arena smaller and smaller and smaller
So they're setting it up they're going to have
5 man teams
And there's 15 teams of 5 players
And then there's also supposed to be I guess another um
You know some open slots for
Individual people as well
But it's a lot of people that start off
In the game
I don't know it was entertaining why I watched it
I'll have to check it out
Is this a regular thing on Twitch
I assume that people are playing?
Yes it's one of the bigger games it's on Twitch right now
Okay awesome I'll have to check that out
I can take a break from Conan Exile streams
Check that out
So is that just all penis flailing to me?
Yes never gets old
Actually that game has died down in popularity a lot
I think finally everybody is like alright it's a penis
We get it
I think Conan Exile streams have died down
A little bit in popularity
Has Conan played Conan Exiles because
I don't know
Well he's gonna have that series soon
The clueless gamer
Or whatever he calls it
Is that on the CW?
No that would be probably on
Was it TBS?
Actually CW has a lot of those serial
Shows now right?
Supernatural is fucking still going
And it's still awesome
All these years later
All the DC shows are there
Supergirl is moving there right?
I'm so far behind
On all that stuff
I have to ask John from
Critical Myth because he still follows
All those shows and they write some great reviews
Over at VOG Network but I admittedly
Don't follow a lot of them
However I will say this
Dark Soccer maybe this is something you know about this
I realize this has nothing to do with games but it's very
Important
Can somebody explain to me why
Riverdale is so popular
I haven't watched it
It sounds kind of amazing
When I first heard about Riverdale I was like
Oh they're turning Archie from the comics
Into one of these shows that's gonna be a little ridiculous
But apparently it's like
Archie but like if all those characters
Were in Twin Peaks
What? Yeah that's what Riverdale
Is
It's like the dark version of
Archie
And it's all the same people like Veronica
Fucking Josie from Josie and the Pussycats
Is there too like it's yeah right?
That's the same face timing
They decided
We're gonna take
We're gonna take Batman
And make it dark
Is that Happily Ever After?
Or something like that?
What's that show that's with all the Disney
Oh Once Upon a Time
Once Upon a Time is that like
Once Upon a Time but in the Archie universe now?
Yes
Something like that I don't know
But apparently everybody I've seen on the Twitters
And all the stuff like Tumblr
They're putting shit up like there's
Gifts everywhere
And everything so I don't know
I feel like it's one of those shows I need to be
Seeing let's see I'm looking in chat
Over at live.vognetwork.com
Come on Noel Gus says Riverdale is pretty good
Brad from Pod Culture says
Supergirl is there I follow
All of them love Legends of Tomorrow
I know they started putting some of that on
Netflix so
I tried to see if Riverdale
If I ever stop hating on DC maybe I'll give them a chance
One of these days but no thanks
Where can I watch Riverdale online?
I would totally watch it
But it's not on Netflix
New shows usually aren't
Hulu I've been using
I have a friend that I may or may not
Be borrowing their Hulu account
So I can watch Golden Girls
And I tried to see I was like
Oh maybe usually that type of stuff shows up there
But there's no Riverdale on Hulu either
But that's fine because I still have like
160 episodes of Golden Girls left to watch
Thank you a couple weekends
It will take me a little while
Maybe by then you know the new season of
Stranger Things will be out so
Oh there's a CW app that's apparently
totally free
Like on
Playstation or Xbox
The Android TV
The Play Store has that and I'm like
Oh CW what the hell do I need this for
Maybe they have
Because my fucking TV has apps
So maybe it's like a Samsung TV
Because Netflix is built into my TV
So maybe they have that
I'm going to look for that stuff
Oh Rama says Comcast on Demand
Thank you Rama
I have Comcast on Demand
I never use it but I will check out this show
Because I'm very curious
I have a purpose now for Comcast on Demand
Alright
DarkSakura why are you telling people to fight you in chat
What are you doing
Shots have been fired
Why what was fired
Brad says that DC is better than Marvel
for TV and I'm like
Marvel is better than DC for everything
Brad's been saying that you two
go back and forth on the DC and
Marvel thing for forever
I haven't watched really any of them so I can't make a judgement
at this point
I think you and Brad need to do a podcast
together called Fight Me
and it's just a DC
Marvel wank fest every week
I don't even like DC enough to entertain
that it might be good
You're such a bitch
and I love it
I like Suicide Squad
Because you know what
it wasn't quite like they were in the comics
Actually I'll tell you this right now
I have gone back to buying physical comic books
again because of one fucking series
I now have a new
series of Jessica Jones
in comics
just focused on her
in the actual comic universe and not the TV universe
and it's perfect
Here's the thing
Dark Soccer and I know you're going to plug your ears and say
la la la but I'm going to try anyway
You should give
if you're going to give any of this shit a chance
try Supergirl
Everything I've heard about that show
I feel like you might dig it
Okay I will admit this
I do have Supergirl on DVD
because I fucking love that movie as a kid
I'm not even talking about the fucking movie
But
I have considered
giving the TV show a try
because of my love for the old movie
There you go and the old movie is not even
that good you guys
I don't fucking care because it has
Faye Dunaway in it as the bad guy
I just want to remind you all this chick stands
for Xanadu
I love Xanadu
You shut up about Xanadu because you know what
Don Bluth
In the studios took time out of their
busy schedule producing
The Secret of Nim
No no The Secret of Nim at the time
to do Xanadu
to do that one little bit in Xanadu
and almost delayed the release of
The Secret of Nim which is also
one of my other favorite fucking movies of all time so don't judge me
I will fight everyone
Here's Brad from Pod Culture with the
selling line
The chick from the original movie plays
Supergirl's adopted mom on the show
I sold
Oh fuck
I know her name
Helen something
How did I know that?
You know what else she was in?
She was in The Legend of Billie Jean
I feel like I had to tap into gay superpowers
to remember that
We just have a knack for pop culture
The Legend of Billie Jean was also a great movie
Alright
Moving on
Let's talk about
Let's talk about an awesome series on the Atari 2600
that you may or may not have ever played
It's Sword Quest
Did you ever play these Sword Quest games?
They were kind of hard to understand
especially at a young age that I was
when these games first came out
They were kind of like a bunch of mini games
but they all came together for this larger purpose
of you were trying to look for
items and traverse the kingdom
and all this stuff
1982 was when the first game in the series
came out it was Earthworld
and then finally Fireworld
came out in 1983
and 1983 unfortunately
is when the video game industry went
so the series was never really finished
Waterworld
did I think get released
really limitedly
through Club Atari and I think you can
get it on some of the flashback stuff
now and then Airworld
which was supposed to be the last game was never made
and the interesting thing about this series is that
there was a prize like it was supposed to be like
if you were the first person to crack the code
you got this prize thing
that was worth like a quarter million dollars
which in the 80's was a lot more
money than it is today and so it was like
a lot of money but they never ended up having to
give the thing away because they never really
finished the series. Here's what's interesting
Dynamite Entertainment has picked up
the rights to Sword Quest they are
going to launch a comic book series
beginning in May
to actually finish
the story of Sword Quest
which Atari 2600 games
didn't have much story
I seem to remember these games
I think were like comic book style manuals
of their own that told a story
so it's interesting that it's all
coming back so that's cool
the creative team
behind Sword Quest is going to be
Chris Simms who wrote Marvel's
X-Men 92 series
and artist Scott
Kolichuk who did Batman
66 for a bit
so that's pretty cool so check that
out because who knows if the Sword
Quest comic does well maybe it
will become a video game movie that doesn't
suck we'll see
anyway one more story for you guys
then we're going to get to the Skype line and
on our last note tonight
Dark Sakura what do you have for us one more story before we get
to Orange Lounge Radio all one word on
Skype I do I thought I did it
yes one more story okay oh yeah
duh usually
you don't go last but this one was too
good this is a good last story
totallyfuckablealiens.com
go ahead right now
into your browser and type in
totallyfuckablealiens.com
you know what you will find?
totallyfuckablealiens? Garris Grabbing Shepherd's
Boob
yes Cards Against
Humanity has teamed up
with BioWare for a mass
effect pack and I
found out how many you can order at one time
three packs it's a dollar
a pack you fucking owe it to yourself
to not only buy the packs
but
also look at the beautiful fan art on the
page it's absolutely hilarious
but you will have to understand mass effect
a little bit for this deck to make any
sense at all right it's just a pack
but yeah yes but
if you try to like just throw it in your regular
Cards Against Humanity pack and like have
a party or whatever and your friends
like we invite Loki over and Loki doesn't play
mass effect he's not going to fucking get it
he's not going to get any of it
if anyone hangs out with me
they will get my mass effect references because I've
explained them and yes
I do have to thank Ranma I've actually
reposted this on masseffecting.tumblr.com
which is my mass effect blog
by the way I'm trying to get to
10,000 followers
you have 10,000 followers?
I have 9,400 and something right now
I'm trying to get to 10,000
because if I get to 10,000
I get to 3 with those kind of numbers
maybe
I don't know
I swear to god if her mass
her mass effecting blog is more
popular than anything on fog network
well I do
plug the show on my blog
I appreciate that we know what we need
more alien penis I know that's right
what video game can I exploit
the alien penis out of?
we take the engine
of the Conan
yes
and cross it with mass effect
mass effect exiles
totally changeable penis.com
perfect
you know how mass effecting started
you had like
one thing that got a million notes
or something and you were like I should exploit this
for an entire blog
I was looking at one of my screen caps
and it's one of the Turian characters cross eyed
so I just wrote
derpians under it and posted it on my blog
because I thought it was funny
cause that's what fucking happens on tumblr
outside of the pornography
I did have to do a little research cause I knew there was tons of porn
on tumblr I mean hello
but if you actually like did like what is tumblr
really supposed to be for
like what they told yahoo to buy it for
is just random
shit like what just dark soccer explained
for the most part it is just random shit
it's memes
dank fucking memes
but like I went from doing like one or so a week
to now doing one every fucking day
to the point that I have managed to get
out of doing two days worth of them
by having a blank
one go up as a caption contest
and picking the winner at the end of the week
nice
who I also have to thank one of my followers on that for
come on Noel Gustin
chat says not to brag or anything
dark soccer does a hair flip
totally happened
kinda did yeah
so I've decided that I'm gonna
try to do a giveaway for my
10,000th follower
no fucking clue cause I'm broke
alien handjob I'll probably draw you like
garris's dick or something
therapy why don't you give away
some therapy for your 10,000th
follower I'll give away some Theraflu
I don't know I need suggestions
come on Noel Gustin chat asks
oh by the way does anyone know of a
tumblr screensaver or autoplayer
can't always scroll
how about your down button
maybe
come on Noel Gustin is working that down button
somewhere else
you're trying to kill me aren't you
this kills the dark sacra
now I can inherit her mass
affecting blog and I shall be
the most popular on vog network
alright
skype line is open
orange lounge radio all
one word on skype
we're a feisty bunch tonight I'm like
this is a good episode if you wanna be a part of it
or if you wanna bring this episode to a screeching hall
give us a call orange lounge radio
all one word on skype
I need to be on drugs more often I think
to talk about anything
I you know when she shows up to the show
I try to be like hey Jamie wanna shot a
stroopwafel you wanna
just kidding I only
offer her coffee which is a drug
of its own well I actually did have coffee
with stroopwafel in you wanna know something
did you steal stroopwafel I have a bottle
of my own I live by a total wine
hello okay okay
anyway it was
the first time I felt good
today was
having a little bit of alcohol
mixing down mixing alcohol with that medication
you're taking I'm sure you felt
I wasn't taking the codeine at the time
alright again it's orange
lounge radio all one word on skype
while we wait for those
flood of phone calls that I'll have to sift through
I'm gonna check in with loki or dark saga for any
last minute stories sure
so we can talk about nintendo suing
a company that's involved in making
real life mario
cards and we'll do that after we take this
phone call god dammit hi you're on orange
lounge radio who's this
hola
envenido a orange lounge radio
quienes
our caller is not coming through
if we can hear if you can
hear me we can't hear you you'll have to try
again this was just a ploy to get loki
to do his story clearly orange
lounge radio alright
loki why don't you finish up their thought
then so they apparently rent
public road carts
to any customer and they lend I guess a costume
of one of the characters
and then of course you
drive around and stuff so
and nintendo doesn't
like that because you know it's
um infringing on their
properties it's
just mario kart they just sue
everybody who dresses up seriously it's people
dressing up cosplaying driving
and go karts I'm sorry you're gonna like
sue people for cosplay
now I guess
they're nintendo alright brad
from pod culture and chat is suggesting is an
idea for an olr fundraiser jamie
does shots of fireball in streams halo
but you don't like fireball how about shots
it actually makes me super nauseous okay how
about shots of stroopwafel in halo
alright there we go and see brad
negotiation is key
so shit I'd do shots of henesi
by the way or sips of henesi
brad from pod culture I hope you're able to make it
to dragon con this year because like you
introduced me to fireball I'm gonna be
putting in my suitcase some stroopwafel and it's
on at dragon con this year that's all I'm saying
anyway you're welcome for that by
the way so before
we so what what do you think about a fundraiser
of video games we fucking hate
like and you are forced to play halo
for charity uh
and this is dark soccer made of face
or it's just charity dark soccer
it could it could
even be like one of your I
hate trump charities or something okay
hahahah
there we go alright
so that's that's that was easy
well offline you
and I should have a talk about something because I will
be having to put together a
charity when I
make novice alright so
forcing people to play video games they don't like so
what would I have to play what's a video game I really don't like
what do you guys you guys listen
to this show more than I do
what's a video game I don't like that I'll
be forced to play don't play
don't say ddr or I'll flap you
yaris yargh
I don't even know if I own yaris anymore
or like um
hmm
I can kind of suck it up
with a sports game we should just get like copies of cheetah men
and play it can I just play tecmo bowl
instead no you'll like
that I have a feast for purpose
so what game would I have to play
uh nintendo
hahahah
I don't hate
that I don't even I've never played
that loki kind of actually likes
stop he says desert bus
loki actually kind of likes a lot of nintendo
games oh oh oh oh
what fuck what was that awfully
bad uh mass effect
loki has to play mass effect
he doesn't have an emotional attachment
one way or another to it I just because I didn't
like it the first time I played I didn't get any
I have judgement
brilliant luck finding
brilliant we will fucking
make it happen there's somebody in sacramento has a
copy of I have judgement oh and now I just looked at
chat and bobby had already suggested it
stop he says for
loki his own game
hahahahaha
you have to code your game on stream
hahahahaha oh my god
that's even better
that's it we have a sub stream of just loki
no while you and I are playing
the games we hate loki
is forced to sit there and
work on his fucking game on the livestream
on the livestream that's fine I'm glad it has time to
actually work on that let's check in with loki
and see if he's done anything for his fucking game
hahahahaha right now he's in
the corner in a fetal position
check out this wonderfully handcrafted
3D geometric shape
of my middle finger
hahahahaha
I've been wanting to do a video game marathon
for like 10 years so I'm glad
something may come of this anyway
William Ritterface says loki has to dress as tingle
well that won't happen but maybe
we could get him to play the tingle
game on 3DS or something
you don't have a problem playing a game with tingle in it
yeah it's a little
I like to force him to work on his game
they should do a new game called tickle my tingle
hi you're on orange solids radio who's this
this is ron man I want to give a giant
fuck you to skype tonight ok
yeah you sound like you're like I feel like
your skype is on one side of the room
and you're on the other side of the room yelling
at it
here's the thing I went out and decided
to update one of the
usb adapters I do my podcast
with and I already set the settings
for the secondary device
for music
skype doesn't pay attention so
when the call picked up I'm like
it's coming through the headphones grab the headphones
I don't hear shit what the fuck is going on check the settings
coming through external sound blaster
I wasn't going to tell everybody you were that
fail call a minute ago but if you're going to
out yourself as that then fine
I have no problem owning up to that
I really don't because in between
that the fact that
I am missing half a carpet in my apartment
and the fact that I went IKEA shopping for
new furniture has been quite a week
alright what's on your mind
tonight Rama besides anger
two things I want to agree
with you on Cards Against Humanity
I have to when I go
out to conventions and certain events
I have to go through
my decks and take out certain
expansion packs so that people
do not get confused
oddly enough everyone who plays
this game are die hard gamers
geeks and nerds yes you probably
have like anime expansions
that if you tried to play with me I'd be like
I this sounds like it
might be funny actually
no the most you probably get
confused with is the Cards Against
New York Cards Against Brooklyn expansion
packs but you will pick up on that pretty
quick I think that I could
probably figure out I watch
enough cop shows
yeah I can kind of agree with that
what's the other thing
alright I'm coming I'm listening
to the shows which is why I was kind of late
getting the classic game in a week
up I want to give a shout out
to Jamie
ah the switch
the switch
I think we're probably the only
two that get that
when you said when you said
that somebody have to go out in the back
oh yeah
yes I've told
friends of mine stories of me
go out and get the switch
now you try to be a smart ass
and get like the smallest switch possible
and you think that oh
this will be an easy beating no
your mom still or your grandmother finds a way
to take this little switch
give you a sound beating and send you
back outside for a regulation size one
for round two oh no no no no
it was always you had to get something that
was right in between
the really
thin ones or a log
I'm going to have to be right in the middle of that
a switch is just the southern
version of the belt
or la chancla right
the switch is literally you go
and you find the camellia bush in your backyard
you pick it off
you pick all the leaves off of it
and you pray that you've gotten all the little
nubby bits too
see I didn't have that
where I lived they were
yellow honeysuckle
branches and bushes growing
that's where I had to pick it from
it was either camellias or azaleas
azaleas or camellias
and for the record
la chancla is the thong
shoes that when you piss
mom off she's going to take off her chancla
and beat you with it yeah
there is a shirt that says I survived la chancla
but we never used footwear because footwear
in the south is all cowboy boots that would murder a child
this murders the child
alright
you just want to make them wish they were dead
rama anything else you want to share with us tonight
I ran
the two japanese girls on the train
and they were amused by
my wireless
headphones because you have custom
ear pads on them mine has the
one half logo on them they found it quite cute
I have not seen
these headphones I bet it was adorable
if you go to vmoda and you get
the wireless crossfades you can get
custom 2d and 3d engraving
only in new york
no this is anywhere really
no I mean only in new york would these
types of things happen
pretty much I mean it got to the point
where I see someone in different colored hair I'm like
do I know that cosplayer
alright my friend
I'm going to let you go to try and squeeze in some more calls
but good luck and fix your skype dammit
I will be working or else
you'll be hearing an explosion this
side of the east river
yeah cos you kind of have a big deal show
on tuesday here I was actually no
no we don't it's next tuesday
cos I'm going to see mega ran in concert tuesday night
oh god I was like here I was pumping
up your 300th episode which I thought was the next
tuesday no that's why I said
march 7th march 7th alright
now alright well good
now y'all have time to plan
well that'll be fun seeing mega ran tell him
olr says hi he was on our show
it was like 5 years ago it was a while ago
tell him olr says hi he'll have no idea who the fuck we are
we were having lunch with him
on tuesday too so
oh I didn't know you all were friends
that's fun
well he's just a cool dude like that
yeah he is a cool dude
alright well have fun at the concert
will do alright bye
bye
if you would like to give us a call
let's see
bobby blackwolf
talking about the cards against humanity issue
that was brought up on that call saying I actually
had to take out the pax pax
that's the pax
p-a-c-k-s from my local
group because they didn't get all the references
cos the pax one is all about video games
and probably the in
jokes of things that happen at pax
so yeah you definitely have to
take those out so
jd is pointing out some of those stories that rama
was telling about in new york could also happen in san francisco
that is for sure
alright
anyway gonna take one last
call for calls orange launch radio
all one word on skype last chance to get in and
have a say on something going on tonight
loki any last minute stories you wanna
they don't see you in touch on
no I will give a
quick promotion I'm going to try to
after the show once everything
is all wrapped up I'm gonna try to roll right over
and do a live stream tonight
cos I'm all set up and ready to go
in the office so hopefully
within about 15 minutes of the show ending tonight
I should be up on twitch over twitch
tv slash rob roberts
I'm gonna play something that is not one of my
usuals tonight I'm gonna do something on wii u
I haven't decided if I wanna do virtual console
or if I wanna do something like
mario maker I need to borrow
your mic
mic like oh the
snowball mic yeah yeah
you can borrow that that's actually that was even
donated to me I think that was something
cody had sent me so I'm sure
I was about to buy one I'm sure he would be
thrilled if you used it cos it'll
work well with garage band cos Dan
and I are talking about doing
our thing yeah do it that'd be fun
so again that's twitch
dot tv slash rob roberts is my twitch channel
and should be or it should
be auto hosted on vog network so if you're at least
following vog network you should get that
um so yeah again
I'm trying to decide what I'm gonna do after this show I'm kind of in
a retro mood so I think I'm gonna end up doing something
virtual console I just haven't decided yet
so you know it is on virtual console I started
and it already annoyed me hmm
mother oh yeah like the
the old school earthbound zero yeah
yeah it's it's worth it how did it
annoy you it's just like some
repetitive shit yeah well I mean
right at the start of the game it was a different day
and age that's for sure so
all right well nobody
else is calling on the skype line so I guess that's gonna do it
for calls tonight I know a lot of our
usual live crowd is probably distracted
by the oscars are they over yet
it's almost god it's almost midnight on the
east coast they've gotta be over apparently
Selma Hayek had a sequined penis on her dress
that's lovely
I know one of my friends just told me I see
did the did uh ask to find a picture
of it now I'm assuming La La Land
won best picture I mean it got
all those nominations god I hope not it's a
fucking movie about Hollywood
being in love with itself that's
what are the oscars dark
soccer it's pretty god
uh pretty godson there was hidden
figures you know there's
much better movies I haven't
I the lat okay the last movie
I saw in the theaters was warcraft
so I haven't seen any of these movies so I
have no doctor strange I have no opinion
but before that it was warcraft um
I want to see
beauty and the beast because
that is my favorite
Disney movie do you know
that I have the work in progress laser disc of that
no is that the
one where it flips with the scenes uh
where it does the I saw this once
uh still and they're in the
animated storyboard like animated scenes
oh that's awesome I have the laser disc of that
I don't even remember how I got it but we
have it hmm
cool uh
says no best picture yet
but the director just won I'm assuming the
director for La La Land won
what the fuck ever and usually usually
the director and the picture are the same thing actually
not all the past couple years that trend's been
broken I think they've they've split
up a little bit so
alright well we are gonna
end up the show tonight uh we'll be
back in seven days to talk about the
switch and whatever else goes on in gaming
news maybe some of you will be checking out horizon
zero dawn I'd like to hear some impressions on that
as well so it's gonna be a busy week next
week we'll see how the news treats us
um in the meantime we're gonna wrap up and get on out of
here thank you so much for listening to orange launch radio if you
were here live or if you were here
um uh via the
podcast feed we appreciate it be sure to
tell a friend or two about the show cause word of mouth
goes an awful long way in helping us
get the word of orange launch radio out there
we really appreciate it a five star review
guys like I can't stress this enough on a
place like iTunes or wherever
it is you found a show found this show if you
haven't left a five star review yet that helps a
lot so please please you could take like 15 seconds
and do that we would love you forever
um otherwise
it's time to go around and get
everybody's final thought for the night
uh Loki your final thought tonight
uh my final
thought is um
I guess I'll work on my game
good answer a game I don't know which
one cause I have started like a million of them
uh Loki uh
my final thought is I can't wait to uh
play with these little mini arcade machines that Dark
Sakura bought me although now I'm
at that point where I'm like do I leave him in the
box as a collector or do I take
yeah I feel like I have to
take them out of the box and actually play them
they're not gonna go
up in value that much
you should find these things on eBay
actually people are flipping them on eBay I couldn't believe it
these people are dumb
and lastly but not leastly Dark Sakura
two things
I want this fucking sinus
infection to go the fuck away
and we didn't do the FUs of the week
no we haven't been
funny enough we talked about that last week we haven't been
for a while actually
it was noticed that we've kind of been missing out do you
need some FUs tonight?
just real quick fuck you to sinus infection
wait wait you cannot give an FU
without the music no we talked last week
we noticed ever since we shifted our show roll around
where FUs were supposed to be at the end we've kind of
just been ending the show but
we said FUs will still be done on an as needed
basis so it sounds like
well alright tonight it is needed Dark Sakura has asked
for some FUs
oh this is bad
here is justice
here is punishment
here is...
this is fucked up
FU to my sinus infection
fuck it fuck it fuck it fuck it fuck it
I'm tired of feeling this way
and also FU to Kaiser for not at least letting me
have some kind of leave
of some kind so that I can
rest when I feel fucking shitty
so I am on week
five
week five
now of my antibiotics
I'm
tired of yogurt
and I'm tired of hacking up
everything that ever
has touched my lungs
tired of it oh my god
and I feel much better now
you're welcome uh
my FU of the week goes to the fact that
award shows are always on Sundays
you know what this show
is always on Sundays and I was
here first okay maybe not I think the Oscars
are like eighty something years old but you know what
the Oscars were on Monday at one point in my
life so go back to Monday
assholes
Loki anything you need to get off your chest for the FUs of the week
I just have a headache but it's from
because my family is trying to suffocate you
alright
there it is the FUs of the week as needed
by Dark Sakura as her final
thought so there it is that's the episode of
Orange Lounge Radio in the can
we're done we're out of here
one last final thought
you said two one was
the sinus infection
fine what's the other resist
goodnight everybody
thanks for being here we'll see you in seven days
to do it all over again later
you've been listening to
Orange Lounge Radio
Orange Lounge Radio is a production
of OLR Studios
to join us for a live show
tune into bognetwork.com
Sunday nights at
9pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern
the views and opinions
expressed in this program do not
necessarily reflect those of the staff
of Orange Lounge Radio or
VOG Network but you know
they were all still true
see you next week
you