[SPEAKER_11]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Our live talk program begins now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio may contain sexual and adult content and many instances of the F-word, which is not safe for children.
[SPEAKER_06]: God damn you, stop calling here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't it 4215, pussy wave?
[SPEAKER_06]: You bitch!
[SPEAKER_06]: Now let me check the zip code.
[SPEAKER_06]: 212, fuck you!
[SPEAKER_06]: You have no morals, darling.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd also like to add that I have my father's gun and the scorching case of herpes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kiss my great news.
[SPEAKER_17]: Mecca lecca hi, mecca hidey ho.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, I hate throwing up in public.
[SPEAKER_08]: Me too!
[SPEAKER_08]: Fucker, yeah?
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm working on it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loser.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lame!
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm the size of my face.
[SPEAKER_08]: Breathing, breath, heaving breath, heaving whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now you all just sit there and keep your mouths shut while I go listen to my Britney Spears records.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am your singing telegram.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somewhere inside the state of California, in the great nation of the United States of America, on the planet Earth, Orange Lounge Radio is now on the air.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're tuned into the Bomani Scene's newest and greatest radio station of all things Bomani.
[SPEAKER_03]: My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Joining me as always is my lovely co-host, Jamie Summers, also known as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is episode number seven for August 4th of 2002.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are joined in studio once again by a whole buffet of guests, including two special out-of-towners tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hello, everybody, to Jazz.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: And DDR Mike.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, you fucking assholes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, he's exercising his internet radio rights there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, we're always joined by a bunch of our usual in-studio friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hello to Matt.
[SPEAKER_03]: Matt.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dave, and in the corner, Bradley.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got to be loud for once.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get picked up there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be talking to everybody a little bit more later, but first we're going to take a quick break and playing some requests that we've had the past few weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any other opening thoughts from Miss Sakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have a specific thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we'll get to why in a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_03]: But first up, a pretty quick break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, this is Mel B of RTF.
[SPEAKER_09]: And for an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Mel B can join us on all the fun together.
[SPEAKER_09]: But hey, if you're a broke ass like I am, why don't you come to one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, this is Mel B of R... Hi, this is...
[SPEAKER_06]: Attention, attention!
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on everybody, let's go!
[SPEAKER_06]: Hop to it!
[SPEAKER_06]: One, two, let's go!
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on!
[SPEAKER_06]: Paying the cards, those things don't mean a thing Words for your brain, pain is my game Why let the rain flow with those frames?
[SPEAKER_06]: A pump from the beach, no such thing as pain Do the jump!
Do the jump!
Do the flip!
[SPEAKER_06]: Do the flip!
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't lose the grip To the right, to the right, to the left, to the left
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Do it slick, do it, do it slick, do it slick, do it, do it slick, and vibe, vibe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Linkin' to the left, linkin' to the left Linkin' to the right, linkin' to the right Crowns down for speed, crowns down for speed Disobey your needs, disobey your needs Double dust, inline skate, on rock climate Don't forget the rhythm, groove and keep runnin' This game isn't hard, it's only through pain Always keep it goin' and get wild like Jane Up the ramp we go, all the way Up the ramp we go, all the way Come on now, we ain't got all day Come on now, we ain't got all day
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Left, right, right, left, right, left, right, right, left Shoot, die, let's take a break
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on, please, for old time's sake I gotta do this every single day You gotta do this every single day Tell you the truth, my hair's curly gray Tell you the truth, your hair's dirty gray You may be old, bold, and with teeth to hold It really, really don't matter to me If you're coming for it, I know you got it down Come on, let's see what we got, yeah, so you can cry
[SPEAKER_06]: I gave it to you, I thought you had it, I gave it to you Oh well then, why don't you get your steak?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh well then, why don't I get my steak?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where's mine, can you please wait?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where's yours, can I please wait?
[SPEAKER_06]: You want it just to get it and just take a picture?
[SPEAKER_06]: I carry a camera for all my adventures You carry a camera for all your adventures That was good!
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you please take a picture?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure!
[SPEAKER_12]: The Orange Lounge Radio With the Ping Pong Ball
[SPEAKER_03]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was the Swedish chef there promoting our little show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, Swedish chef can also be found on Google.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we apologize for the feedback we're getting here tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if it's because we're crammed in a little room and we've got a fan right near us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe we want to move the fan.
[SPEAKER_03]: We might get a little less interference with what's going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll work on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So please pardon the hum in the background.
[SPEAKER_03]: It adds character.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so in that last segment we had, what, Papaya with Supergirl, and I tried to play Mr. T, Take Me Higher, but unfortunately the damn MP3 was corrupt.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we threw in some Sister Mosesha from Parappa the Rapper Part 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very fun stage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now you wanted to give that as a shout-out to some people?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, there's some people who said they'd be listening tonight, so I'd like to say hi to Mary, to Ash, Michelle, and Phil.
[SPEAKER_14]: So hi, people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does anybody else have a shoutout they'd like to give out while we're here?
[SPEAKER_16]: Shoutout!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so like, I hope all you conquered scrubs are listening to this, because... No!
[SPEAKER_02]: Am I even talking?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we can hear you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, gotta go, bye.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is this thing on?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it is on.
[SPEAKER_14]: Testies, test, oh wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, we are joined in studio tonight by some special out of town guests.
[SPEAKER_03]: What brings you guys here to town this weekend?
[SPEAKER_11]: We were bored.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, if we sound a little bit out of it tonight and very unprepared for tonight's show, there is good reason for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like scotch.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like double shots of scotch very much.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you count getting completely shit-faced as a little, then yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go ahead and keep talking, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to filter some things out here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, this pressure!
[SPEAKER_14]: I can't take it!
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't make me talk!
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_14]: Seriously, the party last night was pretty, well, kind of insane.
[SPEAKER_14]: There were a lot of people here, and it was basically, there was 2DX going on in the game room, and I wandered in there one time with Guitar Freaks going on,
[SPEAKER_14]: And then there was also, you know, more drinking and quiche.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you have to say that in the microphone so everybody can hear you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're on the air.
[SPEAKER_14]: Say whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who's listening?
[SPEAKER_14]: Everybody.
[SPEAKER_15]: Who's everybody?
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, people.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Obviously not a mic person.
[SPEAKER_17]: Here, wait.
[SPEAKER_17]: Try again.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi, mic.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm talking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody say hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: The party was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had lots of people walking around the assembly room drunk.
[SPEAKER_04]: People kept locking me out in the garage with my sim all night long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that was fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, I hung out with you and I was drunk.
[SPEAKER_14]: I got to do Drunk Drunk Revolution and I really wish that Wendell had been there because I owe him a match of Drunk Drunk Revolution back from Faname last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we'll just have to invite him the next time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, we have a special message from the chat room for Mike from SoCalKicks.
[SPEAKER_03]: He says, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Special delivery there from our chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you want to join in our chat room and join in the ever-interesting festivities tonight... Plug alert.
[SPEAKER_14]: Plug alert.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tonight will be an interesting show, I guarantee, because we're all kind of hungover.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not hungover.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dude, I'd never get hungover.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not technically hungover.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just... I'm emotionally hungover.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway... We don't have sad music, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, the saddest thing in DDR I can think of to play is, like... Raid of Sorrow or Eversnow.
[SPEAKER_18]: Or...
[SPEAKER_03]: I could play like, how about ballad for you?
[SPEAKER_14]: Do not ever play, there is one of the other songs that will never show up on our playlist.
[SPEAKER_14]: Never.
[SPEAKER_14]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was punctuated with a lovely noise.
[SPEAKER_14]: Burp.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're saying about the party saying Sky was stripped of his virginity.
[SPEAKER_03]: About four years ago, bub.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not last night.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't we normally pass that on the way to the Bay Area?
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a Bimani-related show.
[SPEAKER_03]: A B-Mani show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Talking about Konami's famous B-Mani series.
[SPEAKER_03]: Be money right on this show
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell us about this outfit here.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, well, I was playing Speed Demon, and for any of you who don't know what that game is, it's the most ridiculously easy way to win free tickets.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I played it, and I spent about $2, won 500 tickets.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then, so, me and my friend
[SPEAKER_17]: Like, ooh, it's a hat thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, it opened up into this big kind of lampshade.
[SPEAKER_14]: It looks like a wicker lampshade.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, except that it's not completely round.
[SPEAKER_14]: It looks like a Tiffany lamp, but without the knee glass.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, and it's not that great, but anyway, it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: And for 150 tickets, I bought two.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I had 200 tickets left.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then I saw the fans, which are made of crap.
[SPEAKER_17]: The pretty little birds.
[SPEAKER_17]: Craps with colors on them.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, I took hate of them.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then they gave me two extra, because they're nice.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've got a harmonica.
[SPEAKER_17]: And so, now I put it on, and I walk around and make a fool of myself.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought you did that anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, but now I can stay cool while doing it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ah, see.
[SPEAKER_14]: Literally.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's what I call an intelligent, ridiculous-looking fashion sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish I had the webcam stuff working, but I don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm still working on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll hopefully have that up soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, I said that two weeks ago, so who knows.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's soon in Rob's universe, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to join our chat room, visit any other side IRC server, like irc.egheads.org, and join Channel Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_03]: and you can talk to us and participate live with the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Remember, that's Orange Lounge, not red or purple.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like the band from 2DX where we stole the name, basically.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, let's talk to our guests.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk to our guests here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you guys have anything that you're here to plug tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because usually when guests come on shows, they're here to plug something like their latest album or a TV show or a movie they're going to be in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you guys have anything, tournaments or special appearances you're going to be making or websites or what?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're just here for the fuck of it, huh?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're just here to say, I was on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_03]: I destroyed Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bingo!
[SPEAKER_02]: He's here to watch anime porn with all of us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was the coolest line?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'll ask.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my baby!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not inside of me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to be pregnant.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not my baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what was the other one that we saw?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that one part where he's fantasizing about the chick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah, and then he sees the guy sucking his dick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hence the warning for adult content.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about you, Chaz?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything you want to promote?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ghost Step Squad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, Ghost Step Squad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Go Dave Squad!
[SPEAKER_14]: Team Sack making an appearance at Cesar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why did I grab the mic?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because you were an attention whore.
[SPEAKER_17]: I grab the mic all the time.
[SPEAKER_17]: He's right next to me.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have Rob's mic.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's a big grab.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can already tell where this show is going.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, maybe I ought to take the suggestion and just end the show when the Simpsons come on and we'll just fuck the show, let's watch the Simpsons.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're on the radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: New mirrors for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: DWI, I guess version 2.0 beta 5 is finally out now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, because I did play with the sim last night, I have 976 songs in there now.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem is you can't configure any of the keyboard or joystick options in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically I was stuck without being able to use my pads on it, which really disappointed me.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the movies still don't work on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Step Mania 5 is supposed to be out pretty soon, or at least Beta 5 for that, so hopefully soon, because it said on DDR Mania X that it was already out, but I haven't seen it, and still waiting for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other than that, Tourney Mix 2 is still on for August, so entering that, you'll see all the new songs come up around August 15th on DDR East Coast Invasion, so watch for that, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we still have time to enter that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes we do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well this time around I will be entering.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've already picked which song I'm going to be doing, which will be Outer Limits.
[SPEAKER_04]: So look for that to be coming probably on August 15th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rad.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would like to make a shout out to Ash who just entered the room.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm glad that you made it into the chat room.
[SPEAKER_14]: Enjoy IRC.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, one errand that you guys are running today, kind of speaking about the PC simulations, you guys are running over to Fry's to pick up a copy of Dance Dance Revolution for the PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, and you haven't even gotten to try it out yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I made a copy for myself and then didn't quite get a chance to.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll play it on one of the breaks and I'll be back with my brief review of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so during one of the breaks you can go run out there and install it and give us a review.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's already installed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just gotta go play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll do that during one of the breaks.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll talk a little bit more about DDR for the PC later.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else in news going on in the Bomani world?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys were at that tournament that just happened over the weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not over the weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was during the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Triple Threat.
[SPEAKER_03]: What did you guys think about that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or you weren't there, Justin?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, just Mike.
[SPEAKER_03]: What did you think of the Triple Threat contest?
[SPEAKER_03]: Give us a little summary.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, yeah, for one thing, Mike Nose should know that he should never have a tournament on Thursday and Friday.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he already knows that from the bitching that people have done, including Slip and Meow and all the other fucking flamers out there.
[SPEAKER_14]: I wanted to go to that, and I couldn't because it was on the weekday.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Me too, I had to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I'm just echoing everything everybody else says.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had to work, I wanted to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but anyway, it was a good tournament.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really new, something different.
[SPEAKER_02]: There were three events.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had the Survivor Series, which had teams competing against other teams.
[SPEAKER_02]: A March Madness wannabe thing going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we had the DDE Royal Rumble, which was pretty cool, but some of the things I didn't want to see, like Zero stripping in front of an Emphasis, or Mr. Windle almost eating Emphasis too, which was not a good thing to see.
[SPEAKER_18]: I feel sorry for Emphasis.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, as we all do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gee.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, like, Cory, he was bitching again because he lost.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, he has to get over it and deal with his loss, just like every other PA.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who won?
[SPEAKER_02]: For Royal Rumble...
[SPEAKER_02]: Tigger Eugene
[SPEAKER_02]: His brother, Ree, I believe.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then he just lasted after that all the way up to the 28th person.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Emphasis, he got to come back again because he had tokens.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because every time you beat three people or so many people, you gain an extra so-called life.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can make a comeback.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Jimmy lost to him on Kakume, which sucked because he'd always practice that song a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, March Madness, surprisingly, re-won, beating Eugene by two grades on, um, Waka Laka, Hidden Right on flat, I believe, which is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Scary.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, very scary.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, Survivor Series...
[SPEAKER_02]: I talked too much shit, I thought my team was gonna win, we got knocked out first round.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was, yeah, it was really close.
[SPEAKER_02]: I took out Ree, which is a good compliment to accomplish, because he always beats me at tournaments.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you all!
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, yeah, um, a lot of people came, it was a good tournament.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hope to look forward to another one like that, just make sure it's on a weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, as you all know, on the 17th...
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Sounds Tournament is going to be at Mountain Mike's in Concord.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully all of you will come to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Should be pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like the fourth bracket, this wasted two minutes of my life and I want it back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: For freestyle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would so be my category if I ever actually entered freestyle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you get a chance to see my drunken freestyle last night?
[SPEAKER_03]: On Loki's sim I was dancing, he has Speedway in his sim with steps to it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't see it, however I think that might be an excuse to revive the bats.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what we ought to do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go to this tournament and just get fucking wasted and do a freestyle routine and see how we do.
[SPEAKER_14]: Which for me, if I'm going to freestyle, is it going to be with bats or pom-poms?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're of age.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's acceptable.
[SPEAKER_03]: If other people drive us, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to order a pitcher of beer at Mountain Mike's.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know if it would be against the rules if we could, you know, do the freestyle with the pitcher of beer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't want to spill my beer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: First off, that's alcohol abuse.
[SPEAKER_14]: Second of all, that's a, you know, dance pad that we can't, like, get wet.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, at least from non-organic, well, I guess it is organic.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's bad enough we might get so drunk to the point of, like, accidentally urinating on the pads.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: I may throw up, but I never pee on the pad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rob, shut up!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just thinking of the sound clips I'm going to get from this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: You are not using that.
[SPEAKER_14]: You are not.
[SPEAKER_14]: I never pee on the dance pad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, other news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk about... Yes, other news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's change the direction of this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk about 8th style.
[SPEAKER_03]: 2DX 8th style.
[SPEAKER_03]: 8th style.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got some demo MP3s from 8thStyle, because it's on test location right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so we're going to play some clips from some of the new songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now has anybody else here heard these 8thStyle songs?
[SPEAKER_03]: You've heard them?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, assuming you haven't.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see what you guys think of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll play some quick clips.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not going to play the whole thing because they're kind of long, so we'll just kind of skip to the middle and see what we get.
[SPEAKER_03]: This first song I'm going to play is Airflow by Mr. T.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm confused now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was Mr. T and Motokai F or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh, I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_14]: Blue Impulse Yuki
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm very decent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray, I'm happy he finally ditched Politary.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, that's probably just their pet name.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Brad was here, he would smack you right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, well, he's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's his own damn fault for not showing up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck Politary!
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck Brad!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_14]: Right in the nose!
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope he's not listening at home.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I'll be in trouble if that was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's look at...
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Taka doing Rainbow Flyer.
Yeah, it sounds like I sense a lot of those little like triplet things that you see a lot in 2DX.
It's like da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you have to remember, yeah, these MP3s are going to be crappy because people are recording them off the machine, literally.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't the machines, though, have audio in and out?
[SPEAKER_14]: Why can't they just use that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, because the people who own the arcade are testing the machine, might be kind of watching with an evil eye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially if you have Konami representatives around the bit like, uh, what are you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, give it time, because that's what they did with Max 2 and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, just give it time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody will leak the soundtrack eventually.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the last one here, now this falls into a category called Cuddlecore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds good to me!
[SPEAKER_03]: Mhm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds kind of mellow.
[SPEAKER_16]: I know, you can hear all the conversation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does it get interesting by the end?
[SPEAKER_03]: This kind of sounds like a carnival song.
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm saying in the chat room, I farted better quality sounds than this in response to the Cuddle Corps song.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was from Pyro Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that would be an interesting 2DX song, kind of like in the Kitty.
[SPEAKER_03]: You remember the Kitty song?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Theme of Oopa.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, that's...
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, you know, that song was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: It made it onto Beatmania Pocket for Wonderswan.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that actually is a really good version of Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, if you have to have it with you and you have a Wonderswan, it came with a little scratch pad that hooks over to the right side of the system.
[SPEAKER_14]: And all of the music, it only had ten songs in it, but they were all digitized.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you didn't get, you know, crappy MIDI like with the DDRGB series.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, also still popular in the 2DX world, Sixth Style for the home.
[SPEAKER_03]: Still pretty much new, and lots of people getting that, and more and more people playing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of the Game Boy versions of the Bumani games, you can actually get those at BumaniStyle.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, hey, hey!
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got them there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Free plug!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, free plug.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or you can do what I did and go buy them.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's the right way and the wrong way.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, that's like so 2000.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: I have it on my Game Boy, and I can take it with me, whereas I can't take my whole computer with me.
[SPEAKER_14]: My bio is a little heavy, thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it won't fit into my purse!
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, we're going to go to a quick break here and we're going to test out DDRPC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some people are running out to go play that because we just got it here, a copy of it in the house.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we're going to take a quick break and we'll come back with our initial thoughts on DDRPC, some interesting news involving DDRPC that could be an indication of where U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bomani is headed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also tonight we've got FU of the Week, pretty lengthy this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: We also are doing another additional list list tonight, so stay tuned for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be right back.
Thanks for watching!
Let it rain, let it fly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bitch, get a new song!
[SPEAKER_11]: An open letter from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that was like the very first promo that I ever made for the station.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_14]: I remember coming up with that in your car.
[SPEAKER_14]: You did.
[SPEAKER_03]: The one-hit wonder one?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, not the one-hit wonder one.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm talking about the Jogle one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, the Jogle one?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because we were listening to one of your Dance Mania compilations.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we started... It was playing Bye Bye Baby.
[SPEAKER_18]: That wasn't nice, Drew.
[SPEAKER_03]: But she needs a new song.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, let's face it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they're all the same.
[SPEAKER_14]: The song was playing and I was in the back seat singing Damdaryam.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's like how Matt, who's out in the garage right now with DDRPC, playing, he has an edit for Bye Bye Baby Balloon that's basically just the steps to Damdaryam.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it works for like the first half of the song, but then it kind of gets out of sync.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like there's an extra beat or something that throws it all off.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it works scary well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So as I mentioned, they're out in the garage right now playing DDRPC.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you sure they're not watching the anime porn again?
[SPEAKER_03]: They could be by this point as soon as I left.
[SPEAKER_03]: But when I went out there, they were watching the DDRPC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whole new interface, which I've got to say is weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's kind of like 4th Mix.
[SPEAKER_03]: But not.
[SPEAKER_03]: How do I explain this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Imagine if on 4th Mix you could go...
[SPEAKER_03]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, one thing I noticed right away, the characters are based off some kind of new engine because they're really high resolution, they look really good, the characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is probably why the new hidden characters are such a big deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the big news that came up this week is that they've released the very first downloadable characters for DDRPC.
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe Zack and Alex are the names.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're not based off any other previous DDR characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're brand spanking new.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay for America.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay, we get something special.
[SPEAKER_03]: We get an Earthlight mix and an AMT3P mix and now we get...
[SPEAKER_13]: That makes me spell a patriotic rhyme.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm feeling it in the cockles of my heart.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically the game is mostly based off a fourth mix engine, although it is a little smoother.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd say it's a lot, the arrows seem to run a little smoother, kind of like fifth mix smooth.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was going to look, and they turned it off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, they turned it off?
[SPEAKER_03]: How mean of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: You didn't get to see the interface thing?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's, well, I mean, again, since it's based off of 4th Mixed Engine, it looks very similar, except you kind of could just pick any category you want, and then the songs are in a circle, as opposed to across the bottom.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's circly, huh?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes, circles are good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Circles are round.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I'm also, I'm also being told not to forget Angel Zuken, as opposed to Devil Zuken.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now you got Angel.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why can't we have, you know, Purgatorial Zuken or something?
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, where it's just, you know, kind of boring and just stands there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Japs got Zuken, I mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, since there's like two players, can't they like bend down and shit on their face and everything?
[SPEAKER_05]: And yell out in- I'M CHINESE, OH!
[SPEAKER_05]: So this is our clip for the movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about topless?
[SPEAKER_14]: They should have, like, boyzookin.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet you anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: How long do you think it's... But would they bounce?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the chatroom, they're hoping for a shirtless Emmy.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Then I get pamphlet rage.
[SPEAKER_03]: How long do you think it's going to take?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you think he's going to bounce?
[SPEAKER_03]: If somebody...
[SPEAKER_07]: Jesus, bro.
[SPEAKER_03]: If somebody went and hacked Tomb Raider so that you could play a nude Lara Croft with big old jugs and, you know, how long is it going to take before somebody hacks DDRPC so you can play Topless Zukin, Shirtless Enemy, Pantsless Rage?
[SPEAKER_14]: So what, then merge the first dead or alive with DDR and have, like, Bounce Bounce Revolution?
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, Bounce with B-Bounce Revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: Since now you can play DDR at home in the nude, play along with our characters in the nude!
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, I bet they're gonna have skins you can make for that, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: New skins.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ooh, baby.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, it's gonna turn into this whole big, you know, fad like what happened with The Sims.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, where you can have, you know, Wolverine and, um, who else, somebody random.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, I don't know, Galacticus, you know, hanging out, doing husband-wifey things.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we have the return of... A very observant fellow in the chatroom says, now I can't confirm this, maybe Jamie can, but you can see Rage's ball line in third mix.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, I never bothered to check, but maybe I will.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was Pyromancer then.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a moron.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we have nuts in DDR.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's just not talk about people to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Matt's back joining us.
[SPEAKER_03]: What were your first impressions of DDR PC being a sim fan?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, let's start with the interface.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell were they thinking?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's 4th Mix, but... It's the most retarded interface I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, but I'll give it a little credit, because 4th Mix needed that, where you can go back and forth between the categories.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just...
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks kinda dumb.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, but the idea's good, it just looks dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like if you took the banners from 4th Mix and stuck it on the little CD rotation thing that they have in all music mode, you would get what you have there, which looks like a bunch of banners hanging from a spindle thing, like some sort of like sunglass case type thing that you would see in a store.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the most fucking retarded thing, and they only have like 8 songs in each thing, so even if it was like 4th Mix...
[SPEAKER_04]: Which you gotta admit has about like at least 20 or so in each category I mean, why the hell are they doing that with the interface?
[SPEAKER_04]: It just looks like crap So that's fine, you know, it looks like crap The textures as far as the characters go, really good, looks nice Yeah, the characters look nice, that's the first thing I said too Backgrounds, who really cares, no one watches the backgrounds But they look nice too Did you see any Lego people yet?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the best background with Lego people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what I did like, though, is the fact that you can customize with buttons and stuff for the controllers and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the way I have my pads wired, they're really fucked up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if it was set to how a pad was, it wouldn't work.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm glad they have that, at least.
[SPEAKER_14]: Meanwhile, we have Michael here with a yo-yo stuck in his eye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hyroman sent me a picture.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shall we take a vote on whether to open it or not?
[SPEAKER_03]: It is entitled Rage.gif.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can bet you know what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bald!
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we all vote yes, we're going to open it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I'm going to do with these files sent to me during the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, we're just going to vote if we're going to waste our time with it or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, we voted to waste our time with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just a picture of Rage.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, is that supposed to be that the shadowing there is supposed to be like balls?
[SPEAKER_14]: Unless he's got some really huge testicles.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what Breach Pat likes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that supposed to be the peenie right there?
[SPEAKER_03]: If so, that's not impressive.
[SPEAKER_03]: I expected better from Rache.
[SPEAKER_14]: But keep in mind, you know, Rache goes everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe that's why he's called Rache.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's very angry over the fact he has a small penis.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never thought about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray, this show's resorted to dick jokes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, no, no, it's like that one joke where it goes into get laid at a brothel.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, you know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's doctored.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very scary.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe not, because the shadowing looks right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I guess it's a real thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, Robbie, you kind of look like a woman there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's a woman.
It's a woman.
[SPEAKER_14]: So Rage has a vagina.
[SPEAKER_14]: Chicks with dicks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically the Baxteran rage could make it in the porn industry because of one small defect.
[SPEAKER_04]: So he's turned to DDR to fan out his frustrations.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it's like the joke of the man who went into the brothel.
[SPEAKER_14]: He goes in and this one woman comes running out of the room laughing hysterically, says his dick's had tiny on it.
[SPEAKER_14]: And so another one goes in and she comes running out screaming, I can't do it, his dick says tiny on it.
[SPEAKER_14]: So another one goes in, and she actually has a little bit more patience.
[SPEAKER_14]: She comes out hours later, and...
[SPEAKER_14]: The other goes, so you could do it?
[SPEAKER_14]: How could you do it?
[SPEAKER_14]: He's like, once you got that thing going, it said, Tiny's Bar and Grill, 5734 5th Street, New York, New York.
[SPEAKER_14]: That old joke, I know, but... But see, that's why he has the rage, because nobody will give him a chance when he's in town or something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: That sucked!
[SPEAKER_03]: Now there's talk in the chat room, and if you want to join our insane people in the chat room, you're just going to head over to any other side IRC server, like irc.acheheads.org, and you're going to join Channel Pound Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're talking right now, they're wondering if, well, they've got one more dick joke there.
[SPEAKER_03]: If Afro's hung like a horse, they're going to look into that, maybe get some more pictures.
[SPEAKER_14]: He gets in the contest with Dread Snake.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think Dread Snake has a beat, the name says so.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, man, you've got those robots in there, too, I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows of that kind of stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, really, anything's possible there.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have all those attachments, don't they?
[SPEAKER_14]: And now we've really, really gone into the adult content, so I think maybe we need to... No, no break.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to talk characters more.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, you people need to get out of the gutter because you're all stepping on me, so go away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now these new characters are going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie's thinking about Dick.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what kind of characters do you think will be seen with these new Konami originals?
[SPEAKER_03]: One thing I suggested on a post like this in DDR Freak, of all places, was...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, I have one suggestion.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know Naoki's in DDR?
[SPEAKER_03]: They should put Mr. T in there and have him look like Mr. T. He's like, I pity the fool who don't pay me.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you guys talking?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, anything?
[SPEAKER_03]: Gossiping.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gossip?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, come on!
[SPEAKER_03]: Make it gossip on air!
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on, come on!
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't the KOA guy get fired or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I think that's just rumor.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, everybody!
Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, they'll probably have, like, maybe some of the other Monty characters in there and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: The stupid little rabbits and... No, Pikachu's a Nintendo character.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think he's gonna show up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pikachu needs to die.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to get those guys from Contra in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: See, I have this secret little plan that I'm going to take over.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, that's right, there was Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles.
[SPEAKER_14]: That would be awesome to have the turtles dancing, if the sea hasn't split their dancing.
[SPEAKER_14]: But no, no, I have this plot going on that when I go to Tokyo next year, I'm going to take over Toei and have the rights to Digimon be my own, so we'll have Digimon and DDR, because I'm also going to take over Konami next.
[SPEAKER_14]: With a tank.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we do know that the last unlockable character is going to have to be something very interesting because most of them have a partner.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kid Dracula!
[SPEAKER_03]: But the very last one is Solo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kid Dracula.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I'm being told that anything is possible and things that you might be thinking are rumors very well could be true.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all I can say.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be the guy from the Mike's Hard Lemonade commercial with the crazy head growing out of his shoulder.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, he's got his twin, but it's only one person.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm telling you, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard inside information, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: What about, like, what about, like, three-titted Emmy?
[SPEAKER_14]: I think this, though, would make a... Honestly, Rob, I think this would make a good future list list, honestly.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or they'll have, like, sex slave Zukin in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: No sex slave Zukin.
[SPEAKER_14]: We need no pants rage.
[SPEAKER_18]: Bonded jealous.
[SPEAKER_14]: Guys!
[SPEAKER_14]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you can have Bondage, Alice, and Three-Tint Emmy, then I get, you know, no pants range.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then you gotta have, you know, that Dredd guy, you know, Dredd's everywhere, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, okay, anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cousin Hitler Dredd's.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, now that's a good suggestion I'm reading in the chat room, that the last character should be a Moi head, or Maui, I can't even say that word.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Moi head.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moi, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Easter Island heads that you see in One of Gradius.
[SPEAKER_14]: But then it would get sued by Emotion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, there's joint ownage laws there, apparently.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, Emotion, for long-term anime fans, Emotion uses the Moai head as their mascot.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about getting Sue from Easter Island, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: They had them way long before, you know, Emotion ever came out with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll stop now.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's something about that, you know, the old-school Emotion, you know, intro with the little 80s, you know, drum rock.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lovely suggestion from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about DarkSakura dressed up as Emi?
[SPEAKER_03]: As an unlockable character.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've already done that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But as an unlockable DDR character.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: You want to go model for the lovely folks at Konami?
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, the pictures from Fanime are still up on my FTP.
[SPEAKER_14]: But no, you know, if anybody actually wants to see, I can draw it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have before.
[SPEAKER_14]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe we'll make that for the site.
[SPEAKER_04]: HappyNoodleBoy HappyNoodleBoy
[SPEAKER_14]: Skins for... You can have Godzilla as the last character.
[SPEAKER_14]: Go, Godzilla, go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but like, on the serious side, I'm thinking that they might do, uh, just another artist, like how they did on 5th Mix with Naoki and, uh, 2MB.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was thinking Togo and Senna.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or Taka.
[SPEAKER_14]: Then if you use the both of them, you have Outface.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one-handed V another guy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Lisu!
[SPEAKER_14]: We need DJ Lisu!
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a giant dancing hand.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, then they'd get sued by Nintendo for the end of Smash Brothers.
[SPEAKER_14]: With a giant hand that, you know, pokes you and flips you off the edge of the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, actually, you know, the game Hand of Fate, one of the Cryorindia games, had a giant hand as the villain, so they could be sued by them, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, Matt, I ask your expert quote-unquote opinion, at least probably being the most educated on all the hacking of various DDR-related things in the room.
[SPEAKER_03]: How long is it going to be before we get people creating their own DDR characters, you think, such as Three-Titted Emmy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, that all depends on how they're in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, as far as, like, the music and stuff, it looks like it's pretty much similar to, you know, DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just one huge bin file that's in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, I'm gonna look at it, see what I can figure out.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean, I'm not that great as far as hacking actual programs and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm good with edits, that's about it, but I'll figure out some, maybe.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: For anyone, I will pay someone to make me a DarkSakura as a skin for the DDRPC once I get mine.
[SPEAKER_03]: What about PantslessRage?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm more important, thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I get pencils made!
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, actually, now that I think about it, since you do have the add-on characters now, it might be a little bit easier to make these extra characters, because you can look at that and see what's all entailed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I definitely see it possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, well, I guess I'll have to wait for that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Seriously, I'll pay you a whole 50 cents.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, wait, those are goblin tokens, my bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: But they weren't getting any goblin.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's half a game of DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, SoCalKicks is going to send that to you.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's volunteering to create that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: And by the way, he still needs to send me proof that he, you know, got a 90%, you know, full combo on my Look to the Sky edit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other rumors about DDRPC is that not only will you have the downloadable characters, but you're going to be able to download new interfaces and possibly some new songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: For DDRPC, do you think that's a possibility or do you think it's a load of crap?
[SPEAKER_18]: That's a load of crap.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think it's a possibility and it will make it a lot better.
[SPEAKER_18]: But it's a load of crap.
[SPEAKER_18]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Slightly more songs, more Konami originals, same interface, yadda yadda yadda I foresee it happened And then they're gonna have like the downloadable feature that'll like, you know, it'll allow you to un-stone Palamon Forum Blink blink, nevermind Anyway I'm nodding but none of you can hear it because the marbles in my head fell out last night with the party
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_18]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: It may look like that there's more arrows at the end there, but actually they don't get saved to the new file.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually have a whole thing, a whole section in my FAQ that you can find at www.geocities.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_07]: And blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Edit Hack FAQ.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can find that there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: You said fuck.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe the people in the chatroom will get lucky and we'll put it there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lucky.
[SPEAKER_03]: I personally don't feel there's going to be downloadable interfaces and songs because why do that when they can release DDRPC's second mix, Max, Ultra, 2000, three-titted EMI version.
[SPEAKER_14]: We do not need three-titted EMI version, thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: We need No Pants Rage.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, they do have all these weird games that come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, there's that Matt Hoffman's BMX.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're actually making, like, a sort of adult version of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm dead serious, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: They are making... It's, uh, what was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Matt Hoffman's Trip... Or, it's like Triple Extreme.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've seen actual articles, and I've seen pictures from it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like they're going to have topless riders and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You think... No, we meant, of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Serious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a picture.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will bring it next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, maybe they'll do something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, they'll have strippers and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we'll see an erotic DDR mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: So all the music in it is erotic and they get, you know... What about DDR Volleyball?
[SPEAKER_14]: DDR Volleyball.
[SPEAKER_18]: DDR Volleyball Edition.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have to explain the reference mode.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dead or Alive Volleyball.
[SPEAKER_18]: All the bouncing you can handle.
[SPEAKER_14]: If anyone is an old-school importer like I am, you might remember a couple of games they put out called Konami World, which were basically different adventure games.
[SPEAKER_14]: They were a little platform game that had a... Each level was taken from various popular comic games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like there was a Dracula, a Kumajou Dracula 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: There was... Or for Castlevania, for UN-informed.
[SPEAKER_14]: Gradius, you know, Life Force, there was all that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um...
[SPEAKER_14]: If they did something like that now, it'd be like the DDR minigame, like what's in Tokimeki Memorial, Dancing Summer Vacation, and they would have the pop and music minigame, the 2DX minigame, so you'd be switching out controllers the whole time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I think the absolute coolest character add-on that they could do if they're going to do... Absolute...
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, the most cool, I don't know, anyway, characters you could download would be Goemon and the Doctor, what's his name, with the blue mustache.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember?
[SPEAKER_03]: Legend of Mystical Ninja?
[SPEAKER_14]: And who actually played that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Me?
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You didn't play it!
[SPEAKER_14]: I knew who Goemon was.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would be sure of all people you would have played it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I rented it once.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they had, like, they had the little mini Gradius you could play.
[SPEAKER_03]: If there was a new version coming out, it would have a mini DDR, I guarantee you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, that would actually, that would make sense.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I mean, you know, but we've already had DDR as a mini game for, like I said, dancing, summer vacation, for all of you dating sim fans.
[SPEAKER_03]: An interesting comment about DDR PC from our resident joker in the chatroom, Pyroman, saying that you could put the arrows on stealth and then just please yourself watching Hi-Rez Charmy.
[SPEAKER_14]: and we have people with no sex life in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, on that note, I think we're going to take a quick break and resituate some things around the room.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think our man needs to prioritize a few things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now be nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, we're going to take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be back.
Thanks for watching!
Is your name?
[SPEAKER_14]: Mr. Random Person on the Street, who, by the way, is not an actor, what do you think of the Orange Lounge Bay Money Music and More show?
[SPEAKER_09]: The music is like being transported to just this dancing spaceship place.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's unearthly.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like being at a club, except you don't have to actually ask someone to dance.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's a message from someone who doesn't get a date.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quit whispering in my ear.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're joined by the individual who likes to whisper sweet nothings into my ear.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hello, everybody, to Shivam.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, baby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyone say hello to the bee money freaks of America, Micah?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, Mikey, you don't really play these B-Money games, do you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Everybody sucked at first, except me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wish that was true.
[SPEAKER_14]: Remember, everybody was a newbie first.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, anyway, moving on to a segment...
[SPEAKER_03]: that we have to do every week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I have to point out, though, however, for those of you concerned with the potty level of tonight's show, that don't like the fact that we're talking about three-titted individuals and pantsless people and whatever sorts of things, I would just like to state we right now currently have a ratings record on this show right now, so don't say that potty humor doesn't get you ratings, because we're living proof.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, I think we just need to have Mike here more often just to go, fuck shit, fuck all you people, fuck...
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shit fuck, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Beautiful!
[SPEAKER_03]: There's another spike in the ratings.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, let's just, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's just get the hentai, put it in, and then we'll just say the hell with the rest of the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll go watch, we'll go play DDRPC.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rob, no offense, fuck that, but I feel like ditching.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, we're gonna get... I'm sorry, what?
[SPEAKER_14]: I wanna play DDRPC.
[SPEAKER_16]: DDRPC, do you have DDRPC here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Shivam, it's in the garage, running on my PC, they're politely playing right now The Sims, since The Sims has, you know, 976 songs, whereas DDRPC has 40.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do the math.
[SPEAKER_04]: 40 bad songs, so, 976, 40.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love, I, tough decision.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like, love this feeling, hello, because when, all I had was DDR's second mix on Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_14]: That song came up four damn times in a row on my non-stop.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't you just love random?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I have to laugh at?
[SPEAKER_04]: Endless mode, extra mix.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let the beat hit them four times.
[SPEAKER_16]: Say it again into the mic.
[SPEAKER_16]: Endless mode, extra mix.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let the beat hit them four times in a row.
[SPEAKER_16]: Love This Feeling has nothing on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: What I have to love is at Fry's, they have DDRPC there, and right below it they have Kiki Joys.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for all this, you might be running Sims and stuff, and using Kiki Joys, they don't allow you to push two buttons at the same time when it comes to the directional buttons.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, because they're dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the only converter that they have.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, wait, who's the company that did it?
[SPEAKER_02]: That issued Kiki Joy?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Never heard of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never heard of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I own one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, if you have a Kiki Joy, fucking light that shit on fire, take a shit on it, and smoke that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: The big indicator first is it's a giant pink object.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have nothing to say about that color.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've seen giant pink objects like that inserted in places, you know, not used properly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, hold on, let's do this real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have a Kiki Joy right now, tell us, if you're on the channel, tell us if it works good for you or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: If not, then just tell us whatever the fuck you want out here.
[SPEAKER_14]: In defense of the Kiki Joy, it does work quite well for Metal Gear Solid on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you saying that it doesn't work on a dance pad?
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't work because you can't push left and right or up and down at the same time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, what about a regular controller?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, a regular controller is fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's what most people... I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what most people probably do on the PC anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because... But when you buy DDR, you don't...
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not going to go, oh, I'm going to go buy a plate.
[SPEAKER_16]: Call the pad, okay?
[SPEAKER_16]: It's all about the control.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's all about the DDR personal massager, actually.
[SPEAKER_16]: Everybody knows they want their big bumblebee in the back, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: And speaking of fucking things... Anyway, let's change the subject now, because we've got to get to Jamie's F... And actually, everybody's going to participate.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not everybody, but, you know, the important people.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everything that I had... We'll be participating in the FU of the week this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Two of the topics I had to bitch about are going to be covered by other people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: However, I will mention them.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Cue my music!
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you, this is fucked up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Man, this is bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway, my fuck you of the week, once again, just like last weekend, the week before, goes toward Ragnarok Online.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also, also as... I don't care.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is my fuck you, so fuck you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway, or as my friend referred to it as Cracknarok, but still.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway, um...
[SPEAKER_14]: For any people who have been keeping up with the game, and I'm sorry for people who have recently downloaded Syrah, the international servers have gone down for three months.
[SPEAKER_14]: They've gone the further step to ban any North American, European IPs that try to play on the Japanese or Korean servers.
[SPEAKER_14]: I had gotten to where I was enjoying it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It wasn't kicking me off nearly so much.
[SPEAKER_14]: And guess what happened?
[SPEAKER_14]: They go down for three months.
[SPEAKER_14]: So fuck them, fuck them and their stupid asses.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm downloading a different game now.
[SPEAKER_14]: And the next fuck you of the week goes toward AT&T, which I also hate.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have my fuck you of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: is for AT&T Cable, because they've given us such wonderful new channels this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have Noggin, which is, Noggin fucking rules, because they show the old school 80s Nickelodeon things, and early 90s.
[SPEAKER_03]: Clarissa Explains It All was on, and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: We get G4, which is the new All Video Games All The Time channel.
[SPEAKER_03]: and we have, what else was on there, BBC America.
[SPEAKER_14]: MTV2.
[SPEAKER_03]: And how does this count as a fuck you again?
[SPEAKER_03]: And MTV2.
[SPEAKER_03]: The reason why this is a fuck you of the week, when I tried to access these channels, it said, we're sorry, this is a subscription service.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though we're already raping you $50 a month for cable, if you want these channels, you're going to have to pay $20 more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck you, I pay too much for my cable already.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, why don't you take off these shitty channels I don't want, like, I don't know, MSNBC, and give me...
[SPEAKER_17]: Oxygen.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take off Lifetime with its fucking... The only fucking cool thing on Lifetime is Shop Till You Drop.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they have that on PAX now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Leave Oxygen on, because I got that old lady with the penis talk show.
[SPEAKER_02]: You seen that?
[SPEAKER_02]: She goes, this is a dick.
[SPEAKER_02]: You put this in a lady's pussy hole.
[SPEAKER_17]: But on Lifetime also they have tons of stories about like lesbians and them getting like raped by their parents and then running away and becoming foster children and all the fucked up shit that you can have all in one like hour and a half show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rob, I think you need to cue my music again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm being told in the chat room that they will activate the channels for free.
[SPEAKER_03]: All you have to do is call maybe for the first month.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know, if they're free, why don't they just give them to me?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why do I have to call?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do I have to take a survey?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why do you, sir, a 24-year-old individual, want to be watching Noggin Network?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you a pedophile, sir?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, dammit, I just want to relive my youth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that so wrong?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, Jamie's music.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's time to re-key my music again.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because my fuck you of the week goes toward AT&T Broadband.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, I'm sure quite a few of the people listening know of my drama with AT&T, how I'd be kicked off every few moments, hop up on the tile, go downstairs to check the mode, see that it's back on, go ahead, sign off, AOL, hop back on, and, you know, it's getting frustrating, especially when I was in the middle of, you know, playing that crack game.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_14]: Fuck them and their stupid asses.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, Matt also has a Fuck You of the Week, and I don't have any music really for Matt, so I'm just going to give him It's Raining Men.
[SPEAKER_04]: My first Fuck You of the Week goes to Rob, forgive me, It's Raining Men.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just not right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, my Fuck You of the Week goes to Fuck You of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's better than It's Raining Men.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, anyways, so we're going to give the Fuck You of the Week to Panda Express.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Panda Express is like this wannabe Chinese food fast food place.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have, like, a few things to order, I mean, and today they're out of practically everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does anyone want anything, uh, other, well, white rice, anyone want white rice?
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, I guess, okay, I'll get white rice.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, practically out of everything else, and they, you know, put my stuff in the bag, my napkins got soaked in, I don't know what, some sort of juice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blood.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, blood, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Panda Express is going to give you AIDS.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was probably Panda I was eating anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's not the point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: I got sick from my lunch today.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I was avoiding meat for that reason.
[SPEAKER_03]: What pissed me off, I wanted chow mein.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had to wait 25 minutes for them to fucking make some new chow mein because they didn't think that, oh, when it's empty, when it's starting to get empty and we've got a line going out the door, maybe it's time to make some more, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, not that they could, you know, foresee these things in advance.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have to run out of it first, and then I'll be the next person in line that's like, oh, you gotta wait 25 minutes so we can make more domain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_04]: And my second, uh, my second FU week goes to the stupid bitch at, uh, Fry's.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, let, here's a little information for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I'm peeing with a credit card, that means I'm over 18, you dumb bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: So don't ask me if I'm 18 if I have a credit card here.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what if I'm buying the anime porn?
[SPEAKER_04]: That doesn't mean anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: The dumb bitch had the nerve to tell me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, she's like, are you 18?
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, that's not necessarily true.
[SPEAKER_16]: My brother's only 16.
[SPEAKER_16]: He's got an ATM credit card.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an ATM card!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a ATM card, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: ATM card!
[SPEAKER_04]: She said her 11-year-old son had a fucking credit card.
[SPEAKER_04]: How the fuck is he gonna pay off a credit card?
[SPEAKER_04]: The goddamn kid can't even work!
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, but have you been accused of having a false ID when you're 26 years old at the convention?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been called to hold a platinum card, dude, so it's not even really funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I have not, but I've been refused a movie because I didn't have my ID with me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stupid Chico Theater not letting me see Deadman on campus.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should be thanking them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I did see that later on, yeah, I'm scarred for life.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I was at, this was one of my other fuck you's from Anime Expo that I haven't brought up yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: The fact that when I went to go buy, by the way, the doujinshi didn't turn out to be yaoi, by the way, you know.
[SPEAKER_16]: No yaoi, oh no, no gay penis, what will we do?
[SPEAKER_14]: But no, the guy there, the guy there wanted me to get my mom, so that I could buy doujinshi.
[SPEAKER_14]: and then I showed him my license and my ID.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the topic of anime porn, I have another FU that's long overdue that goes to the stupid makers of that movie, Sailor Moon and the Seven Balls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Goddamn, that movie sucks ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like horrible flash anime.
[SPEAKER_16]: Who the fuck bought that?
[SPEAKER_16]: Why?
[SPEAKER_16]: That was a horrible flash anime that someone made years and years ago and someone actually went out and published.
[SPEAKER_16]: I can't believe you paid for it.
[SPEAKER_16]: What the fuck is wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_12]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: He was dumb.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was stupid again.
[SPEAKER_12]: No!
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway, have we got to the fucking everyone?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now serving, 47.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, DDRholic, hi by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope we see you at Golfland this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Says that they issue credit cards to kids with prepaid limits from Daddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like one of those secured credit cards where, like, Daddy pays $300 so, you know, Junior can have a $300 credit card to buy anime porn with.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, but my credit card didn't say, oh, look, it's a kid card, you know, with the big happy smiley face and the rainbow.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't have Ronald McDonald on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the dumb bitch didn't even have the smarts to look at my fucking, you know... So you didn't get the Sailor Moon platinum card then?
[SPEAKER_16]: To go with your Seven Balls purchase?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I did not.
[SPEAKER_16]: I can't believe you bought that, dude.
[SPEAKER_16]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_16]: Of all the goddamn gimpy anime porn out there, you got something that I could make in my fucking sleeve.
[SPEAKER_14]: He wouldn't have the Sailor Moon one.
[SPEAKER_14]: He's, you know, did think he was younger, so he had, like, Superdoll Lekotan or something.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yay, my Gundam credit card.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, okay, I like watching... Platinum 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like watching 10 frame animation with stupid sound clips repeated over and over again.
[SPEAKER_16]: Then play DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well... Oh yeah, gotcha there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's like the song selects sequence.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know, you sit there and listen to the worst sample out of the fucking one and a half minutes they could possibly pick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, that would kind of bring us back to that old topic we were just talking about, about the characters and all the... No pants rage.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway, moving right along.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know to what.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really have any other subjects to discuss today.
[SPEAKER_14]: Patsy Blue.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I get to talk again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pepsi Blue is really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, shut up!
[SPEAKER_02]: Pepsi Blue is hella good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody at the tournament was drinking that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, okay, anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: That shit was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fucking Rediffusion takes, like, cough syrup.
[SPEAKER_12]: What do you think, Jens?
[SPEAKER_18]: I like Red Fusion better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go to hell anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pepsi Blue owns your daddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to tell some stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk about, let's make this be Imani related and talk about refreshing drinks to play when playing DDR.
Pocari Sweat.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, obviously Ramun, which is probably the greatest drink that ever came in a pixie cup with that damn marble in there so you can't tell how much fucking liquid is in there to begin with.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's all about Pocari Sweat.
[SPEAKER_16]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_14]: Pokari Sweat.
[SPEAKER_16]: Pokari Sweat looks like sweat, smells like sweat, tastes like sweetened sweat, and comes in a goddamn bottle that says sweat.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pokari Sweat is the absolute winner of all fitness drinks.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's one of the worst sports drinks I've ever had in my goddamn life.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would just like to thank Shiva for that lovely description of Pokari Sweat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you, Captain Obvious!
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey, you couldn't have thought of a better fucking name for it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It tastes like, it's citrusy, but it's supposed to be like Gatorade, but it doesn't taste like shit.
[SPEAKER_16]: It looks like salty water.
[SPEAKER_16]: And it tastes like it, too.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is not as salty as Gatorade.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that shit that you bought at... My Propel Water is winter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Propel Water, I like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Propel Water is absolute winter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, speaking of the Gatorade sweat thing, I mean, you know, you see them sweating out that shit, and I'm sure they're just collecting it, and there you go, that's how they get that shit, you know?
[SPEAKER_14]: I've already stated that when we open our Tapioca Express, I'm going to try to have a Pocari Sweat Vending Machine.
[SPEAKER_16]: Boba's an entirely different subject, man.
[SPEAKER_16]: I had that freaking starfruit flavor.
[SPEAKER_16]: It tasted like ass.
[SPEAKER_16]: Subtitles by the Amara.org community
[SPEAKER_03]: and Rob with the... No, no, not those.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm talking about like actual little balls.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can use them to give someone a back massage.
[SPEAKER_16]: Right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Balls!
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Propel water basically tastes like ghetto Kool-Aid shit, so it's really awesome.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, we got plenty of time.
[SPEAKER_16]: Who cares, dude?
[SPEAKER_16]: We'll talk until they throw us off.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, share with us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Before you start your story, I'm going to give you story music, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's find some story music for Mike.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's about our little Mexican friend, Jose.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now don't make this a racist story or I'm going to have to... Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk to Mike and let's hear Mike's story.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the music?
[SPEAKER_03]: The Journey to Wonderland.
[SPEAKER_02]: Word!
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, okay, as all of you know, you know the guy, Jose, who ran the Fremont tournament.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, you all know he was at the tournament on Thursday and Friday, and a couple of my friends, DCB and Chaos, come up to me and they randomly ask me, why does Jose smell like shit?
[SPEAKER_02]: And why is he wearing the same clothes as he was the day before?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm really afraid of where this is going.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've all been to Sunnyvale Golf Land, hopefully, and you've all seen the giant clown mouth.
[SPEAKER_02]: and hopefully you've all seen the picture where you all know that somebody's pissed in the clown mouth anyway you crazy Sunnyvale people so the word's going around that like JL Chiz the Mexican guy slept in the clown mouth Thursday night because he had no ride home from the tournament because it was a two day tournament so yeah that's my story
[SPEAKER_02]: It was supposed to be funny, but nobody's laughing, so I feel like an idiot now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm blinking.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're not laughing at you, we're laughing inside.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not a Pop 8, but I'm a Cool 7.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm a Soul 6.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm not going there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I'm from 2DX.
[SPEAKER_03]: We badly need a break.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, did Matt want to say something real fast?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, well, I was just going to talk about my experience of playing Samba Day, whatever that crap is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make it snappy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I was going to do it after break.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, we'll do it after break.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_03]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Join us in the chat room, any other side IRC server, such as irc.eggheads.org, and join Channel Pound.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_14]: And if you can figure that out, a winner is you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you can also visit our website at orangelounge.skie.cx, or send us an email, orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: We expect you a nice play again.
It's a very good song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you like it?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a very good song.
It's a very good song.
[SPEAKER_07]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: You tell me that I am an angel, but I know that you have envied me.
[SPEAKER_06]: You look at my torso, you look at my eyes, you look at my eyes, you look at my eyes, you look at my eyes, you look at my eyes
[SPEAKER_07]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am the cure, and when you wake up late, thinking it's a dream, the best day for you, no, you can count on me, for me, baby, this lady, you know what you found in me, is a lady, and a lady, that can give you what you need, baby, a kind lady, that will never leave you lonely, baby, this lady, finally, she found me.
[SPEAKER_11]: And now it's time for Erotic Pop Idol, where we will find the next singer for everyone's favorite perverse Bomani band, Erotic.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do it all night.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do it with me.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, that was awful.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bloody terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you take vocal lessons?
[SPEAKER_10]: Kill your teacher.
[SPEAKER_10]: In the heat of the night.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, God, I think my ears are bleeding.
[SPEAKER_10]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shut the bloody hell up, Paula.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, that was cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you even know why you're here?
[SPEAKER_10]: That was just bloody pathetic, Nyx!
Come on, Ava.
[SPEAKER_10]: Come on, do it with me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, that's it!
[SPEAKER_12]: We have a winner!
[SPEAKER_11]: A Star is Born here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, chat room demanding we make some new promos tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're sick of these ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't say I believe them.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: I would assume that we could do a few more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, we could talk about No Pants Rage and 3-Ted Evie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray for boobies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or they're suggesting maybe something involving Politary.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: How about us killing Politary in front of Corona Blender?
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see what we come up with during the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else did they say?
[SPEAKER_03]: They said something else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, they wanted us to talk about how American Idol is trying to warp our minds.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we have a segment to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, we're going to do Listless.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we're going to bring back another.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of old shit, we're going to do...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: and then we each go around and we put up our items until we have a list, in this case of 15, then each of us goes around voting to put one off, then we leave it to our chatroom to vote what the final result's going to be.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't you think I summed that up nicely?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, so on that note... Let's play Listless!
[SPEAKER_03]: That was way too easy.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was beautiful though.
[SPEAKER_14]: Speaking of lovely intelligence.
[SPEAKER_03]: So who wants to start this one?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's start with our guests.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mike, you're number... Oh, our topic tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh yes, we have a topic tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that topic is what we feel is the best 2DX video.
[SPEAKER_03]: The best videos in 2DX ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the chat room, you guys are going to get a chance to vote on our finished list.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you guys will determine the top three.
[SPEAKER_03]: So here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Starting with DDR Mike giving his number three pick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, my number three pick would be Wow Wow 70s.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, good choice, Wow Wow 70s.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number two!
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, no, no, no, you don't get to explain it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Explain it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a brief synopsis for those that may not have seen it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The song kicks ass, and... No, fuck that shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: The song just kicks ass, I'm just gonna say that.
[SPEAKER_02]: The video is really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really detailed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like how they have all the characters and shit in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unlike Colors or Frozen Wave with all that fucking gay shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, come on, Justin.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your pick.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: He needs a microphone to do it.
[SPEAKER_18]: For number three, I pick a song that I cannot say.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think that's how you say it.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a video from Second Cell, I believe, and the girl is dancing in the window.
[SPEAKER_18]: All she does through the video, dance in the window and sing the song.
[SPEAKER_18]: How cool can you get?
[SPEAKER_14]: Cool as Ice, featuring Vanilla Ice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, how about Matt?
[SPEAKER_04]: My pick would have to go to G2.
[SPEAKER_04]: G2.
[SPEAKER_04]: And briefly explain G2 a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: G2 has the creepy alien chick flying around looking like something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tran.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Tran flying around looking like she's attacking the cameraman.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very dark and goes with the song very well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shamey.
[SPEAKER_14]: My number three, um, which, uh, from my list would have to be Ride on the Light, because, uh, well, as my fianc has described it, it's basically, um, like an Eva, Evangelion fight done with little chibi thingies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: My number three pick is, uh, Right Now by Atomic Kitten, because, um,
[SPEAKER_03]: I just, I like crap, and it reminds me of Spice Girls, so there you go, right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, Rob, I'm going to be giving you an early birthday present.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: What, are you going to fart?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not a present, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a present everyone can share.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nah, there it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, it's not the Spice Girls, if you're talking about crap, it's the Shice Girls.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway, you're right.
[SPEAKER_03]: GDR Mike, let's hear the number two choice of yours.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number two for me would be 250 BPM.
[SPEAKER_02]: 250 BPM.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because of the crazy shit, baby, devil baby fucking schizo shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm about to have a seizure.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Satan fetus must die.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kill the fucking fetus.
[SPEAKER_18]: My pick is Love is Dreaminess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Love is Dreaminess.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just because running robots are that cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, my second pick would have to go to Romeo and Juliet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Romeo and Juliet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because of those crazy neon bears in the background.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're so cute.
[SPEAKER_14]: My number two would have to be for the cutest video ever, Sweet Lab.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sweet Lab.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's a good pick.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't even think of that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's so cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Briefly describe the Sweet Lab video a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just us little cute little thingies walking through the forest being cute and doing more cute things.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hardly ever get to watch the video because usually I'm cussing at the song while I'm playing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Crackers!
[SPEAKER_03]: How could you forget that?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: You weren't here when we started making our picks.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't play right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can play next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can listen, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe somebody has Cracker right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're not to the end of the list yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next, my pick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did I get your pick right now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, Sweet Lab, I did get it right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: My number two pick is a very new one, but it's fucking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Strong Yeager.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, with, with, you know, the, with Dungeon Jay humping himself.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's, wasn't that a Jaeger?
[SPEAKER_14]: Didn't you say that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so the strong Jaeger.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, Shivam's trying to take over the controls here, but he can't because we're trying to do something here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, number one picks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, my number one pick would be Cheer Train, because it has the coolest lyrics ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and it's all clay animation and shit, and, like, the stop animation is really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I like, I like Sheertrain.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so, cool, cool, cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: Good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: Go figure, that was mine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, alright, Sheertrain, number one pick for you too, alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, my all-time favorite has to be, uh, Gradius Cyber.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I made the same mistake last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has a really kick-ass animation video, very similar to Burning Heat, but it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: You always call it graduistic, and that is not right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll do what I want.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm actually changing my number one.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can't.
[SPEAKER_14]: Too bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm a woman.
[SPEAKER_14]: I can do it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have boobs.
[SPEAKER_14]: As much as I love reincarnation...
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually am going to vote for Burning Heat simply because I am such a Gradius II fan, it's not even funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that just is like, completely brings back the frustration of, you know, fighting the Fire Dragons and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, my number one pick also happens to already be on the list.
[SPEAKER_03]: I put down Love is Dreaminess as my number one pick, so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then you can stick with Reincarnation.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll, uh, I don't know, give it to a wild card.
[SPEAKER_03]: We never hear from Bradley on this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you want?
[SPEAKER_03]: You get a wild card pick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any 2DX video.
[SPEAKER_14]: Think, man, think!
[SPEAKER_01]: I like the video, but that's not my favorite.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, Outer Wall.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dude, Outer Wall.
[SPEAKER_03]: Outer Wall, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's a wild card pick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Outer Wall.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now here's the fun part!
[SPEAKER_03]: Now we're gonna go around the room and you get to take one song off of the list.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, starting with... DDR Mike.
[SPEAKER_03]: You see the list right in front of you?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can take off any one of those songs you think, why the hell is that song there?
[SPEAKER_15]: Romeo and Juliet, because fuck, fuck, fuck Para!
[SPEAKER_15]: And fuck all you Paralists out there!
[SPEAKER_15]: You fucking faggots!
[SPEAKER_15]: Fucking die, ParaParaTiger!
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm gonna fucking cut your dick off, you bitch!
[SPEAKER_14]: I encourage people to rave on Parapara.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can send those cards and letters to DDR Mike, Kara of Sunnyvale Golfland.
[SPEAKER_03]: Needless to say, Romeo and Juliet is off the list.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and a big hearty fuck you Mike from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I say bye bye to G2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye bye to G2.
[SPEAKER_04]: So long.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to have to say bye-bye to your drink because I hate the lyrics.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate the lyrics and I think the little peeps are stupid.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stand by to win.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, stand by to lose.
[SPEAKER_14]: I vote for 2.50 BPM to go bye-bye because this Satan fetus scares me.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I literally had nightmares about the damn Satan fetus when I first played Fourth Style, so no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, and I'm taking off.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate to do it, but Toto at Kazan, no, I, no, that's second style.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's too old.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it's gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's classic.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that leaves us with our list.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow Wow 70s, Ride on the Light, Right Now, How did that stay?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Love is Dreaminess, Sweet Lab, The Strong Jaeger, Graduistic Cyber,
[SPEAKER_03]: Burning Heat, and Outer Wall.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are our choices.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you would like to vote on those, you have to be in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just send me a private message with your vote.
[SPEAKER_03]: You just double-click on my name, it comes up a new window.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's SkyOL.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm there, and you can send me your vote right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I only take it through private message.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you don't send me a private message, it don't count.
[SPEAKER_03]: You said right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got a whopping three minutes to vote.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to throw on a quick song and then we'll tally up the votes and that'll be the end of the damn show.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, okay, we'll give you a request from Jamie because she's a woman and she wants to hear a woman's song.
[SPEAKER_03]: So here's Batgirls.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Hope no one discovers, I see you every day, secret hideaway, just around the way, if you're so close to me, cause, no one will ever see us, what we have to lose, our secret rendezvous.
[SPEAKER_06]: Linkin' with my baby, we can dance and make it Roll away the king, it's a fantasy, only you and me I want no one that's gone, and we're under common numbers What we have to lose, I'll see if I never forget
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, this is Melby of RTF, and for an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Melby can join us on all the fun together.
[SPEAKER_09]: But hey, if you're a broke ass like I am, why don't you come to one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, that was our special guest last week, Mel B, saying listen to our damn show.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'd like to say, because we're about at the end of the show, thank you guys very much for being here this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR Mike.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: The always, I should say, the always colorful DDR Mike.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was hoping he'd say fuck yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, and, uh, fuck yes.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, uh, big thank you also to Jazz for being here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Meow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well put.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we're not saying goodbye just yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're not saying goodbye just yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wanted to make sure we thanked you guys for being here and coming out tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys think you might be back sometime soon?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Goddamn, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let us then reveal our top three, as decided by the whole listless procedure, I don't know what the hell you want to call it, top three 2DX videos.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: In third place, drumroll please, Burning Heat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, hooray for Burning Heat, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's give them some privilege.
[SPEAKER_03]: In second place is the Strong Yeager.
[SPEAKER_03]: And in first place for the super duper bestest ever 2DX video is everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: is Love is Dreaminess!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so, there's our winners, and, uh, oh yeah, yeah, they win, and we'll give our winner song a little victory dance here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Give me a minute.
[SPEAKER_14]: Prepare your drill.
[SPEAKER_14]: Get the Lego Man out, it's time to play Love is Dreaminess.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or Love is, you know, also on crack.
[SPEAKER_03]: Love is a Hallucination
[SPEAKER_03]: We got a few minutes left.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody's trying to catch my attention in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just tell me whatever the hell you want to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll talk about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got a few more seconds here on the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm being sent a private message.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have as long as we want to have.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, let's let Matt talk there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so I finally got to play that Samba de Amigo or whatever that is.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game is weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, they want you to strike poses and shit like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got, you know, fucking Ricky Martin and the Macarena.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just a bad combo, man.
[SPEAKER_14]: You need my VMU file that has the Burning Ranger song on it and the song from Austin Powers.
[SPEAKER_14]: And yes, we get a thumbs up from that.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you know, the Oopa Oopa theme from Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_14]: You ever play Fantasy Zone?
[SPEAKER_14]: Ah, poor deprived person.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought you guys were talking about something that should be on the air.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're just about to.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm being sent one more preview song for 8th Style.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is Past Career, it's called.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's being sent to me so I can play it for you over the show in a minute.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who is the artist?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have no clue.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where is this from?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not on my list of songs in 8th Style.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you gotta tell me where the hell this is from.
[SPEAKER_03]: The person who's sending it to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Please do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where you got it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It takes a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Use both hands.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, he's saying it's the 7th style theme.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why does it say 8th style?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's supposedly the 7th style theme.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's by DJ Past.
[SPEAKER_14]: What about DJ Present and DJ Future?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm getting angry faces for berating him over the radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dude, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: We still love you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: This could be...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll just play this, I don't know what the hell it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, Pantless Rage.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's going to be a little moment while we go ahead and get that up for everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: This could be a whole load of crap for all I know, so we're about ready to find out.
[SPEAKER_03]: This could just be, this could be porno noises.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pantless Rage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, this is a 7th style theme.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know this song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I've heard this before.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dude, very cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is playable on 8th style.
[SPEAKER_14]: On 8er style.
[SPEAKER_14]: Aired.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, you know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I can imagine this would be really difficult.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tomorrow Perfume was the theme of 2DX 6th style, and now it's in 7th style.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but we're talking about 2DX, not Beatmania, not Five Finger Gayness.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still am of the opinion that
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe that should be our clip of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you SoCalKicks for sending me that file because if I don't say his name he'll cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, I'm sorry, what?
[SPEAKER_14]: He was talking about five fingering.
[SPEAKER_14]: I still have you beat.
[SPEAKER_14]: I talked about the king of iron fingering.
[SPEAKER_03]: On that note, we are going to close out the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you to everybody for listening.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you to all the guests for being here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does anybody have any last minute thoughts?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, if you're listening out there, you're like the coolest gay person I've ever met.
[SPEAKER_15]: So are you!
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_15]: And, okay, half the community is gay, so it don't matter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nakari's cool and all, but, you know, share the love, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck it, I hate everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you the gay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Watch the movie Science, it's like the best movie I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's awesome, go see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't read about it, just go see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Watch the Powerpuff movie, it's better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for putting up with this train wreck all night long.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any last thoughts from Jamie?
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, you get the final word.
[SPEAKER_14]: I told you, my head's empty.
[SPEAKER_14]: I drank it all out last night.
[SPEAKER_11]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_11]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Jamie Summers, also known as DarkSakura, and Rob Roberts, also known as Sky.
[SPEAKER_11]: And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_12]: Goodbye, kids.
[SPEAKER_12]: Today's show was brought to you by the letter, um, bong.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the number...
[SPEAKER_12]: God, you're messed up.
[SPEAKER_12]: F*** you.
[SPEAKER_12]: The number, f*** you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye-bye, kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.