[SPEAKER_04]: All right, boys and girls, we're back here for the Orange Lounge Radio Afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's that part of the show that's too hot to podcast, only available when you listen live here on OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: What should we get into first?
[SPEAKER_04]: How about a little bit of how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat room, go ahead and send me your FUs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send them over private message.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have neglected them for the past two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's high time we got to read some for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: So go ahead and private message me your FUs, and we'll read them tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the meantime, let's do a little bit of how was your week, how was your day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you want to start us off?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, my week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I finally got my bonus money to which I purchased my laptop.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got this Gateway, it's an MX7525.
[SPEAKER_01]: and mobile Athlon 64 bit 4000 plus.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's got, well, had one gig of RAM in it, now has a gig and a half because that's all that the motherboard will allow.
[SPEAKER_01]: 100 gig hard drive, which is all the motherboard will allow because I think it's a bit older.
[SPEAKER_01]: Windows Media Center Edition and an ATI Mobility X600 card with 128 megabytes of RAM dedicated and 128 that shares from the main RAM.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, literally pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_01]: My lap is really warm.
[SPEAKER_01]: I need to really get one of those cool mats for this.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's a pretty slick computer.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's got some interesting stuff on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: The only thing I don't like about it, one, it's gateway.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't really dig the cow computers too much.
[SPEAKER_01]: But this was an open box computer, so I got it for $300 less than it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so it wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: And also, it's going to be great for video editing.
[SPEAKER_01]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spike, thank you for filling in tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was my pleasure.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's always a good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to take you away from festivities in the living room for a little while to do our crappy little show, but we appreciate your contributions.
[SPEAKER_04]: And by the way, cosplay at Fanime, per our conversation at IHOP earlier, is going to rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have the best idea ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: This will be a legendary cosplay, that's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: It took everything in my power not to bring it up during the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to wow you all with my elite cosplay skills.
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_03]: My week was really great, except that I hate having to earn money to make my life happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, that whole, like, earning money things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jobs are so overrated.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, man, but, uh, no, my day and my weekend, which I've, you know, spent in your apartment has been awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm glad you had a good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: My apartment's a fun time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not as fun as my bedroom, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jokes!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, cosplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to be a duck.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nah, now you just jumped the shark.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nah, nah, nah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else, Spike?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: I spent my whole week with my free time playing Kingdom Hearts and Final Fantasy XI, which I was hoping was XII.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it didn't work out that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to come back to Final Fantasy XI this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I took a week break because I needed to give Miklatov some time to catch up to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you really want to play Final Fantasy XI with us, you can always send me a private message on the forums.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't send it to me in chat because I'll miss it tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Best way is to send me an email or private message and we'll get you.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to play me on Xbox Live sometime, just know this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because some more people have been adding me to Xbox Live lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just because I do a podcast on video games with my friends does not necessarily mean I am very good at gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: It means I love gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like to play games.
[SPEAKER_04]: That doesn't mean I'm good at them.
[SPEAKER_04]: So chances are you will kick my ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: So please don't expect that I will actually be a challenge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chances are I will be like playing a 10-year-old.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was a one hell of a challenge at full auto.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unfortunately, I sold the game back because I got all my achievement points.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn you.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if I were to borrow it again, I would be one hell of a match.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was just one of those games, you know, online wasn't that great.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was laggy and really glitchy at times.
[SPEAKER_01]: So maybe Full Auto 2 when that comes out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because that game fucking, oh, I love that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Needs deathmatch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Needs a deathmatch like Twisted Metal because I think that's the only thing that was missing from that game is Twisted Metal style deathmatch.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really have a whole lot to say outside of the gaming stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: The casino was fun, I guess, this weekend, even though I lost money.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was good to just kind of go with friends and hang out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Watched some movies Friday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Watched Mr. and Mrs. Smith, which I hadn't seen yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: That movie was funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just made a wincing noise over there, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: You didn't like it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a fun movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you watch E?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: The brother was pretty good looking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Her brother.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, her ex, Billy Bob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, no, thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This conversation is going... I also watched a really old movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not really old.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's from a few years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was an Academy Award.
[SPEAKER_04]: I watched In the Bedroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: This has nothing to do with gaming whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what you get when you turn into the afterbirth is you get to hear our stupid stories from the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wouldn't it have been great if they made a game based on the movie?
[SPEAKER_04]: In the bedroom, the game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that's the stupidest idea I've ever heard.
[SPEAKER_03]: As stupid as the guy game?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the second stupidest idea I've ever heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever played Chuck Rock?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
Rats.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever played...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to think of the worst 8-bit games I've ever played.
[SPEAKER_04]: Master Chu and the Drunk Nerd Who.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever played that game?
What a what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why would you make me remember that?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're so hardcore for remembering a Color Dreams game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That makes me love you even more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember Color Dreams, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Color Dreams?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're so not cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's because you're a kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not a kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just teasing you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you should see, oh my god, we're just lit up with FUs tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, like, they're just, and I bet you half of these are gonna say, FU to Sky for cutting out the FUs for the past couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: We've just been busy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Deal with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get into tonight's FUs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I'm queuing up some music we can listen to for the FUs.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, we'll use some of our old theme songs here.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we get into chatroom FUs.
[SPEAKER_04]: FU!
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Knight would like to say F you to a six day work week coming up for me and F you to time changes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fever Maniac 64 says F you to fever as soon as I sit up or stand up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Headache.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to Loki for complaining about his crotch being on fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: One word for you, pillow.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to you guys for maybe confusing what I said about the mouse port.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm charging off the port you plug a mouse into on your computer.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to myself for being so unwise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Staying up to 12 a.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: with a fever is not good.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're right, sir, it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Laser123452331 says, F you to you, Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's my era good cool fat mix MP3?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, I forgot to send that in my bed.
[SPEAKER_04]: GK128 says, F you to Microsoft for teasing me with Xbox Live Gold.
[SPEAKER_04]: Such a short time for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now you ask me to pay $50.
[SPEAKER_04]: You win, Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fireboma says, F you to my former choir teacher being accused of six counts of child endangerment.
[SPEAKER_04]: I always wondered why the whiteboard was blocking the window on the door of the classroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yikes Raven's Dolphin says Microsoft making prettier games gets his FU Xbox to Xbox 360 making it prettier for more money FU Microsoft There was a sentence in there somewhere Jazz says FU to Final Fantasy XI I've been camping a monster for a fucking week against guild sellers and he still won't give me his goddamn gloves Squeenix fucking hates me Welcome to Final Fantasy XI
[SPEAKER_04]: Summer Camp, DarkTetsuya says, F you to Beatmania Songlist.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could barely scrape together an outphase expert course, let alone a Taku or Taka themed one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and F you to the mode that's depicted in the attract mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Konami says, it's not actually in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Way to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spirit Snare says, F you to Apple for releasing Boot Camp, which has now really wanted me to make me purchase a Mac.
[SPEAKER_04]: VxJasonXV says, F you to Cox for sucking something of the same name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ranma says, F you to my TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: My TV turns black and white after a few minutes and it sucks to play games and watch TV on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need a new TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Roz says, F you to illnesses.
[SPEAKER_04]: I started off just getting headaches.
[SPEAKER_04]: It developed into a 103 degree freaking fever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I somehow screwed up my back and couldn't walk for four damn days which drove me insane because I can't hold still.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fortunately, I still had Advance Wars, although when you're about to pass out, you will probably not be on top of your game in Tactical Warfare.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of Advance Crack, F you to Uzyum because it's so incredibly lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xander C says, F you to Latin.
[SPEAKER_04]: It still isn't done.
[SPEAKER_04]: People still have to learn Latin?
[SPEAKER_04]: That makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn, Romans.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to Kingdom Hearts 2, says Xander C. Sure, it rocks, but now I suck even worse at Guitaruman.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to my friend for not bringing back my Guitar Hero game.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to not having any ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shame, shame.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you mean the song in DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to not being a duck.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to the big face that chases me down in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too much ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Legend of Zaku says F you to not being able to use up all my meals for the week due to Easter vacation.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to my school for not acting fast enough to get rid of a mouse that was terrorizing my apartment since we had to corner it and scoop him up in a box and release him outside.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to my sneakers since they are on their last breaths leaking water into my feet.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ PooEater would like to say F you to the guy who cut me off this morning, making me spill my chocolatey ice cream treat onto my lap.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you, guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn you to hell.
[SPEAKER_04]: I miss my chocolatey treat.
[SPEAKER_04]: My pants are wet.
[SPEAKER_04]: My lap is cold.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you, guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: GS191 says F you to myself for sucking at Beatmania F you to the postal service for losing my Gamefly mail F you to the MacBook Pro for not having a delete key I have to log into a domain and can't do a control alt delete to log in By the way, I'm not buying a MacBook Pro until they fix this And F you to work for making me work stupid long hours Fuck working in retail
[SPEAKER_04]: Illusion says, F you to people that hate Bucky O'Hare for NES.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100Matt says, F you to my boss for trying to get me to work on Thursday, which is a Jewish holiday that I requested a month ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to totally unrelated Skype calls killing everyone else's time that has something related to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: And F you to Nintendo for not throwing people a curveball and not naming the revolution the dolphin.
[SPEAKER_04]: and lastly, Agent 47 says F you to EA because they're evil and F you to the guy that directed House of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go, chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got your F yous.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aren't you happy?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: The chat room is always there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know there's a few people like Dark Knight and Dark Tetsuya and Misty and some of them that check in during the day and will say hi to you if they see you there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, there's also spinoff shows that we do here on this network.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tuesday nights, pump up the volume.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura brings you her request show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I imagine she will be back, assuming she's over her sickness.
[SPEAKER_04]: She'll be back this Tuesday at 7 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the Rob Roberts show is on Wednesday at 7 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, that's me.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't forget the wiki quote.
[SPEAKER_04]: Matt's wiki quote is currently being queued for deletion.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you wiki heads want to do anything about that, that would be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody suggested merging it into an Orange Lounge Radio article, which I think is a great idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because then somebody could also quote the line from tonight, Resident Evil 4, bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Would be a great quote from tonight and other things.
[SPEAKER_04]: So save the wiki quote, those of you wiki heads that know how to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if it gets deleted, we're not going to cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not the end of the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Matt would probably rather see it go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm assuming.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you have something you wanted to add, Loki, before we get into Cage Match?
[SPEAKER_01]: Reading, they have some more info about Red Steel, that game we were talking about in Part A. They're actually talking about some of the stuff that's done with the controller anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is also from the Game Informer article.
[SPEAKER_01]: The development of the game started just right after E3 2005, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: The first, like, third game, they said you have to be extremely brutal in killing people.
[SPEAKER_01]: What else was kind of cool?
[SPEAKER_01]: They're going to have multiplayer online and split screen and a bunch of different unique multiplayer modes.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It says it doesn't feel like a light game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it says AI is intelligent, will cover while you're attacking and attack while you're reloading.
[SPEAKER_01]: and it says the AI is based on benchmarks set by FEAR or the game FEAR looks pretty sweet alright oh and one thing I thought was interesting they're going to have some different like I guess interactive parts where you'll be talking to people and you can are given like yes no answers and you can nod your head using the rev mode for yes or no that's kind of neat
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else really quickly before we get into tonight's cage match?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, then let's do the cage match, shall we?
[SPEAKER_04]: I just passed this song on Beatmania the other day, finally.
[SPEAKER_04]: Got my way back.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I'm getting my skill back at Beatmania, finally.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually passed a couple of others, even though they were the low-end 4s and 6s.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I passed some 7 stars, and I'm working on the 8s.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I used to be able to pass Colors.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nemesis.
[SPEAKER_04]: I passed Nemesis once.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's probably the hardest song I've ever passed.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm starting to get my Beatmania skills back.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I ordered 9th Style, because there was a website having a sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm not going to give them a free plug, but they were selling it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to know, send me a private message, because they're selling it for only $40, which I thought was a good deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get into Cage Match tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number one is a holdover.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was DarkSakura's winner for the last two weeks in a row.
[SPEAKER_04]: Will it win again tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys have the final say.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to be in our chat room to play along.
[SPEAKER_04]: OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number one tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's only a clip because you heard it last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Babyland.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some great indie rock here with Gary is the song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, song number one in tonight's cage match, Babyland with Gary.
[SPEAKER_04]: Will it win again tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's up to you after you hear these other two songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number two comes to us from Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what did you pick tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Your mic's not on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I picked this song off of this album called Who Am I?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's by, I want to say...
[SPEAKER_01]: Ken O, X-Noise, Diffusion
Time, Space
DarkSakura, DarkSakura
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that was song number two in tonight's Cage Match X-Noise with Diffusion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around and see what everybody in the room thought of that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_04]: Turn your mic on, buddy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a longer version than I normally listen to, so that one was off of kind of a mix.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, nine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Spike!
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was a pretty good song.
[SPEAKER_03]: And grade it on a scale of 1 to 10.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, on a scale of 1 to 10, probably an 8.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, super.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, Extifer, hi!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would you give that song?
[SPEAKER_00]: I would give it a damn 8.
[SPEAKER_00]: An 8.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any reason why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely no reason whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nelly, what would you give your fiancé's song there that he put in the cage, Matt?
[SPEAKER_02]: I wasn't listening, but I'll give it a 10 because I love him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aw, she's putting porn on my laptop, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I noticed that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you such a... Nelly, why are you just... She really is putting porn on your laptop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nelly, why are you... Oh my, that's a... Why are you putting that on his laptop?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because look how disgusting, that'd be so funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, if he shows it to somebody and he doesn't know it's there, like, I shouldn't even show him that I'm putting it on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: They know it's there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you endorse your fiancé looking at porn?
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to song number three.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number three is my pick tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the goth in me that's making me put in this song, or the EBM master.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I like this band.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've been around forever, but I've just started really liking them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is their new single.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Chrome, and the band is VNV Nation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that was song number three in tonight's cage match, BNV Nation with Chrome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's have a look and see what the folks in the studio thought of that one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seven, I was a bit distracted by my fiancé trying to put four in my laptop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aren't we all?
[SPEAKER_03]: Spike.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd have to give that one probably a 9.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm a big fan of VNV.
[SPEAKER_03]: I used to spin them at clubs years back, following them for a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really like those guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spike, do you have any live shows coming up you want to plug?
[SPEAKER_04]: I should have given you another opportunity on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have something coming up, but I don't want to talk about it until it's a good deal, but probably in late May I'll be doing a few clubs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come back to the show and give it a plug.
[SPEAKER_04]: Throw in something gaming related for us.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'd probably close the night with one of the Xanadu mixes from DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're so badass.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, well, the thing is, one of the shows would be at a gay club.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Xanadu, bam.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think I will associate Cunt with that song because I saw it on Loki's computer.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that deserves a pretty much a 9.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm glad to hear it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nelly, what did you think of VNV Nation with Chrome?
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, wasn't listening, so I'll give it a 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I give that song like a 9 because I like VMV Nation.
[SPEAKER_04]: That song makes me want to dance like I'm in Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the people do at the club.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like if you've ever been to the golf club, they dance like they're in Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're like... The sirens are going off.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, place vote now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's review the three songs you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number one, Babyland, Gary.
[SPEAKER_04]: Babyland.
[SPEAKER_04]: And song number two you can vote for tonight, X-Noise with Diffusion.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a bad clip.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's try that again.
[SPEAKER_04]: X-Noise with Diffusion.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't find a good clip for this song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get the beat.
[SPEAKER_04]: And song number three you can vote for tonight is VNV Nation with Chrome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lace vote now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote for song number one, song number two, or song number three.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys have about 60 seconds to do it because we're about ready to pull the plug on this show because if you can believe it, we've been on air for three and a half hours straight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need air.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to go outside.
[SPEAKER_04]: Extifer, you came into the studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure you wanted to ruin the show somehow.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you want to say?
[SPEAKER_00]: I didn't have anything.
[SPEAKER_00]: I bought Harry Potter in Russian today.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why?
[SPEAKER_00]: Because it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you watch it yet?
[SPEAKER_00]: I watched some of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, for those that don't know, you're learning Russian.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, some folks figured this out because I posted a picture of the TV on our forums over at OrangeSoundsRadio.com because I was showing my Xbox 360 with a Mario Kart background.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can actually see the little tag on the TV that says the word television in Russian.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's because you have scattered the apartment with index cards.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're only supposed to be there a week, if I remember right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can take them off now.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know them now.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you say television in Russian?
[SPEAKER_00]: So he's learning.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like lesbians.
[SPEAKER_00]: I told ya!
[SPEAKER_00]: Boy, God, you really lucked out, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_00]: Nelly's the funniest person in the world, and the reason why is because earlier we watched the Silent Hill making of little thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: I already told this story during the show.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can do it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can tell your way if you want.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, she's just funny.
[SPEAKER_00]: She's just like, pussy scared of paper.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's so funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys are so easily amused.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: People should go to Nelly's MySpace, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nelly has the best MySpace I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't even have Orange Launch Radio friended, though, do you?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but I will today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then how can they find Nelly on Myspace?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your username?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nelly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it just Nelly?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's not going to bring up the rapper?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it will bring up the rapper.
[SPEAKER_01]: What you got to do, it's kind of like the six degrees of Orange Lounge or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go to Orange Lounge, go to Rob's page.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, because she's not in my top eight right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: She's in my top eight.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's in Extover's top eight, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so go to Orange Lounge and Extover's in the top eight and then Nelly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And your picture isn't really of you, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's of you throwing babies, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, you gave it away!
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, it's a picture of my favorite sport, which is baby throwing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's hilarious, and nobody at my work thought it was funny because of bastards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, Nellie has the best MySpace page I've ever seen, and you'll know why when you go there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So go to the Orange Launch Radio MySpace, then hop over to Xtapers, and then make sure your sound's up, and hop over to Nellie's.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I helped.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to count up cage match votes now, so somebody's got to fill time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Matt, help us fill time here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, think of a story that we haven't talked about yet tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to say, there's another grant that's out of Liberty City Stories, PSP cheat device update, and they added now where you can just the water levels, so you can flood cities and stuff and drive around the boat, which is kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, and I'm surprised they should really put out tools like that because it is, you know, it adds more replayability to the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I hope that they take, you know, a lesson from, you know, the users' requests on, like, you know, more customization for the multiplayer games and stuff like that because it really needs it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Other than that, I was going to say I hope I get my Game Informer soon because everyone gets theirs before me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't got my new issue of Xbox Magazine.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's already in newsstands.
[SPEAKER_01]: What the hell is the point of subscribing to a magazine then if I'm getting it late?
[SPEAKER_04]: What are the demos on the new Xbox Magazine?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it worth me buying?
[SPEAKER_01]: The new Xbox Magazine is going to have a 360 demo on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was something good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to say the 360 version of...
[SPEAKER_01]: Hitman, Blood Money.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to say it's on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't be positive, but I thought that's what it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do know it has Hitman on there as a demo.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not sure if it's current gen or next gen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, God, what else was on there?
[SPEAKER_01]: Just some really good demos.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to say Hitman was on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't remember, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: I looked at it for like half a second.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Game Informer is always good.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're always near the one.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really weird because their website...
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of the news is really sketchy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some of it's accurate, most of it's not.
[SPEAKER_01]: But in their magazine, it's pretty accurate.
[SPEAKER_01]: It seems to be like they have a lot of exclusives and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's such a separation between the website and the actual magazine.
[SPEAKER_04]: You ready to hear who won tonight's cage match?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a landslide vote tonight, and although all three songs got a pretty fair amount of votes, we had a lot of participation tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for exercising your democratic right to vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will shove this microphone up your pee hole.
[SPEAKER_04]: The song, the winning song tonight is X-Noise with Diffusion.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, it was either this or a song that was by Rammstein.
[SPEAKER_01]: It sounded like it should be in Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_04]: And SSJ100Matt would like to remind you, P. Diddy says vote or die.
[SPEAKER_04]: Vote or die.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though I don't think P. Diddy voted in some of the earlier elections.
[SPEAKER_04]: But hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Diddy now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Diddy what?
[SPEAKER_00]: Diddy what?
[SPEAKER_00]: Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just Diddy?
[SPEAKER_00]: He lost the P?
[SPEAKER_01]: A fucking artist.
[SPEAKER_00]: Someone knocked the P out of him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stick with a name.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just pick a name and stick with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, it's like, you know, they're not like, you know, different clothes or whatever, or Pokemon cards or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Extover, your audio is so jacked up tonight because I had to turn it up for Spike, and now that you've got it, you're like... Yeah, that's exactly what you sound like.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cranbor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just take the mic away a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody needs me!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hobobot or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Winobot.
[SPEAKER_01]: I learn new things about porn every day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cunts really do look like flowers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here it is kids, your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tiki Tiki Tiki Tiki Tiki Tiki
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: And there it is, the Kotimu version of V. Always a good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're now going to cut off the stream and take you back to Bomani and video game music and much more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys, of course, as always, for supporting Independent Radio and Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We love you guys so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, get better soon if you're listening, and take care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a great week.