and many more.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Mention the fact that you nearly fell off the chair.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how I almost fell into the wall.
[SPEAKER_01]: An extra person here talking about using it as a battery for your vibrator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about Wondershowsin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, let's talk about Wondershowsin.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just took over the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wondershowsin is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you Wondershowsin?
[SPEAKER_04]: Then you're so awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like a hot dog.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think you're cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, not as cool as Wondershoes, which is your fairly hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am moderately hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: So anyway... Hey everybody, I just took over the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think everybody should tell me how cool I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: You start.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to do this again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the kid that was dressed up like Hitler.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trevor is the best beat kid on that show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for returning, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the kid about pills, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's my favorite.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pills!
[SPEAKER_00]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the power brick should be bigger than the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: It should be like a 360 or an Xbox that you just slap to the back of the PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: That should be a nuclear generator.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like the power packs in Ghostbusters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Power bricks made out of solid metal.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just gets super hot and you can cook eggs on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mmm, eggs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mmm, eggy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, is this thing on?
[SPEAKER_05]: Testing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Testing 1-2.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm looking in the index, but I don't see anything for how to run a radio show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't understand this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Does this thing work?
[SPEAKER_00]: This thing reads like stereo instructions.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is this on?
[SPEAKER_00]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio, Broke Down Ghetto Bomani Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's one of our old promos.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gotta love that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, RetroOLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: I missed the beep.
[SPEAKER_03]: The beep was from R10K.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, for reals.
[SPEAKER_05]: We gotta get through this or I swear to God we'll be here all night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that was QQQ.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody, shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's my time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki has this look at, you're gonna fuck up.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're gonna fuck up.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I fucked up.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wasn't doing anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: You were giving me that look.
[SPEAKER_05]: You were like, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not doing anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: You willed it to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just watching him talk.
[SPEAKER_06]: I swear to God I quit.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Woo-hoo, we have DarkSakura Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, no, we don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was not even looking at you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuckin' A. I'm turning around.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm turning around.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do we have you on this program anyway?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, this is you talking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right at you.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's like, how am I not supposed to laugh at that?
[SPEAKER_03]: For the sake of the chat room, I was leaning over my laptop, staring at Rob intently.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to be a duck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, okay, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is not a drunk show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop filming.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to turn around and not look at you people so I can get through this segment.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Loki, be ready with a Tomb Raider story and no more giggling.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we have a Tomb Raider story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Know how Bobby Black by himself.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm starting to wonder if that's not a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm pushing your head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we're back here with the Orange Launch Radio Afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's that portion of the show that's too hot to podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's sticky.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's perverted.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have the cage match coming up, which is pretty much going to be just about all we do tonight because we're already at 9 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was an awfully long show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe if you would quit laughing so much during the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not the show itself.
[SPEAKER_05]: When it comes out on the stream, don't stop it.
[SPEAKER_05]: When it comes out on the podcast stream, it won't be very long, but it was like 20 minutes of giggle fits.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I recorded it on my fancy video camera.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, what is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are we going to do a video cast then?
[SPEAKER_00]: Is that the next step?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have to, but this is mainly for E3.
[SPEAKER_00]: Get me a burka then.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because as we know, we were talking about what we're doing, our plans for E3, special plans that no one's doing yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's mainly what it's for, so I can walk through the entire booth and cover everything and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love that video camera.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only problem is the still pictures it takes aren't 100% good.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're like 640x480, not really even a 1 megapixel.
[SPEAKER_06]: But when I figured I'm cropping down most of the pictures anyways, I don't think it really matters.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it'll be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: In random news, it's Bomani related, Sephiroth1215 sent me a private message in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope you don't mind me sharing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he sent me a link over to Konami's website here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Konami has a page here for DDR Supernova.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it says, release date, available now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think there's a webmaster at Konami that's about to get fired.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why don't you email somebody about that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why would I email anybody about that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can't you fix that?
[SPEAKER_05]: You work for him?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can't you fire somebody?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I sent you a link to my Flash thingy and you never said anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: When?
[SPEAKER_03]: I sent you an IM a few days ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was I at work?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's because he's rude.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I leave my IM up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to pull it up and I'm going to show you on my laptop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know you need to friend me now once you get a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once I get a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't even have to get a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Buy some of those Xbox Live arcade games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll probably get Geometry Wars.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't you download the ghost recon thing or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, I'm busy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talk to me later.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to do a little bit of how was your week, how was your day, but I don't think I really care about these people anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, let's get into tonight's cage match, shall we?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, what were you talking about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Now I'm not busy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to put that on my resume and I want you to have people hire me.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cache Match!
[SPEAKER_03]: I vote for Holic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm gonna get busted.
[SPEAKER_05]: Three songs, do battle.
[SPEAKER_05]: and now I have the giggles again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Three songs do battle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Each host picks their favorite song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Three hosts pick their favorite song.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do battle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your guys' votes in the chat room determine the winner.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it goes into rotation all week long here on Orange Lounge Radio's Bomani and Video Game Music program.
[SPEAKER_05]: Started off with song number one, which won the Cage Match last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was Babyland.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, Babyland, who I'm going to see on April 15th in Berkeley.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Babyland had this song called Gary?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that how you say it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Gary?
[SPEAKER_05]: Gary, Gary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well it won last week's Cage Match with its funky indie sound.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I said it sounded like the Postal Service on crack or something, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of their stuff is more industrial sounding, but this I thought was very synth poppy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number one, Babyland.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, song number two in tonight's cage match is coming up.
[SPEAKER_05]: That, once again, was song number one, Babyland, with Jerry.
[SPEAKER_05]: And song number two is going to be a challenger, and it's my pick.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's a band called Goldfrap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I think Goldfrap is just the name of the girl.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know she's got a lot of people helping her out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Goldfrap has a song from her new CD, Supernature is the CD.
[SPEAKER_05]: The song is called Ooh La La.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I like this song.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of pornotastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's my pick tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh La La by Goldfrap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: See if I care.
Ooh La La
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to touch you, you're just made for love
Thanks for watching!
That was it, that was uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number two there in the cage match, Ooh La La by GoldFrap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love that ending, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you know what, that was part of a song I'm not supposed to be playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoops!
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, what did you guys think of Ooh La La by GoldFrap?
[SPEAKER_04]: Miklatov, she needs to quit smoking, one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what did you think of Oolala by GoldPrap?
[SPEAKER_06]: I recognized... I don't know, it was okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's good stripper music, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: It should be called GoldFap.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it would be like 7.5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, how would you rate the bathroom?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or wherever you just were.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could hear the music from the bathroom, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you like?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was poopy.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually liked what I heard of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a little repetitive, but it gets an 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is totally fucking music.
[SPEAKER_05]: I give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh shit, I forgot kids listen to this show, my bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, song number three tonight comes from Cheater Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cheater, Cheater, Cheater Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, listen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do not support Cheater Loki tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Listen, I did the same thing when Kingdom Hearts 1 came out, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: So obviously my choice is going to be Utada Hikaru with Passion, because that is a team song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here's song number three from Cheating Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Utada Hikaru with Passion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, song number three tonight, Utada Hikaru with Passion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go around and see what everybody thought of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who started us off last time?
[SPEAKER_05]: Miklatov.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was long and had bad camera angles.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love the guitar.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the only thing I remember of it each time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yet you used the version without the guitar bridge in the middle, like in the opening video.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I was pressed for time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I had a feeling.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a hunch.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gave it a 9.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really like this song, although as far as I thought that Hikaru was better as far as an opening song.
[SPEAKER_03]: This...
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I really like the song, it's a problem, but I just don't like things about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it gets a 7.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the opening song to Kingdom Hearts 2 should have been Easy Breezy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I think that would have been much better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on, you could have like Sora skipping down.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not as dramatic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, no, I...
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that song a lot, but it's already in rotation, so I give it a five.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, don't get me wrong, I love that song, but Loki sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's recap the three songs you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Babyland with Jerry, song number one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, and song number two you can vote for tonight is Gold Frap with Ooh La La is the name of that song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, and song number three you can vote for tonight is from Loki, and it's Utada Hikaru with Passion.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't listening.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura has a memory like an elephant.
[SPEAKER_05]: She don't forget.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a slightly different version.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't forget.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the one we have in rotation does have the guitar riff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's the one from the movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the short one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sigh.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, dude, I'm going to hit FoodManiac64 with a trout now for being a butt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because he told everyone not to vote for my song so they'd play his.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I haven't guaranteed that I'll play his song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I told people I'd play their songs like three months ago, and I still haven't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just keep dangling out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: He emailed me four times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell him to stop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Block him.
Ah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, since I need some time here to tabulate votes, I need filler, so we're gonna go around and do How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_03]: Shitty!
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, poopy.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, my week was actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got more stuff to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, my whole crappy work situation has improved to such a degree that I no longer feel like I'm going to kill people and then myself in a big emo fit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead, I just feel like, you know, I'm going to mildly maim people and, you know, not, like, actually kill them, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm no longer disgruntled.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm slightly annoyed, but not disgruntled.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've also been playing a lot of Ragnarok online.
[SPEAKER_03]: As of today, my primary character is 5441.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still have to get job 50 before I can go assassin.
[SPEAKER_03]: I donated some money to their server, so I got a bunch of free stuff for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a kiddie band now, and it makes me a very happy bunny.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a kitty band.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need to see pictures.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will send you pictures.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I got a bunch of cards too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a thief bug card and no footwear that I can put it on.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now I need a zombie card.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because zombies are awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like a hot dog.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_06]: My weekend day was okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got to move my desk tomorrow because we do this thing every once in a while once we fire a bunch of people where we do the floor layout shuffle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, for no apparent reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll move people one desk over just...
[SPEAKER_06]: for the hell of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, so I gotta move my desk.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I get my review next week, which should be interesting because my phone time sucks, but I'm the smartest one there.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, it kind of evens out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're supposed to be getting our bonuses.
[SPEAKER_06]: My co-worker taught me this really cool thing with our bonus because they take out twice the amount of taxes as they normally would on your bonus checks.
[SPEAKER_06]: So where I potentially could get $2,000, I only get like $1,100 or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what you do is you put out another W4 or whatever for...
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, exempt for that week, so I get my full $2,000, which is going to a laptop.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, um... What else?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, I got my spiffy camera, which you'll hopefully see some more content for the PSP site.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what the, uh... One of the main reasons was for that, so I can record some of my stuff at, you know... Well, I'm probably going to record stuff at my bachelor party, because...
[SPEAKER_06]: What happens at Bachelor Party stays at Bachelor Party.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also... Do you know what they have planned for your Bachelor Party?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do, but that's all I can say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, the other thing is just your recording wedding stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just it's really fun to play with that camera because it has a 20 gig hard drive in there so you can store tons of video.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lots of video coming from E3, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: So look forward to that and lots of pictures.
[SPEAKER_06]: And...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I think that's about all I have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mikotov, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_04]: My week was boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: Work is boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sick of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then today, slash last night, got myself hyped up to go to Best Buy and wait in a non-existent line at 3 in the morning.
[SPEAKER_04]: That didn't go so well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Best Buy sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then tomorrow, somebody new that we hired is going to be sitting in my office and I'm not looking forward to that because I hate new people and I will not talk to them.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're not a team player.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't need to be a team player.
[SPEAKER_04]: They invaded my space.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can go away.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, uh, I, um... Oh, we started playing Tetris DS at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's over already.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because a lot of people suck and whine too much like me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Back to Apples and Apples.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apples to Apples is occasionally played.
[SPEAKER_04]: We recently discovered the joy of Team Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_04]: at break.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's really fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Team Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and reverses.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you're setting up the options like 150 and computer difficulty if you have computers and all that, there's an option for team.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so you can actually do a four-on-four team.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's pretty much like a regular race, except you have a color icon, like red or blue, and you can still attack your own teammates, but how it works is it's an overall point total for your team.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're no longer working just to be the best.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're working as a team.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: We started out last week when the losers were still playing Tetris, me and the person in my room, or in my office.
[SPEAKER_04]: We played it with computers and he got screwed over twice with really bad computer players, but it's really fun actually, and I didn't even think Mario Kart could be more fun than it already was.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: So now we're playing without power-ups because, you know, they got pissed off at that because I won the rankings this month.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this next month now, we're just trying to... I want to do team games, but the problem is we don't get enough people to participate.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can only do six, and some people are gone or busy and stuff, and that kind of makes it unfair.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, I don't know, we're looking forward to, like, maybe Liberty City Stories when it comes out on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully we'll have multiplayer, and then we can land together some PS2s and play it that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Might be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: That could be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob, how was your weekend?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Besides the whole male PMS thing, I was fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a fine week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to the gym today and my trainer pretty much told me officially today that I'm fat, which was good to hear.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I was referring to.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I had to take the little machine that measures your body fat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you hold it in your hands like away from your body.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it did the little boop, boop, boop thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: The BMI scale.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, and then I turned it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, and he looked at the number and then he turned it around and said.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, you're right here in the high one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, thanks.
[SPEAKER_05]: But oh well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I already knew that was coming anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the whole reason I signed up for the gym.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I just have to make sure I go regularly.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty cool that you have a trainer, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be the only thing I'd be able to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I only get them one more time for free.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then I'd have to pay for them if I want to keep them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, if you come to my gym with me, I'll work out with you and show you what to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not that I don't know what to do, I just, you know, I need the motivation is a huge thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Put a cupcake in front of you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I promise you, next Monday, nothing will stand in between us going to spin.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Word.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, they do spin at this gym, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you have to go to my trainer's spin.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's vicious.
[SPEAKER_05]: I asked my trainer if you could come to this club, and he said with a guest pass you can.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you'll have to come to one of our classes sometime, see if you enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bring me a guest pass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're on.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we'll pick a class to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: And in the summer we can go swimming.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can do yoga or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got all the stuff to do lap swimming.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're outdoors, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was indoors when I signed up.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the ones I have a membership for over here has a lap pool outside.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the snooty one, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to do the indoor pool somewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: Roseville.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to Roseville.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Roseville has three indoor pools.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shall we announce who won tonight's cage match?
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be a good way to get close to the end here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: The winning song of tonight's cage match was...
[SPEAKER_05]: A tie!
[SPEAKER_05]: And here are the two songs... Okay, you know how ties work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's song number one that tied.
[SPEAKER_05]: Baby Man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's song number two that tied.
[SPEAKER_05]: Passion, Utada Hikaru.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in the old Orange Lounge Radio rulebook... I wonder where this is going.
[SPEAKER_05]: That means that when two songs tie, the host who got screwed over... Oh, that's me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gets to break the tie...
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, see, I could be ironic and vote for your pick, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Jamie could hate me all night.
[SPEAKER_05]: That might be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, no, I can't do that because, you know, you totally picked a song that was already in rotation, so I think you both end up winning anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I am picking for Jamie's song, I'm picking Jamie's song, Babyland, because I like the fact that they sound like Postal Service on track.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, so two weeks in a row.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Babyland for the win!
[SPEAKER_05]: Two weeks in a row, not too shabby.
[SPEAKER_03]: So everybody has to go to their show in Berkeley.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now the stripper song was only one vote behind.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it was close.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were all up there.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're all winners.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except Rob's not as much of a winner.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was one vote for Pat, that one song, one vote for Jamie's song, and zero votes for yours.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that was both of our listeners right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, it's about 9.30 and I think it's time to call it a night.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you kids think?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want ice cream.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm thirsty.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm hungry.
I want a cupcake.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they're... No, I think I ate the last one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bastard!
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need... Oh, I want Boba.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's 23rd Magus.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hear you there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you know, TAPEX is open.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop it!
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop it, all of you!
[SPEAKER_05]: I just got told I'm fat today!
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll get you some nice wheatgrass.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want wheatgrass.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want bulimia right about now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then fine, I'll get you a bottle of Ipecac.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a toothbrush.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_01]: You said you wanted bulimia.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, sorry chat room, I ignored your FUs tonight, maybe next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tonight was supposed to be a slow news night, we went on forever, but of course I think that little giggle fit had something to do with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your giggle fit, okay Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: My giggle fit?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you were the only one laughing in the microphone.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were laughing at you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have your giggle fit on camera, so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Partial.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your fortune cookie message.
[SPEAKER_05]: I almost said your moment of zen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you still want to be a duck?
[SPEAKER_05]: Of the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to be a duck.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're tiny, we're toony, we're all a little loony And in this cartoony, we're invading your TV We're comic dispensers, we crack up all the censors On I'm a Toon Adventures, get a dose of comedy So here's at the anchors, it's a whole wide world apart Our homes, we only stand alone, a cartoon work of art
[SPEAKER_08]: The scripts were rejected, expect the unexpected On Tiny Toon Adventures, it's about to start They're furry, they're funny, they're fast and bustin' funny Montana Max has money, Elmira is a pain She's hefty and plucky, busy devil yucky Her balls are chunky, and Go-Go is insane At Acme University, we earned our Toon degree The teaching staff have been getting laughs since 1933
[SPEAKER_08]: We're tiny, we're too neat, we're all a little moody It's Tiny Toon Adventures, come and join the fun And now our song is done