[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bring on the Orange Lounge Radio Afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here we are.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the part of the show you can only hear on OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's too hot to podcast, people.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love this comment from SSJ100Matt in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_11]: Those two should have a Friday Night Nerd podcast.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think referring to Spike and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: So what's the plan for the Silent Hill movie, yo?
[SPEAKER_11]: I know we've got to go see it, but what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I want to get a big, big group together on Friday because I'm having one of our listeners and a good friend come up from the Bay Area to come to the movie with us.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we just want to get as many people together to just nerd out the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it would be cool, though, if we all had those cheese hats and repainted them to look like Pyramid Head.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nerd!
[SPEAKER_03]: That is such a good idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would totally do that and like carry around like, you know, a little three inch spear.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what's sad, though, is that I'm getting invited to a lot of these things.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I'll probably do Jamie's because she does have the birthday advantage.
[SPEAKER_11]: Booyah!
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, I know there's a lot of people planning on going to see this, like a lot of video game fans.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I'm very excited for how... I just hope they don't disappoint us with this movie.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm very excited.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would love to do the cosplay, though, at the movie because that is fucking nerdy.
[SPEAKER_11]: We could put out a press release and everything in the media would be there taping us in our pyramid head hats.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like a hot dog.
[SPEAKER_11]: We should call a movie theater and try to sponsor something locally.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know I'm going to be putting out a massive review on our stuff.orangechallengeradio.com which has been given some attention by me lately.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, I actually looked at it the other day and you're the only one updating it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's going to actually see a lot of updating during E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: My personal plan is to go to the business center at E3 and do intermittent stuff updates.
[SPEAKER_11]: and we're still trying to figure out how we're going to do podcasts unfortunately we're in a weird situation where our hotels are going to be very far apart so I'm just hoping that we can somehow do the podcast still in some way I've got shuttle from my hotel to E3 if someone can get me right back to my hotel
[SPEAKER_11]: We might be able to make that work.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's gravy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Except, now this is what my hard thing is going to be is because I'm pulled between doing DDR Freak stuff and doing Orange Lounge stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm trying to fit everything in.
[SPEAKER_11]: So if worse comes to worse.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm probably going to skip Roscoe's this year.
[SPEAKER_11]: You might have to contribute individual reports or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm probably going to skip Roscoe's this year though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Roscoe's is overrated now.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's so 2004.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't eat Roscoe's anymore just because I get sick off of most food now.
[SPEAKER_05]: So.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I had the bird flu.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I worked.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was my spring break when I had the bird flu, so thankfully I didn't have to go to class on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which was my flash class anyway, and I would have been dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd have been like, ugh, flash, blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love my flash class, but God.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did, though, it was pretty funny because the week before, the teacher had us review our animated ads.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I did the Silent Hill one.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she spent like maybe two minutes on everybody else, like 15 minutes on mine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm trying to figure out how to do that because I'm still a Flash newbie, but at least I've got the design part down.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, congratulations.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually working on a Flash design for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm working on doing a special Orange Lounge photo gallery, but I need to take a picture of your desk.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm going to use your computer as the frame for the placeholder for the images to pop up in.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's going to be a month or so out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to require some work.
[SPEAKER_11]: With all the crap all around and everything?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, the crap is... I'm actually going to add in more crap in Illustrator.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, goody.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's going to be the uber crappy desk, and I'm going to expand your desk by another two feet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I wish I could really have that.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: and I basically went to Golf Land drunk and went and played some mini-golf and I apparently played some Mario Kart GP which I am right now recording to my computer so we can put it on the website because I'm doing a lot of yelling.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the face that I have on the thing is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have to see this.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, I look...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't remember actually playing Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wish I could tell you if it was good or not, but I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know I'm not getting married anytime soon, but I kind of want to have a bachelor party just so I can get drunk and be the center of attention for a night.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll go, and I'll buy you drinks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe I can have an anti-bachelor party, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was punching the screen!
[SPEAKER_11]: As you were, it was great.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, check out that video soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'll be up on OrangeLandrider.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Spike, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_03]: I threw a party Friday night, which was basically a big excuse to play Power Stone with people I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I played Karaoke Revolution several times.
[SPEAKER_11]: Didn't we sing I Got You, Babe?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we did!
[SPEAKER_11]: I do a mean share.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just wanted to point out.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love doing a mean share.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_11]: You're just a regular party animal.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, no, I had a very game-centric week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Threw a party, played games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Played games, not at a party.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the long and the short of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: My week of my day was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I played a little bit of Final Fantasy XI and played other games.
[SPEAKER_11]: I had an overall pretty mellow week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Easter was today, so I went to my parents' where we had leftovers because my parents didn't feel like cooking.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then, I'm trying to think, Friday we went to that party, so that was part of the weekend there because you don't exactly live around the corner, so it's a little bit of a drive.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's good.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was all worth it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I was probably the only sober person there, which was kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that made me a little sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Your share would have been a little better drunk, I think.
[SPEAKER_11]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would have been a lot louder and probably woken up the neighbors.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then driving home wouldn't have been fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, the reason I threw a party this week is because my downstairs neighbors were evicted.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why I wasn't telling anyone to shut their mouth.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, God, that's great.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: We should have held the party downstairs.
[SPEAKER_11]: We could have broke in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Such a good idea.
[SPEAKER_11]: Would have been awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, moving on, let's get into the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sound like a plan?
[SPEAKER_11]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, since we have new people listening for the first time tonight, the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match is where we play three songs for you guys, a clip of last week's winner, and then two new songs for you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, uh, you guys vote, and the winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio's 24-hour-a-day, 7-day-a-week music and video game program.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or I should say video game and music program.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, we got song number one tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: You only get to hear a clip of that because it won last week.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Loki's pick, and I believe it was the X-Noise Diffusion.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was the name of the song?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: So here it is, a clip of song number one, last week's winner you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember, you cannot place a vote until all three songs have played, and at that time I'll tell you how you vote, but you have to be in the chat room to do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: OrangeLaunchRadio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's a clip of song number one, X-Noise with Diffusion.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, that's song number one you can vote for tonight, X-Noise with Diffusion, but it has to beat two other songs, two brand new songs going into tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_11]: The first one is my pick, and I decided to pick a song by a group called Bittersweet, which I think is a good name for a band.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the song's called Dirty Laundry, and I have a lot of that on the floor of my bedroom, so I think this is a very appropriate choice.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I like this because it's kind of jazzy.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I like about this.
[SPEAKER_11]: So here's my pick.
[SPEAKER_11]: Song number two, Bittersweet with Dirty Laundry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, that was song number two in tonight's case match.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bittersweet with Dirty Laundry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go around and see if they like that song in the studio or if they want to wash it.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was cute and it wasn't trance.
[SPEAKER_05]: It gets a nine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It gets like an eight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Spike.
[SPEAKER_03]: That flashed me back to the Sharon Apple portions of Macross Plus.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big, big bonus in my book.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd definitely go with like a nine for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: That for me was music to spank someone to.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ow!
[SPEAKER_11]: That gets a nine from me.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: You've been a naughty listener.
[SPEAKER_11]: You've been a very naughty listener.
[SPEAKER_11]: Song number three comes to us from DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: What did you decide to annoy the listeners, I mean bring joy with tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_11]: Just teasing.
[SPEAKER_05]: This song's called Emo Kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: That should say it all.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, here it is then.
[SPEAKER_11]: Song number three in tonight's cage match, Emo Kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just don't call DarkSakura one or she'll rip your heart out and then stomp on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dear Diary, Mood, apathetic.
[SPEAKER_01]: My life is spiraling downward.
[SPEAKER_01]: I couldn't get enough money to go to the Blood Red Romance and Suffocate Me Dry concert.
[SPEAKER_01]: It sucks cause they play some of my favorite songs like Stab My Heart Because I Love You and Rip Apart My Soul and of course Stabby Rip Stab Stab.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it doesn't help that I couldn't get my hair to that flippy thing either.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like that guy from that band can do.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some days...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm almost emo enough to start shaving my legs Cause I feel real deep when I'm dressing in drag I call it freedom of expression, most just call me a fag Cause our dudes look like chicks and our chicks look like dykes Cause emo is one step below transvestite Stop my breathing and slit my throat
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm dark and sensitive with low self-esteem The way I dress makes every day feel like Halloween I have no real problems but I like to make believe I stole my sister's mascara, now I'm grounded for a week Sulking and writing poetry are my hobbies I can't get through a Hawthorne Heights album without sobbing Girls keep breaking up with me It's never any fun, they say they already have a pussy They don't need another one Stop my breathing and slit my throat I must be emo, I don't jump around when I go to shows
[SPEAKER_04]: I must be emo, dyeing my hair and polish on my toes I must be emo, I play guitar and write suicide notes I must be emo My life is just a black abyss, you know?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's so dark, and it's suffocating me Grabbing a hold of me and tightening its grip Tighter than a pair of my little sister's jeans Which look great on me, by the way
[SPEAKER_04]: When I get depressed, I cut my wrists in every direction Hearing songs about getting dumped give me an erection I write in a live journal and wear thick rimmed glasses I tell my friends I bleed black and cry during classes I'm just a bad, cheap imitation of God Figuring me catch her in the rye and watch me jack off I wear skin tight clothes while hating my life If I said I like girls, I'd only be half right I look like I'm dead and just like a homo I must be emo, screw Xbox, I play old school Nintendo
[SPEAKER_01]: My parents don't get me, you know?
[SPEAKER_01]: They think I'm gay just because they saw me kiss a guy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, a couple guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I mean, it's the 2000s.
[SPEAKER_01]: Can't two or four dudes make out with each other without being gay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, chicks dig that kind of thing anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, diary.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sometimes I think you're the only one that gets me.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're my best friend.
[SPEAKER_01]: I feel like tacos.
[SPEAKER_11]: Song number three in tonight's KH match, Adam and Andrew with Emo Kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see what kind of emotional reactions that got out of our judges here in the studio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember, our votes don't count, yours do.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll tell you how to vote in just a minute.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eleven.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of my friends played that for me, the one who... That song is, like, the best.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: It made me crack up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't care for it very much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Six.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spike, my whole life is a dark room.
[SPEAKER_02]: One big dark room.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, definitely a nine.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_11]: I was going to give that song a high score, but then they had to go and make fun of people that play classic Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry, not cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you lose some points for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: However, it does entitle the song to get a six.
[SPEAKER_11]: As in, six, six, six, the sign of the devil.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want tacos.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want a 39 cent taco.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dear Diary, Mood, Apathetic.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's the three songs you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Song number one, X Noise, Diffusion.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, that was a shitty clip.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's try that again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Much better.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Song number two you can vote for tonight, Bittersweet with Dirty Laundry.
[SPEAKER_11]: And song number three you can vote for tonight is Adam and Andrew with Emo Kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, place vote now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or I'll cut you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Artistic in this context.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that another word for emo?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: But not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Heart!
[SPEAKER_05]: Dear DeviantArt, My soul is black.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is as black as the bottom of a kettle.
[SPEAKER_05]: And because of the darkness within me, I feel the need to draw nothing but pretty light-colored flowers.
[SPEAKER_05]: With sunshine and rainbows.
[SPEAKER_05]: to express my desire to have love in my life.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because otherwise it's a pit of loneliness.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want burritos.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that the name of the new Morrissey single?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that was You Have Killed Me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's actually true.
[SPEAKER_05]: The new Morrissey stuff is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, yeah, so like, let's just go back and just have Viva hate and then kill him before he can make his other records.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I like the one he did with Suzy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Interlude.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that one a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm tallying up cage match votes right now, and Did You Lose a Sock actually has a DeviantArt he wanted to share.
[SPEAKER_05]: I looked at it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And hooray for everybody giving Morrissey love.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm actually a really big Morrissey fan.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen them like four times.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just, this new stuff doesn't work for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh shoot, but the Babyland last night though, I cannot rave enough about how awesome they were.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, this is how the night went to start off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Iguana Girl and I go and get sushi, which you know, me and her and sushi, we fell right into a sushi coma.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was beer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck I love sushi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to take you to this place.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really, really yummy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called Sugata in Berkeley.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really good.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, when I was out in Chesapeake, Virginia weeks and weeks ago, that trip I was on for a couple weeks, I had really freaking good sushi when I was there.
[SPEAKER_11]: And who would have thought you could get good sushi in Chesapeake?
[SPEAKER_11]: But it was actually really good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: This place that I went to was really expensive, but they were very good.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I got a free Japanese lesson.
[SPEAKER_05]: He asked me something that I didn't quite understand.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was like, uh, chotto.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's like, chotto!
[SPEAKER_05]: He's so happy that I used it right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I said, next time I come in, I'm going to order like this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Koreto, koreto, koreto.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, are.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he laughed at that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a bad joke, but hey.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I guess you have to speak Japanese to get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that cute?
[SPEAKER_11]: She sounds like a cartoon.
[SPEAKER_05]: This and this and this and oh, that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, so we went on to the venue and the first band sucked, so we went and got beer at the brewery across the street.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then we went back and the Mormons were on and they sucked, so we went and got more beer.
[SPEAKER_05]: We missed Ninja Academy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go back to listen to 8-Bit and then Babyland freaking owns my soul.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you done tallying now?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, they're done.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm ready to go.
[SPEAKER_11]: You ready to hear who won tonight's cage match?
[SPEAKER_11]: Woo-hoo!
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a good time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's check it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, I was surprised.
[SPEAKER_11]: It wasn't quite a landslide vote tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: All three songs got a lot of lovin'.
[SPEAKER_11]: But in the end, there could be only one.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the wave of the future is... Emo.
[SPEAKER_11]: You silly little emo kids, you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sky, what do you think the revolution's other secret is?
[SPEAKER_11]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe... You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Instead of me cosplaying at Faname, I think my iBook should cosplay, and it can cosplay as Bjork.
[SPEAKER_11]: I could cosplay as Bjork.
[SPEAKER_11]: That might be fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you have to cosplay with me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not doing Naruto.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a headband you could borrow.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know you do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just picked up my Sand Village because I'm cosplaying Tamari.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's too big for my head.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: And this whole time I thought you had a huge head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_11]: So your birthday party's next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: And your birthday birthday itself is on... Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm like, when day is it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Thursday, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, we're doing something on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's not as bad as 40, so smile!
[SPEAKER_05]: But no, I hung out with Disney Punk 10 on last Saturday.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I went to see Babyland last night.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Wednesday I'm going to eat at Bon Lair.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a pub downtown for fish and chips.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't tell the Stalker fans where you're going to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Thursday we're doing something.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Friday is Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Saturday is my birthday party at my annual Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Sunday is me falling into a coma and sleeping.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Monday my massage therapist is taking me to the pub.
[SPEAKER_11]: Lucky.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't want a massage therapist at all, let alone one to take me out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you going to get a massage at the pub?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'd be hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is this pub going to do the candle thing again?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because that sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: They every so often do Ye Olde Pub Night.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wish they would play pipe organ music, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be badass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not in a pub.
[SPEAKER_05]: They need to have bagpipes or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or a pan flute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then I'm waiting for birthday money I'm actually getting something I've asked for one of my birthday presents the one from my husband to be something for the show sweet I've asked for a high MD mini disc recorder I want that camcorder Loki has I've decided it'll make the home porno so much easier I may have my own camera person I may have my own camera person at E3 too if all works out
[SPEAKER_11]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: We hope.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're trying.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're fierce like a diva in a good way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I wear a peacock dress like Margaret Cho does?
[SPEAKER_10]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_10]: What, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: They put out the floor plan for E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, it's up?
[SPEAKER_10]: Granted, I personally love hanging out at Konami's booth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_10]: Instead of Buena Vista being where it was.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the N-Gage Arena!
[SPEAKER_11]: What?!
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, no, they put Konami next to N-Gage?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, N-Gage, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: I heard SNK's not in the main building this year.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're down in Kenshia.
[SPEAKER_11]: So who took their place, is what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but Ketch is the cool place to hang out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like the indie place.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like where all the hipsters hang out.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Rockstar doesn't have a booth this year either, I heard.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, 2K has a booth, and that might as well be Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, we never answered the poor guy's question, what do we think the next secret on the revolution is.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've mentioned holographic, or what was it?
[SPEAKER_11]: What was this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Stereoscopic 3D?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's the... Holo projections.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also mentioned nachos.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's the best serious answer I've got for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: and Roz says more like N-Gay.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: The N-Gage is not allowed to be gay because that would disrespect my people.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was just going to go there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't see an America's Army booth, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to have a contest now, thanks to the chat room, where I give out my infamous nacho cheese sauce recipe.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's get to the chat room, FU, shall we?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to give them an old classic song to start us off.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, chatroom FUs.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're using that again from now on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dark Knight says, FU to me working on Easter Sunday.
[SPEAKER_11]: End of line.
[SPEAKER_11]: Illusion says, FU goes to Loki for not singing karaoke last night.
[SPEAKER_11]: VXJasonXV says, FU to the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_11]: That song blew.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_11]: GK128 says, F you to my GPU fan that it decided it wants to keep flickering on and off, leaving my laptop hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now I have to try and fix you, you bastard.
[SPEAKER_11]: MiniMe283 says, F you to EGM for still not sending me my first issue, and I renewed in freaking December.
[SPEAKER_11]: I complained to them last week, and they said I'd get my April issue in six to eight weeks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it's just like Game Informer.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't freaking got my May issue yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: MiniMe283, you won our freaking 24 contest.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have no right to be upset tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: I retract that FU.
[SPEAKER_11]: The23rdMagga says, Quick FU to having to spend an entire week feigning interest in every little thing a relative says you should be interested in.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also a big FU to being cooped up in a hotel for an entire week.
[SPEAKER_11]: FU to being forced to watch five straight hours of Law & Order to the point where you root for the asshole defense attorney who looks nothing like Phoenix Wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: Legend of Zaku says, something and I haven't played in five months.
[SPEAKER_11]: But the first part of his FU got cut off.
[SPEAKER_11]: How sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkTetsuya says, FU to Travis Donovan.
[SPEAKER_11]: He threatened to move his show to Sunday just to mess with you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: LOL.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, oh, bring it, bitch.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: If you even try and move a show on to Sundays, we will bring the Spike and Dark Sakura nerd show to Saturday nights.
[SPEAKER_05]: And who volunteered to do this for me?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think somebody's just bitter that we have higher ratings this one month.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's alright, we have love for Travis.
[SPEAKER_11]: For the people who don't know out there, why don't you explain who Travis is?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, he's the host of UnderStationLive.org, which I shouldn't be giving him a free plug when he says such nasty things about us, but it was the show that I got my start on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, I should say my second song, because I actually started on a college show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was the most often guest.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's right, DarkSakura had a lot of experience on that program as well, and it was the first live 365 thing we did.
[SPEAKER_10]: And to answer your question, who's taking SNK's booth, it would be Game Infinity.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, they were there.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were there, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: By the way, chatroom guys, you need to send those over private message to me, otherwise I miss them.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll try, because I know we have new chatters tonight, I'll try and read them out of the chatroom, but please, please, please send them over private message if you want to make sure I get them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Legend of Zaku says, F you to myself for not putting more money in for playing Supernova when I went to my nearby location test.
[SPEAKER_11]: F you to having shitty stamina while playing Supernova since I made the mistake of wearing Converse.
[SPEAKER_11]: SSJ100 Matt says F you to Anizona the Arizona anime convention for putting a 1200 person cap on the convention second year in a row they've underestimated the anime fan population in Phoenix Ranma says F you to the internet and file sharing I can't find the theme to Finders Keepers damn that was an awesome game show
[SPEAKER_11]: Jeremy Todd 1 says, F you the week goes to my school because we don't have a spring break.
[SPEAKER_11]: We just get a three-day break for Easter.
[SPEAKER_11]: F you to school.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, and F you to making me sit by the computers for a couple hours straight to listen to your show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Boss Tone says, F you to not having a supernova test location near me.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I think there was one in the chat from somebody new.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, did you lose a sock says F you to the people who hated the emo song.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have it on my iPod.
[SPEAKER_11]: And DJ Kibbles and Bits says,
[SPEAKER_11]: says F you to OXM trying to qualify scoring a 10 for Fight Night Round 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: And HitStun says F you to the feedback of my voice on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's distracting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Turn your volume down when you do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: What, Extifer?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why'd you steal a microphone?
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you have something to say?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you gotta turn it on, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you ever gonna do a show again?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure!
[SPEAKER_08]: When?
[SPEAKER_08]: On...
[SPEAKER_08]: Someday.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I still want a title.
[SPEAKER_08]: If people can come up with a fucking title, I can come up with a show.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought you were going to do Extover's World of Thursdays.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can call it Friday Eve.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh, I won't, but thank you for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Miklatov, say hello to our listeners.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_11]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_11]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anything you want to say about, you know, stuff going on in the world?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow, that was five minutes of radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: He said no like that was just clever or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you high?
[SPEAKER_08]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_08]: Friday is Eve.
[SPEAKER_08]: That might work, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's going to do it for tonight's Afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have a great week, everybody.
[SPEAKER_11]: Woo, doggie!
[SPEAKER_11]: Now you have something to say, Miklatov.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody go watch Silent Hill the movie this coming week.
[SPEAKER_09]: We already talked about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: When is that?
[SPEAKER_05]: On Friday.
[SPEAKER_09]: On Friday?
[SPEAKER_09]: When?
[SPEAKER_05]: The 21st, the night it opens.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will talk to you more about it later than what time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm thinking either the last or second to last show.
[SPEAKER_09]: I could probably do one of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'll post a time up in my lab journal.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell him about the cheese head idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to get cheese hats and repaint them to be pyramid head.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, the color of rust?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'd be hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, we all go in... We have to fill in the holes, because I don't want to be a broken pyramid head.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be the broken pyramid head society.
[SPEAKER_09]: That sounds depressing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we need little, like, three-inch, you know, spikes to go.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll just take a knife.
[SPEAKER_09]: Plastic knives!
[SPEAKER_09]: How about a real knife?
[SPEAKER_09]: We go in with sporks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, sporks would be cool, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sporks.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm a legend.
[SPEAKER_11]: I am a legend.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I said alleged.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought I was legend.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, you're not.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a great book.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a great movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stop talking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I like beer.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you want to say, Christopher?
[SPEAKER_08]: Wondershowsin is so freaking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob got to watch some of it last night.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm seriously ending this show.
[SPEAKER_11]: So tune in next week for more fun here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here it is, kids, your fortune cookie message.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, the day.
[SPEAKER_00]: I will send a flood to wipe out all the bad things.
[SPEAKER_00]: I will save two of everything, but everything else goes.
[SPEAKER_00]: And there'll be a lot of umbrellas.
[SPEAKER_00]: You, Noah, stop what you're doing and build me an ark.
[SPEAKER_00]: And Noah, who is Sean Connery, who is...
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm working on a speedboat at the moment.
[SPEAKER_00]: Speedboat's much faster.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll shoo across the water a lot faster.
[SPEAKER_00]: Be great photos for the Bible.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, I appreciate your sense of publicity, but I want an ark with a big room for poo.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's gonna be important.
[SPEAKER_00]: Speedboat, let's go for a speedboat.
[SPEAKER_00]: We can get all the animals with long ears.
[SPEAKER_00]: They can sit along the side of that ears and... Because I like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, you build me an ark.
[SPEAKER_00]: Put a big motor in an ark if you want compromise.
[SPEAKER_00]: So he started to build himself an ark.
[SPEAKER_00]: Started sawing up timber.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's not actually how you start sawing, is it?
[SPEAKER_00]: You start sawing by going... That first bit where you...
[SPEAKER_00]: Then you're into the middle bit of where you feel like your dad.
[SPEAKER_00]: When your dad used to say, I'm off out to the garage to saw a plank of wood in heart.
[SPEAKER_00]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_00]: No reason for it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, let's see if Dr. Bronowski's still on television.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Ascent of Man.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sundays with my dad, that was.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, yes, um, so the middle bit of the song, and then the end goes back into, and after a while, Noah realized he was actually punching a baboon.
[SPEAKER_00]: Get off me!
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright kids, that's it.
[SPEAKER_00]: End of line.