[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_08]: And we're back here with Orange Lounge Radio for this episode number 179, April the 2nd, 2006.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember, guys, we're coming off of April Fool's Day, so take everything you hear tonight with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_08]: One thing that is the real deal, though, we have a special guest here joining us for Part B. Say hello, everybody, to OLR favorite Miklatov.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_08]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Miklatov, of course, works over at Konami.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: but due to NDAs can't really tell us anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are there any good games coming out this year from Konami?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I guess that's about all we can figure out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you tell us anything about sequels to popular franchises?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you tell us anything about Metal Gear 4?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: So he'll be giving us one word answers all night long.
[SPEAKER_08]: He can tell you that it is coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's public information.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've all seen the trailer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: How's Beatmania?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I'm good?
[SPEAKER_00]: If you eat your vegetables and clean your room and make your bed.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll try.
[SPEAKER_00]: Guitar Room Man Live to PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: Our listing is being put up by several of the Japanese retailers for a PSP title called Guitar Room Man Live due out in Japan at the end of May.
[SPEAKER_00]: No details out, nothing official has been said about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the hint's there.
[SPEAKER_00]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm surprised we haven't seen a Parappa the Rapper game for PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a good point as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why drag the system sales down further?
[SPEAKER_08]: Parappa's awesome, you shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like him jammerlammy, I don't like Parappa.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think maybe the success of Guitar Hero is causing people to go, of course, this is Japan now, not the US, but I would assume that if this comes out in Japan, we'd luck out and get it here in the US too.
[SPEAKER_00]: They need to bring out the Taiko no Tatsujin.
[SPEAKER_08]: for the PSP
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, so I hope that really happens.
[SPEAKER_00]: I really do hope so, and also I have to say that for the message board for where we found this, I do think that whoever posted this, Filler Bunny, has the best name ever.
[SPEAKER_00]: But anyway, I'm really hoping that we see it because, I mean, the one problem with that though, for anyone who played Guitar Room Man is...
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: I was getting hung up on the stupid Parapara stage with the stupid Parapara UFO.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that like the second stage?
[SPEAKER_00]: I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's so good.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like right at the end of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not as good as the Eurobeat song that's in there, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: That is the Eurobeat song.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the Eurobeat song.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's another song in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, that's the one you're thinking of.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, that's the Eurobeat stage with the Parapara UFO.
[SPEAKER_00]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: Parapara Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's such a good song.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game is so good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on, another game that I think a lot more people are looking forward to, Loki, we might have some news on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot more fans of this one than Guitar of Adam.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got to follow up on something we talked about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember the Forerunner rumor?
[SPEAKER_07]: It actually was in Game Informer.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was that Halo thing, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: That whole article was in Game Informer and I actually got to read it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what source they're taking it from.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think it's going to be what Halo 3 is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously they're going to call it Halo 3 or Halo 4 Runner or something like that, which will be Halo 3, like Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter type thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, so supposedly the word on the street is that IGN, once again their anonymous source, has found out that
[SPEAKER_07]: Halo 3 is supposed to be shipping March 2007.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the story is not dated April 1st?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, the story came out March 30th.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, it is close enough to that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it sounds about right, time-wise.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't they want to save it for the holiday season?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it'll sell either way, but... You always pick your biggest things at the holiday season, I thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not if they think Sony or Nintendo is plotting something around the same time frame.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe they think that maybe that's when the PlayStation 3 is actually going to launch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm kind of surprised they wouldn't try to release it in time for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_08]: But of course, you know, something like Halo, you don't want to screw that up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, technically that is in time for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just really early.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wrong year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember the rumors that Halo 3 was supposed to disrupt the Sony PlayStation 3 launch?
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't Gates say that or something?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to be very happy if everything's been kept under wraps.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like I think it has.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you think that this is Microsoft's big thing at E3?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they don't have a new system to show off this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now they've got to give us a big game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or so we know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: They could have their portable that everybody's been rumoring about.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think Halo 3 is definitely going to be the thing that they kick off the focus of their announcements.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's got to be.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that's, what else are you going to do when PlayStation 3 will be like, oh, look how pretty everything is, and, you know, Nintendo's going to be, look how innovative everything is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Microsoft will be like, look, we have Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, so.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the fanboys go, yay!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, by the way, I forgot to mention, three more games have been added to the compatibility list.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Winning 11-9, so some soccer for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Black,
[SPEAKER_07]: and... God damn it, I forgot the last one.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, that whole, like, oh, Xbox 360's gonna be constantly updated with, you know, new backwards compat... Bullshit!
[SPEAKER_08]: We got three in the past couple months.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just in time for their third relaunch of the system.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I can play Barbie, but I still can't play DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, speaking of which, you bring this up.
[SPEAKER_08]: We touched on this in the first part of the show and I tried to kind of retell your experiences, but how was it at Best Buy this morning?
[SPEAKER_08]: How did you come to find out that they were going to be doing this sale and all that good stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I have a relative who works at Best Buy and he informed me
[SPEAKER_06]: That Best Buy was doing yet another relaunch type deal of the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was very hush-hush apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: When we got there, it was only like 8.30 and nobody was there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And by the time the place opened, there was about 10 people in line.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they had about, I think about 90 systems.
[SPEAKER_06]: And my first one was defective, kind of, in my own weird way.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so, I mean, I took it back right before they closed and they still had plenty of systems, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: Is the shortage over from what you saw?
[SPEAKER_06]: At that Best Buy, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was nobody in there today, but I assume it's getting better now, after today.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, enjoy your 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: The second one that you're on now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to see if it works still.
[SPEAKER_08]: What games did you get?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you going to tell us your gamer tags so all the DDR fanboys can start adding you?
[SPEAKER_06]: are you going to get Rumble Roses XX?
[SPEAKER_07]: no, because I worked on that game and I know it's not a good game wow see, that's the point though here's the point though I know I can get that game for free because Konami loves our company and they send us free stuff
[SPEAKER_07]: and usually the people that work with me don't like the Konami stuff because they aren't into music games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And no one has a 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm looking forward to getting Rumble Roses for free because I'm not buying the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't play Dead or Alive 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought, oh, I've got to get this game because it's a really good fighting game.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it looked fun because at least they're
[SPEAKER_07]: Nippalicious, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: The good thing about Rumble Rose's XX is that it has really nice lighting and sometimes good graphics.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to make the most offensive looking character to play online.
[SPEAKER_08]: Miklatov, you're lying because you told me yourself the photo mode was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, photo mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're a dirty, dirty pervert, which I am, it is really good for you because you can take
[SPEAKER_06]: really really bad pictures and share them with your friends when we were testing it I guess some reviewers in Mexico had already gotten it I don't know why Mexico has systems but like they had pictures for us to download and I swear I haven't seen things that bad in a long time wow
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, any interest in taking dirty photos on Rumble Roses XX and sending them to all your friends?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: That sure beats seeing the spam.
[SPEAKER_07]: Check out my burnout clip.
[SPEAKER_07]: I so wish things had worked out so you could have gone to... Wait a second.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what you're saying is you can actually spread those clips online?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can download them.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have this place where you can just download photos that people have uploaded.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you can do whatever you want with them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, can you download them if you don't have the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, because it's like an option in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, damn, because we could have a totally awesome contest.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, Rubber Roses XX, Dirty Photo Contest.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who can make the dirtiest photo?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can also put outlines around your pictures.
[SPEAKER_06]: So when we were testing it, we had two of the chicks really close to each other, and we put a heart around it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was pretty funny and cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that game is worthless.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so confusing and not fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like the actual game.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Talk about some other news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you guys remember the whole Flowers for Jack?
[SPEAKER_08]: That was like weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: We actually gave money to that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, now it turned into this whole other thing that Pixelante is now what they're calling themselves.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they're selling shirts now.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Game Politics ran a story on this earlier in the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are selling their T-shirts.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are able to be purchased now on Zazzle, which I think is a competitor to Cafe E-Press or whatever that is.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Zazzle sells this now.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can see it at Zazzle.com slash Pixelanti Charity.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the shirts are around $15.
[SPEAKER_08]: But here's the part.
[SPEAKER_08]: For every sociopath with a mouse, as Jack Thompson calls it, for everyone that buys one of these shirts, Game Politics is going to donate all the profits to the Get Well Gamers Foundation.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just to rub it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jack Thompson's head on a donkey and making a jackass shirt.
[SPEAKER_00]: because actually he couldn't say it was harassment because it's legal under parity.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's go over now to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura likes to surf the interweb, and she combs it up and down.
[SPEAKER_00]: Day in, day out.
[SPEAKER_08]: And she finds at work, and she finds that one website special enough to share with you kids in a little segment we call DarkSakura's Website of the Week, correct?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Today's website of the week is Kingdom Hearts Ultimania, which is one of my absolute favorite Kingdom Hearts sites for a long, long time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not only does this place have stories on here, it has information about Final Mix, images, artwork, videos, audio.
[SPEAKER_00]: You name it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It has lyrics translated.
[SPEAKER_00]: They have it in the Kanji, Romanji, English, everything.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's really, really just an excellent site.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can get there by going to www.kh2.co.uk Very, very good site.
[SPEAKER_00]: Excellent forums.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just really top notch as far as it's the place to go for Kingdom Hearts information.
[SPEAKER_08]: So all those fanboys and fangirls, somebody labeled it earlier?
[SPEAKER_08]: I usually try not to look at it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I didn't play the first game, but I read a lot of Slash thanks to my friends.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've seen some very interesting Yaoi doujinshi posted a while back.
[SPEAKER_00]: Very interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was very disturbing because they're children.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I was like, why am I looking at this?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what was better about the Slash than the first game?
[SPEAKER_06]: It had a better camera.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that was a Kingdom Hearts joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, speaking of trashy things, are kids able to still pick them up, those trashy, trashy games, the evil games that Jack Thompson says we play?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the Federal Trade Commission released some results of their nationwide undercover sting operation, I guess, of electronic and video game stores.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're basically checking to see if people are still
[SPEAKER_07]: Selling these games to minors.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, well, actually they found that it's been a decrease.
[SPEAKER_07]: According to the survey here, 42% of the secret shoppers, children between the ages of 13 and 16 who attempted to buy an M-rated video game without a parent were able to make a purchase.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, it says in 2003, the...
[SPEAKER_07]: The percentage was 69%, so it's actually gone down quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it says now there's more stricter sales of M-rated games and only about 35% of secret shoppers were able to purchase them now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I bet you 35% is still kind of a high number for this stuff, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: I just feel like we're still going to not hear the end of this.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no actual laws in place for this in most states.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no real laws for this.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I mean, it's just a recommendation.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's all company enforced, so if 35% is down, that's actually pretty awesome that a company can enforce their will upon their employees to make sure that they check for ID and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Exception Rather Than The Rule
[SPEAKER_08]: Universal Studios, one executive over there was quoted saying, sales are near zilch, it's another Sony bomb.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh, burn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Has anybody actually tried to watch a UMD movie?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's not fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: I did.
[SPEAKER_00]: I did on the plane.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did on a plane, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I tried to watch Spider-Man 2 because it came with my system and it was not fun to watch.
[SPEAKER_00]: I watched Hellboy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw Tron.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it was fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tron looked pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have nice, those PSPs have nice screens.
[SPEAKER_08]: The problem is those movies are 20-something dollars, in some cases more expensive than what they are on DVD, and I can't play those on my DVD player.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you don't get the bonus features for the most part.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, and that's the problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: So the format, it was a good idea at first, I think, but I think the problem is there's no...
[SPEAKER_08]: If there were players that supported UMD, hell, even if they would announce that the PlayStation 3 would support the UMDs, which, what, you just pointed, what, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I thought that was one of the things they were going to announce at E3, is that there will be some sort of way to play UMD movies on TVs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's maybe too late.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, okay, good, you can play a UMD movie on TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, why do I have to buy a UMD movie over a DVD then?
[SPEAKER_07]: On Occasion
[SPEAKER_00]: My FU of the week would have to go toward Mountain Mike's Pizza.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was very nice of my boss to buy our team pizza, and she was very thoughtful to get vegetarian pizza.
[SPEAKER_00]: Except that I reacted to this vegetarian pizza the way that I react to meat.
[SPEAKER_00]: My stomach hurt like I had been doing a bajillion crunches, and yet I felt very full.
[SPEAKER_00]: I felt this way until yesterday morning.
[SPEAKER_00]: So a big FU goes to Mountain Mike's Pizza for trying to poison me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_07]: My FU goes to Best Buy and the stupid person they have working in their camera department in their Citrusite store.
[SPEAKER_07]: Guy was an idiot.
[SPEAKER_07]: I asked him questions.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was buying a video camera yesterday and I asked him, okay, what's the difference between this camera and this other camera?
[SPEAKER_07]: That was newer!
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, that didn't tell me anything, you dumbass.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can tell that by looking at it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: Completely useless.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, I did find a camera after having to drive a half an hour to the Elk Grove store, so that sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: That and stupid drivers.
[SPEAKER_08]: My FU goes to male PMS because I think I've had that all weekend.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know you can't tell during the show because I'm my peppy self, but I've had male PMS.
[SPEAKER_08]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not having woman issues, but you know that whole study that shows that men get that chemical imbalance that makes them all moody too once every so often?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I have that this weekend.
[SPEAKER_08]: So be careful around me.
[SPEAKER_08]: In my brain, in my head, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: The area between... Never mind, I'm not going to go there.
[SPEAKER_08]: The other area is just fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's my brain.
[SPEAKER_08]: As many people throw their iPods out the car window in horror at that thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they won't be missed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Miklatov, do you have a nephew of the week you'd like to get?
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: LightLikeLoki, MyFUGoesToTheBestBuy, Citrus Heights, for treating me like a criminal for wanting to take back my 360 today because I had issues with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when we were walking my new one over to the counter so they could kind of fake ring me up to swap it out, the guy from Meteor was like, there's another person taking back their 360?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do they not know how to work it or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to punch him.
[SPEAKER_06]: And preemptive FU to Microsoft because I have a feeling this one will be broken too.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Poo Eater is so winner in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: He says, I get PMS every month.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's a man, he's a mini.
[SPEAKER_08]: I get PMS every month.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the day after my wife's PMS.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a joke.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ha.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wouldn't it be the same day because she's bugging him?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, but he's so exhausted after helping her.
[SPEAKER_08]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Men have no idea what PMS is like.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have no way of knowing what PMS is like.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: The day that you grow a uterus and it decides to... With the exception of the
[SPEAKER_08]: You know the birds and bees part that you learned about in fourth grade and the biological element of it all.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some days I get pretty grumpy and irritable.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I do know that... Ask my loved ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I crave junk food, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I go through the whole motions.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's short of the physical aspect of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, please bring this back to games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't die.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, there's actually been a recall on the Pelican Power Brick Battery Charger.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically this giant brick that you attach to your PSP that gives it more battery life.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately, there's a little problem with it being that, well, it overheats and has actually caused fire damage.
[SPEAKER_07]: According to the website...
[SPEAKER_08]: might be dangerous.
[SPEAKER_07]: According to the website powerbrickrecall.net, there has actually been 143 reports of the recalled battery charger overheating, including one report of fire damage.
[SPEAKER_07]: No injuries have been reported.
[SPEAKER_07]: So basically, what you need to do, and they give you some information of hotlines to call, you need to send it back, is
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, there's better batteries out there, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So don't buy these battery accessories, you know, for your PSP, because, to be honest, it lasts long enough as it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: GameTap
[SPEAKER_08]: Star Trek and Bonsai?
[SPEAKER_08]: and presented by people that seem to actually enjoy games.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's something unreal there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, GameTap, by the way, has also added, I guess, Neo Geo stuff now, because I checked out Baseball Stars, and then they also have Darkstalkers, so that means Capcom's on their way in, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I heard some rumor they're doing a big Street Fighter thing, so I just thought I'd drop that out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: But what's interesting, oh, they also lowered their price.
[SPEAKER_08]: GameTap's now only, I think, $9.95 a month.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I hate to sound like a marketing thing, because really, you know, GameTap has its issues.
[SPEAKER_08]: They still need multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would really help them sell their things.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I do think it's a really just neat concept idea, and I hope it's successful.
[SPEAKER_08]: But a lot of people are saying it's doom and gloom, because, oh, price cut means they've got to move things.
[SPEAKER_08]: But not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_08]: It could be just an incentive to get more people on, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe $15 is a little too high.
[SPEAKER_08]: People might go for $10.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: One game you can play on GameTap is Tomb Raider, but the old ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: But there's a new one coming, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, well, Tomb Raider Legend right now is coming out on PlayStation 2, Xbox, Xbox 360, and PSP in May.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, the only thing it isn't coming out on is the Nintendo systems.
[SPEAKER_07]: No GameCube, no Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: However...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's possibly coming out later this year for them.
[SPEAKER_07]: And apparently, once again from IGN, they have talked to Eidos, and apparently Bill Gardner, the Eidos North America CEO and president, basically said, Laura likes Reggie, referring to Reggie over at Nintendo of America.
[SPEAKER_07]: And basically...
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, they're talking about it being released later on, possibly, I don't know, probably the end of the summer would be my guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, the only thing, though, this was announced kind of around April Fool's, so we don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Personally, I don't think it's gonna, because the GameCube's not really a big system right now as far as releases go.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's like maybe two a month, and the DS, well, you know, it's pretty good, but I don't see being able to port this very well over the DS, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm gonna call bullshit on this story, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think it's coming out on the GameCube or any Nintendo system anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's my thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the problem with April Fool's Day.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like, you don't know what to believe.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, the GameCube...
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe the fact that a lot of people still own one and there isn't a lot of games coming out for it is an incentive to put this game out on GameCube.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it'd be a waste of money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, of course, we all know one of the incentives to getting a revolution is going to be the backwards compatibility with not only Nintendo products, but Sega and TurboGrafx as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we think we might know some of the games coming, possibly?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, there was a wish list that was posted.
[SPEAKER_00]: Game Daily had an article up where they put up a wish list of games.
[SPEAKER_00]: And these were some of the ones that made the list, which are actually all games that I own except for one, which is the last one on the list.
[SPEAKER_00]: But...
[SPEAKER_00]: BUNKS ADVENTURE, BUNKS REVENGE
[SPEAKER_00]: Dracula X, Rondo of Blood, Splatterhouse, and Air Zonk.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so what we have to do now to follow that up is we have to make a wish list of our own.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know there's only one way we can do that, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Are we going to be including the games that were already on this list if we'd really like to see them?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think so because those are all the really good TurboGrafx ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think we need to let those on the list because I have one I want to use.
[SPEAKER_08]: So anyway, the way we do it around here, if you've never heard it before, the way we make lists is through a little segment we call ListList.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a given.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we got to think outside the box.
[SPEAKER_08]: So games we most want to see on the revolution besides Sonic from Sega and NEC.
[SPEAKER_08]: So the way it works, you guys, we're going to go around and give our top three.
[SPEAKER_08]: Myself, Loki, DarkSakura, and our guest Miklatov will give our top three.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then the fun part comes.
[SPEAKER_08]: We take one off of the list, each of us.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then you guys, the chat room, get the final say.
[SPEAKER_08]: You get two votes, so number one and number two.
[SPEAKER_08]: and what you think should be on the wish list.
[SPEAKER_08]: And maybe we'll send this wish list to Nintendo and Sega and NEC somehow.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll look in our little black book and see if we have some addresses we can send this to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, so here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who wants to start us off tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, you want to start us off?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, what is your number three pick for Sega or NEC game you most want?
[SPEAKER_00]: I am making a disclaimer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Two of the games I would really like to see on there, I'm not going to list because nobody's heard of them, like Emerald Dragon and Sapphire.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I suggest people give them a try if they can.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: So my number three is Star Parodia, which also probably only a handful of people have heard of.
[SPEAKER_00]: However, it's a shooting game featuring a flying bomber man, a flying PC engine, and, um, let's see, what was the other thing in there?
[SPEAKER_00]: Because it was three different flying machines.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, oh yeah, and, uh, a, uh, super deformed Vic Viper.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, uh,
[SPEAKER_00]: It was this cute little game, like if you play as the PC Engine, which I always did, you could shoot out CDs and cue cards as your firepower.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was really cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, what's your number three?
[SPEAKER_07]: My number three, I would have to say Splatterhouse.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game's fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: You gotta love a game that kind of mocks Friday the 13th and has a guy that's main weapon is a 2x4.
[SPEAKER_08]: Miklatov, your number three pick.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a disclaimer too.
[SPEAKER_06]: All my games are really random.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: So my number three would be Panic, because that game was awesome and very scary when I was little.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was on the Sega CD.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_08]: At first I thought I'd never heard of this game, and now, oh my god, I have heard of Panic.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's that little kid, and you push buttons and things, and you go to another room, and you get taken places, and it's scary, but I loved it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, what's your number two pick?
[SPEAKER_08]: Popful Mail
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, Working Designs brought it out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really fun, cute little translation.
[SPEAKER_00]: Very, very hard to get your hands on a copy of this now.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it's a little side-scrolling adventure RPG.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, I've never heard of this game, I have to admit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did I spell it right there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Popful?
[SPEAKER_00]: P-O-P-F-U-L, and then mail as in, you got mail.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it's such a cute little game, and I'll bring over my Sega CD one day so you can see this game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I'd have to see this.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it was one of the Working Designs projects back in the day.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you know the types of games that Working Designs brings us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, your number two.
[SPEAKER_07]: My number two.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it was kind of a fun game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Shadow Dancer.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of the best Shinobi games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Shadow Dancer was excellent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Smooth Criminal.
[SPEAKER_08]: You got to throw your hat.
[SPEAKER_08]: My number two would be one of the greatest and most overlooked Sega CD games of all time.
[SPEAKER_08]: And remember that this is, and we don't even know if Sega CD games are going to end up on Nintendo Revolution, but just the whole idea of seeing this on the Revolution would make me giggle in places I didn't even know I had.
[SPEAKER_08]: Night Trap is my number two pick.
[SPEAKER_00]: It had What's-Her-Face in it.
[SPEAKER_00]: With Dana Plato.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: Road Rash Road Rash
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but not next gen.
[SPEAKER_07]: There hasn't been anything since, like, um... There was one on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the original PlayStation, maybe... There was one on 3DO.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember the 3DO one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, what was Road Rash all about?
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember the name, but I don't remember the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Road Rash is, it's basically motorcycle racing and combat.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you're, you know, riding motorcycles and hitting people with chains and baseball bats and stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_00]: I've seen the Final Fantasy 7.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I have played that game before.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, our chat room says, GK128 says, Road Rash was E3, but there was one on PS2 that was canned.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I guess they started to do one and didn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mikotov, your number one pick.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is a game nobody will know, so it should get kicked off right away.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called Zoom.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's on Genesis, you know that?
[SPEAKER_00]: I know Zoom.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game was so awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that a puzzle game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game sucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that game was sweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game was awful.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was an MTV game, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I think it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you're thinking Zoop.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I am thinking of Zoop.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this is also a puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're like this pig head thing with legs and you drew squares and you had to watch out for the scrubbing bubbles things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, that sounds kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was thinking of Zoop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Zoop.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're thinking Zoop.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game was awful.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, this is like really old first generation Genesis game.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, so I get the last say.
[SPEAKER_08]: Number one pick.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was really tempted to do ToeJam & Earl.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, chat room, because chat room is yelling out ToeJam & Earl.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I have to do this for the simple irony.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you were a kid when this whole thing went down, you would know why I have to say Mortal Kombat, the Genesis version, has to be on the Nintendo Revolution.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Nintendo finally gets some Mortal Kombat with blood in it and not sweat.
[SPEAKER_08]: And really small characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wonder Boy in Monster Land
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, here's the list as it stands right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Star Parodia, Splatterhouse, Panic, Devil's Crush, Popful Mail, Shadow Dancer, Moonwalker, Night Trap, Dracula X, Rondo of Blood, Road Rash, Zoom, and Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boy, this was way more random than I thought it would be.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, but here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the part to get rid of the most weird stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: We eliminate one pick before we let the chatroom vote.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, DarkSakura, what's coming off the list?
[SPEAKER_00]: Night Trap.
[SPEAKER_08]: Aw, you're no fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because Dan and I tried to play through that game and it was so stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's slumber parties and Dana Plato and zombies.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, if I wanted to watch stupid, I could watch the Toxic Avenger movies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, what's coming off this list?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I should have put Zombies Ate My Neighbors.
[SPEAKER_07]: Zombies Ate My Neighbors.
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Nintendo 2
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that would have won.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't believe I didn't say Bomberman either.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, nobody said Bomberman, stupids.
[SPEAKER_00]: We've had Bomberman on Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was completely different on Genesis, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, 64 is pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie, I want to take it off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, Matt didn't have one taken off, so I'm going to be fair.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to take off... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to take...
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy VII Skitchin
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys can vote for your favorites in chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Star Parodia, Splatterhouse, Panic, Devil's Crush, Popful Mail, Shadow Dancer, Moonwalker, and Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_08]: So send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your number one and your number two picks.
[SPEAKER_08]: and we'll let you know at the end of the show who the winners are.
[SPEAKER_08]: And boy did we end up weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a really weird list.
[SPEAKER_00]: I sort of wish though now that I put Emerald Dragon on there because Emerald Dragon was such a good game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I wish that they would say, let's bring Saturn games on because then I could say, you know, freaking Black Matrix because that game will never come out over here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think, though, even though our list is really random, I think that's a good thing because we're thinking of titles that a lot of people sometimes don't think of right away when they think of Sega Genesis.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, everybody thinks of Sonic.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, I think this is good.
[SPEAKER_00]: But there's also some pretty, you know, there were pretty mainstream games on there because Devil's Crush and Shadow Dancer, those were really popular.
[SPEAKER_00]: I remember just sitting in the same room watching Dan play through Shadow Dancer and I was like, yeah, this game's awesome because you have a dog.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's why I couldn't take it off the list.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's too good.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura is the administrator of our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_08]: And when you guys send your emails to mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com, she puts on the rubber gloves, because you never know what people send us, and gets in the mailbag and pulls out some letters and reads them for us every week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sometimes my hands get some spam on them, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, if you're adding Orange Lounge Radio a spam email, just freaking stop.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's annoying.
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll hunt you down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we'll kill you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Cheese grater, lemon juice.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, who's in the mailbag this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: I have email from, well, I guess, I think this is Sakurina, I think, but didn't sign it, about DDR Supernova.
[SPEAKER_00]: First of all, I'll just go ahead and read the email.
[SPEAKER_00]: First things first, I played Supernova.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: I really enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_00]: The left pad was kind of sticky, but the music was awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: I highly recommend Seduction Vocal Mix.
[SPEAKER_00]: But yes, it was really awesome and it looked nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_00]: The next one is from TheOtherJamie, who spells the name differently.
[SPEAKER_00]: Remember the fun last year with the Mega Man effect?
[SPEAKER_00]: Though it only could run on a Mac, they've ported it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, the Mega Man effect thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_08]: When you would boot up a... Check out the MySpace.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a clip from the show on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: MySpace.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have time for MySpace.
[SPEAKER_08]: Too bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all I'm giving you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Jerk.
[SPEAKER_00]: Our dear friend Rob with two B's sent us an email about Sega Sammy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would also like to say Rob with two B's has a higher gamer score than anybody on my Xbox friends list.
[SPEAKER_08]: Congratulations, my friend.
[SPEAKER_00]: He actually posted a bit of an article in here about Sega debuting a new headquarters.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sega Amusements, the U.S.
[SPEAKER_00]: game factory that has emerged from the merger of Japanese game giant Sega Corp.
[SPEAKER_00]: and the equally powerful Sammy Corporation, have held a grand opening recently for their new 77,000 square foot sales development and game and prize warehouse facility in the Chicago suburb of Elk Grove Village.
[SPEAKER_00]: Special guests at the event included Sega Sammy Holdings CEO Hajime Satome,
[SPEAKER_00]: who engineered the merger and oversees the combined companies in Japan as well as local dignitaries such as Mayor Craig Johnson.
[SPEAKER_00]: The combination has dramatically enhanced the company's capabilities, said Satomi through an interpreter.
[SPEAKER_00]: Take a look around at what we have to offer and then think about what Sega can do in the future.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, it's...
[SPEAKER_00]: More Sega.
[SPEAKER_00]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hopefully we'll see some good things come out of them.
[SPEAKER_00]: I want to see more freaking Planet Harrier.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now we also got an email from someone whose gamertag is Ldriver but E-I-I-E.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like Kill Bill.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I'm going to go ahead and read this email out.
[SPEAKER_00]: I found out about your site slash show about three weeks ago, and I've been listening ever since.
[SPEAKER_00]: You put out great content that's not only really funny and informative, but also socially responsible and different in relation to gaming.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not to plug another podcast, but Gamertag Radio is also another place I hear similar topics.
[SPEAKER_00]: As a 20-something working professional adult gay gamer, or gamer myself, I was really appreciative to the segments in your past two shows about how not all gamers are straight nerdy teenage boys.
[SPEAKER_00]: You guys also happen to be darkly sarcastic about almost everything like me, so I find myself laughing out loud while listening to your show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Me?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sarcastic?
[SPEAKER_08]: Never!
[SPEAKER_00]: In places like my subway ride to work or at my desk.
[SPEAKER_00]: I do have one quick question for you three.
[SPEAKER_00]: Who or what do you think will steal a show at E3?
[SPEAKER_00]: I personally think PS3 is becoming overhyped, especially in the past few weeks, and that Microsoft and or Nintendo will use E3 to surprise everyone.
[SPEAKER_00]: What are your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for putting out great shows and keep up the great work.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually got to see the videos from the Game Developers Conference, including all the wonderful PS3 in-game shots.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, does it look nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the revolution will be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's going to be information overload this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think E3 is going to be so monumental in a way you've never imagined.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think any one person can steal the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think everybody's going to be constantly one-upping each other the whole day.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think if anybody, I think Nintendo's got the biggest secret out there, and they stand to either really...
[SPEAKER_08]: This is actually my first launch E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't count last year as a launch E3 because...
[SPEAKER_00]: Boom!
[SPEAKER_00]: And we're going to see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was able to pull up that program.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, the Mega Man thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_00]: Firefox.
[SPEAKER_00]: Cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, very cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you better take that off the computer before Extrovert tries to go play World of Warcraft because he's going to go, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_00]: Too bad you can't do the little trick where you turn the stars into chickens.
[SPEAKER_00]: Who remembers that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I do, I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be a cool hack.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, any more email?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, there is more email, so huh.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um,
[SPEAKER_00]: One of our listeners, Justin, has a question for us, and I'll read his letter.
[SPEAKER_00]: I noticed that Lemmings was out for the PSP, but only in the UK.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was wondering if the UK version will play on my US PSP, and if so, what is the best way to import this game?
[SPEAKER_00]: Keep up the good work on the live show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is PSP region free?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, PSP is region free.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Import away.
[SPEAKER_00]: Find whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: Make sure you check the Better Business Bureau before picking an importer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Trust me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Never buy anything from BuyRite.
[SPEAKER_06]: or Toys and Joys.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, Toys and Joys has given me nothing but good service.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Jerks.
[SPEAKER_00]: I bought my guitar controllers for Guitar Freaks from them for cheaper than anywhere else had them and they had just got their shipment in and packed it up that day.
[SPEAKER_00]: We did a phone order.
[SPEAKER_00]: I got it within like a week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've not shopped at any of those stores.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've used a place in the past called Japan Video Games because I went to their actual store once and so I've been loyal ever since.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, that's where I got my drum controller from.
[SPEAKER_00]: But now we just sort of take the drive to Burlingame and go to Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't Network closed?
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't they just close recently?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we were trying to go there the other day.
[SPEAKER_00]: They are closed on a weird day.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think they're closed on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, we've got to go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Worldwide show, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, that was the last email.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, then.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send us more email.
[SPEAKER_08]: More, more, more.
[SPEAKER_08]: We crave it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mailbag.
[SPEAKER_08]: OrangeOnTrader.com is where to send it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We will reveal the listless winner very soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, we have a couple stories real quick for you guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: There is a small announcement, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, what's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Next week, we will be rolling out a contest.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're not going to say anything about it, but make sure that you tell everyone to tune in next Sunday.
[SPEAKER_00]: because also, of course, it's going to be repeated on our podcast, but the first details will be on our live show.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we're working with somebody else to do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, it's a big thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, you got a story for us.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, anyways, before I just play with all this stuff here, basically, we have information, and it's not really much of a surprise because we knew this was going to happen, but
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to be announcing DOA Extreme Beach 2 at E3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, I'm not sure if it's going to be volleyball this time, because I heard basketball is another rumor they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: But basically, yes, the jiggly game will be shown at E3 or announced at E3.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Future of Credit Cards, earning virtual currency for spending in the real world.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Otherworld Bridging.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to make this real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to sum this up.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know how sometimes credit cards give you rewards such as frequent flyer miles and things of that sort for every dollar that you spend?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, now they're thinking of why not give in-game currency as a reward for spending money?
[SPEAKER_00]: That would just screw up whatever currency, whatever economy you've got going on in that environment.
[SPEAKER_07]: So when you use your credit card on in-game currency, you can score more in-game currency?
[SPEAKER_07]: Essentially.
[SPEAKER_07]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, just kind of interesting there.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a very lengthy blog.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not going to read all the details there.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to check it out for yourself, check out from March 2006, there was a blog there.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's just now, I mean, it's an old blog, but it's just now making the rounds on the gaming blogs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Makezine.com is the name of the site there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they go into a lot of details there.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's certainly an interesting idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, nobody's really thought of that before.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, I don't know, most MMO hardcore players I know that might actually sign up for something like this also hate...
[SPEAKER_08]: GoldSellers and GilSellers or whatever the currency is in the game you're playing.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I don't see this working because I think there's a conflict of interest there, but whatever floats your boat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shall we reveal the winners of tonight's list list?
[SPEAKER_00]: Please do.
[SPEAKER_08]: of tonight's listless.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, top three games we want to see on the Nintendo Revolution that is not Sonic from Sega or NEC from the TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot of ties tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have in third place, we have a tie there for third place, Star Parodia and Splatterhouse tied for third place.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good job, everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: Second place, we have a tie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shadow Dancer and Mortal Kombat tied for number two.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the number one game they want to see?
[SPEAKER_08]: Moonwalker.
[SPEAKER_06]: I win.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good job, everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for voting.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we'll be sending that list to our round file.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see what we can do about passing that along.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully we have some insider industry people that listen to the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should email us.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'd like to talk to you, get you on the show and interview you.
[SPEAKER_08]: We want some new faces and things on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: We haven't had an interview in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've been trying to reach out to people, but everybody's like, wait till E3, wait till E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: So whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you don't want us to wait till E3, we'll talk to you now.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's go to Skype line.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, you are on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, the UMD movies.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: What about them?
[SPEAKER_01]: You a fan of UMD movies?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm glad they're going away.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I haven't bought one since that movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought one movie on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Evil Dead.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, that's a good choice.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you have good taste in movies.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's all about Bruce Campbell and his chin.
[SPEAKER_08]: I suppose if you're going to buy one UMD, you might as well buy that or Tron or Kill Bill.
[SPEAKER_08]: Labyrinth.
[SPEAKER_08]: Something cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Starring David Bowie and his... Why the hate for the UMDs then?
[SPEAKER_08]: Were you just not impressed with Evil Dead?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I was impressed with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just I'm getting all my movies off BitTorrent and I'm just encoding it on my computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess that's the realistic world of what PSP has to deal with, is that, you know, the kids want to hack it and put their own movies on there, so it's a questionable legality thing there, but I guess that's what people are doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the other thing, too, is they're also pushing these larger memory sticks, and what the hell are you going to use them for?
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously not pictures.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're going to be ripping DVDs or whatever to... Downloading great podcasts like Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, but still, though...
[SPEAKER_01]: Every week on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, I hear you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you checked out olrpsp.com?
[SPEAKER_01]: Can I plug another podcast, another site?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, all right, sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: pspdrive.com, it has your website.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've heard of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've seen our listing on pspdrive.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a good site.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've actually used the portal.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a nice site.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they have a PSP 2.0, and I just downloaded wirelessly to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were supporting podcasts before Sony was.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's a good site.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've seen our little teeny reduced version of our graphic on there for PSPs, which I think is really cool because somebody obviously had to take the work to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really appreciate those guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just want to say that I have two Windows computers just like Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's a big Windows supporter and I support Windows just like he does.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's good to hear from a Loki fan, because sometimes we get the hate mails from the Mac users.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for calling, buddy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks, Guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, if you don't know what we're referring to there, Loki has made comments about Macintoshes, and he's really sick of hearing about it, too, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm... yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just really, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what happens when people download a show that's weeks and weeks old.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go over to this one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, I'm on Lyft.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it's Ranma calling in right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look, you can see the video of Ranma there.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the problem is, Ranma, when you run in the video, it's really hard for us to hear you.
[SPEAKER_08]: But there he is, his little Zelda hat.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ramma, call back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Turn off the video and call... Oh, there it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: It went off.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Much better.
[SPEAKER_08]: Much better.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, I want to cover a couple of things for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember when you talked about Penn & Teller Smoke and Mirrors?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, the game that was like, yeah, ran on... I'm glad you called in on this.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: It seems that when I was listening to Penn Jillette's radio, his podcast, he talked about the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: What did he say?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was basically the point of Smokey Mirrors was to go after Janet Reno who hated violent video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fabulous.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am posting a link in the chat room now.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you scroll down, you'll find where you can download it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called Penn & Teller's Real Life Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, it's 923freefm.com and you can probably navigate the site from there if you're not in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, what else Ranma?
[SPEAKER_08]: What else is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's go back to Catscom for a bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember the awesome Zelda skit everybody was talking about?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, the one I didn't see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm posting a link to it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you can download it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, if you scroll that all the way down, it's called Katsu2006-link.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, and that video is on the website Usagichan3.com, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, post it in our forums or something so people can find that link later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you guys see that Zelda fan movie that someone made?
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: It missed the cut for tonight's show because it's not really official, but it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would be interesting if they actually finish it and...
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't you think Nintendo is going to bring down the Swift Hammer of Justice on that project?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not necessarily, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just fan stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ranchan, you need to come to Fanime with us.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fanime 2007.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we'll be there.
[SPEAKER_08]: If our panels go over well, tell your friends in the anime community to come to our panels.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unlike they did at KatsuCon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look, you got screwed over.
[SPEAKER_08]: Believe you me, I'm just as pissed as you are.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had to put a dig in there somehow.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I learned a lot.
[SPEAKER_00]: I did make sure to specify that our panel is on a Saturday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I met some great people at Katsugana.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the important thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now there's a guy out there handing out flyers for us.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love our fans.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're so great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ranma, I've got to let you go so we can get to more of our listeners, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: You take care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just cut him off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, didn't mean to.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's go to another call here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, you are on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they're not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is Xander from China.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, Xander from China.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_08]: Kingdom Hearts 2 I'm like 17 hours into it right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, obviously I'm liking it quite a bit because otherwise I wouldn't have bothered going through all the stupid cutscenes.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think that's probably one of my biggest complaints about the game is that the cutscenes are really low quality, in all honesty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Most of them are.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think the cutscenes have been great so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, how far are you?
[SPEAKER_08]: The worst one for me, though, that ruined it, was the one in Mulan.
[SPEAKER_03]: 10 Heartless Chasing Him
[SPEAKER_03]: and there's no music.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was so pissed off.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate their costumes.
[SPEAKER_00]: The part that's funny about that, though, is playing it in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hearing them sing Under the Sea in Japanese is just hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't believe it's a music game where you press one button.
[SPEAKER_08]: Xander, any other comments on Kingdom Hearts 2?
[SPEAKER_08]: I've got to keep it moving because we've got a lot of people trying to call in tonight, but any other comments on Kingdom Hearts 2?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm really enjoying it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very different from the first game, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, if you didn't like the first game, you might like this one, although you wouldn't understand it if you didn't finish it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I agree, but Miklatov's shaking his head no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it still has a bad camera.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it's much better, much better.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's still bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: All you do is lock onto the target, and the camera follows it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's easy.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the first game, you would lock on, and the camera would still go behind smokes and mirrors and everything, and it made it a pain in the ass, but this one's much better.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually disagree on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the camera's actually worse than this one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had less problems with the camera than this one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Screw you people!
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll tell you what, my favorite part so far, I know I just played this part, I don't want to give spoilers, but the boss fight in Beast's Castle was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: The end one?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't say much more.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh man, yeah, that was good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, that's all I can say.
[SPEAKER_08]: Were you watching?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I was watching.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It had a bad camera.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, Xander, I gotta let you go before Shane pisses me off more, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a good one, bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's go.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll do one more call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, I'm in a really hacky mood.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're in a hacky mood?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I've been hacking a lot of things recently, like physically.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who is this, by the way?
[SPEAKER_08]: I forgot to ask who this is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo Maniac 64
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I haven't even thought about doing that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I read that on a forum this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody just casually said putting their controller in the PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I thought, that's a really good idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could use that for Final Fantasy and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does that work?
[SPEAKER_08]: Can I just plug it in and go?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or do I have to hack it?
[SPEAKER_07]: You can download the drivers off of Microsoft's site.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was asking the caller.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: But those drivers suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, they worked fine for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: What did you find?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's better drivers out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can get them off redcloud.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll post the link.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, yeah, post the link.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll check that out because I want to use it for Final Fantasy XI on the computer, which is ironic because I want to get Final Fantasy XI on 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm so sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, we are sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you're doing it too.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you find that you're using the Xbox 360 controller for on the PC?
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you emulating games or what are you doing with it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I do some of that, but not much because my computers are so much crap that I can't do much of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, pretty much the main thing I do is I play F-Zero Climax.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I did some other hacking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, what else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I got my standard headset mic that I'm using right now to work with my DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, is that why you were saying in chat earlier in the show that you really wanted to play Metroid with somebody for voice chat?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I wanted to test it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I played my first multiplayer Metroid last night, finally.
[SPEAKER_08]: I owned at it, I'd just like to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it was when you were sleeping.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_08]: You were sleeping because you had to go to Best Buy at 3 a.m.
[SPEAKER_08]: because you were afraid there was going to be a huge line.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo Maniac 64, I've got to let you go because we're running really long here.
[SPEAKER_08]: But have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, Panzer Dragoon and Die Hard.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I've got my attention.
[SPEAKER_00]: which for anyone who knows about this in Japan it was a Panzer Dragoon RPG but it's really hard to get your hands on however though for the Sega Ages collection there is a Panzer Dragoon collection and Die Hard which was a Dynamite DECA in Japan but however keep in mind these are Sega Ages these are meant to be cheap the Sega Ages 2900 is named 2900 for 2900 yen as in really cheap
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sorry, 2,500.
[SPEAKER_00]: My apologies.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, don't expect them to be, you know, made uber pretty, all gorgeous, everything, but they are supposed to be retouched, looking better.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so, which would be a good thing because I really liked the Dynamite DECA series and Panzer Dragoon was really neat.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, should be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually did find them up for pre-order on a couple sites.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like those Sega Ages games, unlike some people.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, Phantasy Star 2 was just released on the Sega Ages.
[SPEAKER_00]: But we haven't seen any translations for these come out yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_00]: We've been basically playing them when we have a friend over.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the remakes are really nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: And of course, I have the Phantasy Zone and Space Harrier remakes, which are really, really nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can vouch for these Sega Ages collections.
[SPEAKER_00]: Quite a bit of these have been re-released.
[SPEAKER_08]: I also like that Sega and Ages are... Not acronyms, but when you shuffle the letters around.
[SPEAKER_08]: Antigrams, thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you're so smart.
[SPEAKER_00]: I am.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that how you get jobs with video game companies?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're a smart feller.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Loki, anything for us, last minute-wise?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the first thing I was going to mention is that the cheat device for Grand Theft Auto Liberty City Stories is finally 1.0 now, and they added a few things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hover cars, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gather spell, which causes the objects on the screen to basically hover around some fixed gravity point or something like that, and you can throw them at stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a full-size video recorder now, and also drivable RC toys.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any other last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyone?
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bueller?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have any really good, fuzzy last-news story of the night, so sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that brings us to the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: April Fool's Day kind of screwed everything up this week news-wise, so what can you do?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the end of the show, and that's no joke.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Miklatov, thanks for joining us, even if it was for only half the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have fun with your Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll try.
[SPEAKER_08]: May you go through the same hell I went through with the groundbreaking... I can only hope.
[SPEAKER_08]: Add me to your friends list, OMG.
[SPEAKER_08]: I already did.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know you did.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just being stupid.
[SPEAKER_00]: May all your camera angles be nice and joyous.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, may all your camera angles not be like Kingdom Hearts, okay?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did I let you have a final thought?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is your final thought?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, what's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_07]: My final thought is I may be buying a laptop this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought is buy an iBook.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know you want one.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to have my iMac very soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's two against one, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not buying an iMac.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I'm keeping my nice PC laptop.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like I said on a previous episode, I'm bi when it comes to computers.
[SPEAKER_08]: I use both.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then the next one will be my Linux box.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, thank you guys so much for tuning into and listening to Orange Lounge Radio and supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: We love getting emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: We love our chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys in the chat room are so awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish I could just reach out and give you all a big hug or a handshake.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, Rob.
[SPEAKER_00]: We love email.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_00]: We do.
I check it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, flood the mailbag so DarkSakura has work to do this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, I actually do work at my job now.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're done with the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: So until next week, this is Sky for my co-hosts, DarkSakura, Loki, special guest Miklatov, saying have a good week.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_09]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!