[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_08]: And we're back here live on Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 180 for this April the 9th of 2006.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki would like to begin this segment with a small correction, wouldn't you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I would.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, about those numbers about the Revolution launch titles, I was a little off.
[SPEAKER_09]: A little?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I was a bit off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, coming from Game Front, the true number is 20 titles, one-third of which are said to be developed by Nintendo themselves.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: I was close.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had the number 20 in there and there's a percentage.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which means Orange Lounge Radio will be pudding free for those of you that listen to Part A. Thankfully.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_06]: My dignity is spared another day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Still better coverage than IGN.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I say that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can address those cards and letters too.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is your email?
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't have an Orange Lounge Radio account, do you?
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll get you one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remind me to hook you up with one after the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll hook you up with a Spike at Orange Lounge Radio email.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll take you up on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, did anybody notice in the first segment of tonight's show, not a single story on Sony PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because everything's been quiet on the PS3 front this week, pretty much, hasn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there was one little thing, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically, according to some French radio show, there was an interview done where it was leaked out, I guess, that the PlayStation 3 would be somewhere between the price point of 499, 599 euros in the UK.
[SPEAKER_09]: So everyone's speculating, oh my god, it's going to be $650, $700 some dollars here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not the case.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, a lot of times the price point over there, they will get screwed over because their price point will be... For example, for the Xbox 360, I believe their price point is €399 for the premium system, whereas we were $399.
[SPEAKER_09]: So maybe €499 to €599.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm thinking more about €499.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's probably going to be the price point in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think $4.99 is a reasonable price point for the US too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought it was very interesting though because this news kind of came out early in the week and A, people ran with this saying that PS3 price announced and first off I was thinking, okay, no, price was not announced.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some guy made an inadvertent comment that may or may not even be the truth.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I know that this guy was a Sony exec or whatever but, you know, I just, still, it's not,
[SPEAKER_08]: With all due respect to Europe, Europe is not where the magic is happening right now in regards to PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: The magic will happen there soon enough, but that's not where the systems are being made.
[SPEAKER_08]: Had this slip come from Sony in Japan, maybe I would have been a little more, you know, apt to believe it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then how people suddenly made this direct conversion of euros to dollars.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're right, and completely disregarded the fact that usually the UK folks get screwed when it comes to price.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm very sorry, you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just the fact.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys kind of get screwed, so sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not always, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sometimes they get games around the same price.
[SPEAKER_08]: But a lot of times they do get screwed.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that means that usually the amount that we pay in dollars, they pay in euros.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's usually about the conversion.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I think you're right.
[SPEAKER_08]: $4.99 to $5.99 is more of a realistic point.
[SPEAKER_08]: But again, we've got the Revolution and the 360 to compete with.
[SPEAKER_08]: And unless you can sell me that I cannot live without Blu-ray...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Gameplay, eh, it's not the same.
[SPEAKER_09]: We don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: We don't really know anything yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're just talking about the titles that they've announced so far.
[SPEAKER_09]: They don't seem, it's the same game Microsoft's playing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's make the games prettier and not change anything because, hey, it worked before, so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but take a game like Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oblivion could not have been done on the regular Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's so vast and it's so pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that's really a next-gen game right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you spend much time with Morrowind?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a lot, but I'd seen it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It felt the same game, just not as pretty.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if we're talking about gameplay, I wouldn't argue that there's a big difference there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oblivion feels really big.
[SPEAKER_08]: And with everything that they're saying you can do with it and just all the vastness.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, one part I didn't see in the other game was I didn't see character creation.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it as thorough in that game?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: I seem to recall that it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: A good minute, but I do think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure people in our chat room will be able to help out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: OrangeLaunchRadio.com, click on chat if you want.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_08]: But who knows what that could mean for Xbox's future.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, what do you think about that news?
[SPEAKER_09]: Eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Microsoft's just absorbing companies now, so... Spike?
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel similarly about this, about how I feel about their acquisition of Rare.
[SPEAKER_06]: They make one pretty trophy title a game every year or two.
[SPEAKER_06]: But overall, I don't see Anti-Lionhead as a big industry-changing, challenging force.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it only takes a handful of those trophy games to sell your system, asks Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a very valid point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, I don't really count Fable as a very great game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fable...
[SPEAKER_08]: The only reason Fable was so freaking great was because there wasn't anything else like it on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go over to PlayStation 2, GameCube, you got plenty of games like Fable.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although, to Fable's credit, it was a little more expansive than most games in the way that you could control your character's fate.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not that we hadn't seen it before.
[SPEAKER_08]: but it was so fluid and it was such a turning point of the game, I don't think you really saw that in the other systems.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you're right, the gameplay itself was not, I mean it was kind of button mashing was the fighting, it wasn't anything that revolutionary, but it still was really the only game like it on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: for that reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I would argue the same thing is happening with Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think the only reason Oblivion is doing so phenomenally is it's got no competition on the 360 right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is no game even remotely close to what Oblivion is like.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't get me wrong, I'm sure it's a great game that would be good even if there was competition, but still, I think the only reason why I see half my friends less playing this game is because I know my friends.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of them are into role-playing games.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's nothing else for them to play on 360 right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just my thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's go on to another story.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, what's this about the Xbox Live Arcade?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's getting some new games, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Starting off here with Cloning Clyde, which sounds pretty weird, but basically they're keying this as it's going to be a completely unique 3D adventure and puzzle game that may bring a new meaning to the word schizophrenic.
[SPEAKER_09]: So,
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically, Clyde was an ordinary but slightly dim guy before Dupliclone Inc.
[SPEAKER_09]: paid him $20 to take part in a cloning experiment.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I guess, you know, things go crazy from there.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so, yeah, it's going to be coming to the live arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is made by a company called Ninja Bee, who you might remember did Outpost Cloaky X, which is a pretty big hit on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, check it out when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Geometry Wars Crystal Quest
[SPEAKER_08]: Not totally, but very similar.
[SPEAKER_08]: And same with Feeding Friends.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, no, because you don't have a gun in Feeding Friends, but just, I don't know, that whole dodging thing feels... It feels a little similar.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was it Mutant Storm?
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't even played that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's also Robotron.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Robotron's a classic.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, a classic classic.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can't... Yeah, but I'm saying that they're all similar.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not saying that... Robotron's more like Smash TV, if anything else, but both were made by the same company, so you could almost say that Smash TV in a effed up way is like
[SPEAKER_08]: Robotron.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe I'm just crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: We mentioned in Part A that you can get brand new outfits for Cameo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_08]: You can dress them up as Orchid and Killer Instinct characters and all those other things.
[SPEAKER_08]: But also one thing that should be noted about Cameo, they just patched their co-op mode, and now you can do the online co-op play with Cameo.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I believe new achievements come with this as well, but here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because Cameo has already hit their limit of 1,000 achievement points, now there are zero-point achievements that you can get in Cameo with this new patch, is what I'm hearing.
[SPEAKER_08]: You get achievements, but they're not worth anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's dead to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, some people really wanted to do co-op and cameo.
[SPEAKER_09]: What they should do then is still give you the co-op achievements.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who cares if you play over live?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just do the same co-op achievements that they have in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just, you know, now you can play live or local.
[SPEAKER_08]: And HitStun says the online co-op patch is free, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, that is true.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is free.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So enjoy the free things while you can.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure as soon as you put in Cameo, I haven't patched mine yet, but I'm sure as soon as you put in Cameo, it'll say, an upgrade for this game is now available.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_08]: And then it'll just patch its way onto your hard drive.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is assuming you have a hard drive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then we can be underwhelmed with people on the internet at the same time.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what just made that made me think of though?
[SPEAKER_08]: What happens if you don't have a hard drive?
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you just screwed?
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you gonna have to patch this game every time?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you can maybe download the patch to your memory card.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I guess that's a good point.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess you could save it to your memory card.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, how are you going to play anything with a memory card?
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Memory card was just useless.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just something that they put out there and say, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, there's an option to buying the... No, you can take your memory card to an Xbox 360 kiosk and get Uber special downloads.
[SPEAKER_08]: That don't work!
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, where the fuck is my goddamn burnout card that they promised me months ago that I downloaded from the kiosk and then we go to play Burnout?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, by the way, it doesn't work!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, did we say working car?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't believe we did.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: You're fucked.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love setting him off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stupid kiosk thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why'd I spend the money on that stupid card?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, what's next on the news?
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the Michigan game law was ruled unconstitutional.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, we didn't see that coming.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um,
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, basically thrown out because, yeah, it's unconstitutional, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was the Michigan law like the California law, or what was the deal there?
[SPEAKER_09]: To be honest, I don't know if it was very similar or not.
[SPEAKER_09]: I imagine they're probably pretty close.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: They really shouldn't try to regulate the game sales and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it was, as it summed up, intended to restrict the sale of certain games to minors.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they say that was unconstitutional and can't be implemented.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it sounds pretty similar to what we had going on in California here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, I think that they should be able to sell porn to minors too now because it's unconstitutional.
[SPEAKER_06]: Children have the right to porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you no dignity?
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you no dignity?
[SPEAKER_08]: Xbox Live Friendless Notifier
[SPEAKER_08]: and you can even have it in a little task bar and it'll actually alert you when people sign on and offline.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess what it's doing is it's kind of borrowing from exactly what Xbox Live, or I'm sorry, Xbox.com does, but it sort of delivers that news to your desktop.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can see when, you know, if you're stalking someone, you can see right when they come online.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: So like I'd be able to see if Loki's online from my computer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I'm too lazy to access Xbox.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm surprised Microsoft didn't... I think the most surprising thing about this story is that someone beat Microsoft to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think if I were Microsoft right now, I'd be wanting to buy this software from this guy or acquire this guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, they would just want to sue him.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they're Microsoft and they can't... Why would you sue this guy?
[SPEAKER_08]: He wrote a practical, useful application that...
[SPEAKER_08]: GK128 in the chatroom says, I have 360 friends, the program.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's cool, but it hogs RAM.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it might be a little bit of a memory hog.
[SPEAKER_08]: So have a lot of RAM if you're going to be using this program.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know, also, it's a program that has, you know, it's written by, you know, a fan, essentially.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's probably not optimized yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's a first release, it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if this guy decides to continue to upgrade this, it might get a little better in that regard.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: GK128 would like to point out it uses 63 megabytes of RAM currently.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, you have some music game news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: In the groove, PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: As I've been stating before, this game is merely Stepmania.
[SPEAKER_09]: And now, like Stepmania, you can put your own songs in it for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, of course, the tools have been out there already to unpack everything that's in the groove for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: and actually dump that stuff to your hard drive so you can play the official songs because they're just Step Mania files.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, now they have the tools to repack it so you can actually put whatever songs you want in there and be able to burn it to a disc and either play it with any sort of tools that you use to play backup discs on a PlayStation 2 or hacks or work around or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, I guess that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, one of the reasons why, you know, I don't understand why people pay for Step Mania, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: Now you can and I'm just not surprised.
[SPEAKER_09]: I knew this was going to come one of these days and
[SPEAKER_09]: Now that's available, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: You get to play all your songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you like the In The Groove songs, go ahead and play the In The Groove songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you like DDR... Because you put DDR songs in In The Groove?
[SPEAKER_09]: They had it.
[SPEAKER_09]: DDR, all the DDR songs, In The Groove 2, and In The Groove songs, all in one disc.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: They had all this stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you just download this from the website, burn it, and ready to go?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, no, it's not available on the website.
[SPEAKER_09]: You've got to dig for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unfortunately, I cannot give out where it is, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: Your local Bomani downloading ISO place will probably have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: BitTorrent, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: So look for it and have fun, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Follow-up to a story we were talking about a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember the town in Ohio that got slammed on April Fool's?
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, we may not have done this on the last podcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: This may have been my spinoff show I did on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_08]: I talked about this story about the girls who played the prank in the town and had little question mark blocks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: We're not thinking about the consequences of their actions in this day and age.
[SPEAKER_08]: Most people don't know what a question mark block reference is.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you're right, they probably think about Batman or something, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm going to blow up this streetlight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Al-Qaeda will strike us in our streetlights.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my, now the FBI is going to monitor this program.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_06]: You jerk.
[SPEAKER_06]: I kind of agree, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an iconic symbol.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't help but think...
[SPEAKER_06]: 3 out of 3 people in this room are going to know what that question mark is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Back to the OLR statistics magic, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: So 100% of Americans know what a question mark block is and shouldn't have been alarmed, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: But really, the percentage must be over 50%.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't help but believe that this... Not if you're an old person.
[SPEAKER_06]: So your grandmother wouldn't know what a question mark block is?
[SPEAKER_08]: Unless my grandma happened to be old granny hardcore, probably not.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, my grandma would have no idea what a question mark block is.
[SPEAKER_08]: She would have no idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: She would probably think about Frank Gorshin from Batman.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Riddler.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was my Riddler impersonation.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was great, huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: I worked on that all day.
[SPEAKER_08]: I stand corrected.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe we won't be in so much trouble if we find a cure for cancer, right Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, in the meantime, though, you can play a game called Remission, where you can blow away cancer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, in this game, basically, you play a micro-robot by the name of, I believe, Roxy.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you are basically in the body and destroying these rapidly multiplying rogue cells.
[SPEAKER_09]: And basically, it's something that they've
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of done to help cancer patients cope with their illness while educating them and increasing players' sense of control over their circumstances.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unfortunately, though, it should be mentioned that this game does not cure cancer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just to clear up anything, because there's a lot of stupid people out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what it kind of sounds like to me?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of like...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like that old game that would be like the tooth fighter, the cavity fighting game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember I had this on Commodore 64, and you were like, you carried around the giant toothbrush, and you had to wipe the plaque, or you'd get attacked by the little cavity monsters.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what this sounds like to me, except instead of teeth, it's cancer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, and so cancer patients will get to play crappy games now, as if they weren't tortured enough about the fact that their cancer might not be operable.
[SPEAKER_09]: Great.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura is not here tonight as we mentioned earlier in the program.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's feeling sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: She has Asian Bird Flu.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm teasing.
[SPEAKER_08]: She doesn't have Asian Bird Flu, but she's sick and we hope she feels better soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's usually in charge of the mailbox and this would be the part where we would go to the mailbag
[SPEAKER_08]: Mailbag at OrangeLawnTrader.com However, I haven't dug through the mailbag this week, so I have no idea what's in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, I have looked at the MySpace, and we got some questions on MySpace.
[SPEAKER_08]: People who didn't realize they can send it over to Mailbag at OrangeLawnTrader.com So I'm going to go ahead and read a question that we got on MySpace.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this question comes to us from Joey.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, Joey!
[SPEAKER_08]: Joey says, Hey, I just got through part B of this week's podcast, meaning last week, 179.
[SPEAKER_08]: The part where you guys talked about the Genesis got me to my closet and I pulled out my Genesis 3, the slim line of the Genesis, if you will.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then I realized the only game I could find was my Street Fighter 2 Special Champions Edition and Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was hoping to restart my collection and hoping you could help me out by giving me a short list of good games to look for.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now I know all about the Sonics and ToeJam and Earls, so maybe if you guys knew some non-mainstream games, that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, do you remember the name of that new Genesis game being released?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not sure if I heard about it from you guys, but this is the only show I can think of that would have cool news like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry about the length of this, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a problem, Joey.
[SPEAKER_08]: Appreciate the Myspace message.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_08]: Joey, the name of the game you're trying to think about on the Genesis is called Beggar Prince.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was the new game that's being released.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we did bring that up a few weeks ago on this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: And actually, if you want to visit one of our buddies over on allgames.com, Bobby Blackwolf, visit his site at allgames.com slash podcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: And actually, I think he's also at bobbyblackwolfshow.com now.
[SPEAKER_08]: He had an interview with the people that made Beggar Prince.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a really long interview.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you want to hear all about Genesis development in this day and age,
[SPEAKER_08]: Look back in his archives about six weeks or so, and he had an interview a while back, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: As far as non-standard Genesis games, well, you didn't mention Phantasy Star, my friend, so if you're into RPGs, you don't want to miss the Phantasy Star series.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a shame Jamie's not here, because she loves the obscure Genesis titles.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you think of anything, Spike?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, could we start with Obscura and work our way down?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we could go for a good hour here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, try me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Name some titles that this kid needs on his Genesis.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, I would strongly recommend, let's see, Decap Attack.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the funny thing is, if you've never played it, I mean, it's a fairly cartoony game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, yeah, you're a mummy zombie guy throwing your head at people, but it's done in a comical style of, like, Rise Star, which I would also recommend.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rise Star, Gunstar Heroes.
[SPEAKER_09]: What was that one that was, uh... It was, like, in a comic book.
[SPEAKER_08]: Comics Zone?
[SPEAKER_08]: Comics Zone, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gunstar Heroes, by the way, was an excellent addition to that list, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I...
[SPEAKER_06]: I highly recommend it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, if we're going even with, you know, kind of the standard games, don't let yourself forget the Echo games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't let yourself forget Eternal Champions.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you like substandard 2D graphics in a kind of subpar fighting game that's so cheesy you can't help but laugh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Comments from our chatroom here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some suggestions from the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Legend of Zaku suggests After Burner 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ranma suggests Kid Chameleon.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Pooeater suggests Alex Kidd.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wonder Boy and Monster World.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wonderboy and Monster World.
[SPEAKER_06]: My best Genesis.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jamie would say Alex Kidd and Shinobi World.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you even get that in this country?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_08]: There are some suggestions for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, a couple quick, quick emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: My sister sent me an email because I think she's listening to the program or something, but my sister sent me an email, Dana, and she says, Can you tell me what's wrong when I try to DDR and my foot won't work?
[SPEAKER_08]: I try to dance, but when I go fast, my foot quits working.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I really like your Japanese pop.
[SPEAKER_08]: My sister writes her emails like a seven-year-old.
[SPEAKER_08]: Might I share?
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're playing too much DDR and your foot stops working, stop playing DDR for a couple days and then go back.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should never push yourself too much on DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're feeling stamina, soreness issues, any of that stuff, seriously take a break.
[SPEAKER_08]: One other quick email.
[SPEAKER_08]: This came to us from Justin M.,
[SPEAKER_08]: This came to my email box, not the normal mailbag.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if you've heard yet, but they're making a movie of DOA.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: It comes out this August.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome or awful?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, got to disagree with you there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, we know the Dead or Alive movie is coming, but as to the fact that it looks awesome, I suppose if you're into tits and ass, it'll be great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or in Charlie's Angels.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, the first Charlie's Angels was good.
[SPEAKER_08]: The second Charlie's Angels was...
[SPEAKER_06]: Second Charlie's Angels If you believe that, I'd like to sell you this Alone in the Dark DVD I have Stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Be nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Be nice to the people who email me.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, if you have an email you want to send us, send it over to mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura will be back next week to read those emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: And yes, we will be doing a show next week on Easter Sunday because we have nothing better to do because our families don't love us and didn't invite us over.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm teasing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mine did.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mine did too, but I don't know about your house, but Easter dinner at my house is like 2 o'clock, so it leaves me plenty of time to do this program.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cancelled games?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, unfortunately, if you're, you know, really looking forward to spending the night on the internet with people and having virtual sex, think again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Spend the night, the MMO that was going to be put out, basically the sex MMO, cancelled!
[SPEAKER_09]: Difficulty raising funds, I guess, is the reason for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's on hold indefinitely until they can make the money to pay the virtual prostitutes that are going to be in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Imagine that.
[SPEAKER_08]: The sex game couldn't get funding.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there was much rejoicing.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: I disagree.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why is it that we have a bazillion violent games, yet when we look at sex-related games, we have the guy game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Playboy Mansion.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, it's...
[SPEAKER_08]: I would like to see a sexual game that's not super crappy.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you think this was that game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, maybe not, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think we should be frowning on it just because it's a sex game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, there's plenty of violent games out there that are okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but you have to understand, murder okay, sex not okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sex gets companies sued.
[SPEAKER_08]: How do you make the people to murder?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sex.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Where's the logic here?
[SPEAKER_08]: Shouldn't it be murder bad, sex good?
[SPEAKER_09]: What was hot coffee?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sex game.
[SPEAKER_09]: What was Grand Theft Auto?
[SPEAKER_09]: Murder game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Murder game okay, sex game not okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I agree with your point, but I'm way more comfortable leveling with the party of MMO players than I am cybering with them with these 3D avatars.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, people do it anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your guild, obviously, in World of Warcraft is not as cool as mine, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: My guild is called World of Wank and they're a great time.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm totally joking.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope you people don't think I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_08]: But don't you think people do this in MMOs as it is?
[SPEAKER_08]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: The roleplay servers?
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think that is?
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think that's a front for?
[SPEAKER_08]: Roleplay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what Sims Online was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's exactly what Sims Online turned into.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was one giant Vegas.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you are a fan of music games...
[SPEAKER_08]: This story is kind of old.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why is this on the show roll?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I forgot to post it last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: You may have already heard this, but Red Octane CEO Kelly Sumner revealed last week that there are products in development, other products in development.
[SPEAKER_08]: This guy used to be with Take-Two Interactive Europe, but now he's with Red Octane.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can't tell you what the games are and when they're coming, but we kind of believe it's probably not just the Guitar Hero sequels.
[SPEAKER_08]: Perhaps this is a rival to Konami's Bomani brand?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: Could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I think Beat Mania would have been a good game for them to compete with.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think they'd still do it?
[SPEAKER_08]: You say rival, I say cheap knockoff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, wait a minute though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe when you look at In The Groove DDR, I see your point there, despite the fact that it's still controversial.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Guitar Hero vs. Guitar Freaks, I don't think that was a cheap knockoff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Guitar Hero was original enough and did a lot of... Obviously, most of the critics out there, 99% of them feel the same way I do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, because 99% of the critics out there, they don't know the history of the music game series out there and they also don't do the research.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Death to them all!
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a cool game because it's new to us, the US and stuff, but to be honest, when these next few games come out, or the next sequel or whatever, it's just going to be like a whole Guitar Freaks thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, granted, I'm not saying Guitar Freaks is innovative because it's been the same damn game since Fifth Mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've been just cookie-cuttering the whole thing along the way, but still.
[SPEAKER_08]: Spike, you have Adam first, then I'll go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I definitely prefer Guitar Freaks to Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do not like Guitar Hero, but as a musician, I will say that playing Guitar Hero is way closer to playing an actual instrument.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think that in that way, it's actually a superior game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even if I don't prefer it myself, I think that on a technical level, it's a much more impressive work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, here's my deal, and I'm taking the music out of this equation.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not even considering the music in Guitar Freaks and music in Guitar Hero, because that's a matter of opinion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just putting the game engines side by side.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guitar Hero has way more of the fun factor in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guitar Freaks, turn it on, pick your song, go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Turn it on, pick your song, go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guitar Hero has that whole like, oh, you're in a band and you have the shops where you can upgrade your guitars and unlock the songs and you do the whammy and there's a crowd there and they're yelling for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whereas Guitar Freaks is, here, look at this choppy animation while you play your song.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot to be said there that makes it more of a party game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, so you upgrade your guitar, which does what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it changes the appearance of your guitar in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whoop-a-dee-doo.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a crowd!
[SPEAKER_08]: What does Guitar Freaks have?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_09]: It doesn't have any of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has the fact that it was first.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have at it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't call it an original game, call it an improvement of another game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will give you that because when I play Guitar Hero, it really does feel to me like I am playing Guitar Freaks mixed with Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: But with more of the fun factor for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a reason why it's so accessible to people.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't mind it being a good game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate the fact that people are calling it innovative because it's not.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, granted, it may be more realistic to, you know, playing a guitar.
[SPEAKER_09]: Doesn't make it innovative, makes it better, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: And also the fact that people are, you know, kind of basically posing this as an original game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not an original game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It fucking rips off three different games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Puts the best things of them together.
[SPEAKER_09]: Granted, that's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's basically improving on those concepts, but it's not an original game.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I'm just...
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate people calling it original and innovative.
[SPEAKER_09]: Katamari Damacy, that was original.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is not original.
[SPEAKER_08]: Comments from our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: GS191 says the only reason people like Guitar Hero is because of the music.
[SPEAKER_08]: The majority of America does not like the whole techno J-pop theme.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting point there.
[SPEAKER_08]: We also have, let's say, FireBoma says, if you showed critics Guitar Freaks, they'd say it was a rip-off of Guitar Hero at this point in time.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'd agree with you, but that's just, you know, a lot of critics are ignorant.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're ignorant.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you watch, if they decide to release Guitar Freaks over here, people are like, why are they ripping off Guitar Hero?
[SPEAKER_09]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a crappy Guitar Hero knockoff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously, I'm going to fucking beat those people to death is what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if Spike's laughing at the same thing I am, but DarkTetsuya wrote in the chatroom, ignorant, but he capitalized the first three letters of that word, and I'll just let you kind of dream up what he's trying to say there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll leave it to you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then of course our chat room is just going off with what the mystery game could be.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Poo Eater suggests Banjo Freaks, Fireboma suggests Clarinet Hero, DJ Poo Eater, Flute Hero, Hit Stun, Xylophone Hero, Drum Hero says Dark Knight, which I think a lot of us are thinking might be it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: If they're going to rip off Guitar Freaks, why don't they rip off Drum Mania while they're at it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would not be surprised if that's the big surprise game at E3 is Drum Hero or whatever they call it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Spirit Snare would like to point out people in reviews have actually nodded to Guitar Freaks at least once.
[SPEAKER_08]: Depends what site you're reading it from, but you are right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have seen those reviews that have been good enough to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, moving on to a new topic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought this game was already out, but there's a new game coming to the PlayStation 2 and PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fast and the Furious Tokyo Drift
[SPEAKER_08]: Lame!
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, for real?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a Fast and the Furious 3 Tokyo Drift coming out?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't that just initial D the movie?
[SPEAKER_06]: The funny thing is, it doesn't even have Paul Walker.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has a guy who looks like Paul Walker.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought Paul Walker was in that.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Paul Walker is in that movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone was telling me a guy who looks like Paul Walker.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, Paul Walker is in that movie because Paul Walker has no work other than that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it Paul Walker Goes to Tokyo?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that the plot?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: Paul Walker versus the Asian Mafia?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's basically, ooh, the Asian chick who's hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's bring her back and let's bring Paul Walker back because we need somebody from the original series.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe they'll have sex.
[SPEAKER_09]: And yeah, maybe they'll have sex and she'll get all hot and schoolgirl-like.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, too bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: No one's going to miss him.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, does this movie have Vin Diesel in it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, Ranma in our chat room would like to point this out and I'm almost positive he's right here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fast and the Furious was already in the arcade and it was based on the L.A.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rush engine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure it was.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyways, this game is going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's unique about it, well, I'm not sure if it's unique, but it's kind of cool, is they're going to have 500 body kits from authentic manufacturers.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you're actually going to have real upgrade parts.
[SPEAKER_09]: And...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's also going to feature boss races as well as advanced rubber band artificial intelligence systems.
[SPEAKER_09]: I fucking hate goddamn advanced rubber band artificial intelligence systems.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're racing, you're kicking the AI's ass, and all of a sudden, they're going 500 fucking miles to catch up to you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're fucking outracing them... I love it in Initial D because I'm always behind in the race.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll be racing a friend, I'm always behind, and then it totally favors you on the last lap, and then right at the finish line, I get ahead of them, and they're like,
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously, when I'm playing Burnout or something like that, I will have destroyed the car I'm racing as.
[SPEAKER_09]: Racing against one car, and I've already almost slapped the guy, and all of a sudden he's going Mach 7 down this goddamn freeway.
[SPEAKER_09]: They catch up to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I hate that shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyways, this game's coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: PlayStation 2, PSP only.
[SPEAKER_09]: Check it out if it looks good.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: To be honest, it's just going to be another racing game, and
[SPEAKER_09]: Their Midnight Club 3 dub edition remix just came out, what, a few weeks ago?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like 1999.
[SPEAKER_09]: Buy that instead.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't encourage them to make more movies.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't say by... No, no, that's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm saying to the youth of America, do not encourage these people to make Fast and the Furious 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously, who the hell is in this that's, you know, what, the Asian chick now is in this, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Was Vin Diesel in this?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was Paul Walker in this?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ranma in our chatroom is saying, hey, the Fast and the Furious 3 will own, for one reason, Keiko Kirikawa, who is Sailor Mars.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, the only... The Asian chick, as I'm dubbing her, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, she's lending her likeness to other really fun movies like the Dead or Alive movie, which sucks balls, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: You haven't seen it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've seen the trailer, and it sucks balls.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can't judge a movie based off the trailer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, the trailer is fucking, you know, let's rip off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Charlie's Angels 2 I'm trying to think of a movie that had a great trailer that sucked balls Because if that's true, the reverse would be true What's a movie with a great trailer that sucked balls?
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to say Fantastic Four, but I haven't seen it, so I can't really dog on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, how about this?
[SPEAKER_08]: The Transporter 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good call.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Transporter 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about Freddy vs. Jason, maybe?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you know, you see the trailer and you go, that's a fucking great concept.
[SPEAKER_08]: You go and see the movie and you're like, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did I just waste $10 on?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't really rag on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, I mean, you get my point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Freddy vs. Jason was supposed to be cheesy.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the whole point.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it'll be just like Freddy vs. Jason vs. Ash, if they ever do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which I wish they would.
[SPEAKER_09]: Completely off-topic here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Has anyone actually seen XXX2 or whatever?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, why would I do that?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's great, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't seen XXX1.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have this hilarious thing, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's this bonus thing where they're talking about what happened to the original XXX character and Vin Diesel's character.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the way they've done it, they've shot... Every shot you see of XXX is just the back of him because it's not Vin Diesel.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they kill him off really bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was that episode of South Park where they spliced all of Isaac Hayes' lines together to get Shaft.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, children!
[SPEAKER_08]: Would you like to make love?
[SPEAKER_08]: And that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: New story, please.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Namco has new... Namco Bandai, I should say, has new plug-and-play controllers they're going to be releasing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's called Let's TV Play Classic.
[SPEAKER_08]: These controllers will plug directly into your TV and have four playable games, two old ones, two new ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: Namco Nostalgia has the retro Dragon Buster and new Dragon Buster 100.
[SPEAKER_08]: Retail price is just under $30 US.
[SPEAKER_08]: When I'm curious, are they going to have some of those other Namco things they've upgraded?
[SPEAKER_08]: I see Mappy, and it looks like Xevious on one of these box arts there, so there might be some kind of cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, before you start thanking Namco for this kind of stuff...
[SPEAKER_09]: Obviously, Namco is putting out the Fast and the Furious game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, reserve your hate.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well said.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, it's tax season, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who missed the memo?
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, Capcom in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, either...
[SPEAKER_09]: They failed to report approximately 5.12 billion yen.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's about 44 million dollars in the US.
[SPEAKER_09]: And over the course of six years, the penalty is about 1.2 billion yen or 10 million dollars in the US.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so because of this, actually they delayed Dead Rising.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was one of the games that's being delayed right now because of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, um, yeah, it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_06]: Slight oversight there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, we have the file taxes?
[SPEAKER_06]: That seems like a reasonable mistake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were just talking about Namco a minute ago, and there's an announcement kind of circulating this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Old school Namco games are soon going to be available on Xbox Live Arcade because...
[SPEAKER_08]: you know, making that Namco collection that they released on Xbox making it backwards compatible just wouldn't be good enough let's milk some more money out of this franchise and let's put these games on Xbox Live so people can whore gamer points even more Pac-Man and Galaga are on their way to Xbox Live Arcade
[SPEAKER_08]: Complete with leaderboards!
[SPEAKER_08]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_08]: And achievements!
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't possibly fathom what achievements will be available on Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: You ate a ghost!
[SPEAKER_08]: Ding!
[SPEAKER_08]: 20 points!
[SPEAKER_08]: And yet you're gonna buy them, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably, because I'm a sad, sad man.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, hasn't Pac-Man been on like every system?
[SPEAKER_08]: Ever?
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this really isn't much of a surprise, honestly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, just the fact that it's coming to the Xbox Live Arcade, I guess, is a surprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: But notice how Namco Museum, or actually, no, I think the Namco Museum, actually, I might be wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it is backwards compatible.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that 50th one, I think I do remember seeing it on the backwards compatibility list.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think you can play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Doesn't matter anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you had a Ridge Racer, you could play it anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a very good point.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they want you to pay $5 or maybe even $10, who knows, for leaderboards and what have you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, here's an idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about a port of the Pac-Man Versus like you had on the Game Boy Advance that you could hook into the GameCube where you could play it on Xbox Live and some of your friends are the ghosts?
[SPEAKER_08]: and you're the Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, wouldn't that be a lot better?
[SPEAKER_08]: Wouldn't that make my money more worthwhile?
[SPEAKER_08]: How about this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Instead of just porting over the original Pac-Man, how about you port over one of the Pac-Man remakes that they have, you know, where the graphics are at least a little bit better?
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where, you know, it might utilize the widescreen, you know, like it did on the PSP, but no.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, we have to port over the original one and put some art on the side there because, yeah, it's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ranma in the chatroom says, Fuck Pac-Man vs. I want Pac-Mania.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want them both.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why don't we just get like a small Pac-Man anthology there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: For five bucks for old games, come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can give me some other old Pac-Mania.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can give me Pac-Mania.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can give me Pac-Man 91 or whatever it was when they did the souped up versions.
[SPEAKER_08]: Give me some of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sigh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, wait, first I want to mention this.
[SPEAKER_08]: GamerPoints.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was reading the Xbox forums this week and I saw some person say that they had rented Top Spin 2 and that they had figured out a way for them and their friend to play on Xbox Live and whore up the GamerPoints.
[SPEAKER_08]: by, because if you quit out of a match, you still get credit for playing the match.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it was really easy to unlock the 25 and 50 matches gamer points.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it ethical to do this, to cheat your way to getting these gamer points?
[SPEAKER_08]: How about renting games, getting the points, or basically renting games just for the sole purpose of milking out as many points as you can.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that ethical?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, renting games, I wouldn't say it's not ethical.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say that you just, you know, probably could be doing better things with your time and money.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're playing the games to actually get the points correctly, then that's your prerogative if you want to go and rent these really crappy games to get the points out of them.
[SPEAKER_09]: As far as cheating to get points, I don't think it's right, but I do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't go as far as quitting games and stuff like that to cheat, but for example, Far Cry has cheat codes, and Ubisoft, they let you get achievement points with the cheat codes, and they have the same thing with Ghost Recon.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's their own damn fault that they didn't program it in there where you can't get the achievement with those.
[SPEAKER_09]: The outfit has cheat codes, but you don't get achievement points if you have them on.
[SPEAKER_09]: The outfit sucks, by the way, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's their own fault for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I guess it's wrong that they're cheating, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't see a problem with them or any games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I agree with your point.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's renting the games to get the points that's so bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've borrowed games from you, and I've worked my way to getting achievement points, but I would never cheat the system to do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That whole quitting in and out thing, that was just stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm, you know, if I notice that, yeah, I'm going to get 10 points if I do this special little thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe I'll go to, it's like in Geometry Wars, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's going to sit there for 60 seconds dodging all the monsters?
[SPEAKER_08]: You wouldn't usually think to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, hey, it was worth 10 points.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll give it a try.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, it's a little bit of a challenge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Makes, you know, a little task.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of like a mission.
[SPEAKER_08]: I sort of think of it that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think there's anything unethical about doing that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, you can't really rent a game like Geometry Wars, but I think that theory applies.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're going to rent games and accomplish as much as you can, I think that's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think when you resort to cheating and those things, I don't think that's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Specifically for the purpose of getting gamer points.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, if you're cheating your way through the game, then whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've already made that decision.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I do think Xbox should figure out a way to disable gamer points when you're cheating.
[SPEAKER_08]: My point... But if the developers left it in there, that's their own downfall.
[SPEAKER_09]: My point with Far Cry, for example, the game's hard enough even when you are cheating.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just added fun for my... They don't have an infinite health code.
[SPEAKER_09]: They just have infinite ammo and infinite, like, feral or your adrenaline or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's still really fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's still really hard.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it just makes it so where I don't have to go and try to collect ammo and
[SPEAKER_09]: Fireboma wants to know, what do the gamer points do?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing!
[SPEAKER_08]: They really aren't anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's an internet penis thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: The more points you have, the bigger your internet penis is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, even if you're a girl, you know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm talking about that whole, you know, look at me, I'm cool because I have, you know, 50 million gamer points.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's cool too.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ PooEater would like to know, is it virtual boobs for the girl gamers?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, Roz in the chatroom says, my e-penis, hers is 12 miles long on a cold day.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's quite the impressive e-penis there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, what was the other comment in here I saw?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, GS191 said, great, point whoring.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's next, the achievement point police?
[SPEAKER_08]: Head on over to the Xbox Live forums.
[SPEAKER_08]: There are some people on there that have their panties in a bunch that people are cheating their way to getting these points.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to open up the Skype line very, very soon over at our website, www.orangeloundtrader.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Click on Interact With Us, and you can call us on the Skype line to talk about anything that you want to here this last month.
[SPEAKER_08]: A few minutes of the show open forum, but first, a couple quick notes.
[SPEAKER_08]: First off, the other contest we promised we were going to do tonight, we are also doing a giveaway tonight for Amped 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is the action-packed snowboarding game for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, Loki, you actually own this game, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to be honest, I haven't played this yet, but Loki, you own this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I owned it, sold it, bought it back because I liked it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, uh...
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you do in this game?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's snowboarding?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's snowboarding.
[SPEAKER_09]: The only thing that turned me off about it is because it didn't have live support because it would have been pretty sweet live.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's your snowboarding game type thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's kind of cool about it is they have hang gliding in there as well, snowmobiles, sleds, which are pretty cool, and the sleds are fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: and it's just a really weird game.
[SPEAKER_09]: The cutscenes are done with weird comics, sock puppets.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I see a little pink bunny on the back of the box there.
[SPEAKER_08]: That has my interest right there.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's really acid trippy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It reminds me of MTV2 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like Wonder Shosen or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, very Wonder Shosen-ish.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: Or if you're feeling like a cheap bastard, you can win one right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just send an email to snow at orangeloungeradio.com and that's all you have to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're not going to make you name anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just send an email to snow at orangeloungeradio.com and say, I want to win.
[SPEAKER_09]: Plus, if you're an achievement point hoard, there are some pretty easy achievement points in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's got a terrain editor, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: But hey, if you don't have a 360, I was actually at Fry's today and they had some there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, they're making their way around now.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can get a 360 now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so just to clarify, some folks in our chatroom are saying, is this for PS2?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, this is Xbox 360 Amp 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amp 2 and Amp 1?
[SPEAKER_08]: Those are Xbox, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think you get those on PS2.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's made by 2K Games, who also made Top Spin 2, which I talked about earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we can't wait to give stuff away next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be pulling for not just that, but the 24 game we gave away in Part A. And if you missed it, listen to Part A, because we'll tell you how to win the 24 game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, Lara Croft, I bashed the Tomb Raider demo earlier in the show, but at least there's some good news coming Lara Croft's way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, Lara Croft, don't ask me why, I really don't know why.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's earned a Guinness World Record as the most successful video game heroine.
[SPEAKER_09]: To which I ask, what about Mrs. Pac-Man?
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: What kind of a fucking record is that anyways?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not a record.
[SPEAKER_09]: She didn't eat the most chili dogs in the world.
[SPEAKER_09]: She didn't grow the longest carrot.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's just a fake person.
[SPEAKER_09]: in a game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so, okay, over the past 10 years, Lord Croft has sold, they've sold over 28 million games worldwide in the Tomb Raider series.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's appeared on stage with U2 and covers over 200 magazines and more recently, of course, Angelina Jolie put out two really awful movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: And
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and they have even over, it's a $1 billion industry with items from lunchboxes, soft drinks, motor vehicles, and receiving the Lord Croft brand treatment.
[SPEAKER_09]: What kind of fucking vehicle has Tomb Raider edition or something like that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I have not heard of that, but.
[SPEAKER_08]: All that news in the world did not make that demo any better, I'm sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I have to ask, though?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is Guinness Book losing its edge?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, are they just letting anyone come into this book nowadays?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, even fake people.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I can understand if someone did a speed run through Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_08]: Could we get a world record for something?
[SPEAKER_08]: How about most Guinness drank on a podcast?
[SPEAKER_08]: We might be able to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll join in for that one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, well, once again, I am sitting around playing Advance Crack after being sick for all of last week, which is why I didn't call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you get Jamie sick?
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well, what did you call in to talk to us about tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Was one of our stories you have some feedback to or anything?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, we could talk about my wonderful e-penis if you'd like.
[SPEAKER_01]: It actually has a name and a holiday.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was actually going to suggest, because I remember you were mentioning about your large e-penis earlier.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it appropriate for me to be saying that girls who have a lot of achievement points on Xbox Live or other types of online accomplishments have an e-penis, or is that sexist?
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just making sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's absolutely acceptable.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mine has a name, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_01]: I call it General Grant.
[SPEAKER_08]: General Grant.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why do you call your EP-ness General Grant?
[SPEAKER_01]: It all started one night.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it was actually March 29th, which is our made-up holiday.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I just came up with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just thought of the name and...
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, there's some guys out there that name their, you know, I ain't talking about E, okay, they name their real deal, and usually it's just because, now I don't, sorry, but usually it's just, you know, because they think of it one random night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe when they're high or something, I don't know, but it comes to them in a dream, and suddenly it has a name.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can understand that.
[SPEAKER_08]: SpiritSnare would like to point out in our chat room, you named your e-penis, you win the podcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Gizm would like to know, or Gizm, I hope it's not Gizm, that might be bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gizm says, sorry buddy, sorry, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: What am I listening to?
[SPEAKER_08]: Ha, ha, ha.
[SPEAKER_08]: You won the show and I just lost it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Roz, anything else on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, Advance Wars.
[SPEAKER_01]: Holy shit, it's so fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're still playing that game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you ever going to put it down and maybe try some Kingdom Hearts 2?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe I'll stop for a while and play more Phoenix Wright, but I don't think I'll move from those two.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, well Phoenix Wright is a good game too.
[SPEAKER_01]: The thing with Kingdom Hearts is that my PS2 is dead.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, really, really dead.
[SPEAKER_08]: In a couple short months, the PS3 will be out, and then the PS2 is bound to get a price cut.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's probably a good thing for me, because my PS2 is dead, and I miss playing Akaji.
[SPEAKER_08]: Roz, you should beg and plead maybe our chatters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe they'll take up a collection for a new PS2 for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Offer to show them General Grant.
[SPEAKER_01]: Please, General Grant wants a PS2.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Roz, I've got to let you go so we can get to another call, but thank you so much for calling in, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're getting hammered tonight, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not going to be able to get to everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Slam that door.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, this is Spirit Snare.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, Spirit Snare.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why did you have to shut the door there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Were you afraid somebody was going to hear me?
[SPEAKER_10]: That was my brother, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell him to stop being a brat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, whatchamacallit, about Guitar Hero being innovative.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, um, I was actually surprised that you didn't, um, you guys didn't, like, you guys weren't outraged, like, um, whatchamacallit, back when it was announced over at the, um,
[SPEAKER_10]: Over at the Game Developers Conference When Guitar Hero was first announced at E3?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, when Guitar Hero was announced as being the most innovative at the GDC Oh yeah, what do you think about that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: You remember how Guitar Hero won the prize of most innovative among many other awards Guitar Hero's won this year?
[SPEAKER_08]: He's making a jerk-off motion with his hand there, that's lovely It's retarded, let me put that out there
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think you're in the minority.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think a lot of people think... But I will say this, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think...
[SPEAKER_08]: Their amplitude, frequency should have been given more of those types of honors.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, this is kind of like, okay, you know how the Grammys have a best new artist category every year?
[SPEAKER_08]: And sometimes the person who wins the best new artist, this is actually like their fifth album, but they're just now getting noticed, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of what this reminds me of.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like, okay, it's not really a new concept, but they did it so well this time, we're going to notice them.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's exactly what this is like to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but even though Guitar Freaks was released way ahead of their time, even though it's a mixed-up concept and stuff, that really shouldn't have deserved the award.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I guess everybody is open to their own opinion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else you want to share with us tonight, Spirit Snare?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, thanks for your call.
[SPEAKER_08]: We appreciate it, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for listening.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go to another call here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go to this one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, Sky.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's me, Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to comment on that achievement points.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you want to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I hate them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do you hate them?
[SPEAKER_04]: I only have 630 and all my friends got 1300.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have 900.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have more than you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's just great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that the only reason you're upset is because you have a few points whereas a lot of people have more?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm just way too poor to buy $60 games.
[SPEAKER_08]: What about the cheapy little $5 and $10 games you can get on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_08]: Feeding Frenzy, 75 easy, easy points.
[SPEAKER_08]: Crystal Quest, probably 100 easy points right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm saving my Microsoft points for Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to kick someone's ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, Street Fighter is finally supposed to be coming out in, I think, April.
[SPEAKER_08]: Finally, that will come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, of course, they've been saying this, you know, for three months now.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if they're going to fix the lag, I guess it's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's what I'm excited for, but... Can I say one more thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, uh... The Mac bootcamp thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's the greatest thing that Mac ever did, supporting Windows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, yay indeed.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can call me a hypocrite for nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, now I won't call you hypocrite.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's a smart move for Mac as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, have a good one, RavensDolphin.
[SPEAKER_08]: See ya.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're getting a little bit of lag there with Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe we'll do one more call.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do want to say real fast, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody said in chat room, let's see, where is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it really is pronounced jism.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's how you say that name.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's short for neologism.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's actually pronounced jism.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I said the name right the first time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know I do not have something dirty on the brain, you freaking perverts.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's how pure my soul is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zander from New Kineto, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't have a whole lot on my mind tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so glad that you called.
[SPEAKER_08]: You better think of something quick to talk about.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm going to talk about something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, what is it?
[SPEAKER_03]: The problem is I wanted to talk to Jamie about something, but she's not here tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can we pass on a message for you?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'll just wait until whenever she's back.
[SPEAKER_08]: What the hell did you call in for tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Can we help you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have other things to talk about.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, well, you better bring it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I know I changed my location in SHJ.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dang it, now I forgot.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, I have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't hang up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I beat it yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: You beat Kingdom Hearts 2 already?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: How is the ending?
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you spoil it, I'll fly out to New Connecticut and choke you.
[SPEAKER_03]: How is the ending?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of similar to the first one, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the sense that it ends with the king sending him a letter.
[SPEAKER_03]: I said don't ruin the damn ending!
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not a spoiler, dude.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not a spoiler.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, yeah, it's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: The last boss battle is very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It kind of had a Wind Waker-like vibe to it, in a way.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, the way you killed off Ganondorf in the end, it kind of had a similar, like, really flashy... Oh, you spoiled Wind Waker for me!
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, was it worth the $50 you paid for it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, I don't think many video games at all are worth $50, but I mean, I certainly had a great time with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, maybe it was only like 30 hours, but, you know, it was a good 30 hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, there were a few bosses I didn't like, because they're really annoying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you spend three hours on the prologue?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that means 10% of the game is the prologue?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Spike, you had a question?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so my question for you is, did you get the hidden video at the end?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but I saw it before it even came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh man.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the internet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard it, it's, I can't even say, I don't want to spoil, but I heard it's what the hidden video in part one did for part two.
[SPEAKER_08]: Essentially.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you banning me from asking my question on the air?
[SPEAKER_08]: You cannot spoil the game or many people will kill you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send Spike an email.
[SPEAKER_08]: You kids can Kingdom Hearts it out in email.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to see the secret ending, just go to YouTube.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've seen it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have some speculation about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can't spoil, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you make it spoiler-free?
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you make it spoiler-free?
[SPEAKER_08]: Somehow?
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't be able to for what I want to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Xander, we gotta let you go before something gets spoiled, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ansem's still alive.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even hear what he said.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did he say?
[SPEAKER_05]: He said Ansem's still alive.
[SPEAKER_08]: You dick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: I lied.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll do one more call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, I lied.
[SPEAKER_08]: I lied.
[SPEAKER_08]: We decided to take one more call.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um... Well... Oh, yeah, that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_08]: What does that have to do with tonight's show?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um... No, I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get better soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, obviously something's going around.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, seriously.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, it's bothering me.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys keep saying Yen.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's pronounced N.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, the currency?
[SPEAKER_08]: In Japan?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you see, I'm a honky who can't pronounce Japanese words right.
[SPEAKER_08]: You want to go out for some sushi?
[SPEAKER_08]: Want to go get some sushi?
[SPEAKER_08]: And some teriyaki?
[SPEAKER_08]: Can I get some teriyaki chicken?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, alright, so I make mistakes.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, that's why I'm on the internet radio and not on real radio, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else you want to say besides picking on me?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, this is Nintendo Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, hi, Nintendo Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or as I say, Fever Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, anything else on your mind tonight before I cut you off?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, my DS charger cable I've modded so I have headphone jacks on the cord.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can plug in my AC adapter, a USB port, or get this, a mouse port plug.
[SPEAKER_06]: Resident Evil 4, bitch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Man, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I spent 30 hours on Kingdom Hearts this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: My e-penis is huge.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a question for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: God, I love our fans.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, USB port and mouse port.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you can.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why do you install Linux on a toaster?
[SPEAKER_09]: But you can't hook up a mouse to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, like, if I install the cigarette lighter on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I don't smoke.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you would have it.
[SPEAKER_08]: For what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we're going to go around and get tonight's last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any last minute things people want to bring up?
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, you seem to always have something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I was going to mention there was some rumor stuff I was reading.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of them saying that Final Fantasy 7, the remake, is in production for the PS3 right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: that they're trying to also secure the rights for Grand Theft Auto the next Grand Theft Auto for the 360 to be exclusive which is not going to happen and oh god what was the other one that's all I got so far
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I have a real last minute story here.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is coming to us from GK128 in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a post over on Nintendo forums.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rumor is going around that Blue Wave may perhaps be the real name of the revolution.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take into consideration the revolution has a blue light.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's waving the controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's the blue ocean thing people have been talking about.
[SPEAKER_08]: Competition to Blu-ray perhaps.
[SPEAKER_08]: This leak is coming from some type of audio link there from YourFileHost.com Check that out in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: We just posted the link there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure if this is true, there will be plenty of more news about it in the next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right now, take it as a rumor, the name of the revolution to be the Blue Wave, possibly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're retarded sounding.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could see it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could see that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's as retarded as you're making it out to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Spike?
[SPEAKER_08]: I really like the name Revolution.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do too.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it ain't broke, don't fix it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that should be the name of it too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, because it's revolutionary.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's, I don't know, you can revolve the controller around.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm doing little quotation marks with my fingers here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's catchy and buzzy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that it's exactly what Nintendo needs to turn their image around.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something that's going to make people say, hey, wait, this is different.
[SPEAKER_08]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any other last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_06]: Spike, do you have something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, on Friday, actually, Capcom announced the Capcom Classics Collection Reloaded.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the follow-up compilation disc for PlayStation 2 and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right now, the titles that have been announced for it are Eco Fighters, King of Dragons, Knights of the Round.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, it looks like some Commando, Ghouls and Ghosts, and Street Fighter II.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of those games were in the last one.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't get this press release, but it's there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kotaku posted a link, IGN posted a link.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seems pretty kosher, but... Resident Evil 4, bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Resident Evil 4, bitch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any other last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just the one I have.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I also want to say really quick, because somebody in the chat room reminded me to mention our panels at Fanime.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, we are going to be going to Fanime.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're doing panels that's still in the works.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura would know more about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just a reminder, that's Memorial Day weekend.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not only are we going to be there, but Spike, you're going to Fanime as well, correct?
[SPEAKER_08]: You're going to be there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm there just about every year.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you'll be at our panels as well?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Please.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, well, you'll at least be there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what we're doing for them yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll be present.
[SPEAKER_08]: He'll be there to sign autographs.
[SPEAKER_08]: And hopefully some of our other regulars.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know Extrofer will probably be there, and maybe we can get Miklatop to come with us, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that'll all go down at Foundame.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I have one more thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: One more.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is basically coming from the new issue of Game Informer.
[SPEAKER_09]: First off, they're sticking by their information that the new Halo game is going to be called Forerunner.
[SPEAKER_09]: They also revealed that a Project Orion is in existence.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically, it's supposed to be a team put together to explore the possibility of a Halo MMO.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's still in the planning stages.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's going ahead.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, the Final Fantasy 7 remake for the PlayStation 3 is supposed to be going to have the Final Fantasy 12 action battle system in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you're going to be in a real-time battle.
[SPEAKER_09]: All rumors until we see some actual details.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's about going to wrap it up for tonight's program, but not before we get to the last story of the evening, which comes to us from Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were going to make Jamie talk about this, but maybe this is why she called in tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I wanted to first real quick before I go over the last story, I just want to mention what's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you are a PC gamer fan, they have Auto Assault Online Limited Edition with some bonus stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Condemned is finally coming out on the PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: GameCube has Odama
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, on the PSP, we have the Silent Hill Experience coming out that coincided with the movie released next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: They must have bumped that up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I believe they have.
[SPEAKER_09]: Silent Hill Experience, I thought around that time was supposed to be not the Silent Hill Experience, but the collection.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I haven't really heard anything official on that, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: So look for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: See if it's coming.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're over in the UK, you've got coming out this week on the 13th, Dragon Quest, Journey of the Cursed King.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're an RPG fan, you must get this.
[SPEAKER_08]: PlayStation 2, Mega Man Battle Network 5, Double Team coming out on the DS, The Sims 2 expansion, Family Fun Stuff on the PC, Auto Assault also making its way to the PC, and Sega's bringing out Football Manager 2006 on the Xbox 360 and the PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: I believe that is the hard drive required title.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: 360, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next week, you guys have to look forward to Final Fantasy XI on PC and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: Xbox 360, that would be the treasures of Ot Organ, of course.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yes, that's right, that is coming out next week for, no, no, I'm sorry, that is the following week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it's the following week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now I'm into the week of the 20th and 21st, and on the 21st you guys are getting Electroplankton over in the UK, Tamagotchi on the DS, and Tetris DS is also making its way to the DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: Might I also say on the 20th you guys are scheduled to get 99 Nights.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lucky, we're not getting that for a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't believe that, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what the list says.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what I'm reading.
[SPEAKER_08]: So take that with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Big grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, well, that's what the list says.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's just what I'm reading off of.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not uncommon for folks in the UK to once in a while get a game before us, so I wouldn't completely disregard that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, who's bringing that over?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because if that might be Ubisoft, they might be releasing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I closed the list.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it is Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, shoot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's, hold on, I'm looking.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got, Microsoft is publishing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Huh, that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, now we're going to get into the final story of the night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, we have a comment in our chat room there.
[SPEAKER_08]: BlackWolf in our chatroom says 99 Nights is coming out in Japan on April 20th, not Europe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I think that's more correct.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm reading the list.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just reading the list.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going with Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I made a mistake.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, last story of the night.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we've seen a lot of weird things come out.
[SPEAKER_09]: This, I don't think it actually ties in with the actual game, but if you're in Japan and you happen to be near a Japanese sex toy shop, you can find a Kingdom Hearts vibrator.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, the Kingdom Hearts AC.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's selling a Kingdom Hearts branded rabbit vibrator.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, it doesn't look like it has anything to do with Kingdom Hearts, except for the name, maybe a brand name or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Something to get those Kingdom Hearts hardcore fans out there that they might not already own.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now you too can join Organization 69.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Put this on your little black hood.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is something to get those people that have the trans vibrator and can't think of anything else gaming related to get.
[SPEAKER_08]: This reminds me of the Hello Kitty vibrator.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to know how long it's going to take for fan art with Keyblades with these dangling from the end on the chain.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: And Dirty Thief just got the quote of the show there in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a Keyblade that unlocks your pleasure.
[SPEAKER_08]: They win at the internet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Dirty Thief ought to be marketing this show to the masses out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And please, if you guys do want to market the show to the masses, we really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the only way we get big is word of mouth.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't have no big magazine company backing our show.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't have no big website that backs our show.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are independent.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're as independent as it gets.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are out of the spare bedroom of my apartment doing this program, and we need word of mouth.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, I'm wagging my face.
[SPEAKER_08]: The way your head is moving, I wish I could show the audience at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we're hoping to do the video thing soon enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry I didn't get any video this time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just, there wasn't anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, just check it out on olrpsp.com and huge, huge video things to come.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're very, very excited.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I guess that's that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your final thought, Spike.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see you next time here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next week!