[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight, April 2nd, 2006.
[SPEAKER_02]: April Fool's hits the web, but is Final Fantasy XIII a joke?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is the Xbox 360 drought finally over?
[SPEAKER_02]: And are UMD movies about to meet an untimely fate?
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio Hello everybody and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are here gathered together to talk about video games today.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm eating an organic unbleached flour mushroom leek strudel with black sesame seeds on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's delicious!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like eight of those names.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's very delicious.
[SPEAKER_00]: I do a lot of my shopping now at Whole Foods markets, which is all organic food.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's expensive.
[SPEAKER_00]: It is expensive.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I have felt so healthy the last two months since I've started eating all organic and vegetarian and cut out red meat.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I don't drink soda anymore.
[SPEAKER_00]: I had a soda yesterday.
[SPEAKER_00]: I had a diet vanilla Pepsi, and it made my stomach hurt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still drink diet, but I try very hard not to drink regular soda.
[SPEAKER_00]: I make my own soda now.
[SPEAKER_00]: I buy club soda and Torani, the flavored syrups.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, so kind of like Italian soda.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I do Italian sodas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, because you can get the sugar-free ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those aren't so bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I also make carbonated lemonade using club soda and lemon juice and lime juice and Splenda.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-mm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ice Cream Tea
[SPEAKER_00]: Slice apples, popcorn, you know, like some plain popcorn, soy nuts, they're good, cashews, cashews are very good for you, they have good oils, and brown rice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, and super bacon.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, that's bad for you.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's like a heart attack recipe right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's get away from the Food Network and do a little bit of how was your gaming week, the part of the show where we talk about what we've been playing this week and what we've been up to.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know I've got a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about the others, but DarkSakura, you always start us off.
[SPEAKER_04]: What have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, we've had quite a bit of new gaming coming in the house.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've actually got Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been playing the crap out of it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have Kingdom Hearts 2, but since I was already playing it in Japanese, I've been sort of not so much about that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to start over on that probably within the week after I get my stupid Flash homework done.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm also... Fry's, of all places, is carrying import PSP games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I noticed that last time I went to Fry's, for those, because we're nationwide, Fry's is a big electronics chain on the West Coast, and they've started to carry limited import games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I saw Mahjong in the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: The new Initial D game is really, really cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's based off of, I think, the version 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: that's out in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's really pretty.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's Eurobeat fantastic.
[SPEAKER_00]: Lots and lots of Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it's Initial D. There's not much else I can say about that.
[SPEAKER_00]: They also had out the Taito collection that we're sort of considering except that it's coming out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_00]: sort of like a no point to that.
[SPEAKER_00]: And we almost picked up Guilty Gear but that's also coming out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_00]: so we were sort of not so much on that too.
[SPEAKER_00]: and Dan and his friend have been playing a whole lot of Burnout.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm so tired of that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why so tired of the Burnout?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just the same thing over and over?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm in my... Okay, my computer room is on the other side of where our big TV is.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm in the middle of working on my flash homework right now is to do this big photo slideshow.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been trying to get my photos all together.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm just about to do my last little touch.
[SPEAKER_00]: Great.
[SPEAKER_00]: We've also had MAME action going on because one of Dan's coworkers and a friend of mine, George, Necco Boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right.
[SPEAKER_00]: He and our friend Tim, who's actually, for anyone who's in cosplay circles, he's very well known because he does the fabulous Rick Hunter Macross outfit.
[SPEAKER_00]: He did Evo 1 at Anime Expo.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's been in Japanese cosplay photos.
[SPEAKER_00]: But he also has been helping build MAME cabinets in my garage.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you have more than one now.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're building George's.
[SPEAKER_04]: We haven't talked about this on the show in a while, but both DarkSakura and Loki have main cabinets in their house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, DarkSakura, you guys took a pole position?
[SPEAKER_00]: We took a stand-up pole position.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're building this one out of some other generic one, but it has this fabulous 1982 art on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so it's really super cool, but they were working on this all day while me and the fabulous Miss Tia were running around.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where did they get the specs on how to do this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, are they doing it off a website?
[SPEAKER_04]: Off a just crash and burn?
[SPEAKER_00]: There is a website, and if you give me just a second, I can get it, because it's the one that my husband goes to, which happens to be on my favorites bar called, it's arcadecontrols.com slash arcade.htm.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's basically build your own arcade controls FAQ.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's how to build your, it goes a lot into the cabinets, it goes into how to build the controllers, what you need for it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's really, really neat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: And actually, I'll talk to Dan about getting the specs on his cabinet, so if anybody else is interested.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Play any of your main cabinet?
[SPEAKER_04]: You actually built your cabinet.
[SPEAKER_04]: You didn't convert a machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: You built a brand new thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, and it shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were roommates back when you were building that, and I just remember that that was a project.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, to say the least.
[SPEAKER_03]: Most of the project is being stored at my...
[SPEAKER_03]: I played a lot of 360 stuff again I think I played a little bit of Oblivion I played more Outfit and I realized that game really sucks
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, this isn't really my kind of game, so I haven't really been playing a lot of it, but I've listened to other shows that seem to really like this game, so what's your issue with it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, my issue with it, I tried playing multiplayer, and again, we're just with two-player split-screen, which is fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: For one, the controls really suck in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like,
[SPEAKER_03]: I kept calling in the destruction on demand, the big feature where you get stuff to fall from the sky, and the stuff falling from the sky kept crushing my characters!
[SPEAKER_03]: I would aim it further away from me, and the stupid
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: Far Cry Instinct's Predator which I've never played the original Far Cry Instinct's but from what I hear it's not very different as far as graphics and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: A little bit of graphic upgrades and stuff but it is pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is kind of, actually it's very hard, very frustrating.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I started to cheat and now it's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love how they put the cheats in there because cheats make it fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still really challenging but it kind of lightens it up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: so I'm kind of looking forward to that and then played more Burnout more Ghost Recon and I hear that she's working that too and what else?
[SPEAKER_03]: Mimai Katamari Grand Theft Auto Liberty City Stories all that fun stuff I played a little bit of Beatmania didn't like it oh, why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: the interface is too colorful and to be honest I
[SPEAKER_03]: didn't think the new controllers were that great, and I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, before, they seemed to be pretty good, but that turntable doesn't seem, it seems to be sticky, the turntable.
[SPEAKER_00]: It loosens up after you play with it a bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it's just, even the new songs were kind of okay, but I just wasn't very impressed by it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just kind of, yay, cool, Beatmania, anything to be able to go, I'm not going to go rush out to go buy it, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: My Gaming Week also consisted of Beatmania, which I picked up earlier in the week, so kind of funny there.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've all played that, but of course that's not a surprise when you consider that we started as a music gaming station.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously we owe a lot to Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's very interesting, Beatmania, because when you consider it, Beatmania is about, what, eight years old?
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is really the first time that it's coming out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: for console.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, of course we had the
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: much more accessible to beginners in the fact that there is no separate mode for beginner mode, but they fuse the beginning level songs into the normal game, which I think is good, because I think you don't want to scare people off, because even though Beatmania is selling itself as bringing the arcade experience home, which kind of is a little weird to me, because there's really nothing but import machines for Beatmania, it's kind of weird there, but
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a good first exposure for people.
[SPEAKER_00]: I find it... There was a lot of the old 5Key music in there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you notice?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I noticed a lot of really old stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hunting for You and Metal Gear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just really, really old songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think that's cool because they picked some good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a very interesting song list.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the 5Key song list is actually pretty solid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they got a good mix of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: 7Key, for me, could have used some more recent stuff, but I think I understand why they're doing what they're doing because...
[SPEAKER_04]: If there is to be a second mix, then they can start dipping into the later stuff and things, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you like the Moby song?
[SPEAKER_04]: I did like the Moby song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the video.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the Timo Ma song is the best, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dan and I sat there with the Moby song going, what is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's good.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dan and I are both like Moby, but we just didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the interesting thing is that I noticed this in a lot of reviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: Beatmania has been getting a lot of negative reviews out there on the circuit right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a lot of people can't seem to not want to compare this to Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody's comparing this game to Guitar Hero, which I think is kind of funny because this game existed long before Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: They're done well.
[SPEAKER_04]: The cover songs are done well.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're pretty faithful to the originals, and it really ups that fun factor.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem with Beatmania, and why I don't think Beatmania is going to have that same buzz as Guitar Hero is now set at the bar, is that a lot of these songs are not recognizable to most people.
[SPEAKER_04]: They tried a little bit with the song list.
[SPEAKER_04]: They got Toxic and Funky Town.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, people know those songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's a lot of songs in there that are not so recognizable.
[SPEAKER_04]: is that a good thing or a bad thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know I'm spoiled by years of Japanese releases so I do recognize all the songs that are in there it's hard for me to look at this game impartially when I've been raised on the Japanese series for years and years um
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's going to be interesting to see how the general public reacts to this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they going to pick up on this game, even though there aren't a lot of recognizable songs?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had some people over last night, including some people who don't play games a whole lot, and I know a few of them were really digging on Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_04]: They thought it was kind of fun and very pretty, even though they didn't really recognize a lot of the songs in it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you notice that 321 Stars is the another?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, just to make it a little harder there.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, plus they did something weird with five keys is that there's only the one difficulty.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that was kind of odd.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just made some very odd changes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the one that really irks me is that they made the triple A's a lot lower in score to be able to get.
[SPEAKER_04]: And just in general, the grading's a little easier.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think, I mean, I understand why they want to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, they're trying to cater to the beginners and people haven't seen the game before, but
[SPEAKER_04]: Beep Mania
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a hell of a good first release compared to what DDR First Mix was.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think there's a potential for really great stuff in the future.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you just kind of have to think, okay, if Beatmania can grow the same way DDR did, it's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, we have to have a little faith here in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to say hello to our chat room over at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Click a chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: And always looking for your comments there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: The 23rd Magus says, I believe this is a response to Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: They made music games accessible.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a very interesting statement.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people sometimes get put off by the DDR pad and by the turntables and the keys and seeing all those notes falling.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there was something about Guitar Hero that was a little different.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: So again, if you want to join our chat, www.orangeloundtrader.com
[SPEAKER_04]: and click on chat and 23rd Magus wants to also point out that they actually have the calculations if you want to look at calculations for the true AAAs that there are websites out there that will let you know how your score compares to the Japanese version one of them he's mentioning is VJ Army so pretty interesting I did notice that it was ridiculously easy but it was sort of nice because the good thing about this is that I could play it with Dan and Dan's not really a beatmania person he was playing on my old controller
[SPEAKER_00]: I felt so bad for him because really my old controller is now hitting the crappy phase.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think what I call these folks sometimes are the Japanese elitists out there on some of the websites that nothing is good enough unless it's the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_04]: The American versions will always be shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the problem with the Japanese elitists out there on the message boards when it comes to Beatmania is that they forget that these games aren't made for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: They think that Konami owes them something because they've been buying the games for years and years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that got Konami to release the game here, but still, the game is not for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's for everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they'll toss a couple frickin' bones at the loyal supporters.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, there was a couple Night Style songs in there, and there's some kind of neat stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think just having the 5-key and 7-key in there is pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the game's not for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's for everybody.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I honestly did think that the song selection was pretty sparse in comparison.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because think about, like, the last one that I bought was 8th style.
[SPEAKER_00]: And think about just how many freaking songs were in 8th style.
[SPEAKER_00]: But still, when you consider that we have both modes, I do sort of wish that you could do the 7 key stuff in 5 key mode, you know, to do that too.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I see why they did it the way that they did.
[SPEAKER_00]: It really is like you're getting two games in one, just both with very sparse song lists.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I recommend Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_04]: If for no other reason than I want to see a Beatmania second mix be released here in the US.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know, it is good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think everybody should at least check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, because even if you're scared of DDR, there's no reason to be scared of Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_03]: I personally, I didn't pick it up because one, I know Konami sent me a free one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Two, because if it's anything like Guitar Hero, I'll play it once and not play it for again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I did with my Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is leaning up
[SPEAKER_03]: against my MAME cabinet because eventually it will be used for Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guitar Hero is a party game for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's sitting there in the corner and then when people come over they go, what's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Guitar Hero!
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Beatmania is going to be kind of a similar thing around here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still playing it an awful lot but I find that I'm going to use my controller to go back to the Japanese mixes.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you know, I'm different.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not like most of the people listening to this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've played the hell out of those Japanese mixes.
[SPEAKER_04]: For me, this is
[SPEAKER_04]: Good new controller plus best hits is what this game is to me.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, that really is how I feel about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the good thing about it is that now I can have friends pick up, you know, who are like, oh, that's neat, but be so intimidated by it.
[SPEAKER_00]: They've got access now to one that's going to work on their PlayStations.
[SPEAKER_00]: They can practice at home and then come over and play the imports with me.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's gotten me back into Bimani because...
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, having a new DDR arcade mix is all fine and dandy and everything, but I've got a new Beatmania in my house that I've been playing the hell out of.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I went hunting the other day to try to find my copy of 8th Style, and I'm actually considering going and buying 10th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sums it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, more games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good thing it's a slow news week, because I've got a lot of games to talk about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't like Kingdom Hearts 1.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know why I didn't like Kingdom Hearts 1?
[SPEAKER_04]: The camera, the gummy ship.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kingdom Hearts 1 was such a phenomenal idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this is the weird thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the story.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the music.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the cinema.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love everything about Kingdom Hearts except playing the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kingdom Hearts 2, it's all fixed.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is all fixed.
[SPEAKER_04]: The camera, not a problem for me anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Minimap, there now to help my 3D confused butt get through the levels.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kingdom Hearts 2 is phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't describe how incredible I think this game is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have not been sucked into a game this much, I don't think since the Super Nintendo game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have literally been playing with every spare moment I have this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have noticed that Roxas doesn't annoy me as much in English as he does in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think what's great about it, and I know a lot of people have been bitching about that three-hour prologue.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to give any spoilers, but there's like a three-hour prologue, essentially.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to play this game for 3 hours, 3 hours 15 minutes until you see the title screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: The nice thing about it is for those of us that didn't really play it the whole way through Kingdom Hearts 1, it really does explain it in a not cheesy manner.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like it's kind of, I don't want to, I'm trying to do this without spoilers.
[SPEAKER_03]: It tells it through flashbacks, essentially.
[SPEAKER_03]: It also ties in with Chains of Memories.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, right, because Chains of Memories was more event, well, I knew actually quite a number of people who played it.
[SPEAKER_00]: And actually, my plan is to go back and play Chains of Memories.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just haven't had time to.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a complete story.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like that it sort of brings you back into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're not going to play Kingdom Hearts 1, you're playing Kingdom Hearts 2, just read the spoiler fact for Chains of Memories, read the spoiler fact for Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least that way it'll kind of catch you up with the story and then you can enjoy the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've seen the ending of Kingdom Hearts, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have seen the ending of Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's funny because the way I was introduced to Kingdom Hearts is I dated someone a long time ago who was really, really into it and I kind of saw everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got shown all of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you see the final movie from... I did send you the final movie from the deep dive, didn't I?
[SPEAKER_01]: Which was... Maybe.
[SPEAKER_00]: With the international version in Japan, after Kingdom Hearts came out, they labeled it the deep dive.
[SPEAKER_00]: It had the Sephiroth battle in it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it had this extra movie file, which part of it plays in the prologue, with the nameless people at the end.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll show that to you later.
[SPEAKER_00]: I really recommend for people before you play Kingdom Hearts to go back and get that movie off of Deep Dive because it really does tie in a lot more too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Familiarize yourself just even the slightest bit with a Kingdom Hearts 1 story and I think you'll be okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game itself is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so deep.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's so much to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the drive and the limits.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just fought this one battle not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the Beauty and the Beast level.
[SPEAKER_04]: The final battle you do in there is in the ballroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're using the chandelier to attack the monster.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't been that like, whoa, at an RPG level.
[SPEAKER_04]: since I first saw a summon in Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I heard the new system that they have where it's like this action system where you hit the triangle button depending on certain things that are going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll do kind of like the God of War where you'll do kind of cinematic attacks and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are really impressive in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Kingdom Hearts does have a few things that are kind of... Okay, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you don't like...
[SPEAKER_04]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Setsur, Vivi,
[SPEAKER_04]: So, there's just, the whole game is made up of these little fanboy things, and if you watch Disney movies at all, and I don't watch a lot of Disney movies, I've seen most of the big ones, but if you play the Final Fantasy games at all, there's so many things in there to just make you go, eee, eee, eee, you know, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: I highly recommend Kingdom Hearts 2, although I think there's going to be some folks out there listening to this going, I know I wouldn't like Kingdom Hearts, I don't really like those action RPGs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine, you probably won't like Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's nothing about this game that's really going to win you over, but I just think for those that are into these types of games, it's so in-depth, there's so much to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: You probably already have your copy, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else have I played this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't end it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's more.
[SPEAKER_04]: I borrowed Need for Speed Underground or Most Wanted Underground, whatever that game is on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, this is the weird thing about Most Wanted on 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like the showgirls of video games to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so bad, I can't stop playing it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now you see what I was dealing with for, what, three months at my house?
[SPEAKER_04]: There is seriously nothing to like about that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: The cutscenes are stupid.
[SPEAKER_00]: I see a cop!
[SPEAKER_04]: And washed out.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the graphics are crap compared to Ridge Racer and even Full Auto and some of the other games I've played.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is really not a lot to like about this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't stop playing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Until I got Kingdom Hearts, I could not stop playing that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: The cutscenes, they're done and it's supposed to be like that, the washed out, because it's supposed to be kind of like comic book-ish.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I thought the cutscenes were actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: There were too many of them, granted.
[SPEAKER_03]: The graphics weren't that bad, but they weren't much better than the Xbox version.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, I don't know, I never really got in the need for speed.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I thought the game was okay looking.
[SPEAKER_03]: I liked the whole Fast and the Furious thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought you could totally tell it was an upgraded Xbox game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could totally tell.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, that is true.
[SPEAKER_03]: You could totally tell that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the funny thing I have to laugh about.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know how the cutscenes are done in this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know that game coming out, Ace Combat Zero, The Belkan War?
[SPEAKER_03]: Imagine...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Ridge Racer is obviously a superior game, yet I keep playing this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'll just have to take it back and let you borrow it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you're not taking it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you can take it until I beat Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's go to chat room because I'm sure chat room has some stuff they want to say on these games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Legend of Zaku, Kingdom Hearts 2 equals makes fanboys cream in their pants.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's things here that not just for fanboys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there's a lot that's pant cream worthy.
[SPEAKER_00]: I placed a rebuttal in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, did you?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, Kingdom Hearts 2 is fangirl fodder.
[SPEAKER_00]: So much fangirl fodder.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's both.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also in the chat room, Rini says, VV is the friggin' win.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely, but I haven't gotten to the Tron level yet, so I'm going to hold back on the friggin' win.
[SPEAKER_04]: It better not let me down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tron level better not let me down.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've seen the Tron level.
[SPEAKER_00]: It won't let you down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it true you get to play light cycles?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, you get friggin' light cycles.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the light cycle part actually is not as cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: But you do get light cycles.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is great.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're talking about all the yaoi.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ PooEater in the chat room, which by the way is one of my favorite nicknames ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ PooEater in chat says, nothing wrong with the fanboys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope, nothing at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody's fanboy about something.
[SPEAKER_04]: For some people it's football, basketball.
[SPEAKER_04]: For some people it's, you know, crocheting.
[SPEAKER_04]: For some people it's Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know they were saying that they're going to announce at E3 this year that they're continuing the Kingdom Hearts series but in a different way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely it's something they're going to keep making games.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they're thinking about expanding in different ways, maybe not like Chains of Memories, but... God, I'm hoping... You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you know what we were theorizing when we were playing Kingdom Hearts?
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the boys were over, we were talking about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: They say they want to do something different with Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Square Enix says they're working on a new MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm?
[SPEAKER_04]: Would Kingdom Hearts not make the coolest MMO?
[SPEAKER_00]: You know that would totally get me back to play online.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think that's going to be what happens because, one, they're working on something else, not that for an MMO.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember hearing about it last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard that they're doing something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: But my brain couldn't help but go there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something about that seems oh so right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you imagine?
[SPEAKER_04]: And the MMO could be updated with new Disney and Square Enix.
[SPEAKER_00]: I see them doing an anime series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or an OAB series.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm very surprised they haven't already done this.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's actually Kingdom Hearts manga.
[SPEAKER_03]: They could do a CG, like, anime, because this game, I mean, basically cel-shaded CG anyways, and it looks really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it looks very realistic to, you know, true to the animated series that they're pulling from.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, um, oh my god, it would make one hell of a kick-ass movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would be one franchise Disney would
[SPEAKER_03]: Imagine Disney, but with a more mature storyline to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: and you get to interact with it and be in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the great thing about this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she was kind of like, hmm, sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of interesting to try and explain Kingdom Hearts and I'm thinking, you get to interact with Winnie the Pooh in Mulan.
[SPEAKER_00]: The games are a lot more hardcore than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's so hard to explain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: More comments from chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: More, more, more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dirty Thief theorizes Kingdom Hearts 3 could be a theatrical sequel for the movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope that's what I'm hoping for.
[SPEAKER_04]: GS191 says, I would be okay with a Kingdom Hearts MMO, but do a damn true sequel to Super Mario RPG first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is what we need.
[SPEAKER_03]: Screw this Paper Mario crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am done with Paper Mario.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want a goddamn Super Mario RPG 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just remake the whole damn thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dirty Thief in our chatroom says everyone's going to be a Keyblade holder if you do a
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it would be a perfect MMO, but what do I know?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't design them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tigerclaw says, hey, how about a Super Mario MMO, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dirty Thief says he has a way to explain Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_04]: You like Disney?
[SPEAKER_04]: You like Final Fantasy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: April Fool's Day
[SPEAKER_04]: April Fool's is actually against my religion, so I don't really practice April Fool's.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll notice Orange Lawns Radio, we did no April Fool's gag.
[SPEAKER_04]: There will be no gag in tonight's program, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: We did a gag last year, but it was stupid and obvious.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we thought about doing them this year, but then we realized, or at least I was realizing... We're just too lazy and procrastinate too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the time it takes to set up an April Fool's prank, I could be doing something more constructive for the website in the long term.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like the one we did on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_04]: We changed it into Rot 13.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, I have to admit, as it's been with the past three years of the DDR freak April Fool's prank, I click, I go to the site, I roll my eyes, I go somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's been my April Fool's visits.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was lax in my moderator duties yesterday.
[SPEAKER_00]: Everybody was.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be honest, I think the Blizzard ones have been the best.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blizzard has had some good ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Panda Express or Pandaren Express, whatever it was in their name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you see this one?
[SPEAKER_04]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the new alliance class is the Wisp.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not the Wisp.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it Burger Craft?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And their new fast food chain that they're going to... That was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: What were some other great April Fool's pranks played out there on the internet?
[SPEAKER_03]: GameFAQs telling you not to cheat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, my favorite one... Another site that I moderate on is Gorillas Unofficial.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that was actually my favorite prank.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I...
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_00]: for anyone who keeps up with the whole Gorillaz fandom saying that Paula was rejoining Gorillaz and that Noodle was out of the picture for a while and I was like, oh yeah!
[SPEAKER_00]: I just loved watching everybody going, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god!
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm sitting there going...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's funny is I read about that on the Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, Wikipedia had a giant list of every April Fool's prank on the internet yesterday.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was Girls Unofficial Prank.
[SPEAKER_04]: I loved Slashdot's prank.
[SPEAKER_04]: They turned the site pink and was like, you know, my little pony.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just nerdy stuff that was cute.
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually, nobody got my prank because people, I guess, believed it and didn't comment on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I knew it was a prank.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one in your LJ?
[SPEAKER_00]: I said that I was leaving my job next month to be a writer for a holistic magazine.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what my reaction was to that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I went, I read it, I rolled my eyes and went to the next story.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't even read it.
[SPEAKER_00]: But people believed mine from two years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which one was that?
[SPEAKER_00]: When I said I was moving to Washington.
[SPEAKER_04]: because you'd threatened to do it before.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because Dan's been wanting to move us to Washington now for like the past five years.
[SPEAKER_04]: The very first episode of this program you said something about moving to Washington.
[SPEAKER_04]: That hasn't happened yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't go.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have this show.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can't go.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I can do a spin-off in Washington.
[SPEAKER_03]: A spin-off will be called It's Raining Here.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's raining rain.
[SPEAKER_00]: We should, though, bring up our announcement.
[SPEAKER_00]: About what?
[SPEAKER_04]: We have an announcement.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is not a fool's print.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is legit.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is a real, honest to God, or whoever you believe in, announcement.
[SPEAKER_00]: We are doing two panels at Fonamay this year in San Jose.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll be getting dates and everything.
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll be putting it up on our website.
[SPEAKER_04]: Memorial Day weekend, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: It is Memorial Day weekend, last weekend in May.
[SPEAKER_00]: We will be there with two panels.
[SPEAKER_00]: One for sure is on podcasting.
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll be doing full-on presentations.
[SPEAKER_00]: I will be cosplaying.
[SPEAKER_04]: I might too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have some ideas on what I want to do.
[SPEAKER_00]: I am actually taking a suggestion by one of our long-time listeners, DJ Ranma S, and I am cosplaying Tamari from Naruto, like everybody else in the universe freaking cosplays Naruto.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have an idea for cosplay, but I'll tell you off air.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's easy, and I think it's cute, and we could all do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: But then I had another idea, because Tim, who came over, gave us Resident Evil Stars Airsoft Guns with Laser Sights.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dan and I have been shooting each other all day.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's been fantastic.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I'm sort of thinking about reviving the Jill costume, but I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we're about like 40 minutes into the show and we haven't even gotten to the first story yet, so we have to keep moving.
[SPEAKER_00]: Video games?
[SPEAKER_00]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fandomaze is going to be happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're doing podcasting and what?
[SPEAKER_04]: The other one is just gaming?
[SPEAKER_00]: Gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: E3 wrap-up or something?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it will be right after E3, so yeah, that'll be...
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be there.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll probably be giving stuff out too and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: We will be doing, I know for sure that our panel, one of them is on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll be getting official times as soon as they're given to me by my contact.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll post all that info on the website.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you to Faname for inviting us and letting us ruin your con.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, no, no, no Rob is Manfei.
[SPEAKER_00]: Manfei has been done.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that something in the chat room there?
[SPEAKER_00]: 23 Magus brought that up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to be Manfei.
[SPEAKER_00]: For any cosplayers, Manfei is this guy who's not very attractive cosplaying Fei from Cowboy Bebop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, Ranma's offering to send me the Black Mage costume I wore at Katsukan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you listen to the first 30 minutes of the show, you know where my fanboyism is right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: So fill in the blanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can guess what I probably have planned for the cast of OLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're...
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XIII is going to be a surprise at May's E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's going to be a brief teaser video and confirmation from the publisher that the RPG will be a PlayStation 3 exclusive.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, now, 1UP published this on March 30th of 06.
[SPEAKER_04]: People were saying it was an early April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: But 1UP, and in fact, even Square Enix came out and said, Don't forget that people like to play April Fool's pranks around this time of year.
[SPEAKER_04]: But 1UP published another story that said, No, Square Enix is trying to deflect.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have inside sources that says this is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was followed up by Game Informer saying, while there have been numerous rumors about Final Fantasy XIII, Square Enix has never released any information about the title.
[SPEAKER_03]: The recent online article stating that the title being exclusive for PlayStation 3 and Shona A3 is not based on any official information obtained by us.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope the readers will remember April Fool's Day is tomorrow and many print and online outlets pull pranks every year before they get their hopes crushed by a joke.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, still rumor.
[SPEAKER_04]: And 1up.com ran a follow-up story that said, nope, Square Enix is just trying to deflect.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have inside sources that says this is the real deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I think, logically...
[SPEAKER_04]: We all know Final Fantasy 13 is going to happen on PlayStation 3 because, let's see, you had 7, 8, 9 on PlayStation, 10, 11, 12 on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: 13, 14, 15 on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seems pretty logical.
[SPEAKER_00]: We also had the first three on the NES and the second three on the SNES.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly right.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've always... 3, 3, 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only big shock was that they moved from Nintendo to Sony, but that's years old news.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the graphic comes out on the stupid GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: And 10, 2, I'm not even counting any of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not counting any of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's inevitable we're getting Final Fantasy XIII on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be hard to talk me out of that notion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's what the problem is.
[SPEAKER_04]: The surprise is, XII's not even out on shelves over here yet, so to announce XIII seems a little... Well, here's what I don't like.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like people ruining surprises like this, for one, because, yeah, of course they're always going to have something that they're surprising everybody with.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hell, we probably know stuff that we can surprise people with that I haven't heard about yet, but obviously you can't say anything about it until E3, so... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: E3, Final Fantasy XII, Will in the United States
[SPEAKER_04]: They just released Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think XI has any life left in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And their expansion's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it'll be the last one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to get hate mail.
[SPEAKER_04]: All that crap that they showed last year that never came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to get hate mail from the Final Fantasy XI fans.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just saying I think this next expansion is the last one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't see them doing another one after this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they've done three expansions now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Rise of the Zillert technically was an expansion.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just got it for free here in the US.
[SPEAKER_04]: So.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet one more will be coming out and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think a new MMO will replace it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's just my thoughts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I know some buddies of mine were in town this weekend and one thing they did today was go shopping for an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: And why would today be the day for that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Today would be the day because everyone has been hoarding them up because all those increased shipments, Best Buy and Target and stores like such were doing their, I guess, third launch of the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best Buy's had 60 systems per store and I think it was similar over at Target and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they're out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can find them now, finally.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: They drove by at like 3 a.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: to make sure there wasn't going to be a line.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they came back, went to bed, and went right before it opened.
[SPEAKER_04]: And sure enough, he got there and got a premium system.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he said they had 80 in stock.
[SPEAKER_04]: They still have some there right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: He called a little bit ago because I think he wanted to take it back because he was afraid something was wrong with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't been following the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll grill him in Part B.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they apparently still have a bunch in stock.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's not just Best Buy doing this.
[SPEAKER_04]: GameStop was going to release a bunch today as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: GameStop had some.
[SPEAKER_04]: EB.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think somebody else was doing this too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I overheard GameStop earlier this week when I picked up Far Cry that they were going to be having more in.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's great because now we'll see some better games come out because some of the publishers have been pushing back their games because they're afraid that there's not many units out there to sell their games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why the whole Splinter Cell Double Agent got pushed back to September.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does this mean the shortage is over of Xbox 360s?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: The end?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's getting better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me put it that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know our company is selling them in May.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to have them for sure in May in all of our warehouses.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I get them like $5 cheaper than retail.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just asking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we declare the shortage officially over now?
[SPEAKER_04]: When 80 Xbox 360s are sitting there in Best Buy and there's still some on the shelf halfway through the day, does that mean the shortage is over?
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say, well, think about it this way.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to be getting maybe about half that next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, so they're going to start getting them regularly on the shelves.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you don't have one yet, now you can probably get one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's a good time, too, because you're starting to get, you know, the games are starting to slow down a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's kind of dip in the year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's plenty of good titles out right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: March was a great month, so go for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is floating around the internet this week where Iwata over at Nintendo is saying that the simultaneous global revolution launch is not going to be likely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quote, we don't think it's necessary to do the simultaneous worldwide launch simply because others are doing this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony, of course, is doing this big thing where they're going to do a worldwide launch and they're supposed to be region free and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo's saying, maybe we don't need to do this same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: so could that mean that the revolution comes out in Japan this year and we still have to wait I hope not I think it's going to be out in both markets for the end of the year are we talking two week difference month difference who knows I think they'll launch it worldwide if they have the amount you know the units to do it I mean because why not but if they don't big deal
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the unfortunate thing is that some of the countries are probably going to get the shaft, that usually tend to get the shaft when it comes to these launches, like Australia, sorry guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of those other countries that aren't the US, Japan, and Europe, and even Europe gets the shaft half the time, probably aren't going to see this at the same time, which is too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go over to Loki, who has another follow-up story there on the Revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, kind of tying in with the whole Revolution being cheaper than the competition out there, the Revolution first-party games are going to be seeing a price tag of basically $50 or less, which, you know, good and all, but I don't think it's too impressive because if you look at the first-party 360 games, those are also $50, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully that'll kind of start the trend of games being a little bit cheaper, but since, you know, obviously the development costs are going to be less than, you know, developing for the 360 and the PlayStation 3, I could definitely see them having, you know, cheaper games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I mean, it would be kind of stupid to release the least expensive system and then the most expensive games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think this kind of makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Nintendo's, I think, trying to affirm that, yes, we're going to be the cheapest system when this thing releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think their games have to match that, is that the games have to stay competitive.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you're right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's not that competitive.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they'd come out and said, no game under $40 or even $30, now that would be, whoa, that would be something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: In not so much console gaming news, but going on to a certainly big gaming event that's happening this month, right around DarkSakura's birthday, we have the Silent Hill movie coming out, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, there's actually a little bit of talk from Roger Avery, who is the author of the screenplay for the Silent Hill movie.
[SPEAKER_00]: He has basically tried to give his assurances that it will be
[SPEAKER_00]: Very much based around the actual games, which a lot of us who've been looking into this have heard him say already.
[SPEAKER_00]: But he did speak to a reporter in Hollywood recently and he's quoted saying, And I knew how passionate the video game fans are for Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_00]: At the minimum, we didn't want to piss them off.
[SPEAKER_00]: We want to make this movie for them.
[SPEAKER_00]: He also mentioned that it isn't always that way with video game tie-ins.
[SPEAKER_00]: Another quote from him says, Hollywood executives are very quick to throw out the source material of the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Doom kills me.
[SPEAKER_00]: This was one of the movies I wanted to do so badly.
[SPEAKER_00]: I met with them early on and I looked at the original script and asked them, where's the doom in this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the doom in this will be the box office.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you remember the first person shooter part?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, at any rate, I do also have a UK release date for the movie.
[SPEAKER_00]: It will be out on April 25th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's not much of a delay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not much of a delay at all.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ours is the 21st.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's nothing for standard movie delays, so awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've said this on the show before, I'll say it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think when we were lucky enough to go to Konami Gamers Day a few months ago to have Akira Yamaoka sitting next to Christoph Gans introducing the trailer together saying, we are bringing this to you, and Akira Yamaoka of course being the producer of the last two Silent Hill games and doing all the music for all of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: and, you know, Christoph Gans being the director, I think that spoke volumes right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That they're working together.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're presenting this together.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't think you ever saw that happen with previous games.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, sure, maybe they say nice things about each other before the movie came out, and then after the movie comes out, they all distance themselves from each other and blame each other for the movie sucking.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like how they, like, explain, you know, the differences between... Obviously, this movie's based on the first and third games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I like how they explain the differences between why the main character is a female instead of male.
[SPEAKER_03]: and stuff like that and it made a lot of sense and it's not like oh well we did this because uh we get this actress or you know we did this because we wanted explosions or you know something stupid so I definitely am confident that this will finally be a Sean Bean a good movie you get the sense that this movie is a little more Japanese than any other
[SPEAKER_04]: Game Movie We've Gotten Yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then again, we might be a little bit more mellow since it'll be the day after.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll be hungover.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you have a follow-up relating to Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, of course, to tie in with the movie release, Konami's announced a few things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, he previously announced Silent Hill Experience.
[SPEAKER_03]: That one actually has a date now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be coming out, well, maybe a little bit after the movie, on May 28th.
[SPEAKER_03]: which is actually, if I remember correctly, the same day as the Metal Gear Solid Digital Comic, which, you know, same week there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's basically, you know, a bunch of digital comics and music and some, you know, backstory to some of the Silent Hill games, kind of tying it all together nicely for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, also announced is the Silent Hill Collection for the PlayStation 2, which is including games 2 through 4, and that's slated for April 13th.
[SPEAKER_03]: About a week or so before the movie.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what we need is the Game Boy one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I keep forgetting about that one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because we never got it over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or maybe it would be a bonus or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could be like a bonus unlockable, who knows.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I haven't actually found the translation of it outside of, you know, FAQ format.
[SPEAKER_00]: Been hunting it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of movies, you know I got invited to go see Stay Alive this weekend.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I turned it down.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, yeah, I know I do the show on video games and stuff but I just really don't want to see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though somebody gave it a not-so-bad review.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't we get a not-so-bad review in the mailbag last week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I still just... I'll wait for Netflix.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not something I can make myself go see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody was mentioning it in chatroom right now, so I just wanted to drop that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to other gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was announced a little while ago, and they keep pushing it back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It got pushed back one more time.
[SPEAKER_04]: May 21st, over on the game's homepage, is when they say this game's coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that's not too bad of a delay because it was only a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, now people are theorizing that, hmm, could this be because the DS Lite is being positioned somewhere around here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because of course Super Mario is probably going to be the next big...
[SPEAKER_04]: DS game after this Tetris Metroid combo we got.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe the light is being positioned to be launched at the same time.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be a good packing game with the DS light.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be a very good packing game for the DS light.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe this is why the repositioning is happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, we won't know the answers until E3, which is kind of a running theme across most of our stories over the next couple months.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything will be... It's like one of those movies or one of those games with a really contorted plot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything is explained at the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything will be explained at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if it's not explained, we're going to be pissed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, I forgot to mention, and I was reminded by Illusion here, the other thing they announced was they're doing a Silent Hill game for the PSP, not the Silent Hill Experience on top of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I read that too.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to do a whole new game on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: The rumor is that it's supposed to be a remake of the first one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe a remake of the first one with the characters from the movie?
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been actually hearing about a possibility of them doing the movie version of the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which is ironic because I did that as my homework in Illustrator.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you also posted a recent homework thing to our forums, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like a scary little thing that made me jump out of my chair when I clicked on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll post it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_00]: For my Flash homework, we were supposed to animate a banner.
[SPEAKER_00]: So what I did is, not a banner, but animate an ad.
[SPEAKER_00]: So we're going to start working on our new website.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm actually going to be doing a Splash Forest within the next couple of months because my spring break is actually next month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm excited to hear Silent Hill is coming to the PSP because I think that's one of those franchises you can't really do on the DS as well as you can the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the PSP's technology with the movies, I think it'll lend itself a lot better to the Silent Hill franchise than the DS would.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's me tossing the PSP fans that say I rip on the PSP too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's me tossing you guys a bone there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Silent Hill will kick butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think they could do it on the DS as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't rip on the PSP fans.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a whole page dedicated to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: A whole website.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple weeks ago they were getting vicious.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, now the 360 has kind of gotten a cold shoulder in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: People kind of don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what's Microsoft going to do to try and make people care?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to do over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we get a do-over?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to relaunch the 360 in Japan on, well, the rumor date right now is June 29th.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's supposed to coincide with many of the new games coming out, especially one of my favorites, Chromehounds, is going to be coming around that time.
[SPEAKER_03]: But some better games will be out by then.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't see how you can actually do over a launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't just pretend it doesn't happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's like,
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to put more systems out there and go, hey look, we're here still.
[SPEAKER_04]: SUPER JAPANESE HAPPY CONSOLE!
[SPEAKER_04]: Play all your favorite games!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it'll be that bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_00]: 360, I choose you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Since we're traveling abroad right now, DarkSakura likes to travel the world from her computer and tell us what's going on in the UK for our buddies over there overseas.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_00]: I am so friggin' international.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's been an update to the World of Warcraft downloader.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, we've had a bunch of players saying, Blizzard, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: So they actually did a change with a patch of 1.10 that's meaning the downloader will run constantly even if the program is closed.
[SPEAKER_00]: So there's a quote on here from one of the World of Warcraft players from the forums.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I was playing Wednesday morning after installing the 1.0 patch, and in the middle of playing my firewall says the Blizzard downloader is still trying to make an outgoing connection.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Stealing bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I heard about the new patch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that was a worldwide thing, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: But of course, you know, things that happen in the UK and picked up over there often happen over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I didn't know about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, they're taking the BitTorrent method.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, and they've done that before, but they didn't run in the background.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds like the difference there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You knew when it was running.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, basically, when you're done downloading the patch, the connection's going to stay open so that you can share with everybody else.
[SPEAKER_00]: You are becoming part of the whole network.
[SPEAKER_00]: but you know all you're sending out is the patch content but a lot of people were saying that you know part of the agreement is that they never once agreed to offer up their services to Blizzard they're paying Blizzard for their services instead so Blizzard updated their downloader with an option that you can make it stop running in the background you can turn it off if you want to hmm
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: But yeah, I honestly think that it was a very poor practice on their part.
[SPEAKER_00]: Where I understand the logic behind it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially with such a huge patch.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not really, I don't recall seeing anything to that effect in the user agreement.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I'll look back through it again, but I really don't believe that, and you allow yourself to, you know, your bandwidth to be used for Blizzard's own purposes.
[SPEAKER_04]: But to Blizzard's credit, they've been making a lot of mistakes this year, because I can't help but think back to the, you know, politically-ish issue from a few months ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they've been pretty good about coming up with really intelligent fixes, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not always the fastest way, but at least they fixed their mistakes, unlike some companies.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, gotta hand it to them there.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else?
[SPEAKER_00]: We also have a demo for Blazing Angels on the PC.
[SPEAKER_00]: There is a 467 megabyte download available for the demo.
[SPEAKER_00]: You get to train a biplane, fire around Dunkirk and London, shoot stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um...
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll go ahead and link the demo in the chat room, but it is available at 3dgamers.com slash games slash Blazing Angels.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: We also have a demo for Galactic Civ 2 by Stardock Corporation.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's called Galactic Civilizations 2 Dreadlords.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the sequel to, I guess, the first one.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it's set in the future where you go into space.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have different factions that you choose from, different available options for customization.
[SPEAKER_00]: The demo for this is also up at 3D Gamers.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you go to 3dgamers.com slash game slash galactic civ 2 slash downloads, you can find it there as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'll also link that in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_00]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: and the last one that I have is Nintendo is offering basically their European audience a chance to air their grievances basically there was such a long delay for Animal Crossing Wild World a lot of people got very upset over this in fact
[SPEAKER_00]: There was a website opened up called Nintendo of Europe Watch to basically go over a lot of the problems, including a Hall of Fame, a Hall of Shame for good and bad release schedules.
[SPEAKER_00]: There were a few games that they mentioned that made it over there before they made it here first, like Another Code, which I had been waiting on for a while.
[SPEAKER_00]: But there are...
[SPEAKER_00]: Delays from days to months.
[SPEAKER_00]: And even with the release schedules that I've announced, there's been lots of different changes going between them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I seem to recall reading when I checked out that site that WarioWare Twisted was just coming out over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that game came out here last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that was a horrendous delay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what caused that, but they didn't get that game for six, nine months after we got it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is too bad, because it's kind of a cool game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's more interesting stuff on the DS now.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I would check out that site, Nintendo of Europe Watch, because it's a place to... I mean, it's basically giving people an opportunity to voice their concerns over the massive changes in... And even if you're in the US, you can see just how good you have it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, we really... They've been pretty much on the level with us, but then again, we can go to Washington and knock on their door.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, at the same time, we sometimes feel like we have to wait for Japan to get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we'll get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then Europe gets it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not on the top of the ladder either.
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, of course, it depends on the type of game because, of course, we get some games before Japan does.
[SPEAKER_04]: It all depends on who's making it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the last bit of news is release dates.
[SPEAKER_00]: Going over the upcoming release dates for this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: All these are going to be on the 7th.
[SPEAKER_00]: Death Jam Fight for New York, Hooray, Iron Warriors, Lara Croft Tomb Raider Legend, Magna Carta on PS2, Painkiller Hell Wars on Xbox, Polarium Advance on GBA, Top Spin 2, Auto Assault on PC, Dragon Quest VIII, Sims 2, Family Fun Stuff, Mega Man Battle Network 5.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't Def Jam Fight for New York come out here like a year ago?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I remember incessantly making fun of that title.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it's PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_00]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: I stand corrected.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We also get Tomb Raider for us.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, that's one for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_00]: But it is items.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray, the 20 millionth Tomb Raider game.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, Tomb Raider 2 I actually liked for two things.
[SPEAKER_00]: One was locking the annoying butler in the freezer.
[SPEAKER_00]: And... Because then he didn't follow you around anymore in the house.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the second is hopping up on the balcony in her main room and making her jump off and break her neck.
[SPEAKER_00]: How fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: You could also make her explode.
[SPEAKER_00]: There was a little button press code you could do to make her explode.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Eat Taco Bell?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, what's coming out in the U.S.?
[SPEAKER_03]: The U.S.?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not too much this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually pretty slow.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for the PC, you've got full Spectrum Warrior 10 hammers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only about a week late, but still pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also...
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, Double Dare 3?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty lame.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, um... Yeah, so apparently not any... What, like the Nick show, Double Dare?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Nickelodeon?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, uh, not too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: PlayStation 2-wise, you've got MLB 2K6, same also coming out on the Xbox this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, you've got for the PlayStation 2 Tourist Trophy, which is going to be the Gran Turismo of Motorcycles.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Commando Strike Force on both PC, PlayStation 2 and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: And finally, if you happen to be a fan of basketball games, NBA Ballers Phenoms finally coming out on PlayStation 2 and also on PSP from Russia with Love and Bust a Move Deluxe, which is pretty cool, and Kabbalah's Dangerous Hunts for the redneck in you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a hard time believing Bust a Move Deluxe is cool because it's going to be the same fucking game on another system.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, how many times does that game have to come out?
[SPEAKER_00]: Just go buy the Taito Collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: And why did they have to steal the name of the, you know, popular dance game?
[SPEAKER_00]: Puzzle Bobble was such a cuter name.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stupids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, if you like to play games an awful lot, you might be trying to set a new record.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Loki, you know, Twin Galaxies, one of these big sites that tracks records, what are they up to?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're up to no good, as usual.
[SPEAKER_03]: What they're doing, actually, they have a couple things going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: The first is they're actually holding a contest.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called Who's the Toughest Gun in Dodge City of Video Games.
[SPEAKER_03]: and to kind of tie in with everything, there's going to be a bunch of contests being held, kind of demonstrations to see who can get the highest score in like Dig Dug, Donkey Kong, Gorf, Galaxin, Joust, Ms.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pac-Man, Q-Bert and Zookeeper and what they're also doing is they're tying this all into the 2007 Guinness Book of World Records and
[SPEAKER_03]: and actually that Twin Galaxies is going to be tied in with the Guinness Book.
[SPEAKER_03]: So all these records will be going in the Guinness.
[SPEAKER_04]: No Burger Time?
[SPEAKER_03]: No Burger Time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Worthless!
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's kind of funny, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had to laugh because the Qbert one, they actually have this one old woman that's going to be competing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that Granny Hardcore, whatever her name is?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's one that... I can't remember her name.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I saw it in the email I got from them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pac-Man Pac-Man
[SPEAKER_04]: Double Dare 3 is actually a Nancy Drew game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which makes it worse!
[SPEAKER_00]: I wanted Mark Summers... I read Nancy Drew books when I was little.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted Mark Summers to have to explain, you know, the slime pit that he had to jump through and then get really freaked out by it because he was obsessive compulsive, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember?
[SPEAKER_04]: We all saw the 2020... Dateline, whatever the hell it was, aired that special.
[SPEAKER_04]: What does he do now?
[SPEAKER_04]: What does Mark Summers do now?
[SPEAKER_00]: He's a producer.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's a host of a show called Unwrapped on Food Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay!
[SPEAKER_03]: I should know that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You used to watch Food Network all the time.
[SPEAKER_00]: He also was a producer.
[SPEAKER_00]: In fact, I actually saw him.
[SPEAKER_00]: What was that show where they would play these massive pranks on people?
[SPEAKER_04]: Candid Camera?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, no, it wasn't that.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was another one, but he was... Punk'd?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm Mark Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just got punk'd.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, they got him to host a show on there where they were destroying this guy's car.
[SPEAKER_00]: and, I mean, they really didn't destroy his car, they destroyed a duplicate of it, but it was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, for everybody in chatroom yelling out, what would you do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, hello and welcome to, like, ten years ago, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not what he's currently doing anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think he, I think the pie pod is long gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pie pod.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fucking sad, I know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Last week, big announcement from Game Developers Conference that Nintendo Revolution was going to have Sega Genesis and TurboGrafx games on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hudson is saying that, oh, it gets better.
[SPEAKER_04]: CD-ROM 2 CD games are also going to be on the Nintendo next-gen system.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Snatcher, Night Trap, it might happen.
[SPEAKER_00]: My heart is happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what, because the Dracula...
[SPEAKER_00]: whatever, Dracula X, Rondo of Blood, Sapphire, Strider.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one that they ported over to Super Nintendo that was crap on Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_00]: It actually was fun as a game, but when you played the original... Yep, it's poop.
[SPEAKER_00]: I brought it on the show one time and played it on the webcam, remember?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was back in the three hour live show days.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we could get away with doing stuff like that because nobody was listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what else is going to be cool about the revolution?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't know if this is cool, and this is just IGN, you know, with their exclusive on what they, I guess, found out is the specs on the up-and-coming revolution system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, they're saying that it's clocked at, the CPU is clocked at about 729 megahertz, which in comparison is not quite twice that...
[SPEAKER_03]: from the Gecko CPU in the GameCube, but pretty close.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, that the Revolution GPU ATI Hollywood chip is going to be 243 MHz, which the GameCube GPU ran only at 162.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, all this together, they said it's about as powerful as a current-gen Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd have to see, because specs don't mean anything when it comes to games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you have to see what the games look like before.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could put the uber-processor of God in those machines, and it wouldn't matter if the games suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's all about the games, and if that ends up being what the specs really are, Nintendo better put their games where their mouth is.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're all about the games, or what's the surprise, or element of surprise?
[SPEAKER_04]: What was that thing he kept saying?
[SPEAKER_04]: Game?
[SPEAKER_04]: at Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_04]: Games are meant to be one thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fun for everyone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Surprise.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was that thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: He said surprise element.
[SPEAKER_04]: Displacing the scene.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember what the hell the word was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Disrupting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Disruption.
[SPEAKER_04]: Disruption.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the word.
[SPEAKER_04]: Displacing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Where the hell was my mind?
[SPEAKER_03]: Disruption gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to play your game!
[SPEAKER_03]: That's like... Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: And kudos to Bershaz, who was first in the chatroom to correct us there.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a slight delay between when we say things when the chatroom hears it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But he was the first to say, or she, sorry, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bershaz says the first to say disruptive gaming was the term there.
[SPEAKER_04]: used at the Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, really quickly, we're going to wrap this segment up.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a couple quick top ten stories that we're going to get to first.
[SPEAKER_04]: And speaking of Japan, we were talking a couple stories in this segment about Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: We haven't talked a whole lot about what their best-selling games are, but we thought tonight we'd run over their top ten sellers.
[SPEAKER_04]: No surprise there that Final Fantasy XII is at the top of their charts.
[SPEAKER_04]: In their second week, they've now sold over 2 million copies of Final Fantasy XII in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also in the top 10, at number 10, Mario Kart DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: At number 9, and I apologize in advance for this horrible pronunciation, Haru Kanaru Toki no Uchi Day 3, Unmei no Mekuyu.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's by Koei.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a company that does that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that must be another one of those Nobunaga Ambition type of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number 8, Brain Training for Adults.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number 7, English Training.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number 6, Dynasty Warriors 5 Empires.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number 5, Brain Training 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number 4, Animal Crossing Wild World in its 18th week on the Japanese charts.
[SPEAKER_04]: 2.2 million copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: At number 3, Ace Combat Zero, The Belkan War.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number 2, Pokemon Rangers Diamond and Pearl.
[SPEAKER_04]: And number 1, of course, was Final Fantasy 12 there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So very interesting.
1, 2, 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: 3 Brain Training games in the top 10 there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it has not come out here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, now, Loki, you have another top ten of sorts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Top ten games being played on the Xbox 360 or live.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kind of questioning the whole live bit of it when you'll find out.
[SPEAKER_03]: First one, of course, being Halo 2 at the top of the list.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number two is Oblivion, which I don't understand how that'd be played on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that an April Fool's joke, maybe?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because either it's got to be just counting the time that you're signed in, actually playing the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It must be that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But in which case, this chart doesn't serve the purpose I thought it did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought these charts were supposed to tell us what games people are playing online head-to-head.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't get it, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep going.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number three, Ghost Recon 3, Advanced Warfighter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number four, Call of Duty 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number five, Fight Night Round 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number six, Project Gotham Racing 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: And number seven, Perfect Dark Zero, which is surprising because the game sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people disagree with that statement, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't like it either, but a lot of people disagree with us.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going back to play the games again all the way through.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will play it, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I might change my opinion later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, though, they should be able to jump.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number 8, Battlefield 2 Modern Combat, whether that be the demo or the original Battlefield 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number 9, Dead or Alive 4, and number 10, Burnout Revenge.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, I have a hard time believing Burnout Revenge is that far down on the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: When all those games have Xbox LiveAware.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't make any sense to me either.
[SPEAKER_04]: Comment from ChatroomsGK128 says, This is probably ranked by how many games are signed on as LiveAware.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's the only way this list can be legit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I apologize if I'm pronouncing this name wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tyrico says that on Oblivion, you have the chat for live so you can get help for quests and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the LiveAware element, you can chat with your friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: For instance, you know your buddy Eric and Mel, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Mel just got on Xbox Live, and so I was playing Hexic, or, what is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Hexic, I was playing that game earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: She was sending me all these messages while I was playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was sending her voice messages back.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need to friend her.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can do the chat things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to friend them because I don't have them on my list.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll tell you where to get their names and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, you can post your names if you want to maybe be our friend.
[SPEAKER_04]: We sometimes friend people randomly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I friend everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll friend long-time listeners of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't friend people that come out of the woodwork, but I friend people who are long-time listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then if you annoy me, I'll delete you.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's on our forums.
[SPEAKER_04]: OrangeLaunchRadio.com and there's on the forums.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of which, Jason, he told me, you know, hey, add me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I sent him a friend request.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: We're using it to bring you clips from episodes you may not even be able to get anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this week, I actually went through and everybody on our friends list, I left comments in my space.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I didn't get everybody because some of your pages are really wacky and I couldn't even figure out how to add a comment.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if I couldn't figure it out in five seconds, I didn't comment you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send a message and I'll look at it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we're leaving comments with people now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that took a little while, but it's all good.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you want to get a comment on your MySpace from Orange Lounge Radio, we'd be happy to do that for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, I'm making Jamie or Loki do it next time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's www.myspace.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll have more pictures of the Humvee.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to get more picture things because we were doing picture things.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to get you guys to use your art talents because you have much more than I do, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so add us on the MySpace, myspace.com slash Orange Lounge Radio and other cool things to come to the MySpace eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's going to do it here for the first part of our podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: So stay tuned to the podcast and a little later this week will come part number two.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.