[SPEAKER_06]: Hideo Kojima's career section on Wikipedia runs full circle.
[SPEAKER_06]: The film-trained, film-producing hopeful is finally making a movie and for one of his own creations.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, that isn't news.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've known that since 2023.
[SPEAKER_06]: Presumably its production wasn't as active along Death Stranding 2's production, but that is now an impending release.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, the anime adaptation is news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep on keeping on, Norman Reedus.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now it's time for your hosts, Rob Roberts, Jamie Summers, and Loki to tell you more about this story and the rest of the week's gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Starting right now on the show, where every gamer has a voice...
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, my friends out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are live once again with episode number 1049 of our show for tonight, June the 1st of 2025.
[SPEAKER_07]: My name is Rob Roberts, and I'm joined every week by my co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Say hello, first and foremost, to the one and only DarkSakura, or Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Am I?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep, there you are now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_09]: I said hi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it didn't come through.
[SPEAKER_07]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Tired.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: At ballet rehearsal.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have recital next week, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: It certainly was fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got to watch Jamie drink a very dark beer that made her feel a little fuzzy right off the bat.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I have a shortened digestive system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, thank you, Mishi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mishi, wish me good luck at the ballet recital.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you'll get that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll get that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are doing The Witch's Road from Agatha All Along.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a fun choice.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we're doing Dancing Through Life from Wicked.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are doing the legit movie choreography for the last part of the song.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice, nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, well, let's say hello as well to the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, how are you, Loki?
Hey.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_07]: How was your weekend?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's normal.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's short.
[SPEAKER_07]: and Loki has these games that play behind him while we are broadcasting and I don't recognize this one.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says to a T. Oh, is this the new one from the Katamari guy?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it kind of looks like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I've seen that on Game Pass.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm curious about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you played it at all?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's adorable.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, I'll have to get more of your thoughts a little later when we get into our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_07]: But first off, we need to get into the news for this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we'll get into our kickoff topic.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a very interesting week we're sitting at here because we are really on the eve of a big week.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Switch 2 is going to launch this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the Switch 2 comes out on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I...
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember the last time we sat here on the eve of a system launch.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would have been like 2020 and that year was fucking weird to begin with.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this really feels like the first time in a very long time we're sitting here with people actually going to be going to the store to pick up Best Buy or wherever to pick up their consoles or maybe having it delivered though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Amazon didn't get in on the Switch 2 thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they've had some fighting.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's interesting, this whole new console feeling.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Friday...
[SPEAKER_07]: Summer Game Fest Summer Game Fest
[SPEAKER_07]: and so we're expected to get a lot of announcements out of that now of course Microsoft's doing their own thing too we have a couple other companies we'll get to that later on but we expect that there'll be quite a few announcements on Friday so this is a very big week for games so even though it didn't slow the news down for this week but we still have a lot of things to talk about but I know the Switch 2 is on everybody's mind right Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's why, of course, people are paying attention to a Russian YouTuber who has allegedly already gotten their hands on a physical console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which, I mean, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're out there already in the wild.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, you know, if retailers break street date, then...
[SPEAKER_05]: you know that you can get it so uh they've already been showing off what the console can do uh and that is not much because it needs a day one patch in order for it to actually unlock the console and allow it to play games using the cartridges and stuff like that but we got to see some menus so cool i guess um
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, menu.
[SPEAKER_05]: Menus, and it looks like the Switch.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's neat, I guess, but also it's not super early.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's next week or this week, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm less excited about it, but yeah, it is weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess it makes sense to lock the console or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does kind of suck though for the people that maybe don't have good internet or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might not be able to play any games on it until you connect it to the internet but we live in the age of the internet so I guess it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, but it's also interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: What about for people that aren't going to have internet accessibility, but I assume maybe either the date is hard coded or perhaps, uh, there's a lot of talk about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: The early switch to games, which, you know, the few that are physical.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what Mario Kart world and maybe one or two others, uh, will have some sort of firmware update in it or some sort of unlock.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is probably very small.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's probably more like a key that unlocks everything sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I mean, the system is kind of very online as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I guess online isn't required, obviously, because it's portable.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, so much of the game sales are now with these game key cards.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's almost like, I don't want to say internet connection is mandatory, but it's feeling pretty close.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just the direction that the industry is going.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the thing is, if you don't like it, you have options, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, but you have a point.
[SPEAKER_07]: Games don't leak when they are on this keycard download thing because you won't be able to download it until the official release.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it will stop games from leaking.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess in that sense, but that's more of just like digital games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't know if it's Nintendo first party stuff, obviously.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, most likely not.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, we'll still see it happen there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But to what extent, who knows?
[SPEAKER_07]: It is interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: We do not have any Mario Kart World footage outside of the official stuff and Treehouse and all that.
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't have any leaks of that game yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I don't anticipate there's going to be until the 5th of June.
[SPEAKER_07]: So maybe the 4th because of time zones and Australia will be the first to get their go at it in that region.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, now, did you decide you're going to get a Switch 2, Loki, or no?
[SPEAKER_07]: I know Jamie wasn't going to get one.
[SPEAKER_07]: You are going to get one?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alan decided he wanted to keep his pre-order.
[SPEAKER_07]: We got two just to make sure I would get one, and Alan was like, I want to have one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But he's also super into the Elden Ring, Bloodborne stuff, and so there's that one game that's coming out on Switch 2 that's going to be, yeah, for that platform, and I know he wants to play that whenever it comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there is reasons for it, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah, we have one ordered, so as long as the retailers don't screw us.
[SPEAKER_05]: So far, I mean, no cancellation emails since we pre-ordered one month ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, hopefully everything's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't see any point in getting one right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: yeah that's fair there's not a lot of really like new games out the gate there's Mario Kart and like Donkey Kong isn't until next month I'm excited for the performance improvements to old games but I also understand that's not for everybody you know no I have not touched my Switch since other than playing Just Dance with the ballet group for Fuck It Friday yeah
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm actually excited to try in a weird way I'm excited to try Pokemon Scarlet again but I'm worried that maybe I'm setting my expectations for how it's going to fix the game a little high and the performance are probably going to be nominal at best and not really fix some of the real issues I have with that game but we'll see we'll see I'm going to try to have faith but I realize I may be disappointed
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, what you're really forgetting is the true system seller for the Switch 2, and that is, of course, F-Zero GX.
[SPEAKER_07]: Being able to play that online with friends is going to be huge, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm really excited for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Soul Calibur 2, quite frankly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Both of those are really exciting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, going to a chat over at twitch.tv slash VOG Network where we do tape live every Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dolly Partner is in chat saying, I still am worried about the Switch 2 logo.
[SPEAKER_07]: It bothers me.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I saw the post on Blue Sky about that too, where the logo is, it's just a giant 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I guess there's only so many things you could do with it, but I get it, I get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see, Rinmari in chat says, I did poke my Switch yesterday for an F-Zero community championship.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, F-Zero is something I'm very hype about, the F-Zero GX.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know you're talking about 99, but yeah, excited about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm waiting for Animal Crossing, so that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that'll be huge.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's one of those things where maybe we'll see it at Summer Game Fest, but I don't want to hype it too much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it might be a little early for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think a 3D Mario game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe fall, if anything, like a direct during the fall.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't imagine a
[SPEAKER_07]: I would think an Animal Crossing would be next year at the earliest to be honest so it probably doesn't get announced till you know early next year but Nintendo would be foolish not to be working on one as we speak it was such a it sold such gangbusters I mean granted a worldwide pandemic really helped them with that and stay at home stuff but you know I think there's still enough of an audience well if you play your cards right again Nintendo you might get your second pandemic it's true
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't they just discover their first measles cases here?
[SPEAKER_07]: They have so many options.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not going to let you get a vaccine now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's whatever disease is going to come out of RFK from chugging shots of...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_07]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mass Effect and Dead by Daylight, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and Palia.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing a lot of Palia because I am working on a house on my new property that is entirely built in the air.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have, it's eight sets of stairs high with another two sets going to an upper loft.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's all also off of the property grid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Defying the laws of physics and property ownership.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because fuck their laws.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck their boundaries and all of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: To hell with the landlord.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing Fruit Mountain because I love that stupid game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm liking my same games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've really been back into Mass Effect a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm probably going to be playing Mass Effect tonight instead of Dead by Daylight because I want to wait until the new stuff comes out, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, Mass Effect 2 is only one of the greatest games ever made, so not a bad choice at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mass Effect 3 is the best, but I'm on Mass Effect 2 right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And actually, playing them back-to-back really drives home just how much better the controls for Mass Effect 2 are, but it's a lot meaner, even in casual mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I'm just playing it because, again, I just want to get to the Garrus dating part.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Garrus dating sim.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's still in the middle of calibrations, and I just want to smack him around and say, Stop!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's calibrated!
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we'll go over to Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did try to play a few things.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Two of Tea is one that I did check out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I made it through the first one and a half episodes of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like how they kind of bookend all the episodes with a little musical number.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it certainly does feel like it's out of the Katamari universe in fact it's funny the town itself that you're in initially it seems like it's like the end island of Katamari like I'm just waiting for the twist ending where this giant Katamari comes and just rolls up the whole island but wouldn't that be a gag though maybe that should happen it would be hilarious I don't think that's gonna happen since it's a different developer but um
[SPEAKER_05]: or different publisher I should say and so I don't think that they would be allowed to do that but that would be really funny so there was that and then I started up a campaign in Final Fantasy 3 or 6 essentially and I've been playing through that a little bit
[SPEAKER_05]: Not too far into that yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then also I ended up playing Smurfs for the ColecoVision just to show my kids how stupid of a game that was.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Smurfs Escape from Gargamel.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, yeah, it's a really short game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like you can beat the whole game essentially in like a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does get harder, though, as time goes on.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's yeah, it's bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the emulation controls are not good either.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, with some editing, you could have fixed all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's not much... Unless there was no mic audio.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that's what was missing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say, yeah, the music itself just loops over and over.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just the jumping sound, so it really...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, I played that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, of course, lots of Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Put out my Cracker Barrel episode thing with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's a whole, like...
[SPEAKER_05]: you mean your legally distinct Cracker Barrel legally distinct Cracker Barrel yes yes yes highly inspired so I made that and put that video out and yeah now I just need to figure out what I'm going to do next because I don't know and probably lots of planning for the large project I'm going to be working on but content wise I don't know what I'm going to do right now
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, then my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: I also played a little bit of Hylia because I've, you know, suddenly become addicted to that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So making my way through that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I definitely don't have all the fancy shit that DarkSakura has, but I have a comfy...
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll get there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a separate island.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a mechanic for the game that's very similar to some things they released in prior expansions, like Eureka.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think Bose Jan was the name of the one during, not Endwalker, but oh my gosh, everything's a blur with expansions now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shadowbringers was the thing they put with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they have this new island and it's, you know, it's neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very similar in many ways, I think, to Eureka, but a little more streamlined.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't have to worry about all the elemental stuff, but it's neat, but it's not very solo friendly.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I have to admit, that's very disappointing.
[SPEAKER_07]: is that we just really haven't had that solo-friendly hardcore casual content.
[SPEAKER_07]: Last expansion, we had the Island Sanctuary, which I found to be extremely friendly solo mid-core content that you could do and really get rewards from.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this, you can't really solo.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you can grind, but it's not really realistic.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's definitely benefits to grouping up, except Party Finder doesn't work when you're in the zone.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to say it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I know the Endwalker patches were not great with story, but at least the mechanics were decent.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the weakest expansion, period.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I really hope that, you know, the 14 team is taking some of the feedback to light and is going to be instituting some changes with future expansions.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really, you know, just hope to see a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I just don't understand why we couldn't have even had like an NPC that we could do stuff with.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a little bit...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: If you are saying MMOs are only to be played with other people and never to be played by yourself, guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a dated look.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the industry is saying very different things on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's how I feel about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But interestingly enough, the right game came around at the right time to sort of scratch that interesting, I want to play an MMO, but I want to do it on my own schedule and by my own rules.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's Fantasy Life came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe I should have waited for Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: It might have been a little bit even better on that, but it's still fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, I bought it yesterday and I've already put like six hours into the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's addicting.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I liked the DS version of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never quite...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, damn.
[SPEAKER_07]: The treasure was a childhood picture of the... That's deep.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's dark.
[SPEAKER_07]: It throws these things at you.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, I'm enjoying it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yeah, I need to unlock more of the jobs.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there's this whole side thing that's happening.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it does this whole Breath of the Wild thing where the world starts off very, very small.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then the world just explodes in size.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you're like, oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, not to spoil, but these are all things that happen in the first couple hours of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, I'm really, really enjoying it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I will definitely be playing more of it, especially this week as we lead up to the eventual release of the Switch 2, which I know is coming.
[SPEAKER_07]: So very excited about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, been playing quite a bit of Fantasy Life.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's get into some more stories.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just a quick little housekeeping note before we do though.
[SPEAKER_07]: In three weeks, we won't be here live.
[SPEAKER_07]: June 22nd will not be here live because I will be at the Southern Fried Gaming Expo in Atlanta, Georgia.
[SPEAKER_07]: and that's my first of two trips this year because I'm going to DragonCon as well I did this a couple years ago and I really enjoyed Southern Fried and I was like you know I want to go back two trips a year is hard especially when it's so close together but this year because of like baseball play this venue where they have it at is like right across the freeway from where the Atlanta Braves play so when the Atlanta Braves have a game or something's going on at that stadium the hotel's full the parking lot's full all this stuff but
[SPEAKER_07]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: And Bobby and I, of course Bobby's there because that's his backyard But Bobby and I will be doing a panel And we're going to be doing a panel on classic games Obscure kind of classic games that have not gotten enough Because it is a classic gaming expo But like things that have not gotten enough love Like there's classic games that everybody knows about But what about the really obscure ones?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well by the way, that reminds me
[SPEAKER_07]: I should mention this for my gaming week too, because I was at a friend's.
[SPEAKER_07]: My friend has one of these, I think he bought it on Amazon or one of these things.
[SPEAKER_07]: He has one of those arcade sticks, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like an arcade fighting stick, but it has a bunch of classic arcade games built in.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure it's of questionable legality.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like a Pinterest box?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's exactly what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Pandora's Box.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's what the splash screen says.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I've got one.
[SPEAKER_07]: but we also played my friend was like oh let me show you this like hella weird obscure game I bet you've never heard of and it was Pepsi Man and I was like actually oh Pepsi Man actually thanks to our classic Game of the Week segment I have heard of this game before and so we played Pepsi Man which is it's like and even those of us that were kind of playing and watching were like this was like Temple Run's inspiration right here kinda it's one of those you know there's definitely a little bit of Sonic Adventure 2 but it's
[SPEAKER_07]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's well, I don't know if I should say it's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like it's it's cheesy movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's it's that it's that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, I definitely recommend.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you know, it makes it, though, is all the live action cuts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, 100 percent.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I'm like, where is that strip mall today from the intro?
[SPEAKER_07]: That just looked like a strip mall somewhere in like probably Woodland Hills or fucking Van Nuys or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, where is that strip mall today?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: well on top of that just the original Pepsi Man commercials are hilarious so yes I had a good time with that game I'm trying to think if there's any other really obscure ones they were all playing this particular friend group of mine is really into fighting games and I will get into them once in a while but I don't I have to admit you guys I don't know them all so there is some game on PlayStation 5 that is I think based off an anime that is an up-dude version of a PlayStation 3 game
[SPEAKER_07]: and unfortunately and the characters have really funny names and like one of them shoots bubbles one of them shoots rockets from her tits like it's really funny like and that game was really fun to watch and unfortunately I could not tell you the name of it I bet if somebody shouts it out in chat I'll be like yes it was that so or I could text my friend and be like what was that game I'm gonna do that I'm gonna text my friend right now and be like what was that game we'll see if I get a response during the show
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, now I really am done with my game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, I forgot the little classic nugget there.
[SPEAKER_07]: So let's go to some more stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you play Segata Sanchiro?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it wasn't that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I did watch a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that wasn't the game that asked if you played it.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I didn't play that, but I did watch Project Justice because that new Marvel Capcom collection, or excuse me, the new Capcom collection certainly came up with, you know, Capcom SNK and all that shit in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, Loki, you can go.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got some more news regarding Pokemon Legends ZA.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's coming out in October, and they are going to be charging $10 for the Switch 2 upgrade, which is pretty common according to all the other stuff that's been released out there for the Switch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Switch 2 or those upgrades you know for the first gen stuff um along with that I guess so it looks like the 16th in Japan I'm not sure that also coincides with the 16th of October here as well in North America but maybe we'll see um and then along with that of course they also announced that the next uh Pokemon Presents is going to be July 22nd 2025 so look forward to that I guess and more news
[SPEAKER_05]: Coming out about Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really hope they drop a stealth update to updo Switch 1 Pokemon Legends for Switch 2, the Arceus.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would love that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to count on that, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pokemon Legends was so good.
[SPEAKER_07]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I might say, Derek, I say it's my favorite Pokemon game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It really was.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm really hyped for ZA.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll be buying that 100%.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really excited for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I finally stopped playing the trading card game that I was really into for a couple months.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of fell off the wagon for a few days, and then I just never brought it up again.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you know there's things to announce with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure there's other things to announce too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Would it be time for a remake?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it might be.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be the next thing that Pokemon would be due for, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's Legends, and then next year there'll be a remake for Black and White.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, would they do...
[SPEAKER_05]: more of like or even not even black and white would they do like um more of the early games like they redid for uh what was it the Eevee and Pikachu oh let's go let's go yeah there were always that rumors about like a gen 2 of that um I guess anything's possible but um I don't think that's on anyone's radar right now to be announced but that would be cute sure I mean I don't
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: and I don't know if this is like a sense of false security they've been doing a lot of interesting things in Pokemon Go lately like they allowed people to give away a quest that they would usually charge 99 cents for for free as part of a event which was cute and then like Pikmin Bloom has been looking to a lot more corporate sponsorships lately
[SPEAKER_07]: to try to kind of maintain that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: They do a lot more local events or they might turn like a local event into a worldwide thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: For example, I'm participating in the Hot Girl Walk, which starts tomorrow, which apparently is a real event like down in Santa Monica or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you are able to participate worldwide with the virtual Hot Girl Walk.
[SPEAKER_07]: So of course I'm participating.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get my hot girl on.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's, you know, that's something that
[SPEAKER_07]: It hasn't changed yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I completely understand all the reservations people have.
[SPEAKER_07]: Saudi Arabia, da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_07]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm not going to rage quit those games until there is actually an action that substantiates the rage quit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to rage quit over a hypothetical.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that was it for Pokemon Legends then.
[SPEAKER_07]: yes sure SG100 Matt does point out safe bet we'd see some Switch Online versions of classic games you know that is something we're missing and we haven't had in a while I mean we had the 3DS had the that's where like Pokemon Home kind of started you could do or it was called Pokemon Bank right you could play the classic games like Pokemon Yellow and then put your Pokemon in Pokemon Bank it would be nice if the Switch 2 would have something like that and that would be really cool if it was timed for Pokemon Legends maybe so that would be
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be a neat little thing and maybe drive some more Pokemon Home subscriptions, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, let's talk about...
[SPEAKER_07]: You want to say something?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I said, yeah, that'd be a good idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yeah, for sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, let's talk about Dragon Quest.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, we've been waiting a little bit now for the 1 and 2 HD 2D remake because, of course, last year brought us the Dragon Quest 3 HD 2D remake and it did very well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, this week it was announced that Dragon Quest 1 and 2 HD 2D will also be going to the Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have confirmed they will be making a specific Switch 2 version.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is in addition...
[SPEAKER_07]: to a Switch version of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, PlayStation 5, Xbox Series, PC and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: $60 is the price and it will be out on October 30th.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you are feeling extra spendy, you can get the exclusive collector's edition exclusively through the Square Enix store for just $150.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: You get in-game items.
[SPEAKER_07]: You get exclusive digital wallpapers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, ah.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a very vague pre-order bonus, which really could be anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I would assume maybe those Legos and having a complete collection of that might be... Or excuse me, legally distinct Legos might be alluring to some people.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you do have that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we were in for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was bound to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate that it's happening to this group.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Playtonic is having to lay off over a dozen staff.
[SPEAKER_04]: We mean, we don't really know how many staff they have.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've listed about 50 people on LinkedIn.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for those who don't remember, this is the group that did Yooka-Laylee, which is the spiritual successor to Banjo-Kazooie.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's made by former Rare staff that worked on that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I mean, this is ahead of the release of Yooka-Replaylee.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's actually kind of a clever name.
[SPEAKER_04]: so it's I mean we don't really know how big the team is um but the people that are being laid off work in production art design game design narrative design and you uh UX design so UI UX so um I mean they've had issues with with funding you know before I mean that they they
[SPEAKER_04]: They had a good track record with games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, two, yeah, they launched on Kickstarter pretty much, but we expected quality.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now I don't know what's going to happen, if they're even going to make it through everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: that's unfortunate I feel like that Yooka-Laylee did pretty really well you see it everywhere I mean yeah well they had other games yeah of course but maybe that's a sign they were giving it away at some point but still I don't know like Demon Turf, Little Gator Game a few other things but and I mean and they have their past reputation with Rare sure you know but yeah it's sad
[SPEAKER_07]: It is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially on the eve of the Switch 2 where you think would be a console that would lend itself very well to the types of games they're developing.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is very unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_04]: But look who's been tanking the economy.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's a brand new game, and I keep forgetting about this, probably because it feels like it's so far off, but Mind's Eye, it was by Leslie Benzies, who was the original designer for Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think he was a lead designer as well for Grand Theft Auto 5, and still has his game coming soon, but also looking to try to...
[SPEAKER_05]: Get people to make content for it somehow.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says the studio will support the game through PlayMind's Eye with continuous new content, but also hoping to supplement that with user-made content as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: hopefully we'll have some some of them will create compelling content and by some I mean a team at Build A Rocket Boy which is selling the game for $60 with a premium pass and stuff like that so they want me to pay for the game and also make content for it yeah I don't know this seems confusing as far as like you know how it's coming out and all that stuff but it does look like you know like a Cyberpunk Grand Theft Auto and those are two things I like so
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see how it looks when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: But right now, yeah, I don't like the idea of developers wanting people to make them content for free.
[SPEAKER_05]: Make a good game and then people will make content.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bobby Blackwolf in chat points out, that was LittleBigPlanet's entire gimmick, paid for it to make content for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean... Well, that's the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're basically making...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you're making an editor, but, like, is this that type of game?
[SPEAKER_05]: This isn't made to be, like, a little big planet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you could make that same argument with Grand Theft Auto as well because you have, like, the mission editor and, like, the race editor and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And people coming up with their deep dive roleplay content on Twitch and all that stuff is pretty wild.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's separate from all of that, but, yeah, it is...
[SPEAKER_05]: it's both of them to ask for people to pay that money and then also make content for them make a good game, people will be happy to make additional content for them if they're excited about it, they're going to make content for it don't just lead with that let it happen a little bit organically
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, well, our next story is something that ought to be completely stinking obvious, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_07]: And maybe, I don't know, maybe it isn't that obvious, but it seems pretty obvious to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that is that the Switch 2 is the cartridges they are saying with the game cards and the game key cards, they're saying, don't get them too close to magnets.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's some box art that has been released for Bravely Default Flying Fairy HD Remaster.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is a little bit of an underlined warning on the back of the box in Japanese, which says a game key card could become unusable if it comes into contact with a strong magnet.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's worth pointing out that warning is not on other game key card boxes, but I just feel like that shouldn't be completely unreasonable of a warming.
[SPEAKER_07]: You also shouldn't lick them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was thinking it was common sense, but people don't have that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, to be fair...
[SPEAKER_07]: You may not realize some magnets that you have.
[SPEAKER_07]: You may not want to put a GameKey card in your wallet if you have some type of magnetic clip on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or a lot of chargers now are magnetics.
[SPEAKER_07]: You might not want to have your GameKey cards sitting out too close to chargers and things like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you also don't want your bank cards near those things.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, it should be obvious, but maybe not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Allow me to present...
[SPEAKER_04]: Bring a lead case with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm just thinking, I mean, granted, I think it's engaged by electricity, so I don't know how strong they are outside of that, but the Switch has magnetic Joy-Cons.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I get it, that it's engaged with an electromagnet,
[SPEAKER_05]: But there is a magnet in there to get it on there, obviously.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not just always going.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's a relatively strong magnet if it's going to hold the weight of the system up.
[SPEAKER_05]: So kind of a thing that you probably should have thought about.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love the idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura said a lead carrying case, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I love the idea of a DarkSakura lead Nintendo Switch 2 carrying case.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's heavy.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you might get cancer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bobby Blackwolf in chat says, I have a MagSafe pop socket for my phone and it totally demagnetizes those paper tickets that get you in and out of parking garages.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like if I take the pop socket off my phone, the magnet there will demagnetize anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Ranmari points out that DarkSakura's lead carrying case may need a Proposition 65 warning.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, that you see on the door of like every restaurant.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's the one thing that doesn't need it.
[SPEAKER_05]: May contain lead.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does contain lead.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is lead.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is lead.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all lead.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Always has been.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go back to you, Loki, for our next story.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Fortnite finally coming out of the darkness on the App Store or well,
[SPEAKER_05]: Off the App Store because it was banned off of the Apple App Store for the longest time.
[SPEAKER_05]: But thanks to ongoing litigation, it is now back on the App Store.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can download your Fortnites and play your Fortnites through the App Store.
[SPEAKER_07]: You make it sound like Fortnite's been struggling through these dark times.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've been struggling through these dark times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you imagine all of the possible collaborations that they've had to bypass because of all the litigation and money that's gone to it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even recognize this game anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: All the spinoff games they weren't able to do with Fortnite Festival.
[SPEAKER_05]: We could have had...
[SPEAKER_05]: We could have had AI Luke and Darth Vader, but no, we had to suffer not having AI Luke and only Darth Vader because of this.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the recession that we're in.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I hope you understand, you know, the trouble we are all going through with this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to sound so old.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to sound very Gen X, boomer, whatever, saying this, but I still don't understand how somebody plays Fortnite, Battle Royale specifically, on a phone in the first place.
[SPEAKER_07]: Regardless of whether it's iPhone or Google, I don't understand
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, especially, like, don't you snipe in that game?
[SPEAKER_07]: You have sniper controls and stuff?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, it just seems like it's a pain.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I know kids do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess some adults do.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, we've all seen the videos of people sitting at, like, an important function or something, and somebody in the row in front of them is playing Fortnite.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I know people can do it, but it's just like, dang.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now I would think something like Fortnite Festival might be easier because you could like tap the screen.
[SPEAKER_07]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: That I get.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, yeah, Bobby Blackwell for chat says touch controls are natural for younger players nowadays.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's wild.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do your kids play Fortnite on mobile or like iPad or one of those types of things, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: They do not touch their tablets.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we got them nice tablets one year, and that lasted for about a year, and then they got laptops the next year, and then those tablets have never been used again.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they don't play Fortnite.
[SPEAKER_05]: They play dumb shit on Roblox.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're still playing... What was it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Forsaken, which is that... It's like a knockoff...
[SPEAKER_05]: Dead by Daylight and then they also play I Saw My Son Hanging Out in that Grow a Garden just only because it's popular not because he wants to but because it's memeable right now there's like 11 million players on that thing which is stupid but yeah that trash is they've been playing Forsaken for days now days I'm like why don't you just play the regular Dead by Daylight but no
[SPEAKER_07]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And all the killers are like, they're all Roblox lore.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's like the hackers and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like the...
[SPEAKER_05]: Classic, like, noob and stuff is one of the survivors or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know I've seen, because it comes off around my TikTok once in a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen, like, the Roblox, like, Dead by Daylight sort of port, like, with the Huntress and, like, killers that actually exist in Dead by Daylight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, that they're playing in Roblox, which is wild to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I also, the one I get most often on TikTok that does, I will admit, it makes me laugh.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's people that are playing Squid Games.
[SPEAKER_07]: because there's some type of like Squid Games port on there and they're just screaming going bananas in those games because, you know, in the new season there's the one where they have to get so many people in a room or they get locked out, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I get video upon video of people playing that and screaming it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have the new trailer out for season three.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jump rope's in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't watch that.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, I got an answer to my earlier question.
[SPEAKER_07]: What was the game I saw that started as a PS3 game, the fighting game?
[SPEAKER_07]: The answer is it was called JoJo's Bizarre Adventure All-Stars Battle R. Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that sounds about right.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds like a JoJo game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, DarkSakura, we'll go back to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is it that I'm delivering all the bad news?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, the Black Panther game got cancelled.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and thank you EA for being shitty again.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have actually ended the studio that's behind it, Cliffhanger Games, that was formed by former Monolith productions leaders.
[SPEAKER_04]: but yeah the cuts are being instituted quote to sharpen our focus and put our creative energy behind the most significant growth opportunities I mean um
[SPEAKER_07]: If the game was bad and wasn't doing Black Panther justice... Yes, this news is frustrating because we... You didn't say anything about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we get layoff story after layoff story after layoff story, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: But if the game was on track to be a Suicide Squad type of arrival type of game...
[SPEAKER_07]: I can understand why EA games get cancelled sometimes sometimes it's quality, sometimes it's market demand but I don't think it's that I think people would have ate the fuck up out of a Black Panther game so I'm left to believe in the lack of any specifics because everything in this industry is so goddamn secretive I'm left to infer, believe that the game must not have been up to a certain level of quality and again, this was these screenshots look amazing
[SPEAKER_07]: it was almost certainly not the fault of the developers on the front line but probably some type of monetization direction they were trying to go with in the game and you know how that always gets things fucky especially at EA so you know it's a bummer
[SPEAKER_04]: It actually looks like there was some concept art and some... Looks like some other stuff from within the game that make it look really gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that it was... You were going to be playing as T'Challa's son and you were going against Skrulls.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, I mean, it honestly looks...
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, let's talk about another feature of the Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Just needing that little extra power to do a very simple graphic filter melted the Switch 1.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, but it's something that's only going to be available on Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then you can also view and change controls, meaning remap all of the buttons, which ought to be fucking standard for anything, but okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that, no, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I correct myself, that feature will also be on original Switch when it rolls out.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm going to pull it back a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: So at least there will be the remapping ability on Switch and Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that is all coming with the release of the Switch 2 on June 5th.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't have to wait any longer for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: so I think I think it's funny I think there are a lot of people that like one of the first things they're going to play on their Switch 2 is like F-Zero GX and like the classics and stuff because again I can't wait for multiplayer on that stuff it's gonna be fun all right well speaking of classic stuff let's go to our bumper for the next segment
[SPEAKER_03]: And now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where I'll dive into the vault and pull out a classic and tell you about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's time for the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, but once a month, DarkSakura flips the script a little bit and says, you know what, we're going to do a game that is a console to arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: It originally was on consoles, but went to the arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I never even realized this company ever made any arcade games ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: So let's hear more about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so first of all, the game in question came out in 1994 in the arcade from a console game, and it is Battletoads Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it had also been known as Super Battletoads or just Battletoads, but it is a side-scrolling beat-em-up arcade game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was developed by Rare and published by EA.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is up to three players, and you go through six levels to save the universe from the Dark Queen.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have vertical levels, bonus levels, everyone has their own attack, and they've also got some fourth wall breaking funds.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said funds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Rare went a little bit more with the violence on this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was their first game to use 3D graphics that was later implemented in Donkey Kong Country and Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_04]: The gameplay tested pretty well and seemed viable but there was some hesitation behind releasing it and it ended up being unsuccessful and so Rare cancelled any ports that they had including a completely finished and tested Game Boy version.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, actually this game was the reason that there had been no more Battletoads until 2020.
[SPEAKER_04]: it has since been released on console when it was emulated for Rare Replay it came out in 2015 a compilation of Rare games on Xbox One and people were like
[SPEAKER_04]: Really surprised at just how high quality the arcade release was and thought it was one of the best ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a really good quality game.
[SPEAKER_04]: The highlight of the series, they said.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of that package, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: you know, you have the usual Battletoads stuff, you eat flies to regenerate health you beat stuff up, you know and each level has a unique name, like you have Christmas Grotto and some of the bosses from earlier games come back, like General Slaughter and
[SPEAKER_04]: but it seemed that Rare developed it directly it was published by EA in 1994 it's the fifth Battletoads game they were really trying to follow the success of the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles arcade game
[SPEAKER_04]: and they were also experimenting with 3D graphics that were using an application called Power Animator which later on became Autodesk Maya which I took some college classes in and it was their first rare game that used this and of course as I said earlier it was later implemented in Killer Instinct and Donkey Kong Country the game
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: so for the rare replay version that I mentioned earlier they did put in the setting for Unlimited Continues a rewind and replay and a save game progress at any time but they said it bombed badly they said the sales were mediocre and the arcade release rode on the success of the console games and just did not do it um
[SPEAKER_04]: and it was though given a 4 out of 5 stars by some reviewers even comparing it to Turtles in Time and Simpsons Arcade and has been since considered while relatively obscure it's the best in the series and an absolute swan of a rare game
[SPEAKER_04]: It was put on par with the games from Konami and Sega and said it was humorous and funny and that it was absolutely a blast to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: So why it didn't do better?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's why you don't hesitate!
[SPEAKER_04]: as far as its legacy like I said the franchise did go on hiatus after this game and the re-release was 26 years later with a 2020 series reboot and then Rare considered doing a possible sequel in the mid 2000s but they really didn't want to make a failure like at the time the TMNT reboot had been
[SPEAKER_04]: so but their expectations were low but people wanted it and so the newer ones caught on and this one sort of fell into obscurity until that compilation release so there you go, Battletoads Arcade
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, great pick.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kind of with some folks in chat who this was just not on their radar.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm almost embarrassed to say it, but I never realized they did an arcade version of this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: TigerClaw says, never played the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would assume it has those difficult stages later on.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, that would be one way to get your quarters, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I should say that this was not really a port from any of the home versions, but it was a home franchise that came out in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right, yeah, it looks way better than the home versions, to be quite honest.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, yeah, it looks great.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they used, like, you know, they were using early...
[SPEAKER_07]: 3D in these games yeah I always love that in the Battletoads games where like the giant like fist or the giant like shoe that comes out and kicks people I always thought that was such a neat piece of flair in the Battletoads games but yeah you know and I when I originally had brought up your long play of this and saw the Electronic Arts logo I was like
[SPEAKER_07]: Did they ever have arcade games?
[SPEAKER_07]: But I actually was corrected in chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkTetsuya said EA had a few arcade games.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was a Madden game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess I should have assumed that was a thing at some point.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a couple of the Need for Speed games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, of course, those.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I did neglect those.
[SPEAKER_07]: Got arcade ports randomly.
[SPEAKER_07]: But still, it's not often you see the Electronic Arts logo on an arcade game.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a very special sort of release, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Neat pick.
[SPEAKER_07]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Battletoads, your classic console to arcade game of the month.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: With that, let's move into some rapid fire news and talk about some other headlines real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, we'll go to you first.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have some more details regarding the Switch game compatibility with the Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had kind of a long list of games that weren't supported initially.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now, at least of first-party games, that has been whittled down to quite a few games that are not compatible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Only like five we have, so not too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, the most obvious, Nintendo Labo VR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just not going to work because the headset is just completely a different size.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that makes perfect sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, you can still do Nintendo Labo Toy-Con 1, 2, and 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just have to use that with the original Switch Joy-Cons instead because of the IR stuff and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other games that are not compatible, their first party, Nico Nico, Abma, Hulu, Crunchyroll, and Inkypen.
[SPEAKER_05]: are the five apps or whatever that are not compatible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other games that also require the Switch 1 Joy-Cons, Rig Fit Adventure, 1-2 Switch, Everybody 1-2 Switch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just do yourself a favor and don't get those.
[SPEAKER_05]: Game Builder Garage, Nintendo Switch Sports, WarioWare Move It, and then, of course, Nintendo Labo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can definitely guess by WarioWare Move It, Switch Sports, and I'm guessing the other ones, it's all because of that IR sensor.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why you need the other ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Third party, there's a lot more stuff outside of that, but that's at least what you have for first party stuff.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: uh yeah Bobby Blackwolf in chat points out to be fair with many of these it's just certain features so yeah like certain yeah mini games in WarioWare are not going to work and things like that but it's important to know before you get into it especially when we talk about a very big backwards compatible library it's not all encompassing so uh DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: So, well, there's going to be more Death Stranding stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kojima revealed that there is an anime in the works.
[SPEAKER_04]: He just put it out, says, I'm currently working with A24 on a live-action film adaptation, he said.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the next quote is this, when it comes to adapting games into visual media, there are works like The Last of Us, which stay true to the original storyline, and films like the Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: movie, which is more of a service to fans of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to keep reading.
[SPEAKER_04]: all these works have their own merits as a film enthusiast I want to pursue the expressive potential of cinema I aim to create a Death Stranding that can be realized through film one could win awards at films like the Cannes Festival or Venice Festival in fact we are also currently working on an anime adaptation he's really ambitious for this he really really wants this to be a thing but you know the first game did pretty well yeah so yeah
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, well, I have some news on the Evercade front.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, I'm a casual fan of the Evercade stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like collecting them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have one behind me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a little hard to see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sometimes we're broadcasting live.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I have one of these little smaller cabinets.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's, I guess, a bar top arcade is what they call it, an alpha machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I have one that's Capcom, specifically Mega Man branded, and there's also a Street Fighter one that has games baked into the machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not on cartridge, but they're games baked into the machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably that's the only way they can get the license rights or whatever for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it turns out Taito is going to be teaming up with Evercade, and there's going to be a Taito-themed Bartop Arcade coming that is going to be Bubble Bobble-themed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I guess by default, but the little light box above...
[SPEAKER_07]: They send you little sheets, little plastic sheets for all the games in the collection.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I could make this a Strider cabinet if I wanted to because they gave me a sheet for that and all the games that are in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I would assume the title will have multiple besides just Bubble Bobble, but I don't want to assume either.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we do know the games that will be in the bar top will be Bubble Bobble, Kadash, Elevator Action, The Fairyland Story, Growl, The Legend of Kage, The New Zealand Story, Puzzle Bobble, Rastan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love New Zealand Story.
[SPEAKER_07]: and Space Invaders.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, what's also interesting is that if you, I mentioned that it was probably due to rights that they're baked in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, they will be doing separate Taito cartridges.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the bar top arcade is pre-ordered on May 30th.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it already happened.
[SPEAKER_07]: It will go for either 200 euros.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, 200 pounds, 220 euros or $250.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder why the dollars are more this time.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't usually see that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder what happened.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks, Trump.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it will be launching in November.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to get the cartridges separately, you can.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can get separate cartridges and you would actually get more games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Taito Arcade 1.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want both of these cartridges, especially when I tell you the lineup.
[SPEAKER_07]: Taito Arcade 1, Bubble Bobble, Chack and Pop, Colony 7, Dandoko Dawn,
[SPEAKER_07]: Growl, Space Invaders, Pirate Pete, Ranma S, and The Legend of Kage.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Arcade 2 has Alpine Ski, The Electric Yo-Yo, Elevator Action, Kiki Kaikai, Liquid Kids, Rastan, Operation Wolf, The New Zealand Story, and Volfied.
[SPEAKER_04]: That second one sounds better because Kiki Kaikai, I mean, that was Haki and Raki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yeah, so that's coming September, and those cartridges will cost you 20 euros, I'm sorry, 20 pounds, 25 euros, or $30.
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, now we feel the pain of the dollars being more than the others because of who we elected.
[SPEAKER_07]: by the way I have more actually this is turning not so rapid but uh there's just a lot of Evercade news this week we know more Neo Geo cartridges are coming we already heard about Neo Geo Arcade 1 but we also announced uh this week in October Neo Geo Arcade 2 with Artifighting 2, Crossed Swords, Garou Mark of the Wolves, Metal Slug 2, Ninja Commando, and Sengoku 2
[SPEAKER_07]: and Neo Geo Arcade 3 with Ghost Pilots, Metal Slug 3, Samurai Showdown 2, Super Sidekicks, King of Fighters 97 and Twinkle Star Sprites.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Twinkle Star Sprites.
[SPEAKER_07]: All coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And those will be again, 20 pounds, 25 euros, $30.
[SPEAKER_07]: or DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile... Maybe the world will burn.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, let's move on to world release dates and check out what else is coming out a little sooner than those Evercade cartridges.
[SPEAKER_07]: This week, busy week, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's...
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a new console coming.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's going to be a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Switch 2 stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I hope you're ready for Switch 2 things.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we've got Rise of Industry 2 on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_05]: Arcade Archives 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ridge Racer on Nintendo Switch 2, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bravely Default Flying Fairy HD Remaster on Nintendo Switch 2 Civ 7 on Switch 2 Cyberpunk 2077 Ultimate Edition on Switch 2 Deltarune Chapter 3 and Chapter 4 on PC, Mac, Nintendo Switch, Switch 2 PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 5
[SPEAKER_05]: Etheria, Restart on PC, iOS, and Android Fantasy Life I, The Girl Who Steals Time on Switch 2 Fast Fusion on Switch 2 Fortnite on Switch 2 Hitman, World of Assassination Signature Edition on Switch 2 Wizarding Franchise Legacy on Switch 2 Kunitsu, Agami, Path of the Goddess on Switch 2
[SPEAKER_05]: The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild Nintendo Switch 2 Edition and Legend of Zelda Tears of the Kingdom Nintendo Switch 2 Edition on the Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mario Kart World on the Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have Nintendo Switch 2 Welcome Tour.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just don't buy that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobunaga's Ambition Awakening Complete Edition on Switch 2 and PlayStation 5 Puyo Puyo Tetris 2S on Switch 2 The Red Bell's Lament on Nintendo Switch Rune Factory Guardians of Azuma on PC, Nintendo Switch, and Switch 2
[SPEAKER_05]: We have Split Fiction on Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sonic X Shadow Generations on Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Street Fighter 6 on Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Suikoden 1 and 2 HD Remaster.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gate Rune and Dunin Unification Wars on Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Survival Kids also Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yakuza 0 Director's Cut on Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dragon is Dead coming out of Early Access on PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zenless Zone Zero on Xbox Series Alien Hominid HD and Alien Hominid Invasion on PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 5 and that's it
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I'm going to just keep it real.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to just say ditto for the Switch 2 releases for Japan because it's a very similar list worldwide and let's be real, I'm not going to read through that entire list of releases.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're just going to say ditto on Japan and UK, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I will just peak quickly.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do want to
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at PlayStation 5 in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: also on June 5th.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that may be of interest to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Saga Frontier 2 Remastered also gets a physical release in Japan on the PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nobunaga's Ambition Rebirth also hits Japan this week on the PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: So otherwise, I'm just going to say ditto on the Switch 2 launch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, anything you want to clarify with UK outside of Switch 2?
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe I answered that question already.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there's nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: All the same!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's one thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's Tour de France 2025 on June 5th.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Pro Cycling Manager.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you get to spin the sticks so hard you break your thumb on those games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, actually, no, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's an early access for Dune Awakening for PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, just a couple more stories and we'll get to the listener roundtable.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we have an email or two.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, one email and then we'll get to any of your questions in chat or otherwise.
[SPEAKER_07]: So let's get to Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you know how Nintendo has their news app that they put out?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they're trying to prevent people from sharing the news from the news app.
[SPEAKER_05]: They will actually black out the screen with the data, so preventing you from sharing the stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, there are ways around that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And why wouldn't they want you to share the news?
[SPEAKER_05]: So you'd have to go to the app, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's the paywall.
[SPEAKER_07]: Silly.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's silly.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fucking stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I understand that people need to get paid.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I understand people need to get paid, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Windows or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's dumb.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a dumb hurdle to get through for the casual person that's excited about your games and wants to share their excitement with other people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can't have that.
[SPEAKER_05]: God forbid, lock it all down.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, and it's just an example, again, about this industry isn't transparent enough sometimes.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it gets extraordinarily frustrating.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I understand the reason for some secrecy, but like the lack of transparency on some of the decisions that are made is just, you know, fine, you leave it to us to make up.
[SPEAKER_07]: When you're not transparent, you let us fill in the gaps and we're going to just say you're ignorant.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's where we land with this particular headline.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this is...
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be great to have more insight, but we're never going to get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do want to sort of remind people here at the end, Summer Game Fest is next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we have a lot of stuff that's coming that's not just that main event that's happening on Friday at 2 Pacific, 5 Eastern from the Keelyverse, which, by the way, we are going to co-stream here on VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_07]: usually I can't do these types of things because they're during the day for me but I'm doing some different things at work and I'm going to be working a new schedule where I'm actually going to have Friday off so by a nice coincidence I am able to do this co-stream with Bobby Blackwolf so we're actually going to be watching the Summer Game Fest Keeley information I'm expecting it's probably going to be like four hours it's probably something ridiculously long but that is you know something to look forward to but that's not all there are a lot of other
[SPEAKER_07]: Game Showcase is coming.
[SPEAKER_07]: June 7th at 1pm, we have Green Games Showcase.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shining a light on environmental issues and how to contribute to real world causes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess a little bit of PSA type information for the gaming industry.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm curious if maybe it'll get into anything about how to make the games industry more green, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: We also have Frosty Games Fest.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the joke is it is currently winter in Australia and New Zealand.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so we have Frosty Game Fest that's going to be focusing on Australia and New Zealand types of games and things that have been built in those areas.
[SPEAKER_07]: That will be on June 8th at 9 a.m.
[SPEAKER_07]: Australian.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's Australian Eastern Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's Sydney's time zone.
[SPEAKER_07]: So AEST.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's 11 a.m.
[SPEAKER_07]: New Zealand.
[SPEAKER_07]: We also have the Xbox Games Showcase.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is going to be Sunday, June 8th.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the morning before our next show.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a 10 a.m.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pacific though, so that's nice and early.
[SPEAKER_07]: But of course they want the worldwide views because that's more the evening time in Europe when that is going to air.
[SPEAKER_07]: We also have the Southeast Asian Games Showcase is also happening.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't currently see the date and time on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I believe it's June 7th.
[SPEAKER_07]: at, what time?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have a time on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I found it, 3 p.m.
[SPEAKER_07]: Eastern.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's all on a YouTube live stream for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: We also have the Latin American Games Showcase, June 7th at 11 a.m.
[SPEAKER_07]: 50 indie games in that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have the Women-Led Games Showcase coming back for its second year.
[SPEAKER_07]: That will be June 7th at 10 a.m.
[SPEAKER_07]: on Twitch and YouTube, also through IGN and GameSpot.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you check that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, that same team is also doing a Steam sale that is going to start June 6th and run through the 13th, also to support Women-Led Games.
[SPEAKER_07]: So lots and lots.
[SPEAKER_07]: We also have a Devolver Direct event
[SPEAKER_07]: I know Loki loves his Devolver Directs and many of you do.
[SPEAKER_07]: That will be there.
[SPEAKER_05]: They get weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: June 6th at 8.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nothing is ever going to be the year that they put out a playable game that was like E3 Walking Simulator.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_07]: June 6th at 8 p.m.
[SPEAKER_07]: Eastern for that Day of the Devs will also be indie games, of course, will be happening June 6th.
[SPEAKER_07]: 7pm Eastern for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Busy, busy, busy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I hit all the big ones that I know of.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are we going to get a surprise Nintendo Direct maybe?
[SPEAKER_07]: I wouldn't hold your breath.
[SPEAKER_07]: I feel like because the system's coming out, you might get one announcement or two to remind people it's out, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I almost worry a Nintendo Direct would be bad news because it could be a price increase because of everything going on now that the pre-orders have been filled.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: and don't count anything out I suppose but um yeah there'd be a lot of other noise going on right now I feel like if Nintendo just kind of waits a week they could really take the narrative next week you know what I mean so we'll see uh one more direct uh sorry a wholesome direct June 7th at 12 p.m.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know they've had these uh games before these are your cozy games
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, it's not just the big Keeley event.
[SPEAKER_07]: There are all of these indie things happening.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or, you know, maybe more like, you know, not quite AAA studios, but, you know, the next tier.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also making announcements through these things.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's big.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dark Tootsie is saying Nintendo will be at Summer Game Fest.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I mean...
[SPEAKER_07]: Why wouldn't they want to remind people the Switch 2 is out?
[SPEAKER_07]: And maybe there could be a little stealth drop they do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe an update to the classic game library or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe there's your Pokemon idea that came up earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although I think that would get saved for the Pokemon Direct.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you never know.
[SPEAKER_07]: There could be just something a little... We're going to give away that Nintendo Tour for free.
[SPEAKER_07]: Haha, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's get to the listener roundtable.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every week we encourage your emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: Participate at OrangeOnRadio.com is the place to send us emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we'll go to DarkSakura for the reading of the email.
[SPEAKER_04]: The reading of the email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dear OLR, it's your girl Mishi.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wanted to say thanks for the well wishes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doing better.
[SPEAKER_04]: First night back from the hospital.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, enough about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am really enjoying this team deck a lot more than I thought I would.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you have any questions, please don't hesitate to ask and I'll do my best to answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wanted to say thanks for the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And as always, I look forward to the show every Sunday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay awesome and game on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sincerely yours, Mishi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Mishi had a little bit of medical ups and downs this week that I saw on Blue Sky.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm really glad you're in chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're with us tonight and chatting away.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I know that means you're feeling good enough to be here.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I appreciate seeing you and having your presence here tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: And congratulations on the Steam Deck.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have any questions because I also have one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, my question is, have you tried the adventure of sideloading emulators yet?
[SPEAKER_07]: If you need some tips, I'll help.
[SPEAKER_07]: There are some things that make it easier, but you're going to want to read the instructions unlike what I did because I got lost.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because you need to read the fucking instructions.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I didn't do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I own it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I own it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Mish says is in chat and says, I would have found a way to watch the show for the emergency room.
[SPEAKER_07]: I appreciate that, but please take care of your health first.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why this is a podcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really okay if you're not here live.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's many people that have never been here live that have been listening to this show for a very long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we appreciate all of them as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: So thank you, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well thanks for the email.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to send us an email in a future week, participate at OrangeLoungeRadio.com is the place to send the email.
[SPEAKER_07]: We also, at this part of the show, enjoy taking your calls in our green room at VOGnetwork.com slash Discord.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I would encourage you to join our Discord and talk with us throughout the week over at VOGnetwork.com slash Discord.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of stories and a lot of the insight I kind of get on how y'all are feeling about it is because I read our Orange Lounge Radio channel and our general channel and the other stuff on the Discord channel throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: The admins have a no ping philosophy on Discord because we know so many Discords ping you every five minutes.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we've made a decision.
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't ping.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we have a channel if you want to see all the pingable announcements.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's an announcements channel when new shows and things drop.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we will let you choose when you want to look at that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But otherwise, yeah, so if you're worried about that, just join.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come join the party with us on Discord, vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we can take your calls like we're going to do right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure this person wanted to call in last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really want to talk to this person tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: So let's go to the telephone lines, the modern ones, and say hello.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, it's the Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Ranma, good to see you.
[SPEAKER_07]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Good, how about y'all?
[SPEAKER_07]: Good, welcome back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I recognize your shirt.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a shirt from Super Nintendo World, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the extra large, I just put it on a minute ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, oh, it's a lot roomier than I thought it would be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's a different design.
[SPEAKER_07]: So to describe for our podcast listeners, he's wearing a green Luigi t-shirt, and it has, I'm assuming, Luigi written in Japanese below that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's mostly green, but imagine more of a tank top sports shirt type of fit, but then the extended sleeves are blue.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which I think is interesting I know, I know, but the extended sleeves are blue The green is in that shape of a sports shirt I know, I just love the way that looks It looks like one of the VOG Network shirts we used to have That I really liked And there's also a Mario version too, which is really cool Yeah, and I have the Bowser hat I have a Bowser hat around here Actually, wait, I think it's right over here
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the funny thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, I bought my Bowser hat from when I was there, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: The hat that I'm wearing, it is a Luigi bucket hat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got this hat at a convention earlier this year, and I said, this is going to be my Japan hat.
[SPEAKER_02]: For two straight weeks, I had people on the street just point and go, Luigi or Mario.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've had tourists just come by and say the hat is awesome and give me high fives.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am in random people's selfies with this hat.
[SPEAKER_02]: People thought I got it from Universal, but I didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: But when you go to Universal, they have a reversible bucket hat for Mario and Luigi.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's so funny that you ended up in selfies and stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's so cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, I have a group of friends from online and some of the games I used to play that I'm following the Instagram stories of their adventures in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like they're having such fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: And one of them said, we just got interviewed by a third grade class.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I guess people will really just walk right up to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are a lot of people at Narita and Haneda that will just interview tourists that are coming in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, how is Japan?
[SPEAKER_02]: was great now here's the thing I really wanted to call in while I was running around Osaka and Akihabara we just figured you were asleep the gaming stores but here's the thing 99% of the gaming stores open around 10 and 11 o'clock in the morning which is around the time you guys sign off sure
[SPEAKER_07]: No, we figured, and I, you know, last week I was like, well, Ranma said he wanted to call in, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: He's probably having fun and has better things to do than talk to us right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll hear from him later.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I figured you wouldn't call in.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bull and shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me tell you, the first week there, my entire sleep schedule was thrown off by a few hours, which I was perfectly okay with because I woke up around...
[SPEAKER_02]: between 5 and 6, showered, relaxed, went to the Denny's across the street and had a damn good breakfast.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I did.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really want to go to Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I've been saying this for a long time, but like the closer I get to 50, the more I'm like, I just need to fucking go.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I think that's, I don't know if it's going to happen next year because Alan and I are still trying to plan a Europe cruise, but maybe the year, maybe for my 50th birthday, who fucking knows.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I would just, I would really just love to go, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'd be so fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just do not go between May and September.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: because it is sweltering hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I discovered that the hard way and thanks to one of my friends, I had to stop into Don Quixote and pick up these deodorant body wipes called Gatsby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gatsby also makes the hair products I use, the moving rubber.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: These are a godsend.
[SPEAKER_04]: They also sell those at Oto's in town.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure you're probably going to do more of a full recap on your show, Anime Jam Session, on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_07]: But what were some of the highlights of your trip, especially gaming-related things?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like Nintendo World.
[SPEAKER_07]: How was Nintendo World in Japan?
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw the photo of you trying to get into the cart, and unfortunately, too bad, puffy American boy, no ride for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still have fun because I was mostly there more for the ambience and the environment.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: You really didn't miss the ride.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's cool, but you'll be okay, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of my friends, she actually got me a personalized power band, so it was my name and Katakana on it, so that's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I love that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: so I did try to do the whole three keys thing but we ran out of time for a small area Super Nintendo World is there are some pretty long lines and stuff so I did do one ride there I did the Detective Conan 4D Theater Adventure which was kind of fun I would have never thought all the different rides different movies over there well if you're into Jaws there's still the Jaws theme area that's still there nice
[SPEAKER_02]: we're gonna need a bigger boat but um I did get some gaming stuff, not a lot I was trying to track down a couple of video games but a couple of the super potatoes I went to didn't have them but I will say this you will find tons of retro consoles floating around if you're looking to save a few dollars if you don't want a Japanese console I can take that
[SPEAKER_02]: I did stop by the Capcom Cafe and Mako-chan asked for a special request of something.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I assume we've all played Resident Evil, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: At some point in our life, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know how the herbs will give you, restore your energy and abilities and so forth?
[SPEAKER_00]: How about the herbs as teas?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that's a cute idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a cute idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Green, blue, red, and lemon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, yellow.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I picked these up for her.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now you can have literally herbal tea.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I went and picked up a couple of some albums.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I would have to say I have seen the Super Mario Brothers movie at least five times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once in theaters.
[SPEAKER_02]: three times streaming and once on Blu-ray I actually have a CD version and all the limited edition Blu-rays that each retailer was putting out because that's how much I loved it so I feel you on the whole Mass Effect 3 thing so while I was in Japan and I was popping through some CDs and stuff like that and I apologize for the loud sound because the mic is right here so I picked up what did we talk about
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I picked up a lot more CDs than I thought I did.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, um... Oh, that was my controller.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have plenty more.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I picked up... There is a series of remix CDs, anime CDs, that came out in the early 2000s called Power Power Max.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I end up finding... Yeah, I know those.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: And one of them was only 300 yen.
[SPEAKER_07]: I swear to God, one of those CDs you held up I've seen before.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think Jamie had it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me make sure because I think those are the ones I have.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's like a... Yeah, I have like a box set of those.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have the Tatsunoko one too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, there's a Tatsunoko one?
[SPEAKER_01]: I did not know about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Tatsunoko one is like 10 years old.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and those are the four that I picked up.
[SPEAKER_02]: and while I was there, and I think this one you'll appreciate, Jamie, I grabbed this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Describe what you're holding up for the podcast, folks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was getting to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm holding up as a single to the song Equal Romance by the group Coco, which is that first ending, no, second ending theme to Ranma 1.5.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep, that is classic right there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that was only...
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, I didn't even pay them 700 yen.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I mean, CDs are really expensive, but the market for CDs is still pretty booming from what I understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I did pick up both Persona 5 soundtracks for a friend because she's really into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I did get this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did pick up the Super Mario Brothers movie Japanese soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just had to.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish I could have gotten that Firebomber one, but I do have a bunch of Firebomber CDs already.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ranmari in chat is asking what store this all came from.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Super Mario CD came from the Surugaya in Akihabara, which is like right by the Pachinko place.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's where I found a couple of the Max CDs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's Equal Romance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's where I actually found them all at.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I went over to Animate.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have like a little section for CD, for gaming soundtracks and CDs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's called Grate or Grato.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I went back and I picked up the Super Mario Brothers movie soundtrack on vinyl.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's incredible.
[SPEAKER_07]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, I'm walking by and I saw, I'm like, I have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, I'll come back for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I came back and I picked it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is what I got for my... These are the bags that you get at Universal, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very similar to what they give here, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of my friends... On a side note, one of my friends... Her favorite Sanrio character is one of the rarest ones to find stuff for, Choco Cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just happened to be in a Mega Don Quixote in Nagoya, and I found this purse for her, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: I find ChocoCat stuff at Daiso out here a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, that does not surprise me, because I found a lot of ChocoCat stuff at Universal when I went back in December.
[SPEAKER_02]: But because ChocoCat's not that popular in Japan, you're not going to find much on that character, which was kind of shocking that I found stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I keep looking for Little Twin Stars stuff, because that's my jam.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw some stuff here in Little Twin Stars, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, Ranma, when are you planning your next trip?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm actually thinking next year because this time around, I have a few more friends in Japan and I want to spend more time hanging out with them because there's a few I have not seen in years.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because one of the things that happened with my trip this year was the friend that came with me was, this was like her related birthday gift from her parents and the trip was my birthday gift to myself, so we ran into a lot of
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to do a lot of culture stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to do a lot of weeb stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there was a lot of compromises made here and there and some stuff had to get cut off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I have at least one friend moving to Japan, maybe two in the next year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, it's a big country.
[SPEAKER_07]: They may not be in the same place, but they have the transit to get you there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, I love the transit system.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have three different tap cards.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think there's six different tap cards, but they all work one with each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just certain areas have certain ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that the Suika was the major one for just about everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, technically it is, but I have a Suica, I have a Pasmo, and an Iokoka card.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they all work one and the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just that different regions promote certain different ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I want to do when I get to go?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to do what I am dubbing the Ekibentor.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Ekibentor?
[SPEAKER_04]: Where I eat at every train station I can and have their signature bento.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, riding the Shinkansen with a bento and a drink was top tier for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, SJ100Bat was asking about games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will tell you the same thing when it comes to looking for games as is looking for, like, anime merch and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: I may...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, what would you say, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Go on, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say, people would actually hate, I think, going with me, because one of the big things on my, like, bucket list is the Shikoku Pilgrimage.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Shikoku Pilgrimage?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an island of about 88 temples, and you walk the island and get stamped at each of the temples that you go to.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a couple of days of a hike, and you can sometimes stay at some of the different shrines.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know where I put it.
[SPEAKER_02]: is probably my bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: The closest thing to stamping I did was you can get stamped at the different train stations as you travel.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I want to do that too.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the stampers are outside, others are inside.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you don't see them, if you ask the station master, they'll tell you where to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: When it comes to deals, I'm going to tell you this right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you see something good in Akihabara, write it down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Went to Nakano Broadway, found it sealed for $1,680.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's even better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you're online and you see like these awesome T-Mode style, all these anime figures that are going for $30 and $40 and so forth, understand that's two to three times the retail price in Japan because it's covering cost of shipping and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here...
[SPEAKER_02]: These figures are rare.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are unique.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are one of a kind.
[SPEAKER_02]: In Japan, it's a dime a dozen.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are basically Tonka Toys in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to say Tonka Toys, but basically that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Figures I've paid, I was going to pay anywhere between $30 and $40.
[SPEAKER_02]: I paid no more than $11 to $10 to $15 a pop.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's easier to eat cheaper.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you're looking for rare games, yes, start in Akihabara, but go to the book-offs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check for the book-off super bazaars, the book-off pluses.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those will have a larger selection of retro games.
[SPEAKER_02]: The out-of-the-way animates.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's an animate in a mall in Kyoto that had tons of Famicom games there that you can go through.
Ooh.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd love to get a Famicom disc system at some point, although I imagine finding discs that still work could be a challenge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, usually no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was at a book off where they were selling a lot of the Famicom disc games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a book off in Ikebukuro near Sunshine City.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had like a whole display of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you go to a Super Potato, I promise you, you will find one of them selling a Famicom Disk System to pick up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I would say you're probably going to spend no more than $100 on it, give or take.
[SPEAKER_02]: $150 tops.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Dr. Seuss says be careful of the drive belts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it would be a pain to transport, but I think a neat collector's item.
[SPEAKER_02]: True.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will say that I did have to pick up a Sega Saturn for a friend because he moved to Germany and...
[SPEAKER_02]: Movers, moving his stuff, they damaged the Saturn, so I got him another one.
[SPEAKER_02]: US conversion, 92 bucks, and I think it was like $50 to ship to Germany, so it wasn't so bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well Ranma, it sounds like you had a great trip.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm gonna let you go so we can wrap up the show here, but yeah, I enjoyed hearing about your adventures and making me a little jealous, I gotta be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, tell you what, I have a friend named Rose that
[SPEAKER_02]: When you and Alan are ready, come out, talk to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will help you plan this so you can have a great time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I'm into it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here's one thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will have a couple things.
[SPEAKER_02]: One,
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't need a lot of cash on hand because so many places take card.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you find yourself doing big shopping, just put it on your card, do the US equivalent, save a few dollars.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might pay two bucks on a $200 purchase.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, certain cards will even do the translation for free.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been able to do it in Mexico.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bought cheap fucking hats in Mexico that would cost me $80 here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It cost me like $15.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're probably knockoffs, but I can't tell the difference.
[SPEAKER_07]: So who cares?
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also, if you don't need specialty like body soap and lotions and stuff, just use what they have in the hotel.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I promise you, your skin is going to be a lot cleaner, a lot nicer, and if you have dye in your hair, it's going to kind of come out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I don't have air, so it's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I am going to be going at all the skincare stores.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's just no ifs, ands, or buts about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alan loves that stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: y'all are gonna go into overload when you see all
[SPEAKER_02]: Where I'm staying in Akihabara is at least five to six drug and beauty stores, like literally right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: If not outside, we go down into the shopping mall.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was like one of the other highlights of my trip.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the fact that I'm going through these subway malls and these malls and it's not dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are people walking around shopping and enjoying themselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: I felt like a kid in the 90s going through the malls, okay?
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: also I want to go to the thrift stores in Shibuya that sell the resell designer stuff oh you don't have to go to Shibuya oh no there's like five specific stores there I want to go to
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, because there's like six in the Kyoto shopping arcade in the hotel that I stayed by, and it's just, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I did get some clothes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got myself a nice kimono for, you know, to wear during the winter, and a couple of jinbeis for the summertime, so I'm happy about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be comfortable.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, Ranma, well we look forward to hearing more on Tuesday on Anime Jam Session.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be next Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_02]: This Tuesday I'm still resting, relaxing, and putting my notes together properly for a good show.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's fair.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, next Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_02]: That and I'm still in the process of divvying stuff up and mailing stuff out and Jamie, expect a package in the next week or two.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god, thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're the best.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for that, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_04]: Amazing stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, well, and he deserves it.
[SPEAKER_04]: 40 years in business.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's been a staple.
[SPEAKER_04]: People have grown up with this place.
[SPEAKER_04]: Earned that retirement.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's just a little bit more of a local thing, but it's such a big part of, you know, Bay Area and Northern California.
[SPEAKER_04]: So enjoy your retirement, Onishi-san.
[SPEAKER_04]: You deserve it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, Loki, let me check in with you for any other last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I guess we're just all eagerly awaiting the Switch 2 and Summer Game Fest this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: So next week is going to be a huge show.
[SPEAKER_07]: We got a lot of ground to cover.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we hope to see you here next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except, DarkSakura, you're not here because of a conflict with your ballet stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's my ballet recital.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but that's certainly understandable.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we will hold down the fort while you're gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll tell you what, wish me no, in ballet you don't say break a leg, you say merd yes, it means shit yes, well they say that a lot in Claire Obscure too, so anyway I wanted to say thank you as always for listening to Orange Launch Radio if you enjoyed what you heard here, tell a friend or two about the show
[SPEAKER_07]: Help us spread the word because we are the show where every gamer has a voice, but we need more voices to put out on air.
[SPEAKER_07]: A nice five-star review on a site like Apple Podcasts, Spotify, YouTube, wherever you found the show goes an awful long way.
[SPEAKER_07]: So thank you for helping us to get the word out.
[SPEAKER_07]: So with that, Jamie, Mass Effect coming up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any last thoughts?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, I'm moving some things around.
[SPEAKER_04]: After Recital, I'm actually going to be changing one of my Friday nights to a Dead by Daylight night called Friday in the Fog.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I'm gonna be doing Mass Effect on Saturday and Sunday and who knows there might be bonus nights coming up in the future alright well have a good stream we'll see you in a little bit thank you bye alright we will go over to Loki Loki your final thought tonight my final thought is only another week of school for the kids or one of the kids
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: My final thought is I haven't done a stream since February and I plan on changing that this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: So happy pride, everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope to see you later this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoy the Switch 2 release.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope it's everything you wanted and more and enjoy Summer Game Fest.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't wait to see what we're going to be talking about next Sunday that we don't even know about yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the fun of this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So until then, have a great week and happy gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_06]: See you next week.