[SPEAKER_02]: Should I even write a June intro at this point?
[SPEAKER_02]: The headline has been a foregone conclusion for the entirety of the show's life.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can let the music run alone, it's a bop.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yes, I should, especially since I started avoiding the lead story, though that's harder when the entire show is basically made up of one overarching story.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I want to reference the lead, I pick one specific aspect about it, not quite burying the lead, but shining a light on an interesting aspect of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm just the intro voice, the warm-up act, the 30 seconds plus or minus 10 to bring you into the next few hours of news.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the meta intro because you can probably guess what the show is going to cover, but which of the two stories are going to be the lead?
[SPEAKER_02]: Now it's time for your hosts, Rob Roberts, Jamie Summers, and Loki to tell you about the very active week in gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Starting right now on the show, every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello, my friends out there on the Internet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: And poor Jason, our hardworking voiceover guy, I think has analysis paralysis with everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_01]: Every week I'm joined by my co-host, except not tonight, DarkSakura, or Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unfortunately, was unable to attend tonight as, you know, she talks a lot about her ballet hobby and dance passion and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: And she has a big event for all of that going on tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: So she wasn't able to be here as well, but she'll be back next week.
[SPEAKER_01]: But we do have the one and only Techmaster Loki here tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_01]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm doing all right.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's been a busy week for games, hasn't it?
[SPEAKER_01]: It sure has.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is it just me or is this the closest it's felt to like an E3 week since COVID lockdowns, since like 2020?
[SPEAKER_01]: To me, this feels the closest to like E3 week since those days.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, yeah, I mean, it feels like this every year when we do, when they have Summer Games Fest and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is it though?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I feel like the games from like Sony and Microsoft and, you know, maybe Nintendo hasn't had the announcements, but their console launch is sort of an announcement.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's sort of, you know, a similar thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, I feel like that sort of uplifts
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Forge is overly generic.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I feel like Summer Game Fest has kind of always been in that weird sort of mid spot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whereas when it comes to what they do with the Game Awards, I don't know if it's because it's a different time of year or what, but that's always felt like the announcements there are sort of a little bit elevated compared to what we have at Summer Game Fest.
[SPEAKER_01]: Again, I'm trying to choose my words carefully here because I'm not trying to knock on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I appreciate the event.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know especially since there isn't an E3, it's something to do in the LA area.
[SPEAKER_01]: Again, there were things that I liked in that as well, but I just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't get as excited about that as I do the Game Awards, and then I'm really taking the whole thing into account.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, just the fact, and honestly, Loki, it's not just also...
[SPEAKER_01]: Nintendo console, Sony event, Xbox event, Summer Game Fest, but then it's like everything else around Summer Game Fest, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Day of the Devs, then there's a Devolver thing, then there's a women-fronted game announcements, there's, you know, BIPOC game announcements, there's all these, like, industry...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, I feel like it's kind of energizing.
[SPEAKER_01]: E3VL Overwhelmed by content
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: I was able to catch up.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's plenty.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what social media is for.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what news gaming websites are for.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got caught up.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know what they talked about.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't always watch everything live in the moment, and that's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: So don't feel too overwhelmed this time of year.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't see every game on the E3 show floor back in the day, and you can't watch every single games announcement this time of year either.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, well then the other thing that sort of complicates people's ability to watch gaming wrap-ups and summaries and announcements is that a new console got dropped on people's laps this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Finally!
[SPEAKER_01]: This is a big week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I see that face you're making, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not a console.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not a console?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we're gonna call this ROGLI, which there have already been some in the past.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm talking about the Switch 2, Loki!
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I thought you were talking about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that is a new console.
[SPEAKER_01]: so this and you know uh it's it's a big we haven't had a console launch since 2020 and we all know that 2020 was fucky and the consoles didn't really launch the same way we didn't have like the big midnight midnight releases and shit like we had so if you think about it this would be the first time we've had like a major midnight console release lines at best buy and shit since what the switch one probably the switch one was probably the last time we had this
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's really a throwback in some ways.
[SPEAKER_01]: But let's talk about the Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki, you got yours over the weekend, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: How did the launch go for you?
[SPEAKER_01]: You got your console.
[SPEAKER_01]: What have you been kind of like playing on it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just Mario Kart World.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I haven't really been playing because my son took it and I haven't been able to see it since then.
[SPEAKER_01]: The joys of family.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I set it all up and everything, and I did play through Grand Prix, and I watched him play some of the stuff, but, like, yeah, I mean, you know, Mario Kart World is certainly a gorgeous-looking game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just... It's, like, it's... I think everything with, like, the Switch 2 seems to be, like, this is really great, but then there's this one thing that's just, like, not quite right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is this a thing?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, like, in Mario Kart...
[SPEAKER_03]: World, one of the things that kind of stood out to me is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aside from, like, the fact that you can't do co-op free roam split screen, which, like, really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Your console cannot handle that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I'm just...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm confused as to why that's such a thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why your game is so unoptimized in that sense that it really cannot run that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I get it, the world is big and everything, but we were doing split-screen, open-world racing games back on the Xbox 360 just fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: So why is this any different?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just don't...
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't fathom that.
[SPEAKER_03]: When you do that, the game drops down the level of detail incredibly low, and the framerate is so low on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So to me, it's just like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Why was this even a thing that you added to the game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is this a feature in the game when it doesn't represent the game very well?
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't really add anything, and it really shows... This brand new console that you just put out shows how underpowered it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's so confusing to me why they would even treat it like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: and that aside too like you know I'm hearing now with like the teardowns of the Switch 2 and stuff like that and the Joy-Cons and how oh hey the Joy-Con it seems like that the thumbsticks are exactly the same as the old ones so cool so we're gonna get drifting issues with these $90 controllers in like a few months I mean like do we not learn our lesson with this stuff I just don't understand but
[SPEAKER_03]: that's kind of like my whole take on it it's like it's a really good piece of hardware that game is you know really good but like
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm holding it to that $80 price point standard.
[SPEAKER_03]: And some of the stuff that's in there just feels poorly implemented in this generation of gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Certain games don't have split screen and stuff like that anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it feels like you could have possibly been able to implement that somehow.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't imagine that...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if I agree.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I have to be honest.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't spent a ton of time on Mario because I've been playing something else, and I'll talk about that in a minute.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I haven't been playing as much Mario Kart World because I've been going back and visiting Switch 1 upgraded games and playing them the way I really wish I would have been able to play them from the beginning.
[SPEAKER_01]: but I do think you have a point that like when you're in the free realm and maybe this is because of the fact that the tracks have been scoped out to hold 24 people when you're on them by yourself the the free roam actually kind of feels a little bit empty now I've played I've played a very which and
[SPEAKER_01]: Before y'all come at me, because I know the Nintendo fans are ready to snap.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I've seen all the really cute artistic flares and some of the things that only Nintendo can do, like the buses loading up people and the drive-thru where Yoshi is actually working at the drive-thru and waves throughout the window.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I'm not saying the world is devout of life, but it does seem very odd.
[SPEAKER_01]: It just seems like two very different sort of design choices, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: You have racetracks that are wide enough to support...
[SPEAKER_01]: 24 people, which is a lot for a Mario Kart game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then you have this free roam that's limited to just you, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Or, you know, I know there's ways to... Yeah, there's the workaround.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, so we can do a workaround and get it to somewhat work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why not just make that the thing?
[SPEAKER_01]: My honest question is, is free roam really bringing enough to this game?
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, and I don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know the answer to that yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't played it enough yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: So maybe I'm going to come back in a couple months and change my mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it was a big highlight of their...
[SPEAKER_01]: I think even the most hardcore of the Nintendo fans need to really stop for a moment and pause and maybe consider the people bitching about the $80 price tag have a point.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, uh... But, the game is fun!
[SPEAKER_03]: You could balance that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You could balance that with, you know, free roam.
[SPEAKER_03]: You could even tone it down, like, detail-wise for multiplayer, if you want.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what, like, multiplayer games have been doing forever when it comes to split-screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: The racing is really fun and I really like the knockout tour.
[SPEAKER_01]: I really like the one giant long track.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is really fun, I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that is something that the free world approach, I guess, sort of brings to the game that wouldn't have been there otherwise.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I do really like the free roam element.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry, the knockout element and how it utilizes the free roam.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there is that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it does feel very different from other Mario Kart games, which isn't a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, I think we'd also be bitching if it was like, oh, it's just the same fucking Mario Kart game with some new tracks.
[SPEAKER_01]: I understand the creative push to do something really different.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it is a little bit jarring when the first eight Mario Kart games have essentially been the same thing.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm totally fine with the new take on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Spoilers, sort of, I guess, but there is a Mario Circuit track that goes through the first three Mario Circuits from the Super Nintendo game, one after another.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is super cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: The end of that first circuit that has the Donkey Kong rafters, that's incredible.
[SPEAKER_01]: So some of the course design is phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_01]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's really good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alan's here.
[SPEAKER_01]: He just made a Costco trip, and I think he brought me... Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tariff free.
[SPEAKER_01]: Look what Alan got me at Costco.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a Nintendo Switch 2 Pro controller.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you know why this is important?
[SPEAKER_01]: It comes from Costco?
[SPEAKER_01]: $75.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't have to pay for the tariffs and all that stuff because you get the Costco discount for being a Costco member.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's terrific.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is terrific.
[SPEAKER_01]: It sure is because we're going to buy all the food we fucking eat there anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: So yeah, no, it's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just want it to be like, you know, it's like, I'm not saying the game's bad at any means whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just saying, like, I am going to scrutinize it extra hard because it is $80.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that's fair.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's fair.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is the first game to ever charge $80.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so we should be saying, what does this bring to the conversation that justifies $10 more than, you know, some of these new PlayStation 5 games and things like that?
[SPEAKER_01]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and I think... So here's my prediction here, and this is strictly based off of Mario Kart World.
[SPEAKER_03]: So my prediction in the future with how they're going to approach adding... Because how do you add new tracks to this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because obviously...
[SPEAKER_03]: The world is already existing the way it is, so how do you add new tracks to it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think instead they go the route of Grand Theft Auto 5 Online, where you can basically take this big open world and then create your own courses based off of driving from place to place and setting up stuff along that route and save that and share that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's going to be a thing I predict that will come in the future.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm with E3VL in chat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Islands, do it the way Forza does it.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, this game's, yeah, islands, warp pipes, warp pipes, you drive in a warp pipe, and you go, come on, the perfect Nintendo answer, warp pipes, that's how you're gonna do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: so anyway what else about the Switch, so where did you get yours from because you got yours delivered to your house you didn't actually go to any midnight launches it's annoying because it did get delivered after the release date by a couple days despite the fact that I was literally their second one to order that thing so it's kind of annoying that somehow everybody got before me but whatever, we got it it's no big deal that it was a day or so late yeah
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and that's really, you know, Mario Kart was the only reason, you know, the only thing that we got on it right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: We did all the transfer stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am scared to look at it because I've heard of horror stories where people have transferred their content and their saves and their Animal Crossing worlds are gone.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, like, I'm not...
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I got it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I gotta go and delete that stuff yeah that's the kind of thing I wish it gave me the option to like toggle what I wanted to move over or just like hey move over like the game card stuff but don't re-download everything just allow you to download it that's how it should have been but I don't know it's fine I guess and then um
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean, the eShop seems a little bit better, slightly.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's usable, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's much snappier.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the thing about the Switch.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just snappier in every sense of the word.
[SPEAKER_01]: The interface is snappier, and the magnetic connection thing is so sad.
[SPEAKER_01]: People are calling it the fidget toy of the year, although I'm not sure I would want to sit there and attach, reattach, reattach, reattach over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_01]: I feel like at some point, you're going to run the risk of wearing that shit out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had issues syncing my old Joy-Cons with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I have an older set of Joy-Cons I got back closer to when I got my Switch originally.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I have a newer set I just bought for my wife not that long ago that are pink or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: The pink ones were able to sync just fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other ones...
[SPEAKER_03]: I had to connect them to one of those controller attachment things and then plug it in to the Switch directly to get it to recognize.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then when I unplugged it and tried to use them again, it wouldn't sync again.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of annoying as well on a $500 piece of hardware.
[SPEAKER_03]: That it should work just fine with your controllers because I got them to connect one time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why can't they...
[SPEAKER_03]: Detected again.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it wasn't that I had the other switch on or anything in the room, so I was confused as to which system to connect to.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's completely shut off, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of annoying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like I said, I'm going to scrutinize this stuff extra hard because it is that expensive, and I expect perfect if I'm paying $80 for a game and $500 for a system.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to talk about my little launch night story.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I had a pre-order from Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we went over there and thankfully, and I didn't even realize this was going to be a thing until like two days before.
[SPEAKER_01]: But apparently we get West Coast privilege being in California.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they were actually going to launch the system at 9pm our time because when it's 9pm here, it's midnight on the East Coast, which they do with some movies, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: We
[SPEAKER_01]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I think at some point the rule changed, but I wasn't really thinking about it until a couple days before the console launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we went over there.
[SPEAKER_01]: We did a little shopping beforehand.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was like, you know, they'll probably have separate lines.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of them will be for people who haven't gotten the console yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: One will be for pre-orders, and that pre-order will go fast.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so we kind of rolled up around 9.15.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the line was already going.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was one line going all the way around the building to the back.
[SPEAKER_01]: We were out by the dumpsters.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I made some very funny tongue-in-cheek comments like, Happy Pride Month.
[SPEAKER_01]: They made us gaze-wait out by the dumpsters.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, things like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was fair.
[SPEAKER_01]: We knew we were taking a chance, rolling in there late.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm actually not upset about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was funny to look in the dumpster and see that there was Switch 1 standees and promo material for the original Switch that was sitting in the dumpster.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm surprised some of those Nintendo fanboys in line weren't dumpster diving to take that stuff because, I mean, people do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it was there.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we waited and waited and waited and we got towards the front of the line.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then they started splitting it to two when you got towards the front.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: I just thought of it like Disneyland, except instead of getting on Space Mountain at the end, I was going to get a new console, which I haven't had in five years.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_01]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm waiting for a ride.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so it was fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so we got our system, came home, and then it was that long process of transferring everything over.
[SPEAKER_01]: But props to Nintendo for the servers not melting down.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it wasn't too bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: I realized that Mario Kart World was going to be a code instead of an actual full game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a code, and so I had to put the code in and download it, but it went through.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was relatively fast, and I was playing Pokemon Scarlet, which was the first game I wanted to play.
[SPEAKER_01]: The minute I heard it was 60 frames a second, and when I saw the early footage, I was like, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_01]: So my old save to load up by default in Scarlet, I was just blown away.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was like, this is...
[SPEAKER_01]: I was torn between this is an all-new game and this is the game we should have had the first time.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I can't help Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know people wish I would shut up.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_01]: The answer is no.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't get out of my head that this really was supposed to be how it was supposed to be for us when this game launched.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just too smooth and too good and too fast for this to be made or whatever for me not to believe that this is the way it was really supposed to be the whole time.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I really think this Switch 2 was supposed to happen around the time we got the OLED Switch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe not with the same specs, maybe not in the exact same way, but I really believe that technology is, you know, it was out there for some developers and they were developing to it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's why some of the later Switch games
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not perfect.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's some weird bugs with floating Pokeballs and shadows do weird things, but it feels like the world is alive.
[SPEAKER_01]: You really do see the Pokemon in the background doing things.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're not just walking by like a game and watch.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're actually walking, doing the thing in the grass, watching what's happening, getting behind you.
[SPEAKER_01]: It just feels like the world's alive.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's such a better game now.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'm not just saying that because I happened to catch a shiny Fletchling like 15 minutes into my play when I was streaming the other night.
[SPEAKER_01]: It really does feel like an elevated experience.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I saw a stupid take on social media, which what a surprise.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's lots of stupid takes.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I saw a stupid take that was...
[SPEAKER_01]: If you just got a Switch 2 to play Switch 1 games, you're a problem because blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_01]: And my answer to that is, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sit down.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not everything needs to be posted on the internet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, do people buy higher-end PCs so that they can play their PC games at a better frame rate?
[SPEAKER_01]: Do people buy new PCs, new MMOs, like when a new World of Warcraft expansion comes out?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do I play on my higher-end PC?
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Minecraft, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let people enjoy things.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if you want to buy a Switch 2 to re-enjoy your Switch 1 games, that's one of the best things this console has going for it out the gate.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because let's be real.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's like one new game that isn't on another console right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: One new game exclusive to Switch.
[SPEAKER_01]: in the moment and that's Mario Kart World now next month we'll have the Donkey Kong game soon we'll have Metroid Prime we'll see more stuff from third parties you know and I'm not saying things like Fantasy Life are probably a better experience on Switch 2 because of its portability than PlayStation 5 but that's the reality there isn't a lot to make this really special so I just don't understand where a take like that comes from to be honest
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, let's see, uh, Rinmari68k in chat says gamers think politics and game communities are bad, but would gladly break toes of people who buy a Nintendo game they want.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, Truxius, I hope I said that name right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's True, True, Truexius, Truexius, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry if I'm saying that wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: Says I played PS4 games on my PS5 for a long time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: They're still releasing PlayStation 4 games on PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_01]: Still, a lot of the things that weren't out.
[SPEAKER_01]: PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_01]: That brand new Capcom fighting collection.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a PS4 game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And people are still playing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's nothing wrong with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rin Mari in chat says, honestly, as obnoxious as Nintendo stands can be, Nintendo haters can be not right in the head either.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, for sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: For sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, the gorilla 72 in chat asks, damn, where did he get that Donkey Kong cap?
[SPEAKER_01]: I want one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually don't remember where this came from.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry to say it's a few years old, but look at the best part.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, yeah, entire class says you can probably find it online.
[SPEAKER_01]: I should probably look for, I should probably look up the tag on who made this hat and see what other gaming hats they might have.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I would like to see if they have maybe some Zelda themed ones or some other ones that have the stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just when I also, and this last thing I'll say that we can best switch to.
[SPEAKER_01]: I also like hats that bend I like the bendy look on hats you know like some more like baseball hats no baseball hats are flat and trucker hats bend so I like the trucker hats a little better but this one's more of a flat one this is just taking a long time to get like just a little bendy so I don't love the flat ones as much as the bendy ones
[SPEAKER_01]: So, but that's my hat hot take.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, back to Switch 2 hot takes.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, Loki, what are you looking forward to next on Switch 2?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, what do you think happens with Switch 2 a few months down the line?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I'll probably get the Donkey Kong game just because it looks alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not super excited about Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Funny enough, probably we'll end up getting the new Sonic Racing Crossworlds game for obvious reasons.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not really interested in Metroid Prime 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just have to see what else gets announced.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, really.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, unlike you, I'm very interested in Metroid Prime 4, so that's going to be next on my list.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I don't know if I'm sold on Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to wait and see.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm taking a wait-and-see approach to that one.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think I need that one launch day, but I'll wait.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't wait to see how the GameCube collection expands.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, have you tried any of the GameCube stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have not yet, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if it's just an effect of the emulator that you're using or whatever, but similar to some things you see on PC and like Dolphin and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think those emulators are operating on a more level of trying to enhance the experience, whereas I think Nintendo is probably trying to do something that's really portable.
[SPEAKER_01]: But because you now have things that are more textures and less sprites...
[SPEAKER_01]: I feel like when I'm playing... I didn't play F-Zero yet because I'm going to do that on stream, but I played a little bit of Soul Calibur 2, and it was kind of neat to see that, wow, on the TV, this looks a little sharper.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think anything is up-res per se, but it's the Illustrator versus Photoshop, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: When you up-res a vector graphic, it's going to look a little better than a bitmap graphic that Photoshop makes because it's just that resolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's also because...
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, when you first played it, you were playing it on a CRT TV as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is fair.
[SPEAKER_01]: Totally fair.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it looked a little different back then.
[SPEAKER_01]: DJ Ranma S in chat, I think he's talking about something else, but the comment made about it doesn't connect to your phone, which I think is about a smartwatch, which is a different topic.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that reminded me one other thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Make sure you look at this if you haven't seen this yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Nintendo Switch app got way better.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: So definitely check that feature out if you haven't seen it.
[SPEAKER_01]: E3VL says, you can do stop charge at 90% in settings and save your battery long term.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, that's another good feature to look for, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Bobby Blackwell says, you can see the pixelation in the sprites they use for the UI in Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yeah, you can.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can see the bitmap versus vector, the equivalent of that in the game design, for sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: And F0GX cutscenes look rough.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Pokemon Scarlet cutscenes look rougher than the game now, which wasn't the case on Switch 1.
[SPEAKER_01]: But because they were rendered for the Switch 1 screen, which was a lower resolution, they don't look as good on the Switch.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're not bad, but you can tell.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, oh, it's a little pixelated, a little rough around the edges.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Night on VOG where we can all race each other since it's, you know, these huge races.
[SPEAKER_01]: We will do something before Southern Fried, which is in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_01]: So Southern Fried Gaming Expo in Atlanta is in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we won't be here live that night.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the 22nd.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll actually be flying...
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll be at the Gaming Expo that morning, but I'm going right to the airport from the Expo to come home on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'll be on an airplane by the time this show is on the air.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we will not be live in two weeks on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_01]: But before that Expo happens, we will do a Mario Kart night.
[SPEAKER_01]: But we want to give you guys time to unlock things, get a little more used to it, because I have to be honest, I haven't played it a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why I'm a little hesitant to share some of my opinions, because I fully admit they may still change.
[SPEAKER_01]: The more I explore a free world, maybe my thoughts will change.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've only cleared a few of the knockout and a few of the Grand Prix on 50cc to start the unlock process.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I think we'll get to it maybe the end of this week or middle of next.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know I'm still leaving it wide open, but I want to check with Bobby and my own schedule and stuff and just see what lines up.
[SPEAKER_01]: so more to come on that but if you want to join in on that which I hope you will please join our discord server over at vognetwork.com that's vognetwork.com slash discord that'll get you to our discord server and when that happens we will have all the info on discord in fact
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know how you connect to rooms and stuff, but if there's a code or something like that, it will be in the Discord to prevent randos on Twitch from joining, which I notice the more I've been streaming Pokemon Scarlet and that stuff again, people are like, oh, I'll get you a shiny so-and-so.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let me end the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can get a shiny so-and-so.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, bitch, I know that's hacked.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I don't want to interact with people I don't have at least a little bit of familiarity with because unfortunately some people on Twitch just want to Twitch bomb other users and, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we will post any codes and things like that in our Discord server.
[SPEAKER_01]: Again, that's vognetwork.com slash Discord.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, let's talk about our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know we've talked a lot about Switch too, but maybe there's some other things we want to talk about as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki, I will let you start.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, I mean, there's so much.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I guess, yeah, we could start with Sony real quick.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, your gaming week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your gaming week, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, gosh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Mario Kart World and watching a lot of these different game events.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played a little bit of Bellatro, a tiny bit of Minecraft actually because I've been still setting up like a mod pack for... I'm still setting up a mod pack for modded series.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a balance between what features I want and not melting my CPU and GPU from...
[SPEAKER_03]: All of the mods running at once.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it literally is, you know, I'm not exaggerating when I say not melting my CPU because I was getting up to 95 degrees Celsius on the CPU while it was processing, creating chunks with a bunch of mods running.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's with like an AIO of like 100% too.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, need to take that one out.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not good.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, hopefully I'll be working on new stuff very soon in Channel 64.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, I'm at the point now where I have to start working on the Mega Game stuff, so it kind of slows everything down quite a bit, because I have to essentially do a lot of design work and planning behind the scenes before I can kind of
[SPEAKER_03]: Get to the next step in my next episode, which would be making the external part of the the actual dungeon, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: But being that I don't know what the size of the dungeon is or what it's going to look like or how it's going to be laid out, I kind of have to figure all that stuff out first before I start putting stuff into the world because I don't know how much space I need to allocate for myself and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I've been doing like other like making
[SPEAKER_01]: you know quests and um just farms and stuff in between because at least that I can kill time with all right uh my gaming week outside of the Switch 2 I played a little bit of Final Fantasy 14 and last week on the show I talked about how I wasn't really enjoying the solo adventure on the new Crescent Island uh Occult Crescent the that whole content that they just patched in
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: I was playing a lot of Fantasy Life.
[SPEAKER_01]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's still a fun game and something I will sink more time into around all these other games I need to be playing right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's a good time to be gaming, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: I feel like there's just so much.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Switch 2 is really, despite the criticisms and feedback of things in particular about Mario Kart World, I still think it really is just energized a lot in a way that we needed energy in the industry because unfortunately there's still a shit ton of layoffs going on.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Outriders, thank you DJ Ranma S, that was the name of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, that's our Gaming Weeks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, Loki, we can try to tackle some of these announcements from the weekend.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, let's start with Sony's State of Play.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they kind of came out first the day before the Switch launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the other interesting thing is they didn't give us any warning.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just the day before.
[SPEAKER_01]: The day before, they said, tune in tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they gave us what you would expect to have been probably an E3 type of presentation.
[SPEAKER_01]: It had that many heavy-hitting games in it, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I definitely, yeah, would agree with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there was, yeah, quite a bit of stuff that was kind of exciting coming out of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So obviously for us, like right off the bat, we have Luminous Rise, which is essentially Tetris Effect, but Luminous.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's already amazing.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're cheap now, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do miss the licensed music.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do miss, there was a certain charm that Luminous 2, I almost said Shinen 2 because I was looking at Renmari's comment.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a certain charm that Luminous 2 on the PSP had with all that silly licensed music in it that we were supposed to get on the 360 that never happened.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've told this story before, but I remember at E3, I got to play Madonna in Luminous Xbox 360, which never happened.
[SPEAKER_01]: They never released it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was only ever at that E3 where you could play Sorry by Madonna in Luminous.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I don't know what happened.
[SPEAKER_01]: Licensing disagreements or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: So yeah, Rimari says, the pleasure of making colored squares to holla back, girl.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously, there's something kind of charming about that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: It had a great song list.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a lot of good songs in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I will miss the licensed songs a little bit, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: Do we know if there's no licensed songs on it?
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess we don't for sure, but the trailer had what was almost certainly the same creative minds, which I think is just Tetsuya Mizuguchi's group or something, but the same creative minds around I'm Yours Forever, which was the Tetris Effect song, almost certainly did that song that was in the Luminous trailer.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, we don't know for sure, but you know, that's a safe prediction for me.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Luminous Rise, really excited about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Can't wait to play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it looked really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had another game, Pragmata, which looked interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It had this little girl and some AI robot thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yeah, it was kind of sci-fi-ish sort of thing, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it was interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was getting Megan vibes from it, but not quite.
[SPEAKER_03]: If only.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then Romeo is a Dead Man, which I immediately pegged the Suda51 grasshopper manufacturer vibes from.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, yep, yep, yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like a hack and slash game, so it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got an extended trailer for Silent Hill F, which is coming out September 25th.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bloodstained the Scarlet Engagement so I guess a sequel to Bloodstained and it's going to be at least have two player co-op in it it looks pretty cool we have a Digimon Story Time Stranger I don't know I'm not a huge Digimon fan but it looks neat
[SPEAKER_03]: Final Fantasy Tactics, The Eyeless Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_01]: God, the worst kept rumor secret in the fucking industry, finally.
[SPEAKER_01]: We know.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Creative Business Unit 3, the Final Fantasy XIV team working on it, which is not too big of a shock when you consider that team is made up of a lot of the people that worked on the Evil East games to begin with.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there's a lot of folks there that worked on the original.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very curious to see what else they put in the enhanced version.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because you have the enhanced version and the original version, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Although I don't think we should expect anything from advanced or nothing outside of what was in vanilla.
[SPEAKER_01]: We should expect.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I will be curious what changes they might make to the difficulty, if any.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because Tactics was a fucking hard game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: No!
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't like other people.
[SPEAKER_01]: Me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: and fine, but let other people you know, have the little tweaks that help them see the whole story I'll be curious if they rebalance stuff, for sure but I'm really excited this is coming Baby Steps got another trailer, that's the one from Developer Digital, it's kind of like QWOP as a walking sim, but you know, obviously
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be frustrating.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's coming out September 8th on PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had Hirogami, which is a cool-looking origami paper-inspired RPG type thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really cool aesthetic on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's coming out on PlayStation 5 on September 3rd.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody's Golf Hot Shots, brand new entry into that, including they have some unlockable characters with Pac-Man they showed off in the trailer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who gets excited about Pac-Man in golfing games?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not me.
[SPEAKER_03]: But September, coming out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Another trailer for Ninja Gaiden Ragebound, which I think we saw.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ooh, that looked cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'd seen it before, but still.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was either at the Game Awards or maybe at another PlayStation Direct or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, it looked really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Karen, which is a survival climbing experience.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember talking about this one before, but that's coming now on November 5th.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there is a demo out for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Mortal Kombat Legacy Collection.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, we got to talk about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got to go do a deep dive on this one, but go ahead.
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Would people be interested in that?
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're going to buy a fight stick, wouldn't you rather get one that a lot of the other fighting game players use?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, because I'm expecting this to be expensive.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, maybe, but that fight stick looked really good, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, I kind of listen to that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: Digital Eclipse, Ninja Turtles, Gold Master Series
[SPEAKER_01]: Bobby, our pal Bobby Blackwolf, who's live before we are on Sunday nights, the Voice Geeks Network.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bobby actually asked, so the head of Digital Eclipse is actually on Blue Sky and uses it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mike Mika is studio head for Digital Eclipse, Atari, and actually responded to a question Bobby asked that was basically like, what...
[SPEAKER_01]: What made... Okay, so you're saying... I'm paraphrasing.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're saying this isn't a gold master game, but it looks like it has a lot of that same stuff that Atari 50 had, which kind of felt very... What is a gold master game and what is not a gold master game?
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'm paraphrasing the answer here, but essentially, the...
[SPEAKER_01]: Game Collection are kind of a celebration of the game and they are game focused first.
[SPEAKER_01]: Game emulation and the game experience is first.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then they have sort of like the catalog of the deeper dives of the documentary pieces and the game elements and that is second.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gold Master Series is the other way around.
[SPEAKER_01]: The narrative takes the spotlight and the documentary side of things, which you really see it in the Tetris collection that they did recently.
[SPEAKER_01]: You really see it in the Tetris one, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_01]: How they weave in the games into that story they're telling about getting the rights and how Japan had their own version on their Famicom.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have one of those.
[SPEAKER_01]: It really comes together with the story.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the reason why I say that is because you might remember some time ago on this show, after we played the very first Gold Master Series game, Karateka, I said, the next one will probably be Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because there's an interview with, I think it was Tobias, was in that Karateka, and I was like...
[SPEAKER_01]: What he doesn't really have anything to do with Karateka.
[SPEAKER_01]: He has a short little clip in this.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think they were already filming him for something else and asked him to comment on Karateka because, you know, it was a fighting game.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I said, Mortal Kombat, something's coming.
[SPEAKER_01]: And sure enough, here we are.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, to be fair, I said it would be a gold master game and technically it's not, but I still want half a win.
[SPEAKER_01]: But here's the other funny interaction on Blue Sky.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I was writing a bunch of just fucking, you know, posts about what was going on with the Sony thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I put one that said Mortal Kombat Legacy Collection.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did say when one of the creators showed up in Karateka Gold Series, it was likely Mortal Kombat was next.
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess it's not technically a gold master, but it's getting the same TLC so close enough.
[SPEAKER_01]: Must buy for me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mike Mika, who by the way, at the time I didn't even follow, replies to my post and says, we saw your post.
[SPEAKER_01]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: You never know who's looking at stuff on social media.
[SPEAKER_01]: But let this be a note to all of you that the game developers and the people that work on this stuff are watching.
[SPEAKER_01]: So when you make your criticisms, which you have every right to do, keep that in mind in the back of your head.
[SPEAKER_01]: Would you say this to the developer's face, yes or no?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because you probably are.
[SPEAKER_01]: You might be.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I thought that was interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: But anyway, I love that he replied and I just replied, you slipped.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I said that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I said you slipped.
[SPEAKER_01]: And just kidding.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think what you got, you know, the typical... And it's from the heart.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's honest.
[SPEAKER_01]: You guys are doing great stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Love what you're doing for game preservation.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if you ever want to do a podcast when Mortal Kombat's coming out, please let me know.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: SSJ100Matt says, Use your Rob Stradama's powers to get a Miyamoto Gold Master game before he retires.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wish, but that's a big ask.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a big ask.
[SPEAKER_01]: But...
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, I'm not going to say it's not plausible, your favorite, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tigerclaw says, I still think it's going to include Deadly Alliance, Deception, and Armageddon, the console versions.
[SPEAKER_01]: It might.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I guess they're not done announcing what's in it, but I would be careful where you set the bar.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would be very careful where you set the bar.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would think maybe some of the weird hacks and things that came out of the original Mortal Kombat and some of that maybe is what you'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I don't know if we'll get full on other games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, could we get that whole Sub-Zero side story game on PlayStation 1?
[SPEAKER_01]: I just don't know if that fits in.
[SPEAKER_01]: regardless the first four arcade games by themselves with the deeper dive that Digital Eclipse does I think it's going to be worthy of the collection and I'm not just saying that because now I know they might be listening I would have said this even without the blue sky interaction this week so but I did think I did find that humorous so all right that's all I wanted to say on the Mortal Kombat collection um but very happy for Digital Eclipse and very happy for Mortal Kombat it deserves it deserves this nice sort of um museum treatment
[SPEAKER_01]: and I'll be watching for what cameos don't make sense in that either, just so you know yep
[SPEAKER_03]: We got yet another trailer for Melgar's Solid Delta Snake Eater.
[SPEAKER_03]: They teased also Melgar Online at the end with that as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nioh 3 is going to be getting its launch in 2026 and they have a demo out for that as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thief VR Legacy of Shadow coming to PlayStation VR 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tides of Tomorrow, I don't remember what that was.
[SPEAKER_03]: but neat Astrobot getting some new levels so they've got some new challenge levels including special bots Atsu from Ghosts of Yotai and they also have five new levels which are going to be coming out later this month and they had another Astrobot DualSense controller or I don't know if they're bringing the old one back or if they changed it slightly but it's coming back one way or the other
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anchors Away, which kind of look like Sea of Thieves, but not quite.
[SPEAKER_03]: But very Sea of Thieves-like.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's going to be coming next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sword of the Sea which looks pretty cool as well that's going to be coming out August 19th that's from the makers of Journey and Flower and certainly has that kind of same vibe with the whole sand surfing type stuff those games are some of the best games ever made so I'm really excited for this
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, yeah, it looks really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got the first look at 007 First Light, the new 007 game by IO Interactive.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, yeah, it is James Bond.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's next year as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ghost of Yotai, which is... They had a new teaser for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: and then ending things off totally unexpected but I am super hyped about this game a brand new Marvel fighting game, Marvel Token Fighting Souls done by the folks, Arc System Works Marvel vs. Capcom minus Capcom plus Arc
[SPEAKER_03]: Plus Japanese anime stylings and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all in plus arc if you've played Guilty Gear.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is very true, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I am all about this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks incredible.
[SPEAKER_03]: The roster already looks good.
[SPEAKER_03]: The character designs look amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm all about this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I cannot wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's PlayStation 5 and PC next year.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: Capcom Auto Hookup for a fighting game is Sega
[SPEAKER_01]: and I was like, huh.
[SPEAKER_01]: That could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: It could be really interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: I liked that train of thought.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who does Capcom shack up with now?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I was like, well that could be an interesting little like, could Capcom maybe be involved with the future of Smash?
[SPEAKER_01]: and what happens there because I don't know if Sakurai wants to necessarily do Smash anymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I feel like how we've seen... But that doesn't mean there's not going to be another Smash game.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I sort of feel like how we're seeing some very different creative thoughts and processes go into Mario Kart World.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to see some different thoughts and processes go into...
[SPEAKER_01]: Smash.
[SPEAKER_01]: I ultimately don't think the Capcom thing is just mostly tongue-in-cheek.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually don't think there's anything to that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I do think that maybe creatively, there's going to be a lot of changes with the next Smash.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because if you want to play Smash the way you remember it, you have that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Everyone is here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I feel like that's the capstone to Smash, looking like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we'll see where it goes from here.
[SPEAKER_01]: but it could be interesting if Capcom's like we want to give our input because some of our characters like Mega Man are in the game anyway so we'll see anyway anyways yes so like that trailer is amazing yeah I'm not even that into fighting games and that looked like wow this is I'm not that into Marvel either I respect both but I'm just not like but I was like oh I'll play that that was hot
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it looks really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a day one purchase for me, for sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: So how did you feel about the Sony thing overall?
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't have any expectations for it when it came in, but certainly there was some nice surprises in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I think it's all right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think they did a really good job.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think especially considering they're having to contend with a new console from one of their competitors launching the next day and Microsoft doing their own thing today.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: And cheap plug, we did a live stream here at VOG Network on Friday, and that'll be in the archives for 14 days.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unfortunately, we no longer keep archives beyond 14 days because Twitch capped us, as they did everybody.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you have about another week to watch if you want.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I understand the show itself wasn't for everybody.
[SPEAKER_01]: I really feel like there's something in it for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so kind of going over how they announced stuff over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So essentially, they made a big focus about dev team size, it felt like.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were talking about, you know, different indie games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, the top games on Steam right now included like several indies, including, you know, Repo, Claire Obscure, Expedition 33, Split Fiction, that type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was trying to figure out, what was the endgame with those comments?
[SPEAKER_01]: What was the intention behind repeating that so much?
[SPEAKER_01]: Was it a veiled sort of poke at something like Ubisoft or the AAA games?
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: or was it more like a it's going to be okay game devs we've got all these small studios doing great things although there have been a lot of rightful points that have come out after the fact going okay so Clare Obscure was made by a team of 30 on paper but you have a lot of groups that do outsource work what about the voice actors what about the music what about you know and so when you look at the credits for a game there are more than 30 people in it
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it may have also been just pushing to... He was also promoting GameDiscover.co as well, that site.
[SPEAKER_03]: Talking about the game industry and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think maybe it was just like, hey, AAA industry, the way you guys are operating and everything...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not working.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're putting out these games, but this cookie cutter stuff that you're doing, but these smaller games that are taking unique approaches to things or just listening to their fan base and putting out stuff that there's a hole in the market for it, they're doing well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whereas Team Shooter number 457 that's released out on the marketplace...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's not doing as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do think there's a message in there about how the way games are developed is going to really change.
[SPEAKER_01]: And engines like Unreal 5 are kind of doing that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And for better or for worse, AI is going to be a part of this conversation as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be whether you like it or not.
[SPEAKER_01]: And certainly you all know I have my opinions on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like AI in tool-based situations.
[SPEAKER_01]: I dislike AI in trying to replace art with generative stuff type of situations.
[SPEAKER_01]: By the way, that Jurassic World 3 game has an AI warning on Steam that the little user avatars are generated by AI.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why?
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: It becomes more like smaller groups working together as one large group.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the advantage of that, I'm not saying I'm advocating for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just wondering out loud if that's where things are going.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I will say the one advantage I do see in that situation, you don't have the potential for as much fat sack CEOs to be sitting on the top of this and ruining everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, just something interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, but yeah, game reveals, obviously, were the name of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they kicked things off with a trailer for Mortal Shell 2, which features one of the several genres that were in the Summer Game Fest presentation, which was a Dark Souls-like game that is bloody and creepy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so that definitely fit the bill for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is coming out next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: They also talked about some sort of, what was it, they had Death Stranding 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: They showed off a new cutscene for that as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am getting kind of tired of seeing Death Stranding 2 at this point, but it does look good.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is getting to that point where it's like, enough, release the damn game.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the good news is, the damn game's being released in like two weeks, so yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we have a Chronicles Medieval trailer narrated by Tom Hardy, maybe, or at least someone that sounds like Tom Hardy.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's coming out on Steam in 2026.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: This one really was something I got excited about.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, Sonic Racing Cross Worlds.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Sonic Racing games have been always pretty good, and this time they have...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: and then they unveiled because the game is called Cross Worlds that they're going to be essentially having characters from other franchises and levels in there and one of their first collaborations is with Minecraft so they're going to have Steve Alex and the Creeper as characters and a Minecraft actual level I heard the rumor that there is Spongebob is supposed to be another crossover that they're going to have
[SPEAKER_01]: They had a bunch, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: so you know and that's that's i could that's a hard one to make up and get right you know what i mean yeah i could see the nickelodeon thing because that makes sense because if you think about sonic the movie was produced by paramount paramount owns nickelodeon okay okay i can see that you know what else is on paramount plus rupaul's drag race
[SPEAKER_01]: could we finally oh my god you have race you have race to the title that's right could we get RuPaul's Drag Race but it's actual racing oh my god please let Jujubee be one of the playable characters why not it's Jujubee again why not Jujubee and Ginger Minj should absolutely be in Sonic Crossworld Racing why not Crossdressing Racing yeah let's do it let's do it Crossdressing Racing
[SPEAKER_03]: uh Crossworld there you go that that sounds like a RuPaul Drag Race season right there like Crossworld I mean yeah they're gonna run out of twist ideas for all stars eventually so we might as well go to Cross Crossworld and there you go uh let's see
[SPEAKER_03]: We had a bunch of trailers.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Code Vein 2 had a reveal trailer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's coming out later this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: End of the Abyss, a top-down isometric-looking game, and that's by Epic Games as well as Section 9 Interactive.
[SPEAKER_03]: and we had a new updated trailer for Mouse PI for Hire this is the one that looks like the old 1920s cartoons but it's an FPS and of course because he voices almost every character in the world when it comes to gaming Troy Baker is going to be doing the main character voice as well so
[SPEAKER_03]: Game of Thrones War of Westeros looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: It feels like a few years too late, but it looks neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Atomic Heart 2, I'm actually pretty psyched for.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's supposed to be a spiritual successor to the original game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Certainly kind of expands upon everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: They are horny as fuck, though, when it comes to the content in that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, tying with that, though, is also the cube in the Atomic Universe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, that MMO.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's an MMORPG shooter.
[SPEAKER_01]: That rotating cube thing looked kind of neat, though, like as a concept about how the world could kind of, like, rotate and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I like the idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's an interesting concept, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that'll be coming out at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we got a brand new trailer for Marvel Cosmic Invasion by Tribute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're adding Rocket Raccoon and She-Hulk joining the cast as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I honestly love everything Tribute does.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love their beat-em-up games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's got the big X-Men 90s beat-em-up, Ninja Turtles arcade game, Simpsons arcade.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's got that same vibe.
[SPEAKER_01]: So if you're into that, this is going to be for you for sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Onimusha, Way of the Sword looks pretty cool and that's going to be coming out next year I was really excited about this one because it's just such a unique idea but felt that boxing it's a boxing game with puppets
[SPEAKER_03]: But it looks like I'm watching The Muppet Show or something like that because it's so well executed.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was very X-rated, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was very X-rated.
[SPEAKER_01]: They were cursing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it was Meet the Feebles as the arcade game.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, that was one of the highlights of the whole damn thing for me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Although I'm not sure what the game is because I gotta say the game kind of was starting to look like... Is this like a 3DO...
[SPEAKER_01]: Like little mini game game because I just I really hope the game itself is better than that or it's really funny to make up for it because I wasn't I was like, what's the game here?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I have concerns.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it looks funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm willing to check it out when that is released.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had Killer Inn.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a murder mystery action game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, this looks really cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was the one that's like Among Us, but it's like Clue or Knives Out, but with like actual murder instead of like playing Clue, but like you full on are killing the other characters.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not just like implied or suggested or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, 24 player game.
[SPEAKER_01]: That looked fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got an email from Square Enix after for a beta test or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe I'm not supposed to say that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm into that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I figure all the Final Fantasy subscribers got one so that's why I'm yapping.
[SPEAKER_03]: New trailer for Ark Raiders.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's their release trailer.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be coming out October 30th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently that's been doing pretty well in their early tests that they did earlier this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dune Awakening got a new trailer as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: That looked pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chrono Odyssey Not to be confused with Chrono Trigger or Cross Completely different And so that's going to be coming out on Steam The playtest is coming out in a few weeks We had M.I.O.
[SPEAKER_03]: Memories in Orbit They announced a demo for that
[SPEAKER_03]: Outworlds looked pretty cool this one is done in the style of like stop motion and so it looks a little bit like a Coraline or something like that but I kind of got that whole split fiction or takes two vibes with that the controls look like VVVVV where you were like flipping gravity that's what the gameplay was looking like to me yeah yeah
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mafia The Old Country.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got a new trailer for that that's coming out in August on the 8th.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, I just never get into Mafia.
[SPEAKER_01]: No offense.
[SPEAKER_01]: Look, you can't love everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: No disrespect.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had LEGO Voyagers, which is kind of a... Also, once again, like a split fiction or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: That looked really interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, little bricks and you kind of... The graphics were very shiny in that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It looked very crisp.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very much like... I don't remember the last LEGO puzzle game that they had, but similar to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Unreal 5 makes everything look just amazing, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: They really do look like real physical, tangible bricks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: This sounds like a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nicktoons and the Dice of Destiny.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a Nicktoons D&D-like adventure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yeah, it had Diablo vibes to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Nicktoons Diablo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that sounds like a lot of fun to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some were thinking it was Baldur's Gate, Nickelodeon, which I think is also a great idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm not sure exactly how it plays, if it's more actiony or more RPG-ish.
[SPEAKER_01]: It looked actiony to me, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it looks a little bit like Minecraft Dungeon-y, almost.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, curious to check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Liza P. Overture, I believe that's, yeah, DLC that came out today!
[SPEAKER_03]: Shadow Drop, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: A couple days ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fractured Blooms, that was like a weird Silent Hill-looking type of game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blade and Soul Neo and Blade and Soul Heroes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess it's expansions to their ongoing MMOs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then of course Jurassic World Evolution 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they had Jeff Goldblum doing the voiceover on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'm not really sure much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't really played any of the Jurassic World games.
[SPEAKER_01]: They gave one of them away during, like, it was either an Epic Free Game of the Week or a PlayStation something.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's honestly just been sitting in my backlog.
[SPEAKER_01]: In concept, it sounds really good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm a little put off by...
[SPEAKER_01]: This whole AI thing that apparently is in the third game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would like to have more information to make an informed decision, but if they are just using generative AI to make art that looks silly, it's going to ruin the experience, sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you think they would have learned from... I can't even remember the game now.
[SPEAKER_01]: The game was Splatoon, but with bubbles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Foam Stars.
[SPEAKER_01]: Foam Stars.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You think they would have learned from that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because that game honestly wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: But they really sucked the air out of the room by taking one shortcut, they really could have just not had album art.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's easy, anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had Mina the Hollower, which is a new game from Yacht Club Games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looked a lot like a Legend of Zelda type of game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Definitely had NES vibes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it had like NES or Game Boy Color vibes on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's going to be coming out October 31st.
[SPEAKER_03]: Deadpool VR.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm very excited about that, except I don't have a MetaQuest 3, so I can't really play that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Another VR game that got me excited, except it's the wrong VR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Neil Patrick Harris is playing Wade Wilson, so that sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll look great.
[SPEAKER_01]: That trailer was very sharp.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it looks cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dying Light is getting a spinoff game, Dying Light the Beast, and that is coming out August 22nd.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, we had, uh, Living in the 90s, The Game, or Mixtape.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a new game by Annapurna.
[SPEAKER_03]: And... Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_01]: All those references.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was definitely made for people our age.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'm gonna have to get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we had Toa and the Guardians of the Sacred Tree, or basically Buff Corgi Monk and Distinguished Fish.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, that game looked cool, because that was also kind of a Diablo-y looking game, if I'm not mistaken.
[SPEAKER_01]: The character design was really neat, and then they were saying it was inspired by...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't want to misattribute it, but it seems like there's more to it than just coming up with creative characters that is actually inspired by art and other things in the past history.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm very curious about that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It looked neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had another game called Acts of Blood, which is like a beat-em-up game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looked kind of interesting.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: but speaking of beat-em-up games though right after that they uh showed off a trailer for Scott Pilgrim EX yeah wow that was a very pleasant exciting yeah it's exciting as we got you know it's Anamona Gucci back with Tribute Games again uh a different story right a new story a brand new story four-player co-op uh I think it was like seven characters or something like that
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have the first Descendants breakthrough.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a trailer for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even remember what this was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, it's some sort of mech-y combat thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not to be confused with the Disney Descendants.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, definitely not related at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I would say that's... Here's a deep cut here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the first Descendants has enough to do with the Descendants from Disney as did the Final Fantasy Legend of the... Was it Legend of the Crystals?
[SPEAKER_03]: The movie had to do with Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's basically how close those were.
[SPEAKER_03]: Scum, it's Rust Plus, essentially It's crass humor, the game Oh, that trailer was a hot mess, but yes There were butts in that trailer So that's how you know it's edgy There's so many butts Yet still not the edgiest thing that was at Summer Game Fest
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Hitman, World of Assassins or Assassination we got the Madden Mickelson cameo or uh he's playing um Leigh Shreve I guess from Casino Royale because you know obviously IO Interactive is making the the Bond game so they're gonna obviously do some sort of Bond kind of tie in with that for a little bit so you can check that out now um and then the most obvious thing or um
[SPEAKER_03]: Legally Distinct Mario Party Lego Party It's Mario Party but with Lego and on more than just Nintendo systems So that's coming out later this year It actually looks kind of fun
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, then we've got, what was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Wild Gate.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, I was, I was ranting and I was muted, but, um, it, I was gonna say for Legally Distinct, it looked really good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, and I'm kind of excited for Mario to get a little, little run for its money.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, the, the little competition will be good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think the Lego thing looked cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wildgate announced an open beta which is going to be actually out during Steam Next Fest which is launching on July 24th It's like a space warfare game Blighted, that's another roguelike game that's going to be out on Steam as well
[SPEAKER_03]: We had a thing called Ill, which is going back to the very first game we talked about in that gross, nasty, creepy-looking survivor horror game in Unreal 5.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, that looks kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mecha Break got yet another trailer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least it's coming out July 1st.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once again, I'm also starting to get tired of seeing Mecha Break as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Infantessimals.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a very grounded looking game where you play little bug-like creatures and you fight in mechs and big bugs and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looked kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we had the whole tease before the tease.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they did this thing with the...
[SPEAKER_01]: Resident Evil 30th Anniversary teaser and they talked about how like oh look we're doing this stuff and don't worry we'll talk about Resident Evil the next Resident Evil soon later on you know what the fuck was the point of that like what the fuck was the point of that I don't my my thought my honest reaction is that the ultimate Resident Evil announcement was a very late edition like they were going into that with like 50 50 yes or no we're gonna pull the trigger on this thing
[SPEAKER_01]: so I think they may be left in the commercial anyway just because somebody thought it was funny at that point to keep it in but like maybe what was the point of that I don't understand I don't know it's just a trick people like I get I get the trolling element look it's not lost on me it's it's cute whatever but I just was like Capcom you spent money on that ad that was that was an interesting play but okay okay sure it's your money spend it how you want
[SPEAKER_01]: We had a little LOL, but it was LOL in lowercase, where you weren't really laughing out loud.
[SPEAKER_01]: You were... You were just making a little breath.
[SPEAKER_01]: You were making a snort.
[SPEAKER_01]: You snorted out loud.
[SPEAKER_01]: You weren't laughing out loud.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would be GTM, guffaw to myself.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, that's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, perfect.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god, perfect, perfect.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was not an LOL, it was a GTM.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now I'm LOLing.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, or Mortal Kombat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we got Last Flag, which is supposed to be like a 1970s retro team shooter capture the flag game, which I couldn't help but just think it looks exactly like Team Fortress 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, the classes even.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have a scout class even.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Wuchang Fallen Feathers Rise of the Deceiver
[SPEAKER_01]: Unexpected, but great.
[SPEAKER_01]: Co-op action RPG game.
[SPEAKER_01]: They didn't show much of it though.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a little tease.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we had another weird looking game, kind of had some Conker vibes on it, but Into the Unwell.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sort of looked a little bit like Maus as well, but just kind of has that retro cartoon style to it, but also a little bit twisted and weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we got to the next announcement, which we had the dev for, I don't remember which studio, but he was promoting Splitgate 2, and it's that combat game with portals in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: He came out with a stupid hat saying, make FPS great again.
[SPEAKER_03]: And said, I want Titanfall 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then proceeded to show a game that looked very bland and bog standard.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game's getting a new Battle Royale mode.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nailhead.
[SPEAKER_01]: Look, you made a choice, young man, to come out there on stage and be edgy.
[SPEAKER_01]: You said, I'm going to be edgy McEdgelord today, and I'm going to say these things so I either get invited back or I can pout that I don't get invited back next time.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'm going to say these edgy, edgy things and talk about how fucking great this game is and how, you know, da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then you prepare to roll the scissor wheel on a game we've seen a million fucking times with portals.
[SPEAKER_01]: You made a choice, sir.
[SPEAKER_01]: You made a choice.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's all these fucking dog whistles, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you know exactly what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know exactly what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_01]: All these fucking dog whistles and what he was saying, too, let alone the hat that he was wearing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, I literally had to go, is this parody?
[SPEAKER_01]: Is this a joke that is going on and what's happening here?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Ranma says it was parodies.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you listen to what he said, though?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because there's a lot of what he was saying that was very coded.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what they're always saying.
[SPEAKER_01]: Look, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: You made a choice to turn off what could have been a crowd that maybe would have taken interest in your free-to-play game otherwise.
[SPEAKER_01]: And now you're going all in on the other half, which, fine, maybe that'll work out for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe it'll help your free-to-play game get noticed, where a lot of them don't get noticed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe it'll help get noticed.
[SPEAKER_01]: But just remember, it's also the crowd of some of the...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Now I want to bring up the whole parody argument because we hear that a lot nowadays, especially in, or like, I was just joking, I was trolling.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, like, we hear that a lot even in the political landscape when someone says something controversial or something to the point it's like, no human should be saying that type of thing.
Look,
[SPEAKER_01]: Look, when you have the attention of millions of people in a press thing like this, and you're going to make a joke, you better make damn sure it's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't matter if you're joking or doing a parody.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did you have to do that in the first place?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is just a show where you showcase your game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't need to go, look at me, I'm a character.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know who you are, and I am literally not going to be thinking about you ever again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aside from the stupid things that you did.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, like, why, like, why take the focus off of your game?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, why not talk about what makes your game different?
[SPEAKER_01]: What makes your game special?
[SPEAKER_01]: Why should I check out your game?
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think my favorite comment, though, and I don't remember who, somewhere on social media I saw where they compared it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're like, he's a pizza cutter.
[SPEAKER_03]: All edge, no point.
[SPEAKER_01]: That being said, no further discussion on that game is going to be on this program.
[SPEAKER_01]: So let's move on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I do, and yeah, to Ranma's point on chat, he got the spotlight on his company to get people to talk.
[SPEAKER_01]: It worked.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_01]: We shouldn't be giving this any more exposure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Next.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the same studio.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the same studio, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, looks great.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, oh my god, shock, because they told us, wait, you told us you weren't going to discuss this game, and then, boom, Resident Evil Requiem, Resident Evil 9, it's coming out February 27th, unless it gets delayed, because, you know, games be doing that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the trailer did look good.
[SPEAKER_01]: It took a minute to figure out what it was, and then you saw the ruined Raccoon City Police Department.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, oh, this is Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that was it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they crammed a lot into two hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: Certainly.
[SPEAKER_01]: But again, I kind of look back on the things that I was into, and there was...
[SPEAKER_01]: XBOX did their showcase!
[SPEAKER_03]: So we had a lot of things shown off.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the big ones, obviously, is The Outer Worlds 2, which is coming out October 29th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it looks pretty great.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to also, they're going to be, since the launch is going to be, I don't know, it's day and date on PlayStation 5 as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is also their first $80 game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'll take that as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks pretty good, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: But is $8 good?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had a trailer for Haya on Life 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: So definitely a little bit more sci-fi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your character, of course, was like skateboarding around in this one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looks really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so that will be coming out sometime in the near future.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had Resonance A Plague Tale Legacy They revealed that, that's coming out next year
[SPEAKER_03]: and... what else?
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we got the announcement of the ROG Xbox Ally and... Ally!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's... Just in time for Pride Month.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ally!
[SPEAKER_03]: Portable PC, you know, like a Steam Deck type thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, the ROG Ally's been a thing for a while now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now they're doing one that's Xbox-branded.
[SPEAKER_01]: Literally that leak we talked about two weeks ago was it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, we got confirmation.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: so that's no price is announced yet but it's getting powered by why would they announce a price but aren't you supposed to announce a price Loki why would you not announce a price
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess we'll see what it's going to be.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a pretty big competitive space right now with all the different Steam decks and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think I have room for another handheld, but it's not like I don't support Microsoft in other ways.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think this will be neat for a certain audience.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's just a PC, so what's great about it, though, and one of the things that they, you know, touted, I mean, which is true for any PC, but it's like, hey, you know, you can play your Xbox games out here, but you're not just limited to that, you know, you also can get stuff from Steam, you can get stuff from good old games and all that stuff, which is like...
[SPEAKER_03]: You can run your emulators from desktop.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can run your emulators.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can play Nintendo Switch games on this thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can download PlayStation games because they're on PC as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd love to see that ad.
[SPEAKER_01]: Xbox just says fuck it to the legal stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, obviously that's not happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had Blood of the Dawnwalker.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's another RPG game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's done by XCD Project Red Devs who formed the Rebel Wolves.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it looks kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had, uh, this one looked really neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, Super Meat Boy 3D.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they're doing a sequel, but it is, you know, it's a 3D platformer now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Still all the same Meat Boy stuff, you know, lots of blood, lots of saws.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hard as hell, for sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so, uh, looks cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can't wait to see speedruns on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ninja Gaiden 4 got a new trailer.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's going to be coming out here in the near future as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Different from the Ninja Gaiden game at Sony.
[SPEAKER_01]: So Sony's was the retro flared one.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is the retro one.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, the modern take on Ninja Gaiden.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we got the announcement of story DLC coming to Indiana Jones and the Great Circle.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the Order of the Giants, which is coming out September 4th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: and let's see we've got Beast Reincarnation which is by Game Freak and it's a Souls-like game that's coming out next year it's kind of interesting
[SPEAKER_03]: Clockwork Revolution Grounded 2 Honey, I Shrunk the Kids Again
[SPEAKER_03]: Honey, it blew up the kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honey, we shrunk ourselves.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was Honey, we shrunk ourselves.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, looks cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they've got new bugs and stuff in that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to be hitting early access July 29th.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: I feel like, I guess, I felt like Grounded was still being worked on.
[SPEAKER_01]: But to be fair, I played that like a little bit when it was first on Game Pass, then never again.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, but yeah, it's a cute game.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'll be curious about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blooper Team is back with a new horror game, Kronos the New Dawn, which is going to be arriving next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's like a space horror game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That looks kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, they're having a good year with Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I know a lot of their stuff hit kind of mediocre, but the Silent Hill 2 remake hit all the right notes, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have an announcement of another expansion to Elder Scrolls Online with Elder Scrolls Online Seasons of the Worm Cult Part 1 which is going to be launching in about a week.
[SPEAKER_01]: And no more Elder Scrolls for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Please stay tuned for next year.
[SPEAKER_01]: By the way, very important correction from DJ Ranma S in chat, our Rick Moranis expert, clearly, who says, I blew up The Kid was the second movie, and We Shrunk Ourselves was the third film.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because there's a whole Honey, We Shrunk the Universe.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a whole... I'm almost positive there was a fourth film at some point, too, that Rick Moranis had nothing to do with.
[SPEAKER_01]: So...
[SPEAKER_01]: You know they're up to like five.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm joking.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like a universe of those movies.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know there's like five Home Alone movies at this point, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they don't count.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was a TV series.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a TV series they had for that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, and then there was the, oh, I'm well aware of the Disney ride, Honey, I Shrunk the Audience, which was terrible.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was terrible.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was neat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not everybody agrees with my hot takes sometimes, and that's fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: If that's something you want to ride, I'll be in queue for Space Mountain again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I mean, if I am with Captain Neo, Captain Neo was way better, way better.
[SPEAKER_03]: True.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember it was the cutting edge thing with the shrug.
[SPEAKER_03]: The audience was like, we're going to blow air at you and like we're going to make a little rat tail spin around.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it feels like rats are running underneath your seat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it was silly, but.
[SPEAKER_01]: By the way, on that note, RIP Muppet Vision 3D, officially.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Disney California Adventure one closed years ago, but the Disney World attraction finally officially closed this last week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are they making Avatar out of that, too?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's being turned into something else.
[SPEAKER_01]: Muppet will be relocated to the Aerosmith, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Aerosmith is being evicted from Disneyland, which, you know...
[SPEAKER_01]: and they are going to make that rock and roller coaster, the Doctor Mayhem ride, which will be badass.
[SPEAKER_01]: That I'm excited about, but RIP to Honey, I Shrunk the Audience.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: They even had a game called, was that Felion?
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is a narrative-driven sci-fi adventure game by DotNod.
[SPEAKER_03]: It reminded me of like a Tomb Raider, but in space on a desolate planet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whoever this space person is, it is their very bad day.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of space games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had a weird looking game called There Are No Ghosts at the Grand.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's like some thing where you are an interior decorator who also hunts ghosts.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like a cozy sim thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you vacuum up ghosts just like Luigi.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Age of Mythology Retold is getting a Heavenly Sphere.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a Japanese pantheon to the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That era is now coming with 12 new mission campaigns.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, 12 mission campaigns.
[SPEAKER_03]: Neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else?
[SPEAKER_03]: Mundang Two Hearts, which looks just like Splinter Cell.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to be...
[SPEAKER_03]: using Unreal 5 and no word on when that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then Planet of Lana 2 looks gorgeous with the little kitty thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if it's a cat, but it looks like a cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's like a 2D cinematic game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fallout 76 getting a fishing DLC.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kind of surprised they're still cranking out stuff for Fallout 76.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's probably making money.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gone Fission.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do know people that play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Love the pun, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So fishing, you get fishing rods and fishing in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't eat those fish.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, that TV show probably brought more people to it, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I guess, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and Fallout 76 has also been given away for free a few times.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's kind of another one of those games that had a comeback story.
[SPEAKER_03]: yeah uh we have uh let's see solo leveling um they have Arise Overlord or Overdrive so they're showing that off and that's going to be an action RPG I think co-op RPG and that's coming later this year on PC and Xbox or I'm sorry later this year on PC Xbox next year um
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we have Animo, which is like, it looks like a Pal World type game, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's another one, another game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even more legally distinct, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, but you, yes, but you, like, it looks like you transform into the animals and actually directly control them, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's how they get, that's how they make it legally distinct.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we got another look at Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 and 4, which is out July 11th, but they put out a demo for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to say, I saw something on Game Pass today.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: At Fate's End is a 2D game from the Spiritfarer team and looks like a really cool art style with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's going to be probably out later this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gears of War Reloaded showed off some gameplay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It certainly looks like Gears of War and they're going to be launching the pre-release beta later this week, I think, actually on the 13th.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can check that out as well very soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Persona 4 Revival is finally revealed.
[SPEAKER_03]: They kind of teased that off a bit and looks gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_03]: So looking forward to seeing how that does.
[SPEAKER_03]: More DLC for Sea of Thieves.
[SPEAKER_03]: Believe it or not, it's season 17.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so now they're adding smugglers and Tide.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can actually have, you know, they're making an emphasis on explosions and you're able to salvage for new weapons.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, it is, you know, of course, now multi-platform.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's a thing, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is one of those where the...
[SPEAKER_03]: The cinematic cutscene looked incredible, and then when they showed the game, I was like, eh, alright, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Invincible is getting a game, so Invincible Versus, it's a fighting game, three on three.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I had high hopes, really high hopes for it when they were actually showing off the story cutscene stuff, because it looked straight out of the actual show and everything, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: Final Fantasy VII Remake Integrate Xbox One
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe very soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they also announced that Final Fantasy 16 is shadow dropping for today.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need the sales.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please pick up this game right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Buy now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Consume.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keeper, which is a weird looking game where you are playing like a living lighthouse and I don't really know what you do with that, but you are a lighthouse creature and it's coming out October 17th.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else?
[SPEAKER_03]: We had Phil Spencer teasing that there's also going to be more stuff coming later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: More announcements.
[SPEAKER_03]: They said there's a new Forza game coming as well as some stuff with a return of a classic game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe a new Halo game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: and last but not least they showed off a really neat looking sci-fi thing with like robots and stuff and then at the very end it was revealed to be Call of Duty Black Ops 7 and I was like oh never mind I'm not excited anymore
[SPEAKER_01]: There was an interesting... It has the guy from Heroes in it, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: He had an interesting teaser, too, about next year.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's like, there'll be a new Forza next year, Fables next year.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's one other one.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then he said something about... And then we're coming back to one of our 25-year-old games where it all began.
[SPEAKER_01]: All but confirming these rumors that Halo Combat Evolved is getting yet another...
[SPEAKER_01]: Redo, because if you think about it, Master Chief Collection was a redo, but it's going to get yet another one that'll be out, which also kind of makes sense because Halo's kind of due for a new game, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: So that would make a lot of sense for next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Halo Infinite didn't work out, did it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Right.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I thought it was interesting that he kind of teased like laid up 2026's calendar too, which you don't usually see game companies do, which I thought was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's still like more opportunity than out some of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They could do that closer towards the end of the year during game awards or like even...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if there's going to be a lot being done at Gamescom or anything like that, but yeah, maybe.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, Gears of War was the other thing he had mentioned for 2086, something in that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, yeah, but that was, yeah, so the Microsoft thing, I didn't get to watch it live, but it seems like it was fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Again, I think the sort of thing where like maybe there was some stuff in it for you, but maybe a lot of it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that's what, you know, game companies have to kind of try to appeal to everybody, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: So it can be tricky sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Missed opportunity to maybe drip feed a couple more games into the retro classics that just came out a couple weeks ago and has not had any new games added to it yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I thought it would be a weekly cadence like AntStream.
[SPEAKER_01]: It appears not to be.
[SPEAKER_01]: The notifications are still not working on my system on PC.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe they work on an actual Series X. I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: But a little surprise that that one is already starting to wither away a little bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I hope that they will...
[SPEAKER_01]: Put some attention on that as well in the coming weeks Alright, well, that was a lot of announcements So we had Switch 2 releases, Xbox, State of Play, Summer Game Fest But there were a lot of smaller announcements that happened too Loki, I don't know if there's anything that caught your eye I don't want to necessarily recap the 20 other shows that happened this week But were there anything you want to bring up?
[SPEAKER_03]: not a whole lot I know there was the Day of the Devs but they kind of covered some of the same games that some of the other ones did so like Mixtape was shown, Big Walk Marvel Cosmic Invasion that type of stuff so I don't really know if there was anything there that was interesting I did look into the Devolver Digital thing I didn't see their showcase at all but there's a game called Ball Pit
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Ball X Pit, and it's a roguelike game that kind of has a mechanic... It's... I don't remember the name now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there was, like, it's like Wizorb or something like that that was on the Xbox 360 that was kind of like a...
[SPEAKER_03]: RPG, but it had the Arkanoid type breakout mechanics with the balls bouncing around and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Similar to that, but there's no brick breaking in this.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you basically fire balls and they bounce off the walls and it does damage against the enemies and you get different balls that enhance your attack and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it looked kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's something that's coming out a little bit later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't really noticed any other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the kind of thing, even with E3, back when that was a thing, is that there's just a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's hard to visit every booth and play every game, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's hard to keep track of everything, so certainly Steam Next Fest will be a nice way to check some of these things out.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I went through when I saw a lot of these and kind of wishlisted a bunch of stuff so I don't forget about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then you can also like wait and see when stuff goes on sale.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like Avowed just went on sale for 25% off.
[SPEAKER_03]: So maybe I'll look into that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or I may play it on Xbox Free.
[SPEAKER_03]: Game Pass it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, well...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, unfortunately, like my other game consoles, my kids are monopolizing them.
[SPEAKER_03]: So my son is playing Red Dead Redemption 2 for like the third or fourth time now playing through that again.
[SPEAKER_03]: So he's doing that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I guess PC Game Pass.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm complaining.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like it being through Steam, though.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: There's plenty more weeks in the year, and there'll be plenty more news to come and follow-ups, and we'll stay on top of it best we can here at OLR.
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of people were expecting Nintendo to make announcements.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_01]: They launched a console this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think they're going to... I mean, they could do something next week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just... I wouldn't hedge my bets there.
[SPEAKER_01]: My guess...
[SPEAKER_01]: If Nintendo does summer announcements, they'll be in July because they're going to want to remind people that that Donkey Kong game is coming out and to pick it up and all the cool features happening with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there'll definitely be some sort of deep dive with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So maybe a Nintendo Direct to go with that, that maybe will date some of the holiday releases.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do think they want to date the holiday releases.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I think there will be something in the coming months, but I would put my money on July around the time the Donkey Kong game releases is probably a safer bet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, let's get into the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura isn't here.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that means one of us gets to pick.
[SPEAKER_01]: I decided to pick tonight, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to have fun with this.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to have fun with this segment tonight because you're going to laugh when you hear what I picked because I did not pick a game because it was a good game.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all I'm going to say about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So let's roll the bumper, shall we?
[SPEAKER_01]: and now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where I'll dive into the vault and pull out a classic and tell you about it it's time for the classic game of the week okay and reminder DarkSakura is not here tonight so I get to pick instead and the game I decided to pick you know it's E3 week and you know what would have been E3 week historically but it's no more and we have all these other things instead but I thought you know what let's go back
[SPEAKER_01]: to a real E3 moment with our classic game choice tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right, tonight's classic game is Genji Days of the Blade.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is the game that I have picked tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Genji Days of the Blade was a game that was published by Sony Computer Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a direct...
[SPEAKER_01]: Game for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was released under the newly rebranded Japan Studio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Obviously, Japan Studio was around forever.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I guess they had rebranded for the PlayStation 3 or whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're no longer around.
[SPEAKER_01]: Most of their folks are on Team Asobi now, which of course makes Astro Bot.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is very much not Astro Bot.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's based off of historically accurate things.
[SPEAKER_01]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're in a battle with a giant enemy crab.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Genji Days of the Blade is the giant enemy crab game.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's this game.
[SPEAKER_01]: So in this game, you know, it's essentially this game at the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's very similar to Onimusha.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of, you know, Sony's take on that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it did, I mean, the last game did pretty well.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think the only reason this game didn't do well was probably because of what happened at E3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because otherwise it looks like a pretty competent fighter game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've maybe played it once and that might be being generous.
[SPEAKER_01]: But let's be real, for a game of its era...
[SPEAKER_01]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: The game did get an award though from IGN, Best Artistic Design for the PlayStation 3 in 2006.
[SPEAKER_01]: And of course, the real legacy of this game is the giant enemy crab meme.
[SPEAKER_01]: Producer Bill Rich, I'm so sorry Bill.
[SPEAKER_01]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: and there's real time weapon change the power of the PlayStation 3 although in all seriousness I mean the PlayStation 3 a lot of the content being on the hard drive which wasn't a thing that was on the PS2 or PS1 actually having that stuff without loading times actually was somewhat of a technical you know it's not like it never occurred in PlayStation 2 games but
[SPEAKER_01]: but being able to switch things in and out that fast was something that games having installation footprints to the hard drive on the PlayStation 3 would allow it just wasn't articulated in that particular way so yikes you know the official US PlayStation magazine scored this game 4.5 out of 10 when your own propaganda machine can't even give your game a good review it doesn't look that bad there were worse games on the PlayStation 3 but
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, there it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I know, but here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, she doesn't always pick great legendary games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sometimes she's picking a game because of its history, and that's why I have picked this game as well, is its footprint that it left on the memes and the giant enemy crab.
[SPEAKER_01]: Genji, Days of the Blade.
[SPEAKER_01]: Enjoy your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki, we've covered a lot of the news, so I think now we just need to get maybe some of these quick hitting things again.
[SPEAKER_01]: So let's do some rapid fire news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so we got some news regarding the PlayStation Plus Classic catalog.
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe this was during the PlayStation Showcase thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But essentially that they're going to be adding Deus Ex on June 17th, Twisted Metal 3 and 4 on July 15th, and Resident Evil 2 and 3 later this summer as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So look forward to those.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, and then, uh, we've got news that the Switch 2 is selling out, but they are expected or they believe that they can meet the demand through the holiday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, but I'm curious to wonder how, how the tariff situation is going to go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's the unknown.
[SPEAKER_03]: Between now and then, there's a lot of days.
[SPEAKER_03]: So far, Japan hasn't been like kind of, um,
[SPEAKER_01]: and the crosshairs with that but you never know I will say this I think we need to give credit where credit is due for all the shit we've given Nintendo about hardware launches in the past and rightfully so I think they got this one pretty good it does seem like if you tried to get a Switch 2 and correct me in chat if I'm wrong but if you tried to get a Switch 2 you got one
[SPEAKER_01]: And maybe I'm wrong, but there were a bunch of people that walked up at Best Buy at midnight and still walked away with one, and there were more on the shelf the next day.
[SPEAKER_01]: My understanding is because they never said that Costco was going to be a retailer for Switch 2, that Costco probably still has these on shelves.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, they're in bundles, but the bundle's not bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: The bundle is a, because you buy things in bulk at Costco, but it's a Switch, it's Mario Kart, and it's a year of Nintendo Online.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: DJ Ranma S says, also, we're in an endemic state.
[SPEAKER_01]: Products are plentiful now.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't use that excuse with how the NES Classic and the SNES Classic and so many things before went, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nintendo doesn't usually nail hardware, or it's been a long time since I remember Nintendo nailing a hardware launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: So this seemed to go pretty darn well.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm going to give him credit for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So...
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, let's talk about some other headlines in rapid-fire news.
[SPEAKER_01]: Speaking of the Switch 2, there are some unannounced improvements to old Switch games, maybe because they didn't get a new patch, but due to the nature of the hardware, the emulation, they are running slightly differently in a good way.
[SPEAKER_01]: So what I mean by that, Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ultimate, improved loading speeds, but you'd expect that, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Bayonetta 3 is now running at 60 frames a second.
[SPEAKER_01]: Batman Arkham Knight is running at a steady 30 frames a second Hyrule Warriors Age of Calamity now has an uncapped frame rate so it runs like really good on Switch too Witcher 3 is running a steady 30 frames a second it's so wild to think that it wasn't running that smooth before but it was the OJ Switch we're talking about Pokemon Brilliant Diamond Shining Pearl improved loading speeds and Animal Crossing New Horizons also improved loading speeds so generally
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought this was interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: A prototype of Duke Nukem D-Day.
[SPEAKER_01]: This was a Duke Nukem game from Rockstar that was in development in the early 2000s.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is now leaked to the internet.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was supposed to be released in 2001.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rockstar was supposed to publish it, but it didn't end up happening.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like a lot of Duke Nukem things, it ended up getting screwed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently, though, this
[SPEAKER_01]: a build of the game was found apparently Apogee and 3D Realms founder Scott Miller had an industry insider friend who found a build of the game or covered one and a screenshot of the game made its way out and it was never publicly shared but now it's been publicly shared and if you want to go to archive.org you can find it and check out Duke Nukem D-Day for yourself but do remember it was a prototype so you can expect it's going to be a little bit buggy so but it's probably better than Duke Nukem Forever
[SPEAKER_03]: uh probably I don't know all right let's travel around the world and check out some release dates of games coming out real soon um I know we're slowing down a little bit after last week but there's still still a little energy going this week right still some things yeah yeah we still got a few things so we've got uh this week of course Alien Hominid HD and Alien Hominid Invasion on PlayStation 4 PlayStation 5 Dune Awakening on PC Mind's Eye on PC PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series
[SPEAKER_03]: StarTrucker on PlayStation 5, Warhammer 40k Space Marine Master Crafted Edition on PC and Xbox Series, Stellar Blade on PC, Forgotlings on PC, Virtual Girl at World's End on PC and Nintendo Switch,
[SPEAKER_03]: Wizard of Legend 2 coming out of early access on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series The Altars on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series And finally, Five Nights at Freddy's Secret of the Mimic on PC and PlayStation 5 Nice
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, let's go to Japan.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's nothing on the Switch 2 this week, because I have to work that in my releases now, because obviously we had the big blitz last week.
[SPEAKER_01]: But we do have some releases on the OG Switch still, and of course these games play on Switch 2, including we have the Irem Collection Volume 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: This includes Mr. Heli, as in helicopter or battle chopper, depending on the part of the world you were in.
[SPEAKER_01]: That game is in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mystic Riders and Dragon Breed are all a part of this collection.
[SPEAKER_01]: Again, that's on the OG Switch, but, you know, it
[SPEAKER_01]: Virtual Girl at World's End, also on the Switch in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Asande Chess is also out on the Switch this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then I think that's it for the Switch in Japan.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's take a look at the PlayStation 5, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think we are... Oh, that same Irem collection is out on the PlayStation 5, but that's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty quiet week in Japan otherwise.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about the UK?
[SPEAKER_01]: Do we have that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: So in the UK, we've got Mind's Eye on PlayStation 5, Xbox Series, and PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stellar Blade on PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wizard of Legend 2, also coming out of early access on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_03]: Memory Lost on PlayStation 5, PlayStation 4, Xbox Series, and Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_03]: Five Nights at Freddy's, The Secret of the Mimic on PlayStation 5, and The Altars on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lots of games to add to your backlog this week, but not a ton, thankfully.
[SPEAKER_01]: Get a little room to breathe and actually play all those games you bought for your Switch 2 last week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oops, wrong shot there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, let's move on to our listener roundtable.
[SPEAKER_01]: We invite you guys to ask us questions in our Twitch chatroom over at twitch.tv slash VOG Network, but we also welcome your emails.
[SPEAKER_01]: Participate at orangelaunchradio.com is the place to send your emails.
[SPEAKER_01]: I should check Blue Sky as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't remember seeing anything, but I will take a peek.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just to make sure, because I missed one last week, unfortunately, so I don't want to miss anything this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, let me read this, because I missed it last week.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkTetsuya had made a post to us on Blue Sky saying, Just a quick note, thanking all the folks for the support this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: We had a medical emergency fall into our laps, so thanks everyone in the OLR VOG crew for their support.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I'm glad to see Mish is doing great and is in our chat tonight, I believe.
[SPEAKER_01]: So hello, Mish, and hope your recovery is going swimmingly from all of that.
[SPEAKER_01]: We do have some emails tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Believe it or not, two emails tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Participate at Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they're both from people we don't hear from very often, which I love the emailers email us all the time.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love hearing from people we don't hear from very often.
[SPEAKER_01]: So let's get to the email bag.
[SPEAKER_01]: Participate at OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: Our first email tonight from Bryguy2365.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bryguy2365, who sent us an email and the subject was called...
[SPEAKER_01]: How an old fart plays Fortnite Mobile.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you remember this discussion last week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_01]: We were talking about Fortnite Mobile and I was like, but I'm so old, I don't understand how this works.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, with on-screen controls.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, well, here's... So we got this email and I'm gonna... It even has, like, photo evidence and everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm gonna get into this here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello, OLR friends.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bryguy2365 here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Last week...
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: well played I forgot about these controller attachments that you can put on your phone because it is a little weird that Apple doesn't have like at least as far as I know like an official official like first party controller like all these are supported through third parties to my knowledge and I don't you know again and then in the the Google verse there's kind of multiple phone makers anyway but yeah the minute I saw the picture which I'm showing for folks on Twitch uh I was like oh which by the way that's a fancy like gold is that like a gold
[SPEAKER_01]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: Death Star Event
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to get out of the house, which doesn't always happen.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to get out of the house and I'm going to go do raids downtown.
[SPEAKER_01]: There were Gigantamax raids today in Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I went and I threw Campfire.
[SPEAKER_01]: I found the local group and I was like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Screw it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll go and check it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: And there was a decent, there was maybe like 12 people walking around.
[SPEAKER_01]: But because of all the remote people that raided in, we had to ease it.
[SPEAKER_01]: We took everything down super easy.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I got three Gigantamax Cinder Aces.
[SPEAKER_01]: none of them above a two-star appraisal which is sort of irritating but oh well what can you do all right uh let's go to the next email because I said we had two emails tonight our next email oh dang it I closed the tab that had it um Loki do you have something to buy me time while such as a last minute story while I pull up the email again because I foolishly closed it
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we were talking about Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ultimate on Switch 2 and how there's some enhancements.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's also some downsides to some of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently there's some issues if you're playing against someone on Switch 1 and they have a Mii Fighter.
[SPEAKER_03]: It kind of breaks the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so be careful of that because it will kick you out of your game if you try to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, uh, yep.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, I recovered the email.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: The honest answer to that is no.
[SPEAKER_01]: I very rarely go back and look at older episodes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will say this.
[SPEAKER_01]: This has been very interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: So one of our folks on Discord, who I've brought up on the show before, 13xForever, built this script that scrubbed all of our old shows from the OL Archive and basically did these transcriptions.
[SPEAKER_01]: and although you know I always say about the old shows they are relics of the past and of their time and not all of them have aged well and I think you always need to keep that in the back of your mind if you're gonna go you know because there is if you wanted to listen to just about every episode of OLR that ever existed I think there's only maybe two that are gone forever from the live only days and
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: is this whole, you know, and I say this very tongue in cheek.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm very humble about this, but sometimes it is really funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: This whole Rob Stradamus trend where I said something on the show and then, you know, years later it becomes a thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I think the biggest example that I can think of was when the Nintendo Music app happened and I was like, what episode did I talk about that in?
[SPEAKER_01]: and because you can search the transcripts now was able to find what episode I talked about it in so I could put that old clip on up on YouTube and go I am smart and you know and this happened also recently with I don't know something else where I was like didn't I talk about that oh it was the um it was this the Mortal Kombat thing I was like what episode did I talk about that in that came up and then you know well well actually you said it would be a gold master game and it's not a gold master game show you were wrong but
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and it was also, I think, when we were trying to figure out who coined the phrase TTP first.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah, you were trying to figure out the time to penis thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: You found out you weren't first.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I think it was...
[SPEAKER_03]: Spore is like someone I think may have mentioned it around Spore or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let me go back to the email.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's interesting how the older episodes have come in clutch for doing research and that sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: But no, I barely listen to the new shows.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm here now.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm hearing it now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like that's from my perspective.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm living it, so I don't often... But I will go back with the critical ear sometimes and be like, oh, how did that come across?
[SPEAKER_01]: How did that sound?
[SPEAKER_01]: Could it be better?
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, once in a while, but I also try not to overthink it and just let it be because we are live.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's rare, but of course, once in a while, I'll come across an old clip or something on YouTube or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just like, oh, that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: We got together live and we listened to episode one with our commentary over the very first episode.
[SPEAKER_01]: We did this a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, it was like three or four at this point.
[SPEAKER_01]: This was during COVID, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: We listened to our 19th anniversary show, which, yeah, would have been 2021.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: We listened to our first show with commentary.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I think that one is still there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think some of those...
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh no, it was deleted.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a bummer.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't blame you, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_01]: I blame Twitch.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is what it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: So never mind.
[SPEAKER_01]: Carl, never mind.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't say anything about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know what that means?
[SPEAKER_01]: We just have to do it again sometime.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not episode one, but maybe episode 100.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki, if there's a night that DarkSakura isn't here, we need to go back and listen to episode 69.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Only because I say that because DarkSakura wasn't there for the actual.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was when Karaoke Revolution was played live on air.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that was the notorious... That was the notorious Loki doing... I don't want to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't want to even like... I didn't want to even do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I restrainly changed the lyrics.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also one of those things that didn't age well either.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it didn't age well with time, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: I was right there, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: You had permission.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wouldn't have given myself permission.
[SPEAKER_01]: This email isn't really going anywhere to make at least some content out of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: How many years or console generations do you think Rockstar will get out of Grand Theft Auto 6 when it finally arrives?
[SPEAKER_01]: Or a million.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you think that might be their last single player GTA and they'll push towards GTA Online and expansions and versions thereof since it's such a cash cow?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, because I think that they were originally talking about doing that back with 5 with online was supposed to be like that too like they were going to have different cities and stuff I think what they're going to realize much like with everybody like EA has already figured this out that like hey, yeah we could keep expanding this one thing
[SPEAKER_03]: But then that means, you know, if we put out a new game, you gotta buy all that stuff again.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, like, we'd rather you buy it again for a second time or third time or fourth time.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so that's why they will never just make one giant...
[SPEAKER_03]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_03]: So now we're paying for all this server space and stuff to run all this, and it's just not making us the infinite amount of money that we want to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it'd be cool if they had one giant universe, but I don't want to see how that's monetized.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I gotta pay for my flight to Liberty City.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's gonna be $4 million because everything's inflated in that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sure you'll be rammed with Switch 2 release news this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wish you all the best and look forward to future shows.
[SPEAKER_01]: Signed, Carl from Southampton, England.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for the email.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was lovely to hear from some folks we don't hear from all the time.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I encourage more folks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't be shy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ask a silly question.
[SPEAKER_01]: Get a silly answer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or participate at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not that that was a silly question.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was a good question.
[SPEAKER_03]: it would be interesting like we're talking about older episodes it would be and I know like we talk about AI and stuff but this is where we talk about AI in the sense that it's a utility and not necessarily replacing something but like to throw those old audio files that were made for dial-up radio through something to enhance the audio on them
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I wonder if that would be a thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Check out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure, we could check it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not opposed to it because I look at that as kind of like a tool.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I would want to know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would have a lot of questions about what's the tool and what's it going to save from what it listens to and those types of things.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: It could be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, that's it for the listener roundtable.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I think with all the news and things we've covered tonight, I think that's it for the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you all for being here, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Appreciate you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, actually, Loki, did you have any other last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_01]: I only let you do one.
[SPEAKER_03]: yeah one quick thing is I didn't even know this was part of Street Fighter 6 but apparently Street Fighter 6 has a gallery section that you can play games in and so with their newest update with the DLC Fighter Alina they added some games to their game center so you can play Bionic Commando Street Fighter 2010 The Final Fight, Mighty Final Fight and Mega Man 3 they're fully playable oh yeah it's so random but I like that
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, thank you as always for listening to Orange Rounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you enjoyed what you heard, please tell a friend about the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_01]: We are the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_01]: We need more voices to put out on air.
[SPEAKER_01]: A nice five-star review on a site like Apple Podcasts, Spotify, YouTube, wherever you found this show.
[SPEAKER_01]: By the way, one of our...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: I made a boo-boo and the wrong, in my naming commission, I uploaded the wrong file so you got the same episode twice.
[SPEAKER_01]: So by the way, if you did not hear last week's episode, there was a new episode, 1049 on June the 1st.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you did not hear it, go back in the podcast feed and grab it because it was corrected on Monday morning when I woke up to all the messages of, you fucked up!
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, it happened.
[SPEAKER_01]: Look...
[SPEAKER_01]: Look, 1,049, now 1,050.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mistakes happen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, definitely check out last week's episode if you didn't, but also check out, you know, future episodes and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Five-star reviews go a long way.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you very much for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's get final thoughts and we'll get out of here for the night.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki, your final thought for tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully they have to play more Mario Kart this week because my son's going to be taking... He's already played through, what is it, all of 50, 100, I think probably 150 at this point, like CC's unlocked almost everything already.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thankfully it's on his profile and not mine, but like, you know, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: My final thought tonight I'm probably doing a late night Pokemon stream I mean late night, sorry, West Coast and I think a lot of my streams are going to end up late night just because it's the easiest time for me to game I'm probably going to do a Pokemon stream tonight but I'm not rating into myself after the show because I can't do that and I'm going to eat dinner so maybe in about an hour or so we're going to have a late night Pokemon stream so I'm looking forward to that play some more Pokemon so I hope to see you there if not though I understand and I'll be streaming more throughout the week
[SPEAKER_01]: Next week we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll talk about the latest and greatest that's developed over the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe some more surprises, although I wouldn't hold my breath.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura will be here and we'll catch up with her as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we hope to see you all back here next week in seven days.
[SPEAKER_01]: Until then, have a great night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_02]: To join us for our live show, tune in to vognetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_02]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio nor VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_02]: See you next week.