[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, August 1st, 2010, a big MMO plans a free-to-play model, Valve accidentally bans 12,000 players, and the creator of Ultima wins $28 million from his former company.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: We are that program dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_01]: We are that show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_01]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll be joining you over the next few hours here at All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't know you were dining on meat this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every so often I dine on the meat, but I do not necessarily chow on the cow, and I definitely don't dine on the swine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Chow on the cow and dine on the swine, alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember I got that from Danielle back in the day.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki is not here tonight
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki's not here because this is the day that we knew was going to be coming for some time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki's going to be out for a few shows because Miss Loki went into labor this morning at 11 a.m.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all we know.
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't have a lot of updates other than that.
[SPEAKER_01]: The baby is not here, or at least the arrival has not been announced on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if I were Loki, I would not be running to Facebook to announce the birth first thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: My guess is that they do have a tiny one right now who is currently doing a lot of sleeping as is mommy.
[SPEAKER_02]: So during sleep time we should start seeing the messages because the body goes through quite a lot of hell in childbirth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Being born is hard work.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a lot of pushing.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we do have some guests here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because this all happened this morning, we weren't really prepared to have another co-host come in.
[SPEAKER_01]: We are going to have something a little more permanent.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, not permanent because obviously Loki's not being replaced.
[SPEAKER_01]: God know he'll come back.
[SPEAKER_01]: But for about the next month or so while Loki's off being a daddy, we'll have a more long-term co-host next week.
[SPEAKER_01]: But for now, we have some special guests.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a co-host, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Where is it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Aha, your co-host fails.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: My co-host is turned from me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, the batteries are dying on the Dalek.
[SPEAKER_01]: That ought to tell you something.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's not dying.
[SPEAKER_01]: It needs to exterminate itself.
[SPEAKER_01]: We do have some guests here in studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's say hello first, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I've met both of these guests for the first and second time tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I apologize if I'm mispronouncing you, but you're Mila?
[SPEAKER_01]: Myla.
[SPEAKER_01]: Myla Minoki.
[SPEAKER_01]: How are you, Myla Minoki?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I'm glad to be a guest on the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't wait.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're not hearing you at all and I'm trying to figure out why.
[SPEAKER_02]: Turn my mic.
[SPEAKER_02]: See Rob, you were afraid that my mic was going to be crappy.
[SPEAKER_01]: What is going on?
[SPEAKER_01]: Is the switch on?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's always a common mistake.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now much better.
[SPEAKER_01]: First rule of radio, turn your mic on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's try this from the top.
[SPEAKER_01]: Myla!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi there!
[SPEAKER_01]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was actually turned on to the show by our wonderful intern, Drunami, and I guess I'm the sub-intern?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess I count as the sub-intern?
[SPEAKER_01]: You're the intern's intern.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm the intern's gopher.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm the gopher.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're the gopher.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn it!
[SPEAKER_01]: You have a lot in common gaming-wise with intern Drew, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: You described yourself to me as a budget gamer.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the type of video games you're into?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it costs less than $10, I've usually either played it or bought it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm usually very much on the budget gaming, so much so that my MMO of choice is RuneScape.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's free.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gary, Gary, Gary, Gary
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep, that's me.
[SPEAKER_01]: How you doing, Gary?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Glad to be here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's a friend of Punk Night.
[SPEAKER_01]: Really?
[SPEAKER_01]: Everybody is so randomly connected to OLR somehow.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got to figure this out.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might know me as Mindstorm or SMF2045 online.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Either one of those.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be SMF.
[SPEAKER_06]: Getting back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an acronym.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll explain later.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Not entirely true.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got the impression you're more of a games that involve more than six sides on my dice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I'm a tabletop gamer, but thanks to DarkSakura, I picked up SimCity 3, and when I get a chance to play it, I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: SimCity?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was a SimCity 3, I believe.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, SimCity 3000.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, wait till I get you Modnum.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I left off SimCity a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just downloaded Boob Sliders.
[SPEAKER_01]: This isn't the first time I've met Gary.
[SPEAKER_01]: The first time I met Gary was at Jamie's rock band party.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yes, rock band.
[SPEAKER_06]: The beer potluck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yes, that was technically the beer potluck.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't remember the beer potluck.
[SPEAKER_06]: When was that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Your mic is dying.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ouch, my ears.
[SPEAKER_02]: I told everyone to bring beer so we could have a beer potluck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gary brought meat, which was almost as good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because I don't drink.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still have one Guinness left from that time, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: One Guinness.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to drink the fuck out of that Guinness.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll be able to skip a meal when you do because Guinness is liquid bread.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yummy.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's going to be my celebration for being off Vicodin because my hand is fucked up even more now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And by the way, thanks for the peach beer.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was delicious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I couldn't, you remember I couldn't drink the peach Lombek?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gave it to her.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was wonderful.
[SPEAKER_04]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now for the story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, story time?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is how we met.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, Myla.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: We skip names all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, Gary tells me that on our way to Shul downtown that we're picking up somebody.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I instantly am pounce-hugged by this person.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm like, okay, hi, you're fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I instantly like you.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then she was talking about playing DDR, and I said, oh yeah, I used to moderate on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she's like, from Orange Lounge?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know Drew!
[SPEAKER_01]: How funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: Small world, ain't it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, small world.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we both called him and left him what-the-fuck voice messages.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait a minute, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is tonight on OLR like Jew party?
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that what this is tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: What's the matter?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't count.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I thought you... I'm not yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: The people in this room are only half Jewish.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's only half Jewish.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm Jewish by proxy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we have Jew, Jew by proxy, Jew in training, and not Jew.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: And gay.
[SPEAKER_06]: The short word for not Jew is goy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome to the world of oppressed peoples.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I love the Jewish people.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would say I'm not a fag hag, but I'm a Jew hag.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're a Jew hag.
[SPEAKER_01]: What would you call it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like somebody who likes to hang out?
[SPEAKER_01]: You're a goy toy.
[SPEAKER_01]: A goy toy.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't mind us.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're geeks, we're gamers, and we're fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: And very silly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Honestly, guys, this is one of those weeks where I don't know why we're doing a show tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Honestly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_01]: We need this, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: For some reason, guys, like...
[SPEAKER_01]: We decided to do the trial Facebook ad campaign this week, which I'll talk about in a minute.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not a big deal, but we're trying to get word out there more about the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so we probably have some brand new people listening for the first time tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'm thinking to myself... Apologies in advance.
[SPEAKER_01]: Please go back in the archives and listen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, 374 was a good show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad that you have these numbers memorized, because I sure as hell don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, how do you know it's not going to be a good show tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to have fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: and that being really fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially when we're completely just thrown off our patterns.
[SPEAKER_02]: The random is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think all of us tonight kind of collectively, well I can't speak for the guests, but I know Jamie and I just kind of don't give a fuck tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: At least I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys have me on the show, so I know you don't give a fuck.
[SPEAKER_01]: You guys have me on the show, so it's proof you don't give a fuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gave a fuck, but I don't remember who I gave it to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably Dan.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's dangerous.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, there was... We should probably get into the how was our week and day and shit, because there was some stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, technically it's how was your gaming week is how we start off, but I know you're dying to talk about why you're off.
[SPEAKER_01]: I really don't have an excuse.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just... I'm on the rag.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm on man rag tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know what you'd call that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't need that.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's for damn sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Need some freshening, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you feel not so fresh?
[SPEAKER_02]: We could get you a douche.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know how... You're a douche.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your face is a douche.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how... I'll friend your butt.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know you know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seventh grade flashbacks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Somebody will just tell you good morning and you'll want to be like, Why are you looking at me like that?
Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Although that makes it sound like it's about my relationship, which it really is not.
[SPEAKER_01]: My relationship is awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think Alan is the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's everything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want him to be my gay boyfriend.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's bugging me.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't have him.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's mine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, well anyhow.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't know any of those.
[SPEAKER_06]: As I'm eating chips during the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: S-T-F-U.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, you're eating something kind of healthy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a banana for breakfast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: My husband, Dan...
[SPEAKER_02]: Age 34, went into the hospital Tuesday morning at a quarter after 3 for congestive heart failure.
[SPEAKER_02]: My husband is 34 years old.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is something that you could die from.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or suffer massive damage to your other organs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, he was coughing up blood.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And feeling really short of breath.
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't have any of the pain or numbness.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, thankfully, his heart was in good shape.
[SPEAKER_02]: He went in early Tuesday morning and got to leave Friday afternoon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, more like Friday evening.
[SPEAKER_02]: His blood pressure was super high.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thankfully, after numerous ultrasounds and x-rays and what give you rays and tests and things and prodding, lots of prodding, they determined that all the rest of him worked just fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't damage his organs and he could come home.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's on blood pressure medication now, quite a bit of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: And we've got someone in the room who's been through the similar.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Mike,
[SPEAKER_02]: I am talking on my mic.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's... LA!
[SPEAKER_01]: Your connection at the base is... Okay, I'm holding it in.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm holding it in.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I can hear you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, of course you can hear me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I mean through your mic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, let this be a warning to everybody that, you know, don't think this can't happen to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: You really... And I know, again, it's like with Dan's situation, he wasn't ready to change until he got slapped in the face with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ignition Pads 3 of them
[SPEAKER_02]: for $6 at the thrift store.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if they work, but they were in good shape.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to clean the crap out of them, and I'm going to make Dan play some Boom Boom Dollar with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's what my week's been, so really, as far as going into gaming, I ain't played shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except for Ragnarok Online, which I'm playing again.
[SPEAKER_02]: And really, I played that because it was so mindless that I could just play and not have to think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I wasn't able to sleep.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went that first day on an hour and a half of sleep and did not go to bed until something like... I took a little nap, which is my hour and a half of sleep, and then I was up until like three in the morning.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I can't say I blame you.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was up again at 9 the next day, and I just, it's been, I slept really funny, and I've spent, I've never been so freaked out in my life, even though I knew he was in good hands, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is the other thing, too, and, you know, I know I'm probably going into a bit of personal detail, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a microphone, and I'm going to use it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight's the feel-good episode of OLR, everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't make me bust out the booze, Hila.
[SPEAKER_02]: At any rate, the way things were going, you know, Dan and I were talking about, you know, we've been talking about having a kid, me and Dan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I've been forthcoming on this on the show because I'm going to totally get Matt to do our nursery.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aw, mini Sakura, yay!
[SPEAKER_01]: Is this a tangent where I can mention that Matt's nursery was actually on Game Informer?
[SPEAKER_01]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that a big blog or magazine?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Game Informer is the one that's sponsored by... Are they the GameStop one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, his nursery was on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it had nothing to do with OLR.
[SPEAKER_01]: They found his pictures on Flickr.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: However, you can copyright the photos and then they have to pay you.
[SPEAKER_01]: In this case, it's good news.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you just got to be careful what you put up on the internet.
[SPEAKER_01]: If it hadn't been good news, you want to be careful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just be careful what you say on your Facebook accounts.
[SPEAKER_06]: People have gotten fired from jobs because they said something their bosses didn't like.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why mine is fully blocked and I really don't allow photo tagging.
[SPEAKER_02]: If someone's tagged my stuff, I go look it up and only let the stuff I tag myself.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hate that Facebook does not let you approve what you get tagged in.
[SPEAKER_02]: But nobody can see my stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody who's not a friend of yours.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't allow friend-to-friend viewing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Understood.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Back to your traumatic week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So please, share with us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, well, you know, Dan and I were talking about having a kid, and I totally don't want to really do it until I'm sure he's going to stick with this.
[SPEAKER_02]: As much as I would like one, I want to make sure that, you know, and we were actually, the ironic thing is that we were talking about that Tuesday, Monday during the day, is, you know, how, and I wasn't so much worried about him dying, I was worried about him not being able to keep up with the kid, you know, because Dan's a big guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now I'm actually worried about maybe, you know, him dying.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm, you know, I'll say right now, I'm 34 years old.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Dan and I are coming up on our 5th anniversary on September 1st.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've been together for almost 14 years as of January.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, I never thought for an instant I was ever going to have to be without him.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it was...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: People out there, if you have a significant other or someone in your family that is at risk, you need to sit down and have the talk with them because when they think it can't happen, it does.
[SPEAKER_01]: and so you know even though we're being one of those game podcasts yet another one that doesn't actually seem to talk about games for 30 minutes this is important because you know if you are you know sitting there and you're you're down in Doritos and maybe you're a little bit fluffy you know I love that word fluffy chances are me too I think it's a Gabriel Iglesias I think you know and it happens to all of us I'm feeling a little fluffy right now in fact
[SPEAKER_06]: My grandma's got a refrigerator magnet that says I'm not fat, I'm fluffy.
[SPEAKER_06]: My boobs are fluffy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's something to watch out for if you spend lots of time sitting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I used to work in an office and play games, didn't get much exercise.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a wake-up call earlier this year.
[SPEAKER_01]: God bless the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: Even if you're not well, I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if I'd go that far.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still want to borrow your Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Even if you're not fluffy, take time to evaluate.
[SPEAKER_01]: Am I going outside enough?
[SPEAKER_01]: Am I walking?
[SPEAKER_01]: Am I maybe eating not so good as I could be?
[SPEAKER_06]: The straight Cheetos diet is not necessarily good for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is going to be our big thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Watch the refined carbohydrates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Watch the processed foods.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, even if it says low sodium on the can...
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, yeah, that's a given, but you'd be surprised how hard that is sometimes.
[SPEAKER_01]: You'd be surprised how much shit you're eating.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'm honest, I eat a lot of shit.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I really need to cut back on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you smell like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not, I don't mean actual poop shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean crappy food.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bad food.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like McDonald's, Burger King, all that fast food crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know...
[SPEAKER_01]: Everybody knows you're not stupid people.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know how to download a podcast on the internet.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're not dumb.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what's good for you and what's not good for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's okay to indulge once in a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know where I would be in this world without Chicken McNuggets.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you don't order the 20 pack of chicken McNuggets.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you don't do it every day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get a Happy Meal.
[SPEAKER_01]: For one person.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, the other bit of advice I have with this, and Dan is thankfully learning this now, is just the eat when you're hungry, stop when you're not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not when you're full, when you're not hungry.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you also need to make sure you eat at regular intervals, breakfast, lunch, dinner, and maybe a small snack in between, but don't eat super late and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I eat it eight times a day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, that's good if you eat small meals a day.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I eat about 100-200 calories a pop.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a small meal.
[SPEAKER_02]: But as long as I stick with my mostly raw food, I don't have to track what I eat.
[SPEAKER_02]: The one problem is that I don't get enough sodium.
[SPEAKER_02]: Irony.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have the opposite problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have the opposite problem, yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I eat mostly fruits and vegetables, and they're raw and processed.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they're processed, it's because I threw them in my blender.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I know you eat beef occasionally Sometimes When the PMS monster hits We don't talk about that I talk about it all the time This is important to say There's nothing wrong if you are a little fluffy Everybody's a little fluffy It's fine Love yourself the way you are But make sure that you pay attention to your health Just be fluffy and healthy
[SPEAKER_02]: Low Weight Obesity
[SPEAKER_02]: Meaning that they had a higher range of fat to muscle ratio than these other people did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never heard of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Low weight obesity.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: True.
[SPEAKER_01]: True enough.
[SPEAKER_01]: We do reach a wide audience on this show, so if we can save one other person from having to go to the hospital, then... I was so mad.
[SPEAKER_01]: 20... I was mad.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your mic again.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your mic's mad at you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was mad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, once I got over being worried, I was mad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because honestly, who does he have to blame for what happened to him?
[SPEAKER_02]: Himself.
[SPEAKER_02]: When my jeans get snug, who do I have to blame for that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, sometimes I have, you know, PMS to blame for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But usually it's me.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, we have to be responsible for ourselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing, like all those morons out there who are out there suing McDonald's and shit because, Oh, I ate your hamburgers and I got overweight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, don't eat the damn food, stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, so anyway, I'm sorry for going off that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So how about my games, Rob?
[SPEAKER_01]: How about your games?
[SPEAKER_01]: You already mentioned games.
[SPEAKER_01]: You didn't play a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Star Trek Online Episode 2 came out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which I got... Now, my hand has been killing me because... Oh, on top of all this crap with Dan, my hand's infected.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: When I move my finger, it squishes.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Star Trek Online Warp Core Breach Warp Core Breach
[SPEAKER_01]: I meant eject the warp core.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, my mind goes to the drink automatically, but yeah, eject the warp core because of a breach.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because that was like every episode of Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_01]: They had to eject the warp core.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I did find that the warp core breach was a legitimate drink from the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he pulled it out in the same bowl and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cork did.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that it for your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan's buddy, Will, started Crackdown 2, so we just kept making fun of the boss.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, shut up, dude.
[SPEAKER_02]: We know.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: My gaming week, you know, obviously I played a lot of Warcraft as a chatter earlier said, but yourself.
[SPEAKER_01]: Our little raid group finally cleared the Trial of the Champion on Ten Man, which yes, I know is like behind where most guilds are at right now, but we just started raiding like
[SPEAKER_01]: Last month, so shut up.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that was fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: And other than that, though, I've been trying to play games other than WoW, but I didn't have a lot of success this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did play some Game Room.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played Frostbite on Game Room, which just came out.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's an old, old, old school Atari 2600 game that I remember from when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_01]: We used to stay up and play that for hours, and it's still kind of cool, although I think a lot of you that don't get the classic gaming thing will not get this either, so I don't expect everybody to run out and download it.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: as an assassin before I was playing the paladin-y type of class that was more of a defender and it's just like the matches went on forever but as an assassin I'm just like cutting people left and right it's awesome and this time I hope to not miss any side quests like I did the first time you know that reminds me of when you were going around saying bitch I cut you
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's kind of like that, but now on Puzzle Quest.
[SPEAKER_01]: New games this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did check out just the demo for Hydro Thunder Hurricane because I wanted to see, and Jamie's yelling it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually didn't really agree with her.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was just kind of like, eh, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's something about playing that game in a big old cabinet at the arcade with other people that was much more fun to me than sitting at home in my chair playing it on my Xbox controller.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just wasn't feeling it.
[SPEAKER_01]: The graphics didn't do it for me either.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's just something about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I feel like it wasn't...
[SPEAKER_01]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, again, I'm only playing a demo.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not trying to review the whole game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just saying, was I sold on the game based on what I played?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nah.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I ended up passing on the full version.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jamie's yelling she bought the full version, but she is not in a mic right now, so we can't hear her.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can't hear you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: So what else did I play this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sadly, I didn't play StarCraft 2, although it seems like everybody's been playing that because I haven't picked it up yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's too much money right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It seems to be all that most of you guys are talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: StarCraft 2, DC Universe.
[SPEAKER_02]: DC Universe I'm excited about there's that new trailer out for DC Universe that looked pretty hot Dan got Starcraft 2 and it's gorgeous and the collector's edition comes with all the old versions and we did get Hydra Thunder Hurricane except I can't play it right now and he loves it but he loved the old one too really?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know maybe I was just in a bad mood you'll have to see the new levels the level in I think it's in Turkey it's gorgeous
[SPEAKER_01]: There was some interesting mechanics with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't hate it, but there's so much other games to play right now that I wasn't like, I want to drop $15 on this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Especially knowing that the Castlevania game is out next week, and I know I'm going to want that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just based on what games I've liked historically.
[SPEAKER_02]: The problem, I think, with the game so far is the way that you unlock the levels.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you have to keep playing and keep playing and earn credits, and then you unlock the levels.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's not as cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: Other games I've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: On the PC, I actually bought a game on Steam called Rhythm Zone.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a $9 game that is basically Guitar Hero for your computer, but you use the keys to play.
[SPEAKER_01]: I believe you can plug in USB devices, but gonna be honest, didn't really look into that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just played it with a keyboard.
[SPEAKER_01]: the thing about the game is that yes it has a library of songs that it comes with but it also will make a note chart to any mp3 on your drive as you can possibly imagine if you've ever played one of those DDR games that makes up the steps to the music as it goes along usually the note patterns that show up kind of blow and it's just like let's bang on random keys to my mp3 collection that's really a more appropriate title for the game
[SPEAKER_01]: The game is just a straight up jack of Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_01]: Really doesn't add anything new to the mix except for, ooh, I can bang random keys to my MP3s.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, for some inexplicable reason, the screen likes to slowly rotate to the left and to the right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know why, but suddenly, like, you know, you're doing... Like, imagine if you were playing Guitar Hero and then just suddenly the whole screen started to rotate to the left, like 45 degrees.
[SPEAKER_01]: You'd be like, what?
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: And I guess the one nice thing I could say about it is that it does seem like they have saved room to expand the game later on.
[SPEAKER_01]: So as long as they don't make me pay for any of those expansions, because $9 is already too much for what I got, that might be redeeming.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I'm not gonna hold my breath.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, that's Rhythm Zone on Steam.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not a fan.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see, that otherwise is pretty much it, especially as far as new stuff goes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't really play a whole lot of other new stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm going to turn it over to Myla.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have you been playing anything this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: New or old?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not only have I been playing something, but I am playing something currently, RuneScape.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's my new crack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's my old crack.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been a member of this wonderful game for...
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, since 1998.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're not hearing you very well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Make sure that mic's good.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay, yay, it's up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing RuneScape since 1998.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was a member, or not a member, but a free player back when the wilderness was PvP.
[SPEAKER_04]: What a concept!
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they switched it over to PvP servers, which just made a lot of us just very unhappy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: um but then they released uh about a year ago they released the Dungeoneering skill which is what I'm working on right now and it just it brings a whole new level to the game it's you know originally RuneScape was you know something you played on the weekends when you're bored and didn't have really anything to do and you know you do one skill and then you do another skill and it's just kind of you know kind of monotonous kind of stuff and it's really fun and
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: But you also use your crafting skill to make new armor.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you jump into the Dungeoneering levels with no equipment.
[SPEAKER_04]: You build your own equipment.
[SPEAKER_04]: You build your own things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything that you do in the Dungeoneering is based off your regular stats.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's amazing because it really, you know, for those people like me who spent the, you know,
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: When you're soloing, it's a little more difficult, but you get more of the feel of the skill.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you're doing the four-member parties, especially in the earlier levels, it really feels like you're just running in a dungeon, wasting everything, and keep going.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, you're maybe at the boss for like maybe, you know, 15 seconds.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds like playing a PSO back in the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: But as you go down into the levels, the skill increases.
[SPEAKER_04]: But therein lies the problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whenever you start a Dungeoneering level, it takes how many people are going in, and then from there it determines which level you start in.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you've been soloing for a long time...
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll be at level 14, and the dungeons will be really harder, but if you don't do a lot of the four-mans or three-mans, you'll be stuck at the first couple of levels, and you'll be going, Where's the challenge?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything's easy!
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's a little different, but it's really fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really, really fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, RuneScape's been around since 98?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been around forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's...
[SPEAKER_01]: Have they done major makeovers to it since then?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one of those things.
[SPEAKER_04]: RuneScape, it's been slowly evolving over the years.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll release a patch here, a patch there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dungeoneering's really the first full world patch and update that they've done in literally years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shoot, I'm dying.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you playing RuneScape right now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm playing RuneScape right now and I'm just about to die.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the good news is if you die in the Dungeoneering skill, they just pop you back to the home world.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, the only thing that death in Dungeoneering really accomplishes is, yes, you get a sucky score at the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's about all it does.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now there's some folks in chat, I see Drew Nami is in chat and he's saying RuneScape with kind of one of those like, you know, whatever faces.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think he's a fan of RuneScape, but it's free, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's one of the... Is it better than Yaris?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's gotta be better than Yaris.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, my cat's stinky butt is better than Yaris.
[SPEAKER_01]: TigerClaw in our chatroom says StarCraft 2 is a huge graphical upgrade.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's no longer the pixelated graphics.
[SPEAKER_01]: Everything is all 3D graphics.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the cinematic areas are in-game, are real-time.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, and I understand that, but my point was is that, you know, RuneScape, yeah, it's from 98, and people are still playing it today, which might seem weird, but I was just saying, like, StarCraft was out only one year later than that, and hell of people still playing that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've been playing Ragnarok Online since 97.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, my.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that game really that old?
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty old.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can double check.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know it was out in Korea before that, and I was playing on the Japanese servers for a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I was playing on the open beta for IRO.
[SPEAKER_01]: Old games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm still playing it, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anything else you want to give a shout-out to in a game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hey, Drew.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other than that, no, not really.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm literally in the middle of a dungeon right now, and I'm kind of milling through it.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, we'll try not to suck up all our bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_01]: I won't.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gary, now I know you said beforehand you weren't too much of a console.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, you might be a PC gamer?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I used to be console.
[SPEAKER_06]: I grew up with an 8 and 16-bit Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Original Final Fantasy, awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a PlayStation 2 that hasn't seen much use lately.
[SPEAKER_06]: More as a DVD player than a game console.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'd get back into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I picked up a couple of computer games and I always actively look for interesting looking computer games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm seriously looking at Batman Arkham Asylum.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game is great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, another recommendation.
[SPEAKER_06]: The reviews seem to be glowing all around so it's probably something I'm going to have to pick up.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you like the Batman universe, they've got a lot of the voice actors from the animated series.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: DC Universe Online
[SPEAKER_01]: if you want to comment on anything we're talking about tonight chat.orangeloungeradio.com is the place to be or on the Game Surge Network we are in channel Orange Lounge we don't use the regular all games chat room I don't know why it's just we always had a separate room and that way when we have a separate room we're in control and have ops and all that stuff we're just control freaks alright let's see so I was going to ask you about tabletop games I know we don't talk a lot about tabletop games but briefly what types of tabletop games do you play?
[SPEAKER_06]: Dungeons & Dragons 4th Edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, okay, stop with the boos.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop with the boos.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can do anything, just about anything in 4th Edition you can do into previous ones.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm clueless when it comes to this stuff because I haven't played D&D in a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played a little bit like two years ago, but that maybe lasted a month.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why are people so mad about 4th Edition?
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: The teleportation is line of sight, very short distances.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you know, it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just gotta give it a try.
[SPEAKER_06]: The teleporting in previous editions, especially in 3rd, was crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It got to the point where a party would...
[SPEAKER_06]: Teleport would scry, teleport, and kill the main boss, and that was your whole campaign in the teen levels.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, 3.5 D&D tended to break.
[SPEAKER_06]: The entire system broke around 16th to 18th level because they just hadn't... It was a design thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, what it kind of reminded me of was the difference between, you know, WoW in the early levels is, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't have a lot of things, but you can still level up pretty quickly.
[SPEAKER_04]: With 4th Ed, it almost reminds me of the first couple levels of Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_04]: Until you get to 10, you're crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the big misconceptions about 4th Edition is it's an MMO on tabletop.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's not an MMO on tabletop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, they share terminology with World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes it convenient, but you can still do...
[SPEAKER_06]: This is not a ding on computer console games, but you can still do more because you have a living person who can keep making up the story.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're only limited by your imagination.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whereas, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: that's right well yes and you know house rules in a in a home game is the name of the game so I mean you can change the system to a point um and if if there's something that somebody wants to do you know it's just it's it depends on what you like I mean people who don't like fourth edition go play Pathfinder that's fine nothing no problem there I'm glad Paizo was around to put out an alternative for the folks that that didn't like the genre shift but
[SPEAKER_06]: I enjoy Fourth.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm hoping that they'll license or put out a computer game based on the Fourth Edition rule set.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know Wizards of the Coast was having some issues with Atari as their game publisher.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if those got worked out yet or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I like Fourth Edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: I also like hero games, superheroes, champions.
[SPEAKER_12]: I play Champions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Champions is fun, but it's a very, very numbers-heavy game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not a math guy, so I need a character generator to keep the stuff straight.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, eh, you know, I haven't played the Champions Online MMO.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm told it's very different in its mechanics, and they just licensed... Actually, they bought the Champions name from Hero Games and then licensed it back to them.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an interesting arrangement.
[SPEAKER_00]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dundracon
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, they got 6th edition Hero now Is the current edition of that And I have yet to play it But I'm looking forward to doing something different than D&D very soon I've been playing Dungeons & Dragons since 3rd edition came out Pretty much uninterrupted straight Wow Yeah, steady diet You kind of get tired of it after a little while I just, it's the fantasy thing I'm ready for a genre shift myself I want to do a nice steampunk game
[SPEAKER_01]: Let me get to some comments from our chatroom at chat.orange.com Without turning into a tabletop gaming show, although it is important, you know, a lot of computer games we play today are inspired, like Champions Online is a perfect example, directly inspired by the tabletop universe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, without D&D, you wouldn't have World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_01]: No way.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or probably even stuff like Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Comments from our chatroom at chat.orange.com Shaoran says, that's not why 4th edition isn't as good.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not as good because there's next to no customization.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not true.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about we save the debate for another time?
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Monty Boggs says, none of my group wants to spend money on the new books, so we haven't upgraded.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shaoran clarified, though, at least in terms of skills and multi-classing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's also... No fan of the flames.
[SPEAKER_12]: I will leave it at this.
[SPEAKER_12]: I still love second edition for a reason.
[SPEAKER_01]: Take your THACO and shove it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I have.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, I can calculate my THACO in my sleep, sir.
[SPEAKER_06]: THACO in low saving throws, high attack rolls, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Camara says the fourth edition book talked down to me like I was a child.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is what the dice looks like.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is how you roll it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's a problem I've always had with Wizards of the Coast.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't write very well.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game books aren't written very flavorfully.
[SPEAKER_06]: We miss you, TSR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, well, actually, that's one thing I like about White Wolf.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least the old World of Darkness, the vampire, the werewolf books were written very flavorfully.
[SPEAKER_06]: You actually could feel the world when you were reading it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and then they switched to New World and there was much sighing and gnashing of teeth.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't talk about New World of Darkness.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a subject that's left in the closet.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've just made Jodea happy because we're talking about you.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm pleasantly surprised at what a warm reception the tabletop chat is getting from our chat room.
[SPEAKER_01]: We may have to have a tabletop corner or something in the future.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: TSR is dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: They died of their own money grubbing, but unfortunately it looks like Wizards of the Coast might be going the same way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eh, that's life.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, let's get into some housekeeping here so we can get to the video game news of the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Housekeeping going on here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mentioned a Facebook ad campaign earlier, and just to tell you guys what's going on, it doesn't really directly affect the show, but we decided to try a little something something.
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't make any money doing OLR.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to make that very clear.
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't have ads during the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't have any on the site.
[SPEAKER_01]: Really?
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: We haven't for eight years made money doing OLR.
[SPEAKER_01]: So the only exception would be donations, which we don't actively solicit them at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't have a PayPal link or anything, but folks in the past have donated generously to the show, and that's kept us definitely going, be it bandwidth, time, whatever it is, not necessarily just money.
[SPEAKER_01]: But we decided, what the hell, let's take...
[SPEAKER_01]: www.facebook.com slash orangeloungeradio
[SPEAKER_01]: We're also on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll be taking Twitter topics later.
[SPEAKER_01]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's all I have for housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: So why don't we get into some actual gaming news?
[SPEAKER_01]: StarCraft 2
[SPEAKER_01]: StarCraft 2 sold 1.8 million copies on day one.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's not counting Korea, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not counting Korea?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not counting Korea.
[SPEAKER_01]: So 1.8 million on the first day.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's Americas and Europe.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keep in mind, though, I want to say, didn't World of Warcraft sell a little more?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not original WoW, but like Wrath of the Lich King sold what, like 2.8, I think, on day one?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, can you give us some other numbers for context of that?
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to say World of Warcraft, Wrath of the Lich King, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's here later in the story.
[SPEAKER_01]: 2.8 million units on day one as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's another Blizzard game.
[SPEAKER_01]: But here's the difference.
[SPEAKER_01]: With an MMO, especially one like WoW, there's this huge need to be the first person on the server at level 80.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_01]: So there's a lot of people who want to go out and get it right away.
[SPEAKER_01]: StarCraft 2 I think is a little different because I don't think everybody needs to jump on board with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't jump in right away but you know I was lining up.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't line up for Rathalich King.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just went and got it the next day.
[SPEAKER_01]: But there's a lot of people I think that are just kind of chilling with StarCraft 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: They don't have to get it right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: They can wait a little bit or at least for a price drop.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then again, with Blizzard, good luck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good luck on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're still charging $20 for Diablo 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I never heard anyone stressing over missing a raid in anything but World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, as far as the original StarCraft goes, I actually got my copy from a friend who actually bet me money for whether or not I could beat him at StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I didn't know the game, so he's like, here, you borrow my copy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I played Zerg and whipped him good, so that teaches him.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm watching the trailer for StarCraft 2, Wings of Liberty, Ghosts of the Past.
[SPEAKER_06]: Looks intriguing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that's an interesting monster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hooray for the Zerg.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray for the Zerg.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know how I feel about this whole splitting it up into three games, though, because really, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, even for splitting it up into three games, you know, they still gave some outrageous additions to some of the other, you know, like the Zerg, like the Protoss, you know, the exploding Zerglings I absolutely love.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know enough about the StarCraft universe to even profess to say oh this is a good idea or no but I kind of think like okay kind of going from that wow fanboy perspective of maybe these are more like expansion packs these future releases are kind of like expansion packs in a way but they're also standalone because like
[SPEAKER_01]: and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very much so.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a strange experiment they're trying, and it's getting them a lot of crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, there's a lot of people really pooping on StarCraft 2 because of the whole lack of LAN support, but that's... I hate to say it, I think it's more of a vocal minority than anything else.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think it's anything to...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, some of the, you know, looking at all the additions of what they made from the original game to the new game, it really makes, you know, each of the races a little more versatile.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, with the original Zergs, you know, you really only had one option, Zerg Rush.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the only way to really...
[SPEAKER_04]: Make a dent into the opposing sides and to really thrive was just Zerg Rush.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was really your only tactic.
[SPEAKER_04]: With the new additions that they have, like the Explodies, Zerglingo Boom, it makes for a really interesting new way of playing for those people who are just used to one style for, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: for the individuals like the Protoss, like the Terrans.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, stepping away a little bit from the gameplay for a minute here to talk numbers again, because I think this is very interesting and could be very telling for the future.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, again, this report on VGCharts.com is estimating that 31% of those units were sold on Battle.net, meaning that about a third was all digital distribution directly through Battle.net.
[SPEAKER_01]: That could be very, it's almost a telling sign of where GameStop's going to be in 10 years.
[SPEAKER_06]: So do you think games on DVD, CD are going to be obsolete and you just download it in the future?
[SPEAKER_06]: How long do you think it's going to take?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because obviously it is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, have CDs gone obsolete yet?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, not yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: They've had unexpected longevity somehow.
[SPEAKER_01]: They've been punched and kicked and throttled and had their hair pulled.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_01]: But they're not dead yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're not dead yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: CDs are... They're not getting better, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: CDs are kind of where, right now, I think you can kind of look to that to see a little bit about where gaming's going.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's my parallel.
[SPEAKER_12]: Newspapers and online...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, newspaper circulation is down so far, so fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Newsweek is up for sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're not all dead yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, they're not all dead yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Major dailies are hurting, like the Washington Post, the New York Times, but they're not gone.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll see what form they take.
[SPEAKER_06]: The iPad might have something to say about what form they take in the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see how that goes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the Amazon Kindle.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Kindle, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also Sony has another e-reader.
[SPEAKER_06]: I forgot what it was called.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sony's e-reader is actually really, really nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have the Kindle app on my iPhone and I absolutely love it.
[SPEAKER_12]: And keep in mind, I'm trying to go into publication for my field when I'm out of school.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thankfully, there's jobs out there for online publication as well as print publications.
[SPEAKER_06]: Besides just blogging.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you know how to do them both, you're in a good place.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've thankfully been printed before.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hate to do this, but I have actually breaking news, a special report we have to go to.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Live late breaking news, you guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's very important.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's just been a post on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_01]: Joshua Hunter was born at 5.14 p.m.
[SPEAKER_01]: So congratulations to Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there was much rejoicing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I actually think I just saw something in the Orange Lounge from Kitsune.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's how I knew to look.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because they're able to refresh a little faster.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's so cute!
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Look at that little one!
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, she couldn't have waited one more hour to have the baby during OLR.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now it's a Bobby Blackwolf baby.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, babies wait for no one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure Nelly's like, get this child out of me.
[SPEAKER_01]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my impression of Nellie in childbirth.
[SPEAKER_01]: The baby kind of looks like Nellie.
[SPEAKER_01]: He does?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he's got, though, you see that turn of his mouth?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's totally Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, you can definitely see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he's got Nellie's nose.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry to interrupt the show, but that was definitely worth interrupting the show for.
[SPEAKER_12]: I wonder if they're going to have a brist for him, and then I feel really sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Fantasy VII Victory Dance.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that brings back memories.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I should have found that music.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, any more baby news we get during the show we'll bring to you, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, he's so pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he's got red hair.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we're just glad that StarCraft didn't lay an egg.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_04]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where's my... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Too soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where's my rim shot?
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Drew Nami's like, how long before he's eating super bacon?
[SPEAKER_01]: Too soon, you guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good God.
[SPEAKER_01]: Be happy for 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actdeft has a point there.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the first OLR baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gave a congratulations to his sperm and Nelly's hard work.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki and Nelly were only dating when this show started.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, who did all the work?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not saying you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said you got your priorities straight.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a comedian I like called Henry Cho who's a Korean guy from Tennessee, so he sounds totally Tennessee-y.
[SPEAKER_01]: StarCraft 2
Ah...
[SPEAKER_01]: One thing that is supposedly, I guess, coming to StarCraft 2 in the future, I guess it was supposed to be there when it launched, but it didn't make it, is chat rooms.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: You were supposed to have chat rooms in StarCraft 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not there yet, but it's going to be added in a later patch, and that is per a forum post from one of the community managers over at Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_01]: The chat room is going to be, quote, based around groups where you will be able to join public channels that are based around your interests.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sounds like it's going to be like AOL.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that a good thing?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_01]: There will be private chat rooms as well if you are so inclined or you could always use real ID if you don't mind your last name being plastered all over the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is why I use an alias.
[SPEAKER_01]: I tried but Blizzard just kind of took it right off my credit card and was like, oh hey, this must be your name.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyhow, that's in the future for StarCraft 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_05]: Baby.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's obsessed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you, everybody.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because the biological bomb started ticking really hardcore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you feel a Twitter in your... Twitter.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you feel a Twitter in your uterus?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I was actually thinking of Kathy Griffin, so was it a Twitter in the twat?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, too soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where is that rim shot?
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob's got the sad trombone.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got it right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: What, keep going?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, remember we were talking a while back about the R4 being banned, being that that's the little memory card reader thing for the Nintendo DS so that you could play ROMs or copies of games or bootleg games.
[SPEAKER_02]: um so there has well I've got a ninja pass so I'm going to talk but anyway um I really got it for though all my imports it's not mine officer I swear but anyway anyway um they actually um there's been a released uh you know they were banned in the UK and now there's a bit more information that's put out about it they basically said that it was actually related to a number of different devices that were sold by Playable's
[SPEAKER_02]: which is the company that they banned was Playables Limited.
[SPEAKER_02]: The devices are defined, and this is a quote, enabled Nintendo DS users to play unlawful copies of Nintendo DS games with which they have downloaded using the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what Nintendo means about game copiers.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the things that really make it illegal, and this is actually on the list are the R4DS, M3DS, DS1 Supercard, DSTT, DS Linker, Ace Card, CycloDS, Evolution, N5, and EZ Devices.
[SPEAKER_02]: You didn't mention the Ninja Pass.
[SPEAKER_01]: So all the fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't mention the Ninja Pass, so I'm cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they always make the good stuff illegal.
[SPEAKER_02]: but all of these are ones that use the micro SD flashcard and the argument though basically Nintendo's claim was that it was in violation of the Copyright Designs and Patents Act of 1998 in the UK and the argument that Playables put up was basically that it was to play homebrew games
[SPEAKER_02]: you know, but basically the whole big thing is that the device circumvents Nintendo's machine you know, any of the programming built into it that's there on purpose um
[SPEAKER_02]: And so basically, all of these things, the different encryptions, different things that Nintendo built into the hardware to protect from being able to use bootlegs and whatnot, the device is supposed to counteract them, so that's a big thing that Nintendo's got a bug up their butt about.
[SPEAKER_02]: and according to Nintendo they've seized more than 165,000 game copiers that were intended for playables and so basically they're just you know that was the whole deal about it that even though yeah there's a bunch of other cool things you can do with them the whole bless you the whole big thing has to do with circumventing their hard work
[SPEAKER_01]: I get that and all, but doesn't this seem a little throwing out the baby with the bathwater to you?
[SPEAKER_01]: No pun intended.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because this is where they're saying that since you can use this device to pirate games, it shouldn't be out there on the market.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I can use my computer to pirate games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does that mean my computer should be banned?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it's more about what you use it for.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you know, the good thing about the R4 is that it does open it up to homebrew.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, of course, I can see both sides of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a lot of people that can sit there and go, okay, you know damn well there's plenty of people that buy those R4s that aren't using it for homebrew.
[SPEAKER_01]: They are using it for the malicious purpose.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's tough.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, where do you draw the line?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So... That's a tough call because, you know, it's... With the gaming community, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: That kind of stuff is really, you know, it's hard to call because, you know, you got the regular, you know, honest gamers who actually buy their stuff and, you know, they don't get, you know, access to this because, you know, just a bunch of people decided, oh, we're gonna steal games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not fair to both the legitimate players as well as the guys who are doing the stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Either way, it's a bad deal.
[SPEAKER_01]: You see, if Nintendo would open up the DS to homebrew, not that I see them ever doing that, but if they were to do something like that, this cart wouldn't really have a lot of leg to stand on because its only purpose would be for something shady.
[SPEAKER_01]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nintendo doesn't want to open that up because then there's going to be all sorts of scary homebrew things.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, there would be homebrew to play Sony PS1 games on your DS or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_01]: Which would just be horrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: How many people originally bought a PSP to play the NES emulator that was out at the time?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't buy one.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's another thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Games that strictly come out for the PSP like Dissidia
Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's part of the reason why I didn't play Kingdom Hearts Chain of Memories is because I didn't own a DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but at the same time, emulators, especially to play current games, are super duper illegal and just as bad as what they're banning.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, at least know what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least with the R4 and those devices, they are contingent on you having the system.
[SPEAKER_01]: True.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was there more you wanted to say there, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it was just quoting other cases in Europe that had to do with reel-to-reel tape copiers, but said that this was far worse because it did actually go right on the edge of copyright infringement.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, well, look, if you want something for free, here's something new that's going to be for free that doesn't involve questionable legality things.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is a totally legit thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: EverQuest 2 is soon going to have a free model.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, EverQuest 2 is getting EverQuest 2 Extended.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is not like when Lords of the Rings opened up.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, D&D opened up to free-to-play.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: DDO Opened Up and Went Free
[SPEAKER_01]: EverQuest 2 Extended
[SPEAKER_01]: It's interesting because they show all these different types of plans.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can get a free plan for bronze.
[SPEAKER_01]: What they call the bronze level is free.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a silver plan that's a $10 one-time purchase that gets you more character slots, more spells opened up, you get more bag slots and so forth, more...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting tactic.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if there'll be a lot of platinum and gold players on there, because I think they would be all in regular EverQuest, but I bet you'll get a lot of bronze and maybe even some silvers.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that isn't going to cross over with the regular EverQuest, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be its own separate thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what they're saying now.
[SPEAKER_01]: But my curiosity is, well, then what if one population starts to really off-balance the other?
[SPEAKER_01]: Is there a possibility they might merge them later on?
[SPEAKER_01]: I was reading on this thing about if you've already got an existing subscription for EverQuest then you basically get a gold account okay that's what I figured is that if you're already paying them 15 bucks a month that's probably what the regular ones are paying them interesting though that not only have they launched and maybe this is the unreported part of the story is that not only have they launched a free but they've also launched a pay us more version with that platinum tier
[SPEAKER_06]: is it more expensive than the regular games monthly subscription?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think the regular games monthly is the same as that gold $15 a month at least that's like the average MMO subscription but $200 a year I mean that's not as terrible as it sounds because you have to divide $200 by 12 so it's about what maybe $18 a month so it's not terrible
[SPEAKER_04]: um you know how you were saying with the the going to free to play um I when I actually had the power on my computer to do it um I used to play this game uh Cartoon Network's Fusion Fall don't knock it till you tried it um it's we're big fans of uh um robot unicorn attack here so yeah
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so the Cartoon Network Universe MMO, originally when it first came out, you would have the future levels, which was like about five sections of the world and a couple of quests and things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then in order to go to the past was a whole new world, was a totally expanded world.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was like 15 a month.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now I think it was back in April, they went completely free to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: and they literally skyrocketed their membership because it finally went free to play because a lot of us who really enjoyed the game were pissed that most of the game cost you money because me being a poor gamer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am totally against paying any sort of money for a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, within $10.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, there's a lot of people listening that are probably in the same boat you are.
[SPEAKER_01]: But there's a shout-out coming here from Giovedea in our chatroom at chat.orangelandredi.com Fusion Fall is amazing.
[SPEAKER_01]: VidPower in our chatroom says those old Cartoon Network Toonami Flash games were great.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkTetsuya is saying Adult Swim needs an MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: yeah, well, FusionFall is close enough to an Adult Swim MMO because the graphics of the game really remind me of this wonderful artist called Bleedman who's on DeviantArt and look him up, he's awesome it's like making the cartoony, you know like Dexter, not so cartoony, like he actually has a body and hands and arms what a concept so very cool DarkSakura, what do you got next for us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we have some other stuff for fans of Force Unleashed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Force Unleashed 2 has been in development, except the executive producer quit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hayden Blackman resigned from LucasArts after being with them for 13 years, and he just said it was time to go.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was like, I am not putting Jar Jar Binks in my game.
[SPEAKER_01]: F you.
[SPEAKER_02]: well as a quote while the decision to leave LucasArts did not happen overnight or come easily I really feel that now is the best time for me to move on and explore new creative challenges and look forward to the next phase of my career meaning god I hate this place I want to quit I know like totally reading through the lines there's huge drama that went down that you're never going to know about and LucasArts is saying that his departure is not going to affect the game's development at all yeah
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh no, it won't affect quality at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you never know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I know we're sitting here kind of poking fun, but it could get better.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, you know, LucasArts left the dry.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are extremely grateful for his many contributions, fully support him in his new endeavors, and wish him all the best in the future.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we're a company in California, and you're not allowed to say really anything bad about your previous employees, including the reasons why they left.
[SPEAKER_01]: by the way, I had a friend that worked at LucasArts and she totally got me in the Skywalker Ranch didn't you have George Lucas walk right by and you said something about you wanted to fling your sandwich at him?
[SPEAKER_12]: I was in meatless flicking distance of George Lucas
[SPEAKER_01]: I've heard this story on the show before.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted my money back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank God for your self-restraint.
[SPEAKER_06]: What a concept.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think one of the new things people will be excited about too is how we're going to be able to penalize people who are habitually quitting out of games, which isn't exactly cheating, but it creates a really negative experience for everybody else in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're going to penalize rage quitting?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: We actually have new tools now to detect that, and eventually people who do this habitually will actually be penalized.
[SPEAKER_01]: We want to be able to remove them from the population so they can't make everyone else keep having a bad time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, of course, they don't elaborate on what exactly they're doing, but doesn't that sound to me like if you rage quit too much, you're going to get banished to Rage Quit Island, where you will play with nothing but other rage quitters?
[SPEAKER_12]: and not be allowed to rage quit.
[SPEAKER_01]: That sounds kind of amazing actually.
[SPEAKER_12]: They should make them do Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_12]: For real.
[SPEAKER_01]: But at the same time, okay, they say they're going to be able to tell the difference between a rage quit and a disconnect.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, let me tell you this.
[SPEAKER_01]: In Final Fantasy XI, my version of rage quit was to go turn off the cable modem.
[SPEAKER_01]: So how would they know that that was... How did they know that that's me rage quitting and not a disconnect?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, you know, I get backing out of a match and all that or quitting or whatever, but how do they know the difference between that and a legitimate drop of the connection?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know those wonderful ninja mods.
[SPEAKER_04]: You never know where they are.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe it could be the timing of it, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, if you are habitually always quitting when certain circumstances met, then that's when you get banished to Rage Quit Island or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, if you're down and you always seem to lose your connection one minute before the match is over, you're probably going to get targeted for exile, is my thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tigerclaw says maybe someone with high pings lagging out and disconnecting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ah, maybe kind of seeing like, oh, the pings suddenly get slower and slower.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a legitimate disconnect where somebody who just had a really good connection and suddenly, oh, it's gone.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe a little less.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd be very curious to see how this all plays out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: How they're going to treat that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I love the idea of making all the rage quitters play together on their own little island where they can all rage quit and, you know...
[SPEAKER_01]: Go F themselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like trapping a bunch of trolls on a single island.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love the idea of Xbox Live being like the continent of awesome people and then trolls banished to their own island.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sounds great to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they're trolls they need to be banished to their own bridge.
[SPEAKER_01]: To go live under?
[SPEAKER_06]: As long as the bridge doesn't connect to anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure, I'm all for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: My hand is broken!
[SPEAKER_01]: Use your good hand.
[SPEAKER_01]: God gave you two.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to go take some more Vicodin.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, anyway, Valve made a whoops.
[SPEAKER_02]: They banned 12,000 legitimate Modern Warfare 2 players.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, the software that's in Steamworks to get the cheaters
[SPEAKER_02]: went on an extermination rampage and banned 12,000 players over the last two weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically what happened is that, and this is a quote from the email that was sent out by Gabe Newell, who's the Valve president, the problem was that Steam would fail a signature check between the disk version of a DLL and a latent memory version.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, basically, they said, you know, our bad, sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whoops.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that he used angst.
[SPEAKER_02]: I apologize for any frustration or angst that may have caused you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Can you all turn your caps lock off now?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: So he's also promised a giftable copy of Left 4 Dead 2 to all of those affected, as well as a copy for themselves.
[SPEAKER_01]: So if I get accidentally banned from a Steam game, I'm going to get two free copies of a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: One is giftable.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right, that's basically two free copies, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: One for you and one for someone you really like.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so hey, any of you that's been affected by this, gimme!
[SPEAKER_01]: Right?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's kind of where I'm at, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like, you know, I have Left 4 Dead 1, but not 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I think why they're giving Left 4 Dead 2 out is because, you know, when you get banned from a game like Modern Warfare 2, you know, the only compensation you can get is to go around killing a bunch of zombies is compensation, you know?
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a fair trade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Playing a big hairy biker.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Besides the also obvious part that it's also their game, you know, it is Valve's game, it's kind of one that they can give away.
[SPEAKER_01]: It actually is kind of impressive that they instead didn't go, oh, well, whoops, we'll give you a copy of, what's cheaper, Left 4 Dead 1, you know, or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Magical Unicorn Fart.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I don't think that was a Valve game.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can have a free copy of Alien Swarm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alien Swarm Oh wait, everybody's getting that free So, have we talked already about the wonderfulness that is Portal 2?
[SPEAKER_01]: on this show we have.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you watch all the tech demonstrations?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the slippery thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: The what?
[SPEAKER_02]: The slippery goo?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, the goo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the goo.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the bouncy goo?
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the bouncy goo.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was so great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was very much pleased with the entire concept of Portal.
[SPEAKER_04]: The fact that they changed the... Oh, and I died.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you still playing RuneScape?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I'm still playing RuneScape.
[SPEAKER_04]: The zombie just killed me.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're worse than Loki in Magic Robot Unicorn.
[SPEAKER_04]: He plays Magic Robot Unicorn.
[SPEAKER_01]: He denies that he does it too, but he does.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, the only grief I kind of have is the fact that they're theoretically using the same protagonist, but she looks nothing like the original game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did they put a picture of her?
[SPEAKER_00]: Of Chell?
[SPEAKER_04]: They did, but they didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't seen the picture of her.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I saw the one that was in Game Informer, the different one they had.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know she's also supposed to be, the actual person is supposed to be showing up in Half-Life 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: We also might have set off an LOL, Accidental False Alarm, in chat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thamster says, wait, is that out now?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no, no, it's not.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not until 2011.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_01]: But there are some sexy demos on YouTube if you want to go check it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's go to release dates, travel around the world, and talk about games that are going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Portal 2 will not be on the list this week, but maybe some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm going to start with the U.S.
[SPEAKER_01]: tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to shake things up a little bit because obviously Loki's not here.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm going to cover U.S.
[SPEAKER_01]: tonight and pronounce things correctly for once, I hope.
[SPEAKER_01]: Monster Rancher DS is out this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to cost you $30 if you want that on the DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sing it, family hits.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right, because you know you want to sing songs from Beauty and the Beast and The Little Mermaid, all from Disney, coming out on the PlayStation 3 and the Wii this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what's interesting though?
[SPEAKER_01]: The PS3 one is cheaper.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, because the Wii one comes with a mic.
[SPEAKER_01]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gary, I know this is going to be the one that gets you back into console games.
[SPEAKER_01]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_01]: Dora the Explorer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dora's Big Birthday Adventure on the DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: 30 bucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I were to get another console, I'd get a PS3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Junior Classic Books and Fairy Tales, $20 on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is basically, you're paying for $130 that are pretty much in the public domain, or were really cheap to license.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if you want that, hey, have fun with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, quite a barrage of some more wireless controllers and accessories also out this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I think we might have hit on most of the games...
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's kind of a slow week in game release world.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm trying to see if there's anything else this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: They got anything good in the budget bin?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, this new game on the Xbox 360 is only $30.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a role-playing game, and for an Xbox 360 game, that's something.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's Agarest War, and it comes out on the 5th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Record of Argorist War
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all I have for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_01]: this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, like I said, the U.K.
[SPEAKER_02]: is looking pretty bare.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing until next week, so I'm going to do Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry to take your pronunciation away from you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put all that anime pronunciation skill to the test.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we've got a few things that don't really particularly have a date on it, but they're for PC and Mac.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Arma 2, Operation Arrowhead, Battle vs. Chess, City of Heroes Going Rogue, Elemental War of Magic, Cannon Lynch 2, Mafia 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going to...
[SPEAKER_02]: The PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's Assassin's Creed Bloodlines from Ubi the Best, so it's basically re-released.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's Hayarikami 3, which is another re-release.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Oretachi no Sabage Versus, which is a new game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also coming out on the Nintendo DS, we have Battle Spirits Digital Starter.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is a game that I totally want to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Chokowai Hanashi DS Aonosho.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, it means like super scary stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all ghost tales.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what they are.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then also we have Heartcatch Precure Oshare Collection.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, there's also Jewel Pet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mahono Oheade Isho ni Aboso.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Asobo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I said that wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not just me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, I just read too fast.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we have Mame Goma Kawaii Gaipai.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no, I'm thinking opai.
[SPEAKER_02]: Opai means boobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tetris Party Premium also on August 5th.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, there's a game about boobs coming out?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's Ippai, and I thought I was thinking Oppai, which is boobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 2, we have J-League winning 11 2010 Club Championship, and Persona 3 FES, which is a PlayStation the best to re-release.
[SPEAKER_02]: Persona 4, also PlayStation 2 the best.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Shin Sango Musou 4 Empires, which is also a re-release.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, Madden NFL 11 is also on the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Persona games were really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really liked them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Believe it or not, we have sports fans that listen to the show who want their roster update for the year, just like DDR fans want their song list.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm wondering who in Japan likes American football.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, on the way, we have Tetris Party Premium and Twinkle Queen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, Arcade Shooter.
[SPEAKER_01]: Twinkle Queen?
[SPEAKER_02]: Twinkle Queen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me look this up.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think I met a drag queen like that once
[SPEAKER_01]: Been there, done that.
[SPEAKER_01]: How many all-chick fighting games have we seen at this point?
[SPEAKER_01]: They are not going to sleep with you when you beat the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: A few undated things that I just think is funny is Gunblade New York and LA Machine Guns Arcade Pack, which I would totally get.
[SPEAKER_02]: Love you, Sega.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cold Gym Dance Workout.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: And Lucha Libre AAA Heroes Del Ring.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was the one they were plugging at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Disney Guilty Party.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know what game that is, but that's just a funny way of phrasing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love the name.
[SPEAKER_06]: Disney Guilty Party?
[SPEAKER_01]: Who's guilty of stealing the cookies?
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that like Clue?
[SPEAKER_01]: It kind is.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like a whodunit game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Disney characters?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like an original Disney game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not like Ariel and Beauty and the Beast and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only Disney game that I'm actually looking forward to that they were plugging in E3 really, really bad was Epic Mickey.
[SPEAKER_04]: That looks amazing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Epic Mickey does look epic, but I gotta give a shout-out to Tron, because I don't stand for movies very often, but I will be there day one, Tron 3D, and I'm gonna have the biggest fanboy boner in the galaxy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gamers unite!
[SPEAKER_06]: Then you know they're gonna sell so many tie-in games with that, it's gonna be ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_06]: If it's a good movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, I hope it's a good movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, back to the Japanese list.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 3, Assassin's Creed 2 Special Edition, and Tiger Woods PGA Tour 11.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: And then finally for Xbox 360, we have Assassin's Creed 2 Special Edition Platinum Collection, and Magna Carta 2, which I know is pretty big.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a Platinum Collection.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that would be all.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of those were budget bin games or re-releases, which I really like.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Magna Carta 2 is a re-release.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Japan seems to be doing a lot of price reductions this time of year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't know what the occasion is, but hey, I'll take any excuse.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, so will I. Somebody's got some serious rage against Mickey on the chat room.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would actually be Drew Nami.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some folks in our chat room are asking, where is, where was it here?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going back to our chat room.
[SPEAKER_01]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com, and I think the whole Twinkle Queen brought this up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Frisbee's asking, where the fuck is the RuPaul's Drag Race game?
I think we should.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, come on, chat room.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which would you rather play?
[SPEAKER_01]: The Bachelor or RuPaul's Drag Race?
[SPEAKER_01]: RuPaul.
[SPEAKER_01]: Look, even you guys who have no interest in drag whatsoever, completely secure in your masculinity and your love of women, I think you would play RuPaul's Drag Race versus The Bachelor.
[SPEAKER_06]: And why do you say this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's awesome!
[SPEAKER_01]: Because The Bachelor is gayer than RuPaul's Drag Race.
[SPEAKER_01]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I won't argue with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, this is my thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I see my husband spend hours customizing wrestling characters...
[SPEAKER_02]: Like they're dress-up dolls?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's Barbie, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Barbie for men.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, yeah, men really like to do this too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, wrestling is just soap opera for men.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's nothing wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Men need their stories told.
[SPEAKER_01]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And speaking of the whole rage-quitting thing for Halo, I just rage-created RuneScape because I was sick of dying.
[SPEAKER_04]: I died twice.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're going to get banished to Rage Quit Island.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, actually, don't get me started on the fact that I started the game day one in RuneScape.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, how to fend for myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Had to learn how to use all my skills on my own.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then about, you know, two years after I started playing, they introduced Noob Island.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oy!
[SPEAKER_04]: Noob Island.
[SPEAKER_01]: They basically show you... There really is a place called Noob Island.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: They basically show you how to get to fifth level.
[SPEAKER_04]: They walk you through it tutorial style on how to craft... Does a little hand come out of the monitor?
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Come with me.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like that stupid Milo thing they were showing at E3 last year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come with me!
[SPEAKER_04]: They were probably losing too many new people.
[SPEAKER_04]: It reminded me of that annoying paperclip guy on Word.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh god, it was turning the thing off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just got a pepper in my wound.
[SPEAKER_01]: Every Word computer I ever log into for the first time, I'm always like, okay, first things first.
[SPEAKER_01]: Launch Word.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right click, disable.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kill the paperclip!
[SPEAKER_06]: Or the wizard, or whatever form it happens to take.
[SPEAKER_06]: That thing is so bloody annoying.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, look, I'm all about whatever makes you happy, but at the same time, don't complain about your system being slow when you have Miss Kitty running around chasing yarn.
[SPEAKER_02]: My word for the whole thing is, why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a question, just why?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hold on, Dark Tetsuya is making the Project Journey game for OLR, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Can we have a level where Dark Sakura shoots paper clips?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that would be appropriate.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: She can euthanize Mr. Paperclip.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just making that request.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not gory enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: That guy needs to die horribly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, then a paperclip can just attack her hand if she loses.
[SPEAKER_12]: The giant paperclip, but when you shoot him, he bleeds kittens.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: I was thinking just Mr. Paperclip could melt into slag slowly and painfully, but okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, can I do a story?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, you may.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Disney acquired PlayDom.
[SPEAKER_01]: What does that mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, PlayDom does sorority life, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: My favorite Facebook game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I seriously played sorority life religiously for like a month and then I got... Don't judge me!
[SPEAKER_08]: I see you judging him.
[SPEAKER_01]: You totally were just judging me right there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you see that look?
[SPEAKER_01]: That was the look of judgment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chips.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need to grab the chips because this is just entertaining now.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was playing, look, but do you know why I was playing sorority life?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because there was a dress up your character mode and I was the fiercest diva on the block.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got nothing.
[SPEAKER_01]: And she would beat bitches down with her purse because that's what she did in sorority life.
[SPEAKER_01]: But here's what started frustrating me about sorority life.
[SPEAKER_01]: They implemented, and I cannot believe we are giving this any face time on the show, but I really want to reiterate this week, I don't give a fuck.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right?
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: So anyway, so sorority life.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whatever floats your boat, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever sinks your battleship.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, that too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorority Life, yeah, I played it for like a month and I quit finally because I got really irritated that whenever you log in for some reason it would instantly put you up to the top of other people's list of who wants to beat down this bitch and so like I would log in and within three seconds I would be out of energy because I would basically get gang raped by all these blonde bitches the minute I log in so Sorority Life needed to give me at least like two minutes to bank my money or something
[SPEAKER_01]: But I didn't do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's my complaint with sorority life.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I've totally wasted two minutes of your life that you're never going to get back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I keep going?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Playdom also has Social City and Market Street.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those are their other kind of big ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Disney acquired them.
[SPEAKER_02]: It now has sorority life.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe we'll get Princess Sorority Life.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now that would bring me back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would play that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, just real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to see Belle give everyone the smackdown because she's the brainy woman.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tiana being the new girl on the block is not old and aged like Belle so she will beat you all down.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's Jasmine who probably has her whole... Jasmine will just whine.
[SPEAKER_02]: She'll just, you know, stick her tiger on people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to have a tiger!
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to be a princess with a tiger, Rob!
[SPEAKER_02]: Not with a frog.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought you wanted a princess with a pony.
[SPEAKER_02]: No!
[SPEAKER_02]: Tiger!
[SPEAKER_04]: Or a goat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm officially decreeing the wah-wah sound to SSJ Matt for a Facebook game, getting FaceTime on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who would have thunk it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, he gets the wah-wah sound.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see what you did there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've bitched about how much I hate Farmville.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh god, don't get me started.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm playing Hotel City and I actually like it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You say that like it's supposed to make it better.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like it's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, now how about a real game?
[SPEAKER_01]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: This game is called, it's an old school game, Pango.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pango was, let me see if I can find some music from Pango because Pango was pretty epic back in the day.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was this game where you would play a penguin and you walked around a maze and you could push ice blocks.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's freaking hard too.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't remember what it's inspired by but let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here's a
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess I'm a pango.
[SPEAKER_01]: So yeah, then you push these little ice blocks around and smush the guys in the stage.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like Pac-Man with a penguin.
[SPEAKER_01]: And there's no dots either.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are those green things trying to chase you?
[SPEAKER_01]: The green things are, I guess, trying to eat you.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: We recognize the music too That became later on I know, I've heard it before What other game was it in?
[SPEAKER_01]: DDR Raver's Choice Oh wow Anyway, that's not the point The point is, it's coming out on the PSP Yay
[SPEAKER_01]: No, wait, no, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's actually... I'm sorry, no, this is something completely different.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: It looked like a PSP screenshot at first.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's actually an arcade game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's coming out in arcades in Japan.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be an eight-player version.
[SPEAKER_01]: Eight-player simultaneous penguins running around the screen.
[SPEAKER_01]: No graphical upgrade at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course not!
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, now, speaking of classic games Wait, wait, speaking of Sega What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to enlist the aid of the chatroom because I used to know the name of this game and for the life of me I forgot about it It's a Sega Saturn game that was visual, not visual, it was audio only and you grew seeds with it A.K.A.
[SPEAKER_02]: the game came with a packet of seeds
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura likes to dig through the gaming vault and find a game that she says, Hey!
[SPEAKER_01]: You little children, babies of the world, including the new one born tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Listen, babies, you should be schooled on these old games.
[SPEAKER_01]: When I was your age, I played these games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_01]: Right, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: You weren't really a baby.
[SPEAKER_01]: You were probably like 15 when this particular game came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I wasn't.
[SPEAKER_01]: How old were you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I would have been 20.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would have been 19.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, well, enough talk about what age you would have been.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's talk about what the game is.
[SPEAKER_01]: What game did you pick for the folks tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Guardian Heroes.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you will play the music, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the character select.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me...
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Saturn music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, yeah, the game came out on the Sega Saturn in 1996.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, it was kind of funny because this came out before it did in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: It came out January 25th in America, January 26th in Japan, which I think might have actually, if I'm doing my, no, because then, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to think about, you know, across time zones if that would have been right, but no, I think Japan's a day ahead of us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a sequel that came out in 2004 for the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was Advance Guardian Heroes.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's sort of an RPG touch to the beat-em-up genre.
[SPEAKER_02]: As you can, those of us in here can tell on Rob's computer.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ooh!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I very much like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of got the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles feel.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was thinking Street Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's not a fighting game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a beat-em-up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sort of like how Final Fight and Double Dragon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except this one has magic and swords.
[SPEAKER_02]: Magic and swords.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there's no blood.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, going forward, it had a versus mode where you could pick up to six different characters individually.
[SPEAKER_02]: and compete with the main characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get unlockable monsters, bosses and civilians with a timed battle or to the death.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get experience points during each scene and you can customize your characters with six different attributes.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have strength, vitality, intelligence, mentality, agility and luck.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually luck is good for the spell casters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, there is, of course, the story mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can actually take different paths along the story.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you've got different endings, different bosses, different levels.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, basically it has a ton of replayability just because you can really keep going.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, this is one thing that I know my husband loves about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a path that will lead to gold and silver from Gunstar Heroes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And keep in mind, this was put up by Treasure.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it gets the, oh my god, Treshar!
[SPEAKER_02]: Award too.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, the gold and silver as the final boss uses the gem power like he did against our heroes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, you really can, um, it has multiple levels in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You usually only have three planes of battle, the four, the mid, and the back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, and you can switch them out in sequence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, and...
[SPEAKER_02]: There's also the shoulder buttons that make you move back and forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: You also have evasive moves.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you also have, like, if you get surrounded, you can change your planes.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can move to the foreground or background and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: With the games, you have Samuel Han, who is just a physical powerhouse type of guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have Randy M. Green.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who has some spells.
[SPEAKER_02]: Their elemental magic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ginjiro Ibushi, who is more moving attacks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nicole Neal, who has different magic.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Serena Corsair, who's supposed to be just a knight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty well-rounded.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, it's the big game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's...
[SPEAKER_02]: and also good luck freaking finding it now in Japan it was common as dirt I mean super common in the US not so much because they really didn't release very many copies over here and of course we didn't they released plenty of advanced Guardian Heroes but the Saturn one in the US pretty hard to find and it's got really crappy Americanized artwork on the cover makes me kind of sick
[SPEAKER_02]: But apart from that, though, I mean, it's a pretty damn good game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll leave the cover in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_01]: There it is, folks, for the Sega Saturn, your classic game of the week, Guardian Heroes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kind of a neat little combination there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like it when genres collide.
[SPEAKER_12]: And on top of that, it's treasure.
[SPEAKER_01]: is there a treasure game you haven't done at this point as a classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: we haven't done like Chameleon Twist or um so you guys can guess what will be done before well no I might have to eventually do that have I done Silhouette Mirage?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think I have done Silhouette Mirage you have to check the wiki I can't remember there's been over over 125 classic games of the week at this point crazy
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyhow, we're going to go ahead and take a break.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have done it.
[SPEAKER_01]: There is plenty more of Orange Lounge Radio to come.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to talk about Microsoft Connect in the next segment.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to talk about Silent Hill and a new comic book apparently coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: And yes, believe it or not, more Facebook games.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have to talk about Zynga tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't tune out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I promise you.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be lol-tastic.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we'll be back in just a little bit with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello everybody and welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: We are taping live on this August 1st of 2010 here at Orange Lounge Radio headquarters live at allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: And today is actually a very special day in OLR history.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki is not here tonight because his baby boy was just born earlier this evening at about 5 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_01]: Joshua is the boy's name in case you were wondering and you didn't hear earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm gonna blast Yay
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm having an absolute blast.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is so much fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I know why Drew comes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, we're only halfway through.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the best part.
[SPEAKER_01]: We haven't even gotten to emails or tweets.
[SPEAKER_01]: We got Twitters to get to a little bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: But wait, there's more.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, there's more.
[SPEAKER_01]: In fact, you only got about five more minutes to get Twitter topics in.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have not been able to do any plugs on Twitter tonight because I've been so busy.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I don't know if we're going to have anything waiting for us there, but I'll look.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have spam in French.
[SPEAKER_01]: We get spam in French all the time.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was just laughing because I can read it.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess these are some rumors picked up it was on buy.com but the listing was since pulled I can tell you this though the rumblings around and people that I know and you know I got friends in low places and so forth Orange Lounge Radio wants to tell you guys this is true these are happening but I mean also that's kind of like telling you like rain will eventually fall from the sky next month of course there's going to be limited editions of these huge games shouldn't be a huge surprise
[SPEAKER_01]: Activision hasn't officially announced it yet, but they will.
[SPEAKER_01]: Prestige for $150, Hard Edition for $80.
[SPEAKER_01]: Couldn't tell you what's in those.
[SPEAKER_01]: Although we're hearing possibly something about maybe a little car.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, take that with what you will.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is one that Activision will talk about.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is DJ Tiesto is actually joining DJ Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's actually going to be in the game as a playable character and he's going to be doing two new mixes in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that's kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_01]: No news yet as to exactly what he's doing, but there was a little video that was released.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm not sure what this video shows us.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it just shows him in game and it might be like playing one of his mixes here.
[SPEAKER_01]: But they did release a little clip here from DJ Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm trying to get a little more of it here in studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first one was really awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I love DJ Hero 1.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm a DJ.
[SPEAKER_12]: I play for so many people.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm very lucky that I have that opportunity.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nah, I don't want to hear the whole interview.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was hoping to hear more of his music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Being part of the DJ Hero game is...
[SPEAKER_01]: He'll be in DJ Hero, hooray for him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, Kmart.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow, this is like three shows in a row we've actually had a Kmart story.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't get this.
[SPEAKER_01]: When did Kmart become relevant?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is so weird.
[SPEAKER_01]: They've done the whole rebranding thing, so perhaps... Well, they're really trying to appeal to the gamers, and this is a pretty big one.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is a great way to appeal to gamers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sell stuff cheap.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Wii console, down to $179.99 this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: A whole $20 off.
[SPEAKER_01]: But hey, that's 10% of the cost, so hard to complain about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: By the way, the deal runs out tomorrow, so you better hurry up and get on that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Aw, damn.
[SPEAKER_12]: Came right around the corner from my house.
[SPEAKER_01]: Both the white and the black Wiis, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no money, no!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, how about some other stuff?
[SPEAKER_01]: How about it?
[SPEAKER_02]: This makes me particularly happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: In Rock Band, we have Blondie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_01]: There's already a little Blondie in there, but I'm never going to say no to more Blondie.
[SPEAKER_02]: and also a group that I like, Family Force 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: So actually, with this upcoming pack that's going to be out on August 3rd, we have Rapture for Blondie, Jesus Freak DC Talk, whatever, The Perfect Crime No.
[SPEAKER_02]: 2, The Decemberists, I Only Want You, Eagles of Death Metal, Saturday Morning Eels, Love Addict Family Force 5, Sturm und Drang, KMFDM, and Bulletproof LaRue.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shut up, what, in Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_01]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're getting Bulletproof?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love that song, even though it's like way overplayed on the radio right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_01]: I loved it like nine months ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm getting DC Talk, that's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's give them a break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, ESRB has Fatal Labyrinth, which was a Sega Genesis game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's supposed to be set up on the PC downloads, but it's also going to be available for Wii for the Virtual Console and Mac, PS3, Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's in the Genesis collection thingy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't bother.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the Sonic Ultimate Genesis collection.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, get the Sonic collection.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's great, but don't bother with a $5 standalone release when you can get that collection for $20.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you get tons of stuff right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes it is worth it to pay more.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that game kind of blows.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I hate to say it, but it's kind of like somebody decided to port... I don't know if you guys know Rogue, the old-ass game from years and years ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: Somebody decided to port Rogue to the Sega Genesis, and that's kind of what you got.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Rogue is more fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, um, now also in other news, um, there is a mandatory update for, um, PS3 FromWorth, uh, 3.41 So, um, it's gonna add in a You May Like section to the PlayStation Store And, really, that's about it There's nothing else But it's mandatory!
[SPEAKER_01]: That's like how Twitter now shows me people I ought to be following I don't give a crap Anyway
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, I'm like, a lot of these people I'm not following for a reason.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just so you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, let's go to Twitter topics and visit the tweeter and see who's sending us messages.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: and this is definitely one that I think is interesting that we did overlook and it comes from the International Business Times that he's actually linking us to China is actually pushing a real name system for online games and that starts today, August 1st you're going to have to register using your real name if you want to play an online game this is like real ID gone wrong, really wrong
[SPEAKER_01]: That comes from the Ministry of Culture.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was announced on June 22nd.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's part of a nationwide campaign to improve management of the virtual gaming industry and protect the minor from unwholesome content.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you do realize this is China, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I know, I know, it's different.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's obviously a lot different than Real ID.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, they have some serious issues with people not managing their time well on these MMOs, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, but then again, we have some people with issues not managing their time well in America as well, so it just seems to be a lot worse.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some of the stories you hear are really, really scary over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what they're talking about, Shifty Eye, Shifty Eye.
[SPEAKER_01]: But anyhow, how would you like it if they stepped in and said, hey, everybody's going to have to play online games with their real name.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do not want.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do not want.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good luck with that, China.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, next up, though, speaking of China, how about Chinatown?
[SPEAKER_01]: Matt, SJ100Matt on Twitter actually wanted to link us to this.
[SPEAKER_01]: He kind of wanted to give a shout-out to one of his local arcades.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've heard of this place, but I've never been, and he was very proud that Kotaku had featured it this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: As you know, they're one of the big boy gaming blogs, and so they feature stuff once in a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: and they are talking about the Chinatown Fair Video Arcade it is located on Mott Street in New York City's Chinatown apparently it is also this environment that LGBT youth can just kind of be themselves yeah I read about that kind of interesting that it's gaming and LGBT colliding although I thought it was really cool when I went to that place in Portland they had like an LGBT night once a month which I thought was kind of fun all the gay gamers can get together
[SPEAKER_02]: I really feel they need to include the asexual in that list too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, there's a big old long string of alphabet soup, but at some point it gets too big.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_01]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: So it just sounds like this hodgepodge of just go play and have fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what video games should be about anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: It shouldn't even be about LGBT or Rayvars or Otaku or whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: It should just be about just have fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't be a dick.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: We got enough clicks in the real world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Always remember rule one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't be a dick.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't be a dick.
[SPEAKER_01]: And don't bring your click into the virtual world.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then lastly, DarkTetsuya on the tweeters wants us to plug his latest retro review for Mega Man on the site.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's actually pretty awesome, so go check that out at OrangeLaunchVideo.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't want to say expose on Mega Man, but it's a nice little retrospective.
[SPEAKER_06]: The original Mega Man games, I remember those very fondly.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh man, you've got to see some of the new ones, because the new ones invoke the old ones very well.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's very cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very, very cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, let's get back into some other news here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to start off with a story on Kinect.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kinect, of course, being the motion control device coming out from Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_01]: We announced last week that it was going to be $150, although obviously speculation had run rampant on that for a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's coming with Kinect Adventures.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, of course, they got a lot of shit for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I guess they came out this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was the marketing manager, Brett Siddons.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's the marketing manager for Microsoft Connects.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was at an event in the UK for Amazon.
[SPEAKER_01]: He says that Connect is, quote, very competitively priced.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, since he was in the UK, he was talking about UK pricing, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's all the same deal at the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's basically saying that the navigation controller is going to be an extra $30 on top of the $100 bundle.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: and DJ Ranma S.
[SPEAKER_01]: uh so anyway uh Microsoft is basically trying to say hey if you want two people to have fun you only need one connect whereas with all these other systems you need two of everything and we kind of knew they'd go this way and I think as we talked about last week a little bit it's kind of like well but your console then offsets the price of a Wii and it's really all about the games at the end of the day honestly I mean you can charge plenty for this system as long as you have the games to back it up but if Dance Central is going to be your only good game
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it's worth the time of all the E3 games that I saw for the Kinect the one that I really would love to go over to a friend's house and play because I do not own a 360 god forbid is the Children of Eden looks amazing it does look great it's too bad they didn't have a playable one on the show floor so we don't know enough about it but if you just imagine it's going to be Rez using your body that's cool enough for me
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that just looks absolutely amazing.
[SPEAKER_01]: It'll be great.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, DarkSakura, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, this is actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Silent Hill 8, the guy who's writing it, Tom Waltz, is also working on a comic book crossover called Silent Hill Past Life.
[SPEAKER_02]: Set in 1867 and is about an outlaw called Jebediah Foster who meets a widow that changes his ways.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they move to Silent Hill to escape the Wild West.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, but, of course, Silent Hill screws them over.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, but, it's that, um, the game is going to feature a character from the comic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although the game is in modern times.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, hey, I hope that they do better.
[SPEAKER_02]: The trailer is out, though, for Silent Hill 8, and I really need to sit down and watch it.
[SPEAKER_01]: They showed a little bit at E3.
[SPEAKER_01]: It looked alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that you have to put in your birthday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's not awesome?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, because it's restricted content, young lady.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, well, while she's watching that, I have to bring this up.
[SPEAKER_01]: I apologize in advance, but let's all poke a little fun at Zynga this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because they did something where they're getting a lot of shit for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So if you don't like Zynga, you can kind of jump on the bandwagon with this.
[SPEAKER_01]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_01]: Zynga has this game on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's called Street Racing.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they announced, with really no rhyme or reason, that they are shutting the game down tomorrow, August 2nd.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, Zynga came out this week and said, quote, as an acknowledgement of the inconvenience these changes may have caused, we have offered credits to all players who have made a purchase in the last 90 days.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: So these players will receive a credit for the exact amounts of their purchases, plus an additional 100 units of premium currency in any of Zynga's nine most popular games.
[SPEAKER_01]: So in other words, if you bought stuff, they're not going to refund you.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're just going to let you have credits for other games.
[SPEAKER_01]: What if I don't want those other games?
[SPEAKER_01]: Although we can kind of sit here and kind of point and laugh and ha-ha at Zynga and who bought that shit anyway, it does kind of lead to this scary precedent.
[SPEAKER_01]: For example, right now you can buy things in World of Warcraft, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: And what if in World of Warcraft you buy, I don't know, like a pet?
[SPEAKER_01]: What's going to happen when World of Warcraft goes away?
[SPEAKER_01]: You lose that pet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which, you know...
[SPEAKER_01]: Duh, you should know that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Games don't last forever and so forth.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it should be something you think about before you get these, you know, untangible items, correct?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think this serves as a little bit of a lesson.
[SPEAKER_01]: If ever this game decides to shut its doors...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you don't lose it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't lose it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which, you know, the whole thing that they're shutting it down, you know, it's for no rhyme or reason, nothing.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyhow, let's see, where are we at?
[SPEAKER_01]: Comments in chatroom, chat.orange.com Bonds006 says, but Neopets, PetPet, they live, I hope Neopets is another one of those sites that might go away someday Hitstun, if ever Xbox Live goes offline, you can't play any of the Xbox Live indie games you bought
[SPEAKER_01]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, original Xbox was just shut down a couple months ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does that mean in about five years the Xbox we have now is also going to get shut down?
[SPEAKER_01]: And then all these indie games go wrong?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of funny because a lot of people were giving crap to OnLive, the new service that's out that lets you play games through the streaming service.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, you're going to buy this game for $50, but it's really only guaranteed to work for three years.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then they might pull the plug on OnLive.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whereas if you go to the store and buy a game for $50, you pretty much have it quote-unquote forever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just things to think about.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know one way or the other.
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of almost reminds me of the old school Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every time a new console would come out, you can't use the old school games in the new console.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's like you just plunker down 15 bucks to buy that really awesome version of Zelda that won't go in your Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing was backward compatible.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I kind of stuck to the PlayStation series so I can play my old PlayStation games on the PS2.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess they're all backward compatible with the PS3 too.
[SPEAKER_01]: PS1 is, and this is what doesn't make sense about Sony.
[SPEAKER_01]: It depends what console you got and how early you bought a PS3 if you can backwards compatible or can't.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think she can, but I can't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can because we have a first release PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: They took out a lot of the extra bells and whistles with later releases.
[SPEAKER_02]: so if I bought a PS3 now I wouldn't be able to he probably couldn't do jack shit no sir not unless you got really lucky in finding a used one and a lot of people jack up the prices of those that are backwards compatible you know what's extra funny is that usually Dan and I wait until second releases come out when we get stuff because we're usually not initial adopters of consoles and phones and stuff but we got this right away and we sort of got a reward because our discover card gave us back a hundred bucks
[SPEAKER_06]: So would a new PS3 let you play a PS2 game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I know they still sell PS2 games.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, I think I've got an extra PS2 you could probably borrow.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a PS2 that works just fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can play PS1 games.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Imports, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Import PS1 games.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, the region locks are still in place for PS1 and PS2 but it's region free for the new games.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: PS3 games are region free.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which is interesting but you might remember like Loki imported a racing game that he thought was awful but he imported it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the exciting thing is, if Beatmania 2DX ever comes out on the PlayStation 3, I know that was the game that made me buy a Japanese PlayStation 2 so I could play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Same here.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's how obsessed with this music game series I was.
[SPEAKER_01]: If they do release that on PS3 in the future, which I hope they will, it's going to break down that...
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, we did ours too.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of people did.
[SPEAKER_01]: It wasn't just me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still have my old clunker at home.
[SPEAKER_04]: My wonderful, the original PS2 box.
[SPEAKER_01]: Props to those PS2s for holding up after all those years because I believe we heard Bobby on the show right before us talking about his Xbox 360 red-ringed.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of my friends just sent me a text over the weekend, my 360 red-ringed frown face.
[SPEAKER_01]: They don't build them like they used to.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, they don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: My PS2 is still up and going because I don't use it that much, mostly for DVDs, but yeah, it still works.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not real confident about Sony optical drives, just bad experiences, but we'll see how long it lasts.
[SPEAKER_06]: So far, so good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Breast Lowell is in our chat and says, I still want to get a JPS2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the good news is it's really cheap now.
[SPEAKER_01]: You probably get it for only about $100 now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe $120, $150.
[SPEAKER_01]: For a Japanese PlayStation 2, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: But keep in mind, if you import a console from Japan, it's only going to play the Japanese games.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there's got to be something out there that you can't get here, like dating sims.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's go to our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see if some of the faces have changed in our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're talking about some things never change.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see about the emails.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com if you want to send us an email.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think we got quite a few this week, right Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: A few more, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, this is your friendly neighborhood Mexican, except in Arizona, Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_02]: First of all, very late congrats on your 8th anniversary.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, sir.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that I said that, I want to comment on some stuff you talked about on your last show.
[SPEAKER_02]: First, about the connect and the move.
[SPEAKER_02]: You asked people if they're going to buy either of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll probably get the Kinect later when it gets cheaper, because I really want to try both Dance Central and Dance Master, and probably other games that Microsoft may release in the future.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Kinect does really look awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the move, first of all, I don't own a PS3 yet, so before I get the move, I need a really good reason to get a PS3, which right now is nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I consider that their biggest problem and why the move may fail.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the PlayStation Network in Mexico and other Latin American countries sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, little to no content at all, and they want me to pay for a plus service too?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, this is a long email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another thing that you discussed was controllers versus keyboards and mouse.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really think it comes down to what you're playing and how you're playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: For first person shooters, sure, keyboard and mouse are way better because of precision and other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But for platformers or action games, I prefer controllers since it will give more comfort and allow you to do more stuff like jumping and attacking.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to put two games as an example, Mirror's Edge and Psychonauts Mirror's Edge, while you can play with a keyboard and mouse just fine there are a lot of button combinations that are easier to do with a controller and with Psychonauts the game was designed for consoles so the keyboard controls are just plain awkward
[SPEAKER_02]: There are games that are easier with keyboard and mouse like Team Fortress 2 and Left 4 Dead, not to mention point-and-click adventures, western RPGs, strategy games, or MMOs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think you just need to learn both ways of controlling games and get the hang of both.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no better way of playing games in general, just a more comfortable way to play certain games, which I agree with, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's all I want to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for reading.
[SPEAKER_02]: Until next time.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry my lack of articles on the OLR main page, but no internet at home makes it difficult to do so.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Suck it, Arizona, and your racist laws.
[SPEAKER_02]: Deft is Cabrown.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, well, I think, especially the keyboard mouse part, I think a lot of the debate usually is around first person shooters, but definitely you bring up a good point about, you know, it really depends on the type of game you're playing, absolutely, is that, you know, keyboard mouse ain't gonna cut it, I think, as well for a game like Psychonauts, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: For me, I don't know if it's because... I don't even know how to explain it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I used to play Quake just fine with keyboard and mouse, but some of these new games are just too many buttons.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, I know, but yet when I hold a controller in my hand, it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't explain it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't expect anyone else to understand it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just the way it is for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll tell you what's funny is that when I was playing PSO, I could not, I mean, you can play it with a keyboard, it just was much more comfortable with a controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Final Fantasy XI, everyone was saying, why aren't you playing with a keyboard, why aren't you using a keyboard, why aren't you using a keyboard?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, because I can do just fine with my controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted one for World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate playing World of Warcraft because I hate playing it on the keyboard.
[SPEAKER_01]: What about Star Trek Online?
[SPEAKER_01]: Isn't that all keyboard?
[SPEAKER_02]: It is, but for some reason, when you get into space combat, it really helps to have a mouse.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you can rotate your camera with it, as well as do direct targeting.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it works a lot better.
[SPEAKER_04]: As well as the difference between even different versions of the same game, like the different Wii versus PlayStation versions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I played the original PlayStation 2 version of Okami...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Fun game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I played the Wii re-release, and surprisingly, I liked the PlayStation 1 better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the Wii Remote, I don't know what it was, it just felt more...
[SPEAKER_04]: Clunky.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: It felt like it was rushed.
[SPEAKER_04]: It felt like it was, you know, they were just trying to hurry it out as fast as they could and they didn't bother with the calibration that they needed to make it good.
[SPEAKER_04]: With PlayStation 2, you don't have that problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do not have that problem with Okami.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about the next email?
[SPEAKER_02]: We're fond of calling it the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_04]: Weemote, Weemote, Weemote, Weemote, Weemote, Weemote, I don't know this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't own one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good morning everyone, this is Jeet, it's the other Swede, writing in once again.
[SPEAKER_02]: This time I'd like to comment a bit on the discussion that was brought forth last time concerning the accuracy and comfort when it comes to controllers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I could start a five-page rant about why a mouse and keyboard is far superior to any console controllers, but I won't.
[SPEAKER_02]: The reason is that I am very biased, and due to that bias, I can't objectively say that the mouse is better.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's only a personal preference embedded in me during my childhood thanks to my uncle who introduced me to PC gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's simple, whatever controller you like, be it an Xbox 360 controller, Playstation Move, or mouse, it's only the best peripheral for you personally, not the whole world and everyone in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you!
[SPEAKER_02]: To sum it up, the discussion of what control method is the quote best is pointless since it all comes down to what you are skilled at using or prefer.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Note that I didn't apologize for any spelling errors this time.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's because I realized it's rude for someone who grew up with English as their primary language to comment on minor flaws of someone who learned it as a second language.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see you typing a letter to me in Swedish without grammatical errors in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still love you, even you, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: And by the way, if I know someone's typing from another country, I don't give them a hard time.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I don't, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for reading my letter and I hope your hand is feeling better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_01]: Drew Nami in our chatroom at chat.orange.radio.com says, IKEA controller for the Swedish email.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_01]: And yeah, apparently it's international email night at Orange Challenge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: But hey, that's awesome to know that we have listeners all over the globe.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, next email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey Orange Lounge, long time listener, first time responder.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, we got the cliche.
[SPEAKER_01]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: As for the move, personally I think it will be the better motion control option.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, the price point is high, but I think it will be the most accurate on the most powerful system of the three.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw some great screen tests demonstrating its abilities and I think it could be a hardcore alternative to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the main reason I have avoided the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: It lacks the hardcore devotion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Snow5.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just playing devil's advocate to your email.
[SPEAKER_01]: I kind of get that perspective and that's why a lot of people have avoided the Wii, but what about games like Brawl and Metroid Other M and some of these other kind of like, and GoldenEye, some of these other cool things that are on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, is that not hardcore enough?
[SPEAKER_05]: No More Heroes?
[SPEAKER_01]: yeah I mean I don't know it's kind of like I it feels like there's some cool stuff on the way I mean granted maybe not as much and yeah we kind of made some errors when it comes to not being online I think that's one of their like biggest flaws is that there's the multiplayer online is just a joke you know compared to what else is out there I agree but appreciate the perspective we have two more emails to go no
[SPEAKER_02]: Too bad!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's why you sound like an auctioneer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Second is I'm wondering if there was a way to get the live stream via mobile platform, i.e.
[SPEAKER_02]: a MotoDroid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Third is actually two things in the first letting being that DarkSakura is a fiend for grammar, spelling, and punctuation.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it might interest you to know that the site has lasted, has several
[SPEAKER_02]: Lastly, I wonder what point during this email she stops reading this and starts to have convulsions.
[SPEAKER_02]: As I've written this without punctuation, I have made several misspellings and several grammatical errors on purpose.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that I don't like her or anything, I just thought that I might get a giggle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times all and keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I figured by then it was, hey, you did use...
[SPEAKER_01]: You gotta laugh at me anytime somebody writes in to give DarkSakura some shit.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm laughing at this because I realized by that point that it was on purpose.
[SPEAKER_01]: So this is a punctuation troll?
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow, we have our first grammar troll on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get a gold star.
[SPEAKER_01]: You totally get a gold star.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is from Kane I Am.
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't sign it, but I'm taking it from the email.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kane IM, you get a gold star for being the first grammar troll at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the subject of the subject is we, yay, wahoo.
[SPEAKER_01]: Please, that is not encouraging others to copy what this gentleman has done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because if you do it the first time, you're clever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyone who does it the second time is stupid.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, what was the real question here, though?
[SPEAKER_01]: There was something in there I actually wanted to answer that had come up in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, Loki's job.
[SPEAKER_01]: He works for a game distributor.
[SPEAKER_01]: So he actually, like, he's kind of the middleman between gaming companies and the actual stores.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know that for iPhone we use apps.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's an All Games app on the iPhone, supposedly, but I guess it disappeared this week, so I don't know what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a Scott question, not a Rob question, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I will say this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Any program that can use Shoutcast can listen to the All Games stream.
[SPEAKER_01]: You just have to get the link for the Shoutcast feed.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a little silly for me to yell it out here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Pandora has a...
[SPEAKER_01]: Go to all... Well, Pandora's... Does it have shoutcast mode in it, though?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: But most mobile phones have some type of shoutcast tuner app.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, anything that's like, listen to thousands of internet radio stations is probably a shoutcast app.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if you go to allgames.com, you can get the link to listen to all games radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's pretty easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the grammar thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which I'm laughing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually laughing because I realized it was on purpose.
[SPEAKER_01]: How funny, Tiger, I'm sorry, I have to say this, Tiger Call in our chat room is saying since the All Games app isn't up right now, you can get the Video Game Outsiders iPhone app because they're another show on the network, they do Tuesdays here, and I guess their app does it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I guess a backup.
[SPEAKER_02]: The last one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Greetings, OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rini here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will soon be the proud owner of a new Beatles Rock Band limited edition bundle that I scored for $20.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, I have not owned a Rock Band game until now, so I was wondering if you and the listeners could give any advice on what I should know about keeping my gear in great condition.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would say...
[SPEAKER_02]: Sanitize it if other people play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially if they have greasy fingers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or liquor is being mixed with those controllers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, um, those monitor wipes that you can use to clean, like, your computer screen, those might be good for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alcohol prep pads, yo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because alcohol just dries... Clorox wipes are, like, the greatest invention ever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but you gotta be careful with those.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, that's true, you don't want to bleach your controllers, I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, the horrible thing is, is when you said, you know, if alcohol's being mixed with drinks, I got this horrible mental image of a Rock Band controller mixing a giant vat of alcohol.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wouldn't use it for that purpose.
[SPEAKER_06]: You must hate your rock band if you're doing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, when you store them, make sure that you don't have them stacked up haphazardly.
[SPEAKER_02]: We usually stand ours up on end and put them in a corner to where they won't really fall on each other.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you really want to take good care of them, and this is the way to do it, just go get one of those big plastic storage tubs at Target.
[SPEAKER_01]: It would cost you only a couple bucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ikea would have them too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Any place ought to have it.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't Stop Believin'
[SPEAKER_01]: is really all you need.
[SPEAKER_02]: Skull Crusher Mountain.
[SPEAKER_01]: Definitely look for the free stuff on the Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jonathan Colton stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really about what type of music you're into.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Stephen Colbert.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Blah yourself.
[SPEAKER_01]: Haters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Haters gonna hate, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Haters gonna hate.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop the hate.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have actually said this, Rob, and I made this statement clear when we went out to Vic's Ice Cream downtown, that I do not dislike Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_02]: I dislike the radio versions of her songs, but every time I've heard piano versions, I've really liked them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: No one cur.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought you just disliked the performance art aspects of her videos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't like her videos, but I mean, I like the video for Alejandro.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't like the videos, but the songs are pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like video games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, let's go on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I also like Angst.
[SPEAKER_01]: What a perfect segue into our FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_01]: And now for those new to Orange Lounge Radio, this is the part of the show where we just say a big F you to whatever we've been waiting to say an F you to all week.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to the hole in my hand and to my husband's blood pressure.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're gonna beat you, butthead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm gonna give an F you to all the sand in my hypothetical vagina that I apparently have today.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just...
[SPEAKER_02]: are you feeling a little gritty and not so fresh?
[SPEAKER_04]: yes I have to say a big F you to any gaming company who is willing to charge multiple dollars for copies of games that I already own yes, I'm talking to you, PlayStation
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, the biggest FU, well, general FUs all around too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see, the list is long and distinguished, we'll keep it short.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fox News, Sarah Palin, Meg Whitman, boo!
[SPEAKER_06]: Carly Fiorna, oh god, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought you were keeping it short.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah, I am keeping it short.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the whole Republican Party, go rot, FU.
[SPEAKER_01]: That won't generate any emails tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, Rob, as an official woman, you can have an honorary vag.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just what I've always wanted.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can keep it.
[SPEAKER_01]: These things are nothing but trouble.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you don't have to have a hypothetical one.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can have an honorary one.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't want one.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's the difference?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're both non-existent.
[SPEAKER_01]: Send it back.
[SPEAKER_01]: Return to sender.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do not want.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob's pet vag.
[SPEAKER_01]: My little vag.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's a product idea for Hasbro.
[SPEAKER_12]: Imagine vagina.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki is in our chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: He joined on the hospital Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: For free Wi-Fi?
[SPEAKER_03]: I second that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if he's listening or what.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just sent him a private message if I can call him, but I don't know if he can see.
[SPEAKER_01]: He probably can't hear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Free slow Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what you get when it's free Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's slow Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we'll see if we can call them or not.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: But for now, we're going to keep on moving with the news.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Metroid Other M. Now here's a Wii game that's going to be pretty hardcore for that person earlier.
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, I'm excited about this game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm finally going to dust off the Wii after like six months of not playing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is kind of an interesting mode they're putting in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be a theater mode in Metroid Other M. That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you want to just watch the movie Metroid Other M, you can do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a theater mode, according to one of the designers at Nintendo, Yoshio Sakamoto.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a theater mode that lets you view all of the cutscenes linked together seamlessly as a single movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: We placed just as much weight on enjoying the story as we did on the action aspects of the game, but it's hard to fully communicate a storyline in a video game with just one playthrough.
[SPEAKER_01]: At the same time, though, it's asking a lot of players to beat the game twice to get it all, so that's where the idea for that mode came from.
[SPEAKER_01]: It lets you make a lot of discoveries, things you missed, or dialogue that makes more sense in retrospect.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hope it helps people understand the story better.
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting approach.
[SPEAKER_04]: That almost kind of reminds me of Final Fantasy X. They had the theater that was in Luka that you could go to and buy the individual cutscenes, which was really nice when you wanted to look at them all together.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I was going to say, people have been kind of doing this whole like cutscene movie thing for years.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, I'm pretty sure I could probably go on YouTube and just see, you know, nothing but cutscenes from some of the more recent Final Fantasy games and get a pretty good sense of what the story is all about.
[SPEAKER_01]: So kind of interesting that the game is now kind of officially endorsing that idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I like his reasoning behind it.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's just kind of like, you know what, you shouldn't have to beat the game twice to get everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: and you might kind of go it's nintendo easy mode just hit the button or whatever but you know i i i i'll give them a little credit i think something as epic as metroid is is worthy of a theater mode so is it cheating if you watch the whole movie first and then you play the game or yes but in my opinion that's no worse than going on the internet and reading the entire faq before you play the game good point yeah that's true i mean is it really any worse i
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm okay with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: TigerClaw says, now the question is how long is the theater mode?
[SPEAKER_01]: Usually cutscenes, when you add them all together, they aren't usually an hour.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're saying two hours.
[SPEAKER_01]: Two hours is divided into chapters just like a DVD.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not just the cutscenes.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's actually pre-recorded gameplay that will be intertwined with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Although I guess at one point they wanted to actually have recorded bits of you playing the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: that would then go into theater mode, but it's too big of a pain in the ass, basically, and I'll tell you why.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's because there's no decent storage on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: Even though that's not what they're saying, I'm totally filling in the gaps there and making it up.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's gotta be the reason.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't store that information.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it is watching an actual movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kinda cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, how many people are perfectly content?
[SPEAKER_01]: Dark Sakura comes in here, and a lot of her gaming weeks usually are, I watched Dan play blank.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a lot of people that game by watching other people game.
Well,
[SPEAKER_02]: Part of it for me is that he'll play a lot of single player stuff and loves to just completely dominate the front room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Usually if I'm out there and he's playing something, it's just me watching him play something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially now since I had my hand surgery.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really get a lot of enjoyment out of just sitting down watching him play.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could sit and watch him play Grand Theft Horse for a while because it was very cinematic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't watching games boring?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like watching a movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a DVD that's all the cutscenes of Final Fantasy X-2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alan will watch me PvP in WoW and he enjoys it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, he likes to play backseat driver too, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like doing that.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, one more story and then I've got one more story as well and then we're going to get to the phones.
[SPEAKER_01]: 877-GAME-OLR in just a moment.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of funny because this is something I downloaded and never got a chance to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was actually sitting here trying to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the Gorillas Escape to Plastic Beach, which is on iPad and iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good band.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that about?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's basically them trying to get to the plastic beach.
[SPEAKER_02]: You either play Murdoch, who flies on a doom glider, and he's trying to keep 2D from escaping.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, so it's...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's only $1.99 and you can get it as a browser game too.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's pretty cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here, let me start it up again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know this is fantastic because you won't probably be able to hear it very well.
[SPEAKER_01]: It seems interesting to me though.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean usually these are the type of things you put out before an album comes out to kind of raise awareness about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's a little weird that this is coming out now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is this picking up?
[SPEAKER_01]: Very quietly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Most of our listeners probably won't be able to hear it very well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Headphone people will probably be able to hear it okay, but speaker people probably not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to let you hear the beginning of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's loading.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just beep beep boops.
[SPEAKER_01]: We can hear it there a little bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I'm so British.
[SPEAKER_01]: Making more money off the characters.
[SPEAKER_01]: But hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: If they can have Britney Spears apps and sing along to Tap Tap Bieber or whatever those games are.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's such a cute little girl.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who?
[SPEAKER_01]: Justine Bieber That's awesome I was like, who are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_01]: Britney Spears?
[SPEAKER_02]: She's not a little girl anymore No, Justine Bieber Oh, Justine Bieber, okay She's the cutest little lesbian, I swear I'm a big Gorillaz fan, so this is so cute But man, looking at the iPad version though, I'd really love to play the iPad one
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Murdoch and his Doom Glider.
[SPEAKER_01]: One more story for you guys about a guy who now will have plenty of money to develop games on the iPad if he chooses to.
[SPEAKER_01]: Richard Garriott.
[SPEAKER_01]: He is the guy that made Ultima many, many years ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember Ultima?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was epic epicness.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I spent a lot of time playing Ultima Exodus.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently, it came out today that out of the $47 million that Richard Garriott was seeking, he was actually awarded $28 million.
[SPEAKER_01]: Touching.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently, they did find that there was some misrepresentation going on there and some contracts were breached and so forth.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what's unfortunate, though, is that NCSoft makes a lot of... I hope they have good insurance, like legal insurance or something, because...
[SPEAKER_01]: they make a lot of MMOs and hopefully this won't hit them in the pockets really hard because they've got a lot of stuff under development at MCSoft right now this is going to suck that they're going to have to pay this guy out $28 million because they screwed up some things
[SPEAKER_01]: Tabula Rasa was an interesting game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of a bummer.
[SPEAKER_01]: It got kind of a crappy break.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe they just didn't promote it well enough.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or maybe just nothing was able to beat WoW at that time.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: But there it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: We are going to go ahead and open up the Skype line if you want to give us a call at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go ahead and give us a call and we'll take a few calls before we end the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Close up shop tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username is Orange Lounge Radio I was hoping Loki would call us but I guess his Wi-Fi at the hospital is not so great he's not getting the private messages but that's okay he's got better things to do than talk to us honestly I know we're his friends and everything but he's got more important stuff tonight it's all good it's all good
[SPEAKER_01]: We should try to take the mics on the road and go see the baby.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be absolutely cute.
[SPEAKER_01]: At the same time, everybody probably wants to be left the fuck alone right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep in mind, for like the next month, all this baby is going to be able to see is Blur, Blur, Blur.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, Red!
[SPEAKER_01]: But you like Blur.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're a great band.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dork.
[SPEAKER_01]: We got a phone call.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, it's Ranma, back from Otakon 2010.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, Ranma, what's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: Sup?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm a little tired, but it's a con.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you expect?
[SPEAKER_02]: You didn't get con funk, did you?
[SPEAKER_11]: Cons are always exhausting.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, just so you know, the term con funk is officially dead.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's been replaced with hobo.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't heard that before.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hobo.
[SPEAKER_11]: Horrific otaku body odor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: A similar thing happens at game conventions, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Confunk, but keep in mind, Confunk also, though, encompasses con disease.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which was coined here in California, which was coined for quite a while here in California as the Dorbola.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because remember, we can track it back to Doreen.
[SPEAKER_01]: I remember that, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: He got married.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: How was the con, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_11]: It was good, despite some of the couple of things that happened this weekend.
[SPEAKER_11]: I had fun, my staff had fun, and I saw an ITG3 machine there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, they made an In The Groove 3?
[SPEAKER_11]: There was an In The Groove 3 machine.
[SPEAKER_11]: It wasn't on, so I don't know what was on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: My game report, I'll have to ask her what was on the machine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Didn't they get sued to all hell and they can't make any more?
[SPEAKER_01]: Was there a third mix officially?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it was in process before it got shut down.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, you know, maybe someone snuck it out and threw it onto a machine or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: I do have a picture of the unit.
[SPEAKER_11]: A purposefully leaked prototype.
[SPEAKER_01]: You said unit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hitstun in chat says ITG3 is a mod of ITG2.
[SPEAKER_01]: That wouldn't surprise me either, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_11]: And oddly enough, there was no DDR machines there.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was just that one ITG machine and two Pump It Up Pro 2 machines.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, very.
[SPEAKER_01]: What else in the gaming world?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I didn't cover too much of the gaming because I was more covering everything else.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I can tell you about gaming cosplays.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can tell you this much.
[SPEAKER_11]: Every year when a Final Fantasy game comes out, everybody and their mother does cosplays.
[SPEAKER_11]: And for the longest time, the big cosplay was always Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can tell you this right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: There was about 12 to 13 Final Fantasy cosplayers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Six to seven of them were from XIII.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, 13's very cosplayable.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_11]: It is, but I don't think it really went over well with a lot of the fans.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because from what I've talked to a lot of people, at first they love 13.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're like, what the shit is this?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I still like 13.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know what y'all's problem is, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: I enjoy 13 too, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: The battle system just kind of threw me.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's probably what it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: gotcha someone was supposed to lend me their copy I keep forgetting I'm sorry you have to like text me right before a show one night when I'm not in the bay so let's see what else do I want to ask you about the con well quickly any really cool like events even anime style or whatever what were some memorable moments of the con
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, my best memorable moment was the concert I went to this afternoon.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was a Japanese hip-hop group called Homei Kazoku.
[SPEAKER_11]: The best way I can describe them is, if you remember hip-hop rap music from the 80s when it was good, that take it to the next level.
[SPEAKER_11]: I see.
[SPEAKER_11]: As good as Dragon Ash?
[SPEAKER_11]: Honestly, I think they're better than Dragon Ash.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_11]: And generally, when a lot of Japanese artists come over, they always have a little bit of trouble speaking English to the fans.
[SPEAKER_11]: They were speaking 100% English.
[SPEAKER_11]: No stuttering, no rough edges.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was just straight, clear, right across the board.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I've been to a lot of J-rock, J-pop concerts at Otakon and other conventions.
[SPEAKER_11]: At this concert, everybody was on their feet going nuts.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have never seen a crowd this wild.
[SPEAKER_01]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, Ranma, we gotta wrap up so we can get more calls.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you have anything else you want to say about the con?
[SPEAKER_11]: There was a fire at the convention center.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did somebody say fire?
[SPEAKER_01]: So what'd you say on fire, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: You're a dick.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I still love you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, like, not everybody gets that joke, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, well, tell us about the fire real quick.
[SPEAKER_11]: What a con-ruiner.
[SPEAKER_11]: and at least it wasn't snowing outside.
[SPEAKER_11]: And talking to some people, I kind of figured out who started the grease fire and I think only me and Jamie will catch this joke as I post a link to the comment in the chat.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did, I did, I did.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like what Amaze Satsuma says in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_01]: Con's on fire.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nice, I like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can be the theme song for when your con gets set on fire.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to hang up on you now so we can take more calls.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dude, fuck GameStop.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to take another call real quick.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then I want to know more about why you're angry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: This is Kane IM.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry, what was that?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Kane IM.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kane IM.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's up, Kane IM?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I did find a way to run the live show off my phone.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I do appreciate your guys' help.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, he's the same guy who emailed in about getting the... Okay, so what did you end up using?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a shoutcast program.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did a little bit of searching online.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I'm glad you were able to find something.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't call in because I wanted to know...
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you guys have any suggestions on how to get an IRC program for my phone?
[SPEAKER_10]: so that I can join in on the chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that there is one for iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know about the Droid.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hate to say iPhone again, but again, that All Games app, whenever it comes back, because I imagine its disappearance is only temporary, you can get on IRC.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Droid has a browser, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you have a PSP?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, if you have a PSP, go to olrpsp.com and you can do the chat and the stream all from the PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately, I'm a truck driver and Wi-Fi is kind of scarce.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm opening up to our own chatters right now to see if they have any suggestions at chat.orangeloungeradio.com I guess just try to search for something IRC.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because with any IRC client, you should be able to connect to the Game Surge Network, which is the network we're on.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then it's just channel Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_01]: Any IRC client can get to our room.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here in studio, we use MIRC.
[SPEAKER_01]: As Toa Gak in our chat says, IRC is IRC is IRC, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, that's correct.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unfortunately, I don't know what IRC clients exist on that platform, but you have to run a search and maybe Google can tell you.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, thanks.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, well, good luck to you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, any games that you've been playing while you've been out on the road?
[SPEAKER_10]: I just got Naughty Bear and my one sinful pleasure is Harvest Moon.
[SPEAKER_02]: How do you like Naughty Bear?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I really want to play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Picture Manhunt with teddy bears.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's about all it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's good for a giggle.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: It sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I remember when we were looking at the previews here in studio, we were so excited and everything else.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I've heard the game is real shit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, it's getting terrible reviews.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm kind of, you know...
[SPEAKER_01]: Not that reviewers necessarily know everything, but it did kind of give me pause.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was like, wow, this game is doing really bad in the reviews.
[SPEAKER_01]: Can you see that, why that's happening, or do you think it's totally unfounded?
[SPEAKER_10]: The controls are a bit clunky.
[SPEAKER_10]: The camera doesn't seem to want to cooperate with you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I'll wait if you really want to play it until either someone else buys it, or we play it bargain-based.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can... Maybe I'll do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bargain Basement then.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's too bad they can't get some of those basic things right.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like they don't even play the game or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then, in about, you know, a couple of months, I might just pick it up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, I thought you were an Xbox owner.
[SPEAKER_04]: That doesn't mean I can't go over to somebody's house and play.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's usually where I get all my gaming experiences.
[SPEAKER_04]: I usually have some... I know a guy who knows a guy who knows a guy who owns a 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, well, KaneIM, we're going to let you get back to your thing, but thanks so much for the call, and good luck with the mobile phone quest.
[SPEAKER_01]: We appreciate you trying so hard.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, no problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys try and keep, you know, do what you're doing and take it easy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keep on trucking.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
Bye.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've always wanted to say that to a truck driver.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, anyhow, let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm looking at chat and some folks clarifying some things about the OLR PSP and HitStun is saying, OLR PSP's chat is a shout box, not an IRC chat.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that is correct.
[SPEAKER_01]: There is no IRC clients that work on PSP right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki tried to get that to happen and he couldn't because you're absolutely right.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's nothing that works right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: We can do at least one more call.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, you're on Orange Silence Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, hello there, you all are.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is that one, Aki Ripper, from Sweden.
[SPEAKER_01]: Aki Ripper.
[SPEAKER_01]: From Sweden.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the other Swede.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's another Battle of the Swedes night.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_01]: We had our emailer, and now we have Aki Ripper.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, there's always room for at least two Swedish people.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: If a third Swedish person wanted to listen, I would welcome them, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: And if there were four, we could make our own version of ABBA.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, Aki Ripper, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_01]: What the funk?
[SPEAKER_01]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_09]: I rambled on on the network one time and well, Stormcatcher 2 could be wonderful if I could play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did they lock Sweden out?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: The thing is that I can't play it due to the thing that Battle.net
[SPEAKER_09]: refused to accept that I have tapped in my key in Battle.net and said it's listed, but when I launched the game and said like, no, you do not have a StarCraft key associated with your Battle.net account.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, it's all listed there, but the game refuses to say yes or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have an angry, angry Swede on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: You hear that anger in his voice.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm quite pissed in that regard.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, around 900 Swedish crowns, which is like... I'm going to be rough.
[SPEAKER_09]: How much, by the way, is the collector's edition?
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, it's the collector's edition.
$99.
[SPEAKER_01]: How much you pay it in...
[SPEAKER_09]: And they can do it all, but it's somewhere around, well, it's somewhere around 90 bucks or even less.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, here's a suggestion.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't even know if this works.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've probably already done this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have you logged on to the web portal, going on to battle.net on the web and making sure that the game is associated there?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, well, it's listed there.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, well, the thing is that, well, I've...
[SPEAKER_09]: And here's the other thing, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: The workaround that I'm trying to do is, well, change password.
[SPEAKER_09]: If word for the following fact that I have forgotten my, like, hidden question... Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's my problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, and I've... And, well, I've tried... Tried calling the...
[SPEAKER_09]: calling Blizzard about it, but here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Trying to call the Blizzard line around these parts apparently seems quite hard.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the irony is that I've managed to call the US one when I had problems with the... when I had problems at the time when I was playing World of Warcraft on US servers, then I got straight along.
[SPEAKER_09]: And now it's like...
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you're out of luck or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, well, anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Has your WoW account been inactive for some time?
[SPEAKER_09]: My WoW account, both of my WoW accounts have been inactive for like...
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you have an authenticator on that account?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I did not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because the authenticator, when I played the authenticator, wasn't released yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is possible, and I don't know, but it's possible that your account got hacked.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I have heard of people that even though they had inactive Warcraft accounts, that some people would go in there and reactivate them to get access to the characters.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's crazy, crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just hypothesizing that that could be what's screwing with you over there.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, definitely, you're going to have to keep on Blizzard and, I guess, email if nothing else.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will have to call them or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, well, but one of the problems that I have also is that, well, if I'm right, to be able to identify, well, I'm going to have to go find... The problem is also is that I need to find a scanner
[SPEAKER_09]: or the scanner because I need to scan in my passport or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: to send, well, to basically, like, made in a file and send it to them and say that, yes, this is me, of sorts.
[SPEAKER_01]: What a pain.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or are you just going to have to give him the angry Swede?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds like this angry Swede's quite justified in his anger.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I wish you the best.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wish there was a magic wand.
[SPEAKER_09]: In that regard, I am quite pissed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, and also, because, well, and also, because, well...
[SPEAKER_09]: StarCraft 2, and here's the other thing though, in a kind of way, I already know what happens in, because also the thing is, playing StarCraft, I wasn't that hyped for StarCraft 2 in a kind of way anyway, since, uh,
[SPEAKER_09]: The thing that I did is that since I got the Collector's Edition, you have this special DVD of sorts when you get all the video frequencies from the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm all like, yeah, let's watch this.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah, you just got spoiled the whole game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, here's the other thing, though, and even more fun, is that, well, if I...
[SPEAKER_09]: and especially actually in a kind of way since I'm like one of those players that played through the first StarCraft game were playing like code power overwhelming yes please which was that well god mode activated well Aki Ripper I wish I could fix it for you but it sounds like you're just gonna have to keep on Blizzard customer support but do let us know what happens okay buddy
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'll keep you updated.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, I hope you can get to the Zerging soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, hang in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, poor guy.
[SPEAKER_01]: But hey, tough lesson for everybody.
[SPEAKER_01]: Learn at Ake Ripper's expense.
[SPEAKER_01]: Learn at the expense of the Swedes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't forget your security question, because that sucks when that happens.
[SPEAKER_01]: You gotta be very careful with that stuff, so make sure you will be able to remember it later on, or else you're gonna have
[SPEAKER_01]: All those problems that Aki Ripper was talking about there Alright, well that is going to do it for Orange Laundry's phone calls tonight We're going to close up the Skype line I don't know, usually Loki is the collector of last minute stories I don't know if DarkSakura pulled anything I did You did?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well DarkSakura, what do you have for last minute stories tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically Canadians are luring game developers out of Alabama I didn't realize there was this whole avalanche of game developers in Alabama in the first place
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the province of Newfoundland and Labrador paid $300,000 to a Huntsville, Alabama video game development company so it could set up a studio in Canada.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Bittrap Studios Canada is doing multiplayer online games and wants some help.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're hoping that it will infuse $1.6 million into the local economy I see, I knew those Canadians were up to no good It's an economic war that they're declaring, I see Time to start pouring your maple syrup down the sewers Dude, I'm from Alabama, so it was cool
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just, obviously, I'm teasing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: We like our neighbors to the north, really.
[SPEAKER_06]: Usually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most days.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_01]: Was that it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, that was not it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Or no, there's nothing else?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, there's nothing else.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm being a jerk.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's going to do it for Orange Laundry Radio tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's about time for us to go around and wrap everything up and put the nail in the coffin of the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_01]: But first, I have to thank our guests for being here tonight because they did great work, really did good work tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: I really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, Gary, thank you so much for being here tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a pleasure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Glad to be here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hope the show has inspired you to get up in console and PC gaming.
[SPEAKER_01]: I saw you were doing the Dungeons & Dragons download.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but I'm also thinking about what console I should buy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, tough decision.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tough decision.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let me talk to you after the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: And do come back and let us know what you end up getting and what PC games you do end up getting into.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I'd love to come back.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Please do.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, Myla, thank you so much for being on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a shout out to my lovelies in the chat rooms who actually know who I am.
[SPEAKER_01]: We love the chatters.
[SPEAKER_01]: Appreciate them.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go RuneScape.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Myla, keep enjoying your 12-year-old game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Definitely appreciate the budget gaming reports.
[SPEAKER_01]: So between you and Drew Nami, I think we'll be pretty covered.
[SPEAKER_01]: So come on back sometime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: With this economy, you need it.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, I'm going to ask for your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: What is your final thought?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura deserves our full sympathy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been a rough week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want a cookie.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need a hug.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a cookie.
[SPEAKER_01]: And a pony.
[SPEAKER_01]: And a dinner.
[SPEAKER_01]: I need to give our guests their final thought too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gary, do you have a final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been too long since I've done any console game or any computer game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to get back into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like things have taken quantum leaps from the last time I did this seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw the screenshots of Arkham Asylum and was blown away.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm glad we could inspire you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_01]: Milo, you have a final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: DC Online Wow I'm totally going to be there too Can't wait And my final thought is I think Pinkberry would make it all better I've never been there It's really good But sadly it's Sunday and they're not going to be open But anyway, tomorrow
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, that's it guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have a wonderful week.
[SPEAKER_01]: We will be back here next week to do it all over again.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unfortunately, Loki's going to be out for a little while longer, but hey, DarkSakura and I are perfectly capable of holding down the fort, so tune in next week to see what the antics bring, and I've got duct tape.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to have a co-host next week to fill in for Loki, so more on that next week.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see you next week here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I almost forgot.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you did enjoy our show, please tell two people about the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Help us spread the word because we're not a multi-million dollar organization.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're excited when we have $10 in the budget to spend on a Facebook ad.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we really, really can use your guys' help in helping us spread the word of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, so we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have a great night.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next week!
DarkSakura