[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't intend for that to happen, I swear.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a couple of shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was too good.
[SPEAKER_07]: We got to save part B. In order to do that, I have to stop the recording for a minute and play some music.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we'll be right back in two minutes with the afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yes, right, Dan, there's even more show to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be right back, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the sticky part.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_07]: My thoughts exactly We'll be right back
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, we're back with the Orange Launch Radio Afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the part of the show that's too hot to podcast, and I really apologize that we don't have a webcam anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Way too hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys missed it during the break there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan was doing the lasso.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mystique was trying to white people dance.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was white people dancing.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it was pretty scary.
[SPEAKER_03]: You were trying to... I did the sprinkler.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: You were trying to glow stick rave without glow sticks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And with the lights on.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a very rave-y song.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: And meanwhile, I'm over here sitting... I don't know these people.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know these people.
[SPEAKER_03]: All these people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Somebody's confused!
[SPEAKER_07]: You were kind of wagging your finger a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: She was over there trying to get more viruses off her computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dan!
[SPEAKER_03]: Where's my treble?! !
[SPEAKER_06]: In the closet with Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob is not in the closet.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I ain't in the closet.
[SPEAKER_07]: True that.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Usually we would do the cage match right about now.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we don't have a cage match right now because Loki ain't here.
[SPEAKER_06]: They wouldn't let me pick a song.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, we will.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they banned my idea of a song.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would have been afraid of what Dan would pick for a song.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we will do some FUs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did we get sufficient chat remains?
[SPEAKER_03]: Six.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought you said four.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I've been nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like even numbers, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're never nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Play the music!
[SPEAKER_04]: She's trying to confuse people.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first one is... Mike's out.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to the mic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Heihachi Suendoshi, who's also Alpha Kananagram, F you to Hatsune Miku Project Diva 2nd for not including the song Far Away by KZ, my favorite song from Diva 1, yet including the level, stage, elements, and edit mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it's a special unlock.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan, have you ever played Project Diva?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have no idea what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a Hatsune Miku.
[SPEAKER_04]: It can't be the game I'd play if I still had PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: That makes me want to kill you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranma, F you to my friend's husband.
[SPEAKER_03]: Be thankful I didn't slap you out at Otakon last weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: You ungrateful piece of trash.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, fuck that guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should get on the knees and worship that woman because she does a lot more than you think.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also stop blowing your paycheck on frivolous shit and take care of your kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Blaze Kid, F you to Westroads Mall Arcade for fixing everything else but in the groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: Twigak.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't fix a broken game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm terrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to my computer for being the slowest piece of crap ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will smash you to the ground if you don't shape up Twigak's computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for scaring my computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, fuck that computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jodea.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to you for demanding F you to you, you demanding wench, you heart.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, fuck that wench.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Patty, that was amazingly hot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't stop thinking about you now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have no idea what happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: Last one, Emei Satsuma, F you for getting jury duty.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least I was able to request a postponement because of school is coming up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan just got a look on his face like, oh, I think I got jury duty this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jury duty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck it right in the ear.
[SPEAKER_05]: You do have jury duty?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck it with something hard and sandpaper.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: You might want to find out.
[SPEAKER_07]: You kind of like have to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or you call them and tell them you have severe diarrhea and you can't do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to call in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell them that you've died of dysentery.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell them you were in the fucking hospital last week and they'll probably do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it wasn't last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like starting tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you better call in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks to my wife for telling me what I already knew.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck her!
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that was kind of the point.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what got you in trouble.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like mustard on my french fries.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell is happening to this program?
[SPEAKER_03]: It imploded.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what the show needs more of?
[SPEAKER_06]: Structure.
[SPEAKER_06]: I swear to God, if she put on that Vuvuzela thing, I was going to throw her phone in the toilet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did I forget my ferret?
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you talking about, the Vuvuzela?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have fucking no idea what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll unplug your mic.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's doing it here.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are you grabbing me for?
[SPEAKER_03]: For your information, Dan, for your information, Dan, four square, bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I forgot to check in because I want to become the mayor of the house.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're never going to be the mayor of the house, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: I check in every day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I'm the mayor of Walgreens.
[SPEAKER_03]: We went right by the Walgreens near my house, and I said, I should check in here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob is the mayor.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob lives nowhere near the damn Walgreens by my house.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Rob is the mayor of Walgreens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't feel bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: How does this happen?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm the mayor of the Walgreens across from my work.
[SPEAKER_04]: And naturally my work.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm the mayor of a Chinese restaurant over by my house.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aren't you the mayor of Cowschwitz?
[SPEAKER_07]: I got dethroned as the mayor of Cowschwitz, which pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Melody was the mayor of Cowschwitz, and I was the mayor of Near the Stinky Cows on I-5.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else am I the mayor of?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm the mayor of one other place.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I can't remember what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Walgreens.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's not Walgreens.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm the mayor of Walgreens, the Chinese restaurant and one other place.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another Walgreens.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, you should create a place that calls the chair in Jamie's house.
[SPEAKER_07]: The chair at Jamie's house.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will let you be the mayor of the chair.
[SPEAKER_06]: Practically in the closet.
[SPEAKER_07]: In the closet at Jamie's house.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: The fabulous OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ranma in our chatroom says, Rob is the fabulous mayor of Walgreens.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fabulous.
[SPEAKER_07]: Am I really that gay, you guys?
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: You are wearing a shirt with a hot dog on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not just a shirt with a hot dog on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has a rainbow, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: It does.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should take a picture of my shirt, but I just don't want my fat old gut to be out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just needs glitter to make it complete.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to see where I'm the mayor.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm the mayor of three places.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jack in the Box!
[SPEAKER_06]: You're the mayor of Jack in the Box.
[SPEAKER_06]: A week ago, Jack in the Box sent out the most amazing coupon sheet.
[SPEAKER_06]: It had all sorts of cool freebies on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob totally made the Pee Wee Herman face.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I'm checking in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Places.
[SPEAKER_07]: I gotta be careful how I do this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to tell the listeners where you live.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is so too hot for the podcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is amazing radio right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: As Rob plays with his iPhone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Live!
[SPEAKER_07]: On the air.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie is the mayor.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Check in here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck yes, I'm the mayor.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're the mayor of where?
[SPEAKER_03]: This house.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just pathetic.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least on Foursquare.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just had to check to make sure my zipper was up when she took... All Games Radio is switching between its live and on-demand feed.
[SPEAKER_01]: This may take several moments.
[SPEAKER_01]: Visit all...
[SPEAKER_08]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_06]: Be back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mad Libs Mad Libs
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty good timing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: The claw.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is our master.
[SPEAKER_03]: It decides who will go and who will stay.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can ask us anything you want.
[SPEAKER_07]: Within reason.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: Type.
[SPEAKER_07]: Message.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can ask anything unreasonable, but we may not answer it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ask what color Misty's undies are.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to tell her.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to have to speak.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because she'll tell you.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's checking.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just looked over.
[SPEAKER_05]: Panties were hanging out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was all for you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie's taking pictures.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't even turn around.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob, Rob, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan gets on the show, all hell breaks loose.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm making shit happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got girls taking their pants off.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's crazy around here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's misty.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's misty and misty being on the same time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do not put that on the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would not put that on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm putting it on our website.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't put it on the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look, stars!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, it's not like she's going beaver.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I want to watch Roger Rabbit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can we do... Are you ready?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ask OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look, every little red screen right there is a question.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we got a lot of questions.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm seriously crying.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranma says, I demand a fucking web camera.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, can we go?
[SPEAKER_07]: Can we go?
[SPEAKER_07]: Tough shit, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sing a song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you help me out, Dan?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_07]: What will we find out tonight on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_07]: Will we find out the color of Mystique's panties?
[SPEAKER_07]: I deeply wish I had a lyric because I want to sing that song.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's like if we're trying to sing about some chick's panties.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is very fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a good time singing the song with you.
[SPEAKER_07]: The greatest thing is this part isn't recorded.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I do have a recording running.
[SPEAKER_07]: I usually just throw this out, but tonight I might save it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should save it for the DVD that we're never going to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: The DVD we're never going to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: We will do the DVD.
[SPEAKER_07]: Free with every t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_04]: If we ever get the damn shirts out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gold Anthro asks, what color are Misty's underwear?
[SPEAKER_06]: They are blue with stars on them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stars and moons.
[SPEAKER_02]: And moons.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no pink diamonds or horseshoes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or Pikachus.
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Blaziken asks, what was your first Bomani experience?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to defer this question to Dan.
[SPEAKER_07]: What was your first Bomani experience?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it would have been what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Me bringing that Burn Over?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I mean, it was in the arcade for sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we had the... Down at Milpitas.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it was at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it was before that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We played DDR in 99 when they were first coming out in California.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember, though, pretty early on, I imported the Dreamcast version for Jamie.
[SPEAKER_06]: He got it for me for my birthday.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was probably the only version of DDR that I really bothered to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then Julie bought a second dance pad, which I promptly stole from her and never gave back.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, he's not kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's in the box.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, we still have it in the box.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you ask her about it, she'll probably say, oh, I should get that back from you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, my first momentary experience where I really enjoyed it was Guitar Freaks at Milpitas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which George got me to play because George was like, no, no, no, it's cool, you'll like this Because I was like, DJ, fuck that game, I'm gonna play Street Fighter And he was like, no, man, you gotta try Guitar Freaks, and I played Guitar Freaks And Guitar Freaks at first was the greatest Bimani game because you could suck at it, but it didn't hack you too hard
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate that fucking game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ranma asks, Sky, how fabulous are you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: I will defer to the others in studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: How fabulous am I?
[SPEAKER_03]: To quote Ulala, in a paraphrase, you are fabulous.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hot dog!
[SPEAKER_02]: Misty?
[SPEAKER_02]: Boom shakalaka.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not quite sure brilliant comes to mind, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jaguar!
[SPEAKER_04]: Jaguar!
[SPEAKER_07]: SSJ100 Matt asks, how did Dan propose to Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you propose?
[SPEAKER_07]: Even I know this story.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I know this story and you two don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: We just more like decided that we were going to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it had something to do with pro wrestling.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were watching UHF.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it UHF?
[SPEAKER_06]: On Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were watching something and there was a lot of sex involved.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Jamie got to drink from the fire hose.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just so you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but we were drinking, we were, no, this is how you knew that one day your wife would be Jewish.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we were drinking Manischewitz.
[SPEAKER_06]: I fucking didn't know you were going to be Jewish.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still barely, I still barely, I still don't even want to realize that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mazel Tov!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to get seven days of presents.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love pencils and erasers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan is a real humanitarian.
[SPEAKER_07]: He tries to see the good in everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: My wife's going to be Jewish.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eight days of presents!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay, two Christmases!
[SPEAKER_03]: I just now see the irony in the proposed, the sort of co-decision.
[SPEAKER_07]: When are you all coming to New York City?
[SPEAKER_00]: New York City?
[SPEAKER_07]: Get a rope When I ain't a broke ass When Sister Act is on Broadway Yeah, I need to accumulate some money before I can come crash When someone invites me for free I've never been to New York
[SPEAKER_03]: I have.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do love New York.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is how long ago I went to New York.
[SPEAKER_03]: There were still these really two large buildings and one of them had a hole in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are so many ways to die in New York City.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you, Dennis Leary.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Rob, does that date when I went?
[SPEAKER_06]: Start spreading the news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I've already been to Chicago sometimes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love New York.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chicago.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have the best nights out in New York City.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because they never end.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to go to New York with Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: We will have the best time.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to go to Broadway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Broadway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next question.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to go see Mamma Mia on Broadway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we can make Go LRG finally happen and it can happen in New York.
[SPEAKER_07]: Giovedea is asking quite a few questions here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of them have already been asked.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll start here.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you had Lady Tatas, what would their names be?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, Dan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe that could be Lady Gaga's sidekick, Lady Tata.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dr. Evil and Professor Chaos.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think mine would have, well, on that note, then I would have to name one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alejandro.
[SPEAKER_07]: and the other one, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enrique.
[SPEAKER_07]: Telephone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rikki Martin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Rikki Martin and Alejandro.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Giovedeo wants to know, Rob, will you be my gay boyfriend?
[SPEAKER_03]: Have we ever played that song on the show before?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you have a lot of money?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, when it comes to being the hag...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkTetsuya says, since there probably won't be a show, can we finally run the best of next week?
[SPEAKER_03]: If I'm not too lazy to upload it to the all game server, sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just get on me about that mid-week and I'll make sure it happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: ToyGak asks, oh, a game question.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is that, a video game question?
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought he was going to ask me what color undies I was wearing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: ToyGak asks, Would you rather have a game with an amazing storyline but last-gen graphics or amazing graphics and a poor storyline?
[SPEAKER_03]: I would go with amazing storyline.
[SPEAKER_06]: Graphics cease to mean anything after your first few hours of playing the game, so the storyline is pretty much vital.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you comparing panties?
[SPEAKER_06]: What is going on over there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Take off your shirts!
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh god, she did it!
[SPEAKER_05]: Shit's getting crazy up in here!
[SPEAKER_05]: Where's the malt liquor?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not my panties I was talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, very nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I want amazing graphics and poor storyline because you know the spanking game has no storyline whatsoever and that sounds better than anything else.
[SPEAKER_07]: Spanking and massage.
[SPEAKER_07]: Simspank.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the next question?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm getting to it, I'm getting to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Toagak also asks, why are there so many nicknames for boobs?
[SPEAKER_07]: Boobs, knockers, tits, fun bags, etc.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jumblies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because breasts sound so formal.
[SPEAKER_04]: People do stupid shit like name their cars, so why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a song that talks about the many names of a penis.
[SPEAKER_03]: Monty Python did it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tallywhacker.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't it awfully nice to have a penis?
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't it awfully good to have a dung?
[SPEAKER_02]: Your piece of pork, your wife's best friend, your pussy or your cock.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can wrap it up in ribbons.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can stick it in your sock.
[SPEAKER_07]: Amaze Satsuma says, can you give me a job slash occupation for Mad Libs?
[SPEAKER_07]: Jizzmopper.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I prefer Cumbucket.
[SPEAKER_07]: Erotic Engineer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Cumbucket.
[SPEAKER_07]: Frisbee.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dear Strong Bad, how do you type with boxing gloves on your hands?
[SPEAKER_07]: Wrong show.
[SPEAKER_07]: That question was totally crappy.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was all the questions.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a question, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: What the fuck are we on?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that's going to do it for Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: All Games Radio!
[SPEAKER_04]: Who said we need to be on anything?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not even unbiking it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all the time we have for Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: We hope you learned something tonight on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: SD has blue panties.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blue underwear.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all I learned and now I'm scarred for the rest of the night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jizzmonger.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, Ranma's asking a serious question.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, this is a serious question.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Downer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, Ranma's saying... Thanks, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think I've ever told this on a show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are we really going to do this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ranma says, when did you come out of the closet and how did your family take it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan, do you want to answer this?
[SPEAKER_06]: They knew when I was young.
[SPEAKER_03]: In Dan's case, when they finally removed the deadbolt and he came out blinking into the sunlight for the first time in 13 years.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were all surprisingly accepting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: My mom asked me for like three months straight every day, are you gay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you gay?
[SPEAKER_07]: And it kind of got annoying.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, because
[SPEAKER_07]: This is what it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't like the fact, you know, because I had a tough time in high school because I got called fag and all that stuff a lot in high school and I didn't really like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I didn't really know I was gay then because I was just trying to be normal, you know, have a girlfriend and, you know, this is how we roll.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I'm a hot stud playing the clarinet in the marching band, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, and trying to do that whole thing, I didn't really want to admit I was gay because I didn't want all those people to be right.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then when I kind of realized I was gay, like I, that was one of the first things I had to conquer.
[SPEAKER_07]: So when my mom joined in on it, I really didn't appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Finally, one day it actually kind of exploded in a, yes, are you happy?
[SPEAKER_07]: Now leave me alone.
[SPEAKER_07]: And she ran off to her room to cry for the rest of the day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bitches.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: But...
[SPEAKER_07]: Then the next day she came out with her eyes all puffy and she's like, I just want you to know I still love you and I've known since you were four.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm like, how do you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't know until I was like 17.
[SPEAKER_07]: How do you know when you're four?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because mothers always know.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had a kid in my family, my eldest cousin, who was gay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I miss him.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never...
[SPEAKER_06]: I never put too and too into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just he was who he was.
[SPEAKER_06]: But my folks and people in my family were always like, we knew from the time he was a young, young boy that he was gay.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a part of me that doesn't like that, though, because it insinuates that being gay you act a certain way, and I don't think that's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: As I sit here with my legs crossed.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so fucking true, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tapping on the table.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not like you can't act gay if you're straight.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't act straight if you're gay, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: But what is straight acting and gay acting?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's not, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: You fucking know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do, but.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I understand, I'm not trying to perpetuate the stereotype.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But like, I looked at Rob when I first met you and I was like, wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: and you're not wearing like feather boas and shit although he has I didn't come in and go hi Dan I was just like oh you know not in a bad way Dan's gaydar has improved I wasn't threatening I probably had my arm around Jamie and we were skipping and Dan was like somehow this is not threatening to me I'm not a threatened kind of guy that's true that's true
[SPEAKER_03]: Dan knows that I have complete and utter devotion to the gays.
[SPEAKER_03]: To the gays, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: The truth is, you know, I realize that any who oppose me can be summarily dealt with.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, dealt with.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you know what I finally told my mom about that I had a girlfriend before?
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what she said?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't need to hear that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me either.
[SPEAKER_07]: You do?
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well, here's the other thing that's important, because my mom said, and this is a very important part of the story, is my mom said, I called your grandma, and I told her, I'm like, why are you telling everybody?
[SPEAKER_07]: She's like, no, I want you to know what your grandma said, because it meant a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: She said, I told your grandma that you were gay, and I'm like, what'd she say?
[SPEAKER_07]: And my grandma said, so what?
[SPEAKER_07]: So rest in peace, Grandma Shaw.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, Dan, I do miss your cousin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, me too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I got along really well with your cousin.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was a cool cat.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, we'll talk about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lastly, God, it's like the all-gay OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Blaziken asks, what do you think about Prop 8 being put in the fire?
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously, obviously it needed to happen, and it's a good thing, but
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: But honestly, this issue just isn't over until the Supreme Court decides on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I am a little nervous about the Supreme Court deciding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whose rights are we going to take away next?
[SPEAKER_07]: I just hope that history and things that happened in, you know, Loving v. Virginia and some of these other things that happened in the past will kind of set the precedence for overturning Prop 8 at the Supreme Court level.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I worry.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's unfortunately that many ignoramus people in the world who, for whatever reason, want to have their say in my life.
[SPEAKER_03]: The moment they bring the 14th Amendment into it, you know it becomes an even bigger issue.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I kind of think that some of those pro-Prop 8 people might actually have more to fear if it goes to the Supreme Court.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because then if they uphold the ruling that yes, this is unconstitutional, that's national precedent.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're a bunch of scared-ass, insecure fuckers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, it's just like, what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I assure you, I don't want to have my wedding in a church and I'm not going to sue any church that doesn't want to have my wedding because I'm not...
[SPEAKER_07]: I just, people can do whatever they want to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, here's what I have to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can do whatever you want to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me do what I want to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, here's what I have to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it okay if, you know, the fundamental Christians want to use Leviticus as their standing point for saying, you know, which is actually in Jewish law, man shall not lay with another man like a woman.
[SPEAKER_03]: That just means that I guess you can't have boobs or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, if the Christians want to use Leviticus, they also have to keep kosher and grow out their beards and wear tall black hats like the Hasidic do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I put the fun in fundamentalist well it's not even quote the bible all you want or any religious text but there's like an amendment in the constitution that says freedom of religion meaning I am free of your religion well see and that's my other point I mean my point is that if they're trying to use if they're trying to use a law when they admittedly don't follow the laws themselves then that's just being hypocritical
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the end of the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am encouraged by the fact that folks our age, and I see a lot of people in chat going, I have a gay friend, who cares?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that seems to be the attitude of most 18 to 35 year olds in this day and age.
[SPEAKER_07]: They just need to vote.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the good news is, when we're the old farts on the Supreme Court making the decisions, this will be over.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're just going to have to wait for the ignorant people to pass on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I mean, if you take a look at the Civil Rights Movement, the 14th Amendment passed 100 years before Brown versus the Board of Education and the Montgomery Boycott, the Montgomery Best Boycott with Rosa Parks.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so how many of us our age look back on that and go,
[SPEAKER_07]: So even if I'm not around to see it
[SPEAKER_07]: I know someday it will change.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just saying, if anyone is still listening, make sure that when the opportunity comes up for you to vote on important issues like this, that you do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I was watching the voter turnout during the whole Prop 8 thing, and I was completely dismayed.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were really relying on the Berkeley area, and the voter turnout was only something like 52%.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it could have completely turned the whole thing because the vote was 52 to 49.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just if the rest of the voting population had put in the effort, it wouldn't have even been an issue.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: This was a very interesting election year, though, because either way the tide had gone, you were going to have a minority in the White House.
[SPEAKER_07]: Either you had a racial minority or you had a sexual minority.
[SPEAKER_07]: You would have had one crazy-ass fucking woman in the White House, but you would have had a woman in the White House, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think my problem with Hillary is that she...
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm not even talking to her.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm talking to Sarah Palin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hillary hasn't been to primaries.
[SPEAKER_07]: But whatever happened, you would have had a minority in the White House when we were there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I felt... Two minorities right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Two minorities in one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mystique's going to run and that's going to be the bill.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is what we need.
[SPEAKER_03]: What we need, Rob, is a Jewish black woman.
[SPEAKER_07]: What we need is just
[SPEAKER_07]: Someone who's not a dick.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's just all I want.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to get too political.
[SPEAKER_07]: That means I'll never be president.
[SPEAKER_03]: President Dan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I put the dick in dictator.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need Renna.
[SPEAKER_07]: We need Renna.
[SPEAKER_07]: President Cat.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what we need.
[SPEAKER_07]: President Cat.
[SPEAKER_07]: You will meow this mess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Should we declare nuclear war?
[SPEAKER_03]: Would you like to play a game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go to the fortune cookie masters of the day.
[SPEAKER_07]: This show's getting too deep.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, this is supposed to be a ha-ha funny show.
[SPEAKER_06]: We sung the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: The segment's over.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quit asking questions.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: Erotic chat in Goldshire.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keep in mind, this is what happens when geeks grow up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Geeks!
[SPEAKER_07]: Guess what, all you kids?
[SPEAKER_07]: Read Geek Life!
[SPEAKER_06]: Geek-life.com That guy from Sweden.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here it is, your fortune... I think he is our age.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's your fortune cookie message of the day, kids.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's a fucking leprechaun.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's rockstar shit.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Leprechaun is amazing.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll eat your dog and shine your shoes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fuck you, I'm a Leprechaun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Magically delicious, yellow moons, pink hearts, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll eat your dog and shine your shoes.
[SPEAKER_00]: They'll eat your fucking dog.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're not fucking around.
[SPEAKER_00]: And they'll shine your shoes.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's a complete 180.
[SPEAKER_00]: I saw the movie Leprechaun years back.
[SPEAKER_00]: Awesome piece of film.
[SPEAKER_00]: They eat your dog, but they'll shine your shoes.
[SPEAKER_00]: One minute, the next minute.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_00]: My dog's important to me because my dog licks, but a fucking leprechaun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Whoever came up with that, by the way, fucking genius.
[SPEAKER_00]: They are drunk.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're mean.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're green.
[SPEAKER_00]: They got rotted teeth.
[SPEAKER_00]: All they care about is money.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're my agent.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll eat your dog and shine your shoes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Irish spring.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're wonderful little fucking creatures.
[SPEAKER_00]: And if you go outside when you leave here tonight, you fucking see a leprechaun.
[SPEAKER_00]: You shoot that motherfucking thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: You kill that dead.
[SPEAKER_00]: You put that down.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was Bob Saget, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's crazy, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Night, Michelle.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you guys so much for staying up late with us.
[SPEAKER_07]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know I had fun tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope you guys did too.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see you back here in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the end of our broadcast day here at All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: But stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's lots of other great shows coming your way.
[SPEAKER_07]: including Dead Pixel.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's that show?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dead Pixel Live.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, we like them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Derek's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: He put on the big battle.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's a good guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Works hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's going to be on at 4 o'clock Pacific, 7 o'clock Eastern tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Spooky Hour, Horror Hour, lots of other good stuff coming up through All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We hope you enjoy tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Support the station.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a great two weeks, everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good night.