[SPEAKER_12]: Sky, and Loku.
[SPEAKER_12]: Tonight, March 24th, 2013, new games are shown at PAX East.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wii U shop age restrictions are lifted in Europe.
[SPEAKER_12]: And could an exploit in Origin allow malicious code on your PC?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm eating something evil thanks to Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I totally stole her joke.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it was funny.
[SPEAKER_17]: You bitch.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here, here's a quarter for that joke.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's a cup of coffee for that joke.
[SPEAKER_17]: I love this coffee.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's very delicious.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also say hello to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: I ate so many breadsticks that my head hurts now.
[SPEAKER_08]: who's bringing the food, supplying OLR Studios with breadsticks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I ate most of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just I couldn't finish the last two.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, ten was enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys didn't know this, but every week at OLR is a potluck, you know, where everybody brings a dish.
[SPEAKER_08]: I bring the coffee, which is funny because Loki doesn't drink coffee.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki brings the pizza and breadsticks, and DarkSakura brings...
[SPEAKER_17]: Healthy stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gross.
[SPEAKER_08]: Salad and Chinese food.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who wants that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Chinese food isn't that healthy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I bring you coffee sometimes.
[SPEAKER_08]: It depends what you get at Chinese food, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Depends what you get.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went to Panda and I had the mandarin chicken with no sauce over vegetables and fried rice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Delicious.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we're not a food show, believe it or not, but we are a show about video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure PAX East, on a lot of your minds, we're going to be talking about some of the news that came out of PAX East.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sadly, I didn't get a chance to go this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I went to PAX East the very first year, which was I think 2010, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I went to PAX East that year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had a great time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sadly, it's a little tricky to get out to Boston from here.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a bit of a plane trip.
[SPEAKER_08]: And just with my day job and everything, there was no way I was going to get out there this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'll tell you what, y'all made me jealous through your Twitter updates and your forum posts and all that stuff I was watching.
[SPEAKER_08]: Y'all made me jealous I wasn't at PAX East.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember, Orange Lounge Radio does tape live every Sunday night at the Voice of Geeks Network or VOGnetwork.com every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Blackwell show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not tonight, though, because Bobby is one of those folks that was at PAX East, and he's on a plane home right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is now the Mass Effect show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think the entire group from Anime Jam Session was there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Ranma, Geovidea, R.A.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rockefeller, they were all there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Critical Myth, I know, was there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to think who else from VOG shows.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that was it from the show shows, because obviously the gals from Britain didn't come out for it, and British Invaders.
[SPEAKER_08]: One's in Canada, one's in Britain.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think they went out for it either.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, but certainly a lot of shows.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they'll be giving you some updates throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm hoping some of our regulars, because a lot of our regulars were there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know Misty was there, Matt was there, Ranma was there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm hoping to get some calls from people a little later on tonight to talk about PAX East and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um,
[SPEAKER_08]: For now though, we weren't there.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to get into the big news that came out of PAX East in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to ask because this is what I ask every time there's a PAX.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was the Megafon event this year?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I was watching... The final... I was watching Seg's Twitter and he posted it and I forgot already.
[SPEAKER_08]: It didn't sound like a new game or anything to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe somebody in chat can help us out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Live.VogNetwork.com is our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: And ActDeft in our chatroom live tonight confirming, yes, Critical Myth, AJS, and Bobby Black were all there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: We were kind of looking back because what was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody joined chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's this guy's name?
[SPEAKER_08]: Catastrophic Moggy joined chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I was getting that name confused in my head with a guy that used to be here locally that was Moogle Hunter.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it was his name or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we were talking about all these people from I'm talking like the
[SPEAKER_08]: Old School OLR Days
[SPEAKER_08]: So here's my little request for what it's worth.
[SPEAKER_08]: And another old school person is in the mailbag tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I know we're going to get to that later.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would really love to hear from some of these really old school people that used to be on the show a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: My house is open to you all that can make it on April 14th, which is the big show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bring me birthday presents.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just so y'all know, no show next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm registered.
[SPEAKER_08]: Easter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Episode 499 is April 7th.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, April 7th.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then episode 500 is April 14th.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I would really love for the old school people to show up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would love to see Anita, who I know is a DDR angel, if she can make it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just some of the old school people would crack me up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I chatted with her on Steam the other day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see her hubby on Google Plus all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: He put out an Android game.
[SPEAKER_02]: We sometimes exchange recipes and things too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I know she runs a blog now and all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Her blog is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called The Eco Maker.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyone who wants good home stuff, check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was Space Team.
[SPEAKER_08]: Space Team.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that an old school game?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's a new Android mobile game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a cooperative team game or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard a girl won, which is interesting because it was not Pork Buns who was on the show last week, two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: The gal we had on the show last week, sadly, she got eliminated the first round in Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the curse of coming on OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember trying to register that as an address Oh really?
[SPEAKER_02]: and why I had to get Sackbimani instead.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know who I know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because some Catholic organization registered it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know who I know would come?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who?
[SPEAKER_08]: And who I am friends with on Facebook and I literally haven't seen.
[SPEAKER_08]: We just keep in touch on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: Miss Janae.
[SPEAKER_08]: And she married Dark Child.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you know that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, and she has a little one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, they had a baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: This show is so fucking old.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have a baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's a lot better than a baby.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a cat too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love kitties.
[SPEAKER_02]: She doesn't drool on me.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, she does chew on cords.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki has a baby, but well, not even a baby anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like a toddler.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys went bowling the other day, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: You have a small person.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's like almost three.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_08]: The video was adorable though, the bowling.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you guys have fun?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a short video.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, the long video, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: He didn't let us bowl, because we have the little ramp thing, because he can't carry the ball.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, the lightest ball is like six pounds, and he might be able to carry that, but I'm not going to have him carry a big ball that's got the oil from the lane on it and stuff with his feet.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's not a good idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he had fun just pushing it down the little ramp so that it would knock stuff over, but he wouldn't let us have a turn.
[SPEAKER_05]: I managed to bowl twice and my wife once and he bowled like two whole games worth of turns for three people Catastrophic Moggy in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says What is this?
[SPEAKER_08]: A show about gaming or a trip down memory lane?
[SPEAKER_08]: Now I'm sure that comment is tongue in cheek and you don't really mean anything negative by it but you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: When you've been gaming with the same crowd for so long and you know
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys have to remember when we did the DDR stuff, we were really heavy into Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_08]: We would meet at the arcade every Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was like clockwork.
[SPEAKER_08]: Every Wednesday or whatever day it was at the time, we'd go, we'd play some DDR for a few hours.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then we'd go and have dinner, sit down.
[SPEAKER_08]: You kind of build up a little bit of a family.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: It is a little more than just video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's about family.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm on my second cat.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of sane people turn up here and chat every week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm on my second cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've been through a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Memory, all alone in your life
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course I played Mass Effect because I've got the high-res mod working on Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have Oliver.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Mass Effect 3, got the high-res mod working, and then it started crashing whenever I would do...
[SPEAKER_02]: The Tango, and I figured out that the problem was my Coalesce INI was what was doing it to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I had everything set by the old version of the Hi-Rez mod, and the new version doesn't require you to change any of your texture settings in the Coalesce file.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went and used my old Coalesce file, everything worked fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only problem that I have with it is that it makes all of James' textures black.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tango down, tango down.
[SPEAKER_02]: The cool thing about this mod is that one of the textures that comes with it is one where you can sort of see Tali's face through her mask.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she's got the extra little bits they photoshopped on that one picture in Mass Effect 3 if you happen to be romancing her.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I thought it was a neat touch.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's got little bits on her eyebrows.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway, I also played some Mass Effect 2, which I have now figured out how to use Ashley's skin and hair, except with a completely different face structure so it doesn't quite look like Ashley.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm using Warren's outfit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I've been playing around a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've gotten the game to crash once.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was proud of myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, um, I'm not doing the Fandango Actdeft Um, I also started The Secret World And the problem is that I've had a sinus infection all week As I've said on a previous episode This time of year, sinus infections Like you wouldn't believe, allergies all over the place
[SPEAKER_02]: and um so I got through like the very beginning of the uh Templar uh scenario and then I was like oh my god gunfire my head hurts I can't look at this anymore so um Secret World's that MMO I remember playing this too in beta is it totally free now or is it yeah like Guild Wars model
[SPEAKER_02]: It's... You can pay a subscription and get all the premium shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can buy a few things here and there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just have the completely freebie model.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of... I mean, I haven't gotten too much into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The controls are alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I did sign up for the next Final Fantasy XIV beta.
[SPEAKER_02]: So hopefully that'll work out for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't cancelled WoW yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every time I think I am, I was like, Oh, but I'll miss everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Weh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just a tip on that Final Fantasy XIV beta, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you do get in, it's under NDA, and you're not even supposed to say if you're in the beta.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, trust me, it would be a real shame if you got in the beta of Final Fantasy XIV, you couldn't talk about it on this show, even though you very much wanted to talk about everything that you were seeing in the beta.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you couldn't do that if you're under NDA.
[SPEAKER_08]: Trust me, I've heard from very close, very respected, very handsome sources.
[SPEAKER_02]: All I said is that I applied for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I applied and said yeah, I own every single one of these consoles that's on this list.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's your point?
[SPEAKER_02]: Except for the 3DS and the Vita.
[SPEAKER_02]: I own the good consoles on that list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, the Vita and the 3DS are cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: and God, I started playing, I was going to play Mirror's Edge and Dan's like, you're going to throw up, you're going to get sick, don't play it, you're going to get sick, you're going to get sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, fine, I'm going to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, the show is on whoever you are, VOG 155.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell us about your week, don't re-chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I played Mass Effect 3, shut up, Rageinator.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, they derail you.
[SPEAKER_08]: When you go to look at chat window, you've been saying it derails you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just most of the time, I didn't really have much of an energy to play much of anything just because I was on so many damn sinus medicines.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was on Dayquil, Sudafed, Benadryl, and Allegra in various doses, and then NyQuil.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, get better, damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel much better today.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just my nose feels like it's the Sahara.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft is asking about Mirror's Edge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was that something you were supposed to start this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's what I was going to start this week was Mirror's Edge.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's the one that Dan says, you're going to get sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine, I'm going to get sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's pretty though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm gonna play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to wait until... Because the other problem is that all this week I've had bad equilibrium issues.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know if I've made it evident to our lovely listeners yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've started drawing again.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we actually rearranged the vault slash computer room to where I have my... Your old desk, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_02]: The table.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there is my drawing surface.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I've actually been dedicating quite a bit of time to rebuilding lost skills.
[SPEAKER_02]: And...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been, but I've been trying to, when I play a game, if I'm pausing at a point in it, I'm actually starting to sketch out what's on my screen just to sort of help me with proportion and space and distance and that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been a pretty interesting exercise, but I figured my first love has been video games and art, so why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: And your second love is Garrus.
[SPEAKER_02]: My second love is Dan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Garrus is third.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, how was your... Oh, followed by The Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played Gary's Mod this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually bought that on their little Steam sale that they have for some indie stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was only three bucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was trying to get to work with the game, you know, the Xbox 360 controller, and it's a little awkward because they don't have the keys mapped out quite correctly.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I couldn't really do a whole ton...
[SPEAKER_05]: And also I kept losing my gravity gun, which was kind of annoying because I can't arrange stuff without that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so basically all I was able to do was throw a large iron beam in the air and crush myself with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so that was kind of boring.
[SPEAKER_05]: Instead, I went and tried to... Well, that kind of prompted me to look into some other games that supported controllers.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I had Cave Story Plus, which I knew that supported controllers, but for some reason I couldn't find...
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't look, I guess, for the options for the controller support.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then I found it, and so I started playing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so I'm enjoying that quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also played more Saints Row the Third, both on PC and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: And going through, grinding through the activities, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's...
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope the next game doesn't do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, let me introduce you to these activities that you've played before.
[SPEAKER_05]: They didn't do that in the second game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They didn't even do that in the first game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just had the activities there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the third game, half the missions are just like, hey, you have to do this activity for this reason, even though it doesn't really quite apply to the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Before Saints Row 2 and 1, it was drug trafficking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now it's merchandise trafficking.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like,
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: These guys are like, you know, big time gangsters now and we're trafficking merchandise like, you know, bobbleheads and shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or, you know, oh, hey, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't even go along with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's an escort mission where you have to escort them with a chopper.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like Guardian Angel is what it's called.
[SPEAKER_05]: Half the time, you're firing rockets out of the side of a helicopter.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the other time, you're, for some reason, repelled down the side of a building and sniping.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could snipe on top of the building.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to repel down the building a little bit for some damn reason to snipe.
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: I was one activity or one car theft away from completing all of the activities and all the Saints book stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, of course, you know, lost my safe.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was always fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, I also had Bioshock Infinite to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't gotten the chance to do that because I was cooking this morning and also the Defiance beta on 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: But by the time I get to play it, the beta is going to be over and Defiance will be out next week or the week after next.
[SPEAKER_08]: All those Bioshock Infinite reviews ought to start hitting tomorrow, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because the game's out Tuesday?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Am I right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I mean, there was the one from IGN because, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: They bought it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they bought it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm sure the game's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure the game's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unlike the Walking Dead game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Holy shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's been a source of comedy this week, hasn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like.
[SPEAKER_05]: EA's, I bet they're glad that, you know, The Walking Dead came.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like seriously one company after the next.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder who's going to have this shitty game next.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is Injustice going to be any good?
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or like, you know, maybe Defiance because it is based off a sci-fi series.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's not absolutely positive.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, my money's on Injustice actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't shade a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dead Island Riptide maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't shade a game I haven't played Saints Row 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a ways away.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some of the feedback coming out of backseas is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, I can't shade a game I haven't played.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what's confusing me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to buy Saints Row 4 just because... You're a whore for Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like Saints Row, but at the same time, what they've shown me isn't necessarily giving me the most confidence that this game is going to be good.
[SPEAKER_05]: First off, I...
[SPEAKER_05]: Saints Row the Third, I really wish it was more toned back towards two.
[SPEAKER_05]: Two was the best.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like the best balance between a gritty game and ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then three is just like, we're just going to go crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And four is like, we're going even crazier.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and we're going to have a dubstep gun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Come on, that's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to have a lot of DLC, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, yeah, I remember the DLC from Saints Row the Third, your 20-minute mission.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need someone who was at PAX East and played the game to call in and tell Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: No one played the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They watched a video, a short video.
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't playable?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope, 10-minute video they watched.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would have been playable, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why it's not coming to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not because they fucking hate the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's because they have the engine done already and they're not going to port it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else for your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: My gaming week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had a very Blizzard-tastic week because obviously I played a lot of WoW.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been working on a Hunter who's like my PvP character and been having fun with her.
[SPEAKER_08]: Played some more Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did I mention last week on the show, I can't remember when this happened, but I sold an item on the Real Money Auction House.
[SPEAKER_08]: on Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, you didn't mention that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I sold, guess how much I made?
[SPEAKER_08]: A dollar.
[SPEAKER_08]: I made 25 cents.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Woo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because the minimum you can list an item for is a buck 25, so that's what I put the item up for.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then the transaction fee is always one dollar, no matter what it sells for.
[SPEAKER_08]: So a dollar 25 minus a dollar, 25 cents, baby.
[SPEAKER_08]: It worked for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can put that towards a card pack and Hearthstone, but we'll get to that later.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, I've been having fun with Diablo 3, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm kind of into it right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, I played StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I did not play that new expansion, but all my friends kind of going back to StarCraft because of that expansion made me want to load up the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I was like, whoa, the launcher totally changed for this.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I loaded up Star Jeweled.
[SPEAKER_08]: Star Jeweled is the reason for me to play StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I don't have the new expansion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Until I sell about 100 more items on that real money auction house, if I can raise $40 on Diablo 3, I'll buy it.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I make a quarter every two weeks, I don't think that's going to happen pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, there was that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Been playing some console stuff too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to admit, I played the Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate demo on Wii U. The demo's awful, you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is awful.
[SPEAKER_08]: And here's the thing, like, I have friends that are really into that game right now that are, like, having a lot of fun with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And one way it was kind of described to me is that it's like Phantasy Star Online, kind of, but a lot more grindy because it's a JRPG.
[SPEAKER_08]: but I played this demo on Wii U and I just like the reason why I want to bring it up not that I like to review games based on the demo but here's the reality
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, way to sell your game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so now I'm like, okay, but my friends like really- Was Laundry more fun?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was.
[SPEAKER_08]: And like, I know there are Monster Hunter fans that listen to this show that are like, Rob, you're so ignorant.
[SPEAKER_08]: The demo doesn't show this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: That doesn't work for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, if the company is going to sell me on the game, sell me on the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So now, if I'm to be sold on this game, either I'm going to have to go play it at a friend's house who's going to have to explain to me what's going on, maybe I'll put it in my Gamefly queue, but it's not like something I'm like... The urgency of doing so just dropped a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me just put it that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, go into comments from the chatroom at live.vognetwork.com Actdeft says, Rob, you need to play Team Fortress 2 more You can sell stuff for over 100 US dollars You know, I actually, like, I was seriously going to boot up Team Fortress 2 the other night And then I got distracted and did something else And it was because of, like, last week's show Orange Right in our chatroom agrees with me about Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate That demo did not sell me on the game at all And it's a pity And you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: and I kind of have to remind myself Nino Cooney had a pretty bad demo too but the full game's great and like I don't know what convinced me to take the leap of faith there or I would like I refuse to do it in Monster Hunter but maybe because the Nino Cooney demo I kind of figured it out and it was fun in the long run once I finally figured it out I don't know
[SPEAKER_08]: One other game I played this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just bought it today, so I haven't had a lot of time to play it, but I did buy Luigi's Mansion on 3DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so I've only got to do some of the early levels, like where you go into that first little mansion.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did not play the GameCube version, which I know a lot of people might be like, what?
[SPEAKER_08]: But I didn't get my GameCube until well after the launch stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, I remember Loki bought me the GameCube as a really awesome present when Animal Crossing came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So by that point, you know, Animal Crossing was all the rage at that point.
[SPEAKER_08]: We didn't have time for Luigi's Mansion or any of the launch titles.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I never played the original one.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I've played the new one, but only a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I can't really give it a full review, but I will say some pretty good 3D effects.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it really reminds me, and this is a compliment, it really reminds me of an old school PC game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like just in the way you're kind of walking around the mansion on the top screen and it's like you're finding items.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like it's...
[SPEAKER_08]: for some reason kind of reminds me of an old school puzzler like an old LucasArts game almost with a little more action though obviously because you know you're sucking in the ghosts and all that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you can find him hanged.
[SPEAKER_08]: No multiplayer or anything like that yet because I've literally only played the game like 30 minutes so I can't tell you any more about it at this time but it was fun and the 3D effects were fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the whole little pixelator thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like something out of Tron.
[SPEAKER_08]: That cracked me up.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so Luigi's Mansion 3DS and that was my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's get into some housekeeping real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, I think I mentioned this before, but just want to make sure you all know there is no Orange Lounge Radio next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a great Easter or Sunday off.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll be drunk on mimosas.
[SPEAKER_08]: Will you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, from brunch?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, where we're going for brunch, Marie Callender's, they give you like never-ending mimosas.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of places do that for brunch.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so happy.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's like the friends that I have downtown that we like to go to brunch with all the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like we can't go to a place unless they have endless mimosas because our one friend is like, no, I'm not going if I can't get have mimosas.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So good times.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, so no show next week, but we will be back on April 7th.
[SPEAKER_08]: I believe Bobby's here next week, so those of you guys that turn out here pretty loyally on Sunday night, you'll have something to look forward to next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: There may be a best of or something, but there won't be a pre-recorded show because we're intentionally setting it up so that we know episode 500 is on this day, so that way we can kind of plan a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Twitter.com slash OLR, Facebook, Orange Launch Radio, yada yada.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get into gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this was completely unexpected, but Capcom announced, I guess, a little bit ahead of their World of Capcom panel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I think it was teased before that, but announced at their World of Capcom panel that they're going to be remastering DuckTales, like the old NES DuckTales game, which is pretty fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should have seen the flappy hands I made when I heard that news.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was really unexpected.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, very unexpected.
[SPEAKER_05]: And basically it's going to have hand-drawn sprites.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to have all the original voices.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's coming to Wii U, PlayStation Network, and Xbox Live Arcade.
$15.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably, I want to say it was, I think it was this summer maybe?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if they had a date yet on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yes, all the...
[SPEAKER_05]: Granny Gummy
[SPEAKER_08]: The guy who does Uncle Scrooge was also Mr. Ed way back in the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, then, now I have an excuse to play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stop asking me for quotes, Tim Schafer.
[SPEAKER_17]: You had an excuse already, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to give you the Cliff Notes version, though, here, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: So, like, here's, you know, Capcom and, like, the inspirational music and the few games are so rich with such a wealth, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's like setting up for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, okay, so after all that...
[SPEAKER_02]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sing along!
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that it has the bopping head.
[SPEAKER_08]: But look how it looks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: How can I cut this off early?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, I have to let it play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's what, I'm very, the only thing I'm disappointed in is that they didn't show the moon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they gotta keep something a secret.
[SPEAKER_08]: They gotta save something.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like there was only Transylvania in there and one other stage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it also can't be complete.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's probably not done yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't watch gameplay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently they retweaked all the bosses so they're harder now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like they have more sequences to them.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to remember, as awesome as the game as DuckTales was, it really was only, like, six stages.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was about as long as the first Mega Man game, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: There wasn't a whole lot to it, so I don't know if they're, like, adding or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, like, seriously, when I just heard it, I was like, oh, way forward?
[SPEAKER_08]: And Capcom, like...
[SPEAKER_08]: Who brokered that deal?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because that is like inspired genius for real.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because WayForward did a great job with the Double Dragon Neon, and they did some of these other remakes too.
[SPEAKER_08]: They did the Contra game on DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've done a lot of good stuff, and to trust them with DuckTales was...
[SPEAKER_08]: Genius.
[SPEAKER_08]: So when I saw the trailer, I was just like, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't we all kind of go like, Capcom has made a lot of bad decisions in the past year, and this is the first time where you're like, oh my god, I can like them again.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please love us.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's cool to like Capcom again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's something you want to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have WayForward redo Link to the Past.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or, let's just see if we can take that further.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have them redo Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go into some comments from our chat room at live.vognetwork.com Gamer Girl says, LOL, I'm still laughing because I had the lyrics wrong for so long.
[SPEAKER_08]: The trailer did kind of make a lot of you guys realize that, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but Dan regularly breaks into that theme song at my house.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I have no excuse not to know that and the Darkwing Duck theme.
[SPEAKER_08]: Extover says, I admit that I didn't play much of the original NES game since we only rented it once, but I'm amused and excited by the remaster.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't own it either, and I'm in the same boat.
[SPEAKER_08]: We rented it like three times.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you used to rent it all the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I did own the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to say I did own that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's what makes me more, because now that I'm an adult and I can buy whatever the hell I want, I'm going to own this.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: I should actually text Dan and see if he knows about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkTetsuya says, there's your list list.
[SPEAKER_08]: Series way forward needs to update for 2013.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a great idea, DarkTetsuya.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe not tonight, but soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft says, the moon is going to sound so fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Technus says, $15, huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it took five seconds for it to make me want to buy it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ditto.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the bottom line, as excited as we all are, please don't fuck this up.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is sacred territory, people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Please don't fuck this up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop raping our childhoods.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was that it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did we talk about the other series?
[SPEAKER_08]: The possibility that they said they were going to do Rescue Rangers possibly and some of this other stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh God, that'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, no, it's in one of the other, I think it's in the second link.
[SPEAKER_08]: They said that if this does well, that there is the potential that they'll do like Rescue Rangers and some of the other Capcom Disney stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm sitting there going, Mickey Mousecapade, Mickey Mousecapade, which is kind of basic, but I loved it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I literally tripped over that cartridge the other day.
[SPEAKER_02]: because Midna has been trying to get up on the shelves to get the stuff and she knocked it down.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was in the case and everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, would this mean that maybe we'd start getting into some of the later games like Aladdin and Lion King?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that was one of the other things they said.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said Chippendale Rescue Rangers, Darkwing Duck, and Aladdin.
[SPEAKER_02]: Darkwing Duck I would be happy about.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100Matt says, from what I saw at the show, they didn't mess it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank heavens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it looked good from what I saw.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had the boss fight against, who was it, Magica the Spell.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looked pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: So excited.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope this is the beginning of a beautiful relationship.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the other thing I wanted to say about this.
[SPEAKER_08]: They need to make sweet, sweet Disney love.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know we've got a Mega Man thing coming up later on, but I have to bring this up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why not just let WayForward do Mega Man?
[SPEAKER_02]: That made me spat so hard I dropped my mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why not just let them do Mega Man?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they'll probably do the game we all want, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: So hopefully this is the beginning of a beautiful friendship.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, you know who should really be doing the next Mega Man, if they did one, would be letting the people who did the Street Fighter cross Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_08]: The anniversary, the freebie that was on the internet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe, maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of the other big games that came out of PAX East was somewhat of a surprise announcement from Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I had the other show, Horde House, where we talk a lot about World of Warcraft and things.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there were a lot of people thinking that it was going to be like a big thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like it was going to be another expansion or that it was Titan, even though Blizzard said time and time again it's not Titan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it kind of did come out of left field.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is not something people were predicting.
[SPEAKER_08]: The game that Blizzard announced at PAX East was called Hearthstone Heroes of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a card game, basically.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a virtual card game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be playable on PC, Mac, and iPad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of think...
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't they have a card game already?
[SPEAKER_08]: Blizzard?
[SPEAKER_08]: they have a tangible WoW trading card game but this isn't that I think it's a simpler version of that and it's not meant to be a tangible game it is a little weird because both of those exist but I think there's room for both I mean if Magic the Gathering can be successful in both a tangible game and an online game I don't see why Blizzard can't have two properties out there
[SPEAKER_08]: Now here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is going to be a free game, but it's freemium.
[SPEAKER_08]: You earn more cards.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can earn them through playing the game and you win medals when you do PvP against people.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you'll also be able to buy expansion packs, of course, with real money.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're thinking about $1.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what they're thinking right now for the packs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hearthstone will have 300 cards in the initial collection.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's hero versus hero.
[SPEAKER_08]: You play as one of the nine Central Warcraft classes, each represented by a hero.
[SPEAKER_08]: For example, you can play, I believe Thrall is the shaman.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know Anduin is the priest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Malfurion, I think, is the druid.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can play as one of the big characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it looks really good.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, did you see this at all?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think this is their trailer that talks about... Actually, let me see if I can find the match.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Jaina would be mage.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you buy me a little time here, I'll try to find the...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm broke, so I can't buy you anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, well, I'm trying to think over who would be better.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the gameplay video where it's... I'm going to go kind of midway into this here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me make this a little bigger so you can actually see it here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your turn.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'll notice it's very cartoony and animated in the way it looks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you've got little panda houses.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it definitely has some of the newer, even though we only see old Warcraft characters in this, it definitely has some of the newer inspired stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I quit playing Magic for a reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you don't think you'd be into this?
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a time sink.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, Loki, I could see them wanting people like you who don't touch any Blizzard IPs as of right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Someone like you would be great to get into this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any interest in this for you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: I just don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you're not a big card game person.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Makes sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I'll give it a try.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's where my mind went, too, is I was like, oh, remember when Tetra Master was in Final Fantasy XI and you had to pay like a dollar a month to play it?
[SPEAKER_08]: God, I never touched that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did my 30-day free trial of Tetra Master and I think I maybe paid for one more month.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't bother.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it was like 10 years ago, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: And, I mean, you know, technology's come a long way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hated it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll try this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'll try this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: I downloaded it.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it sucks, delete it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It can't be worse than Yaris.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: It already looks better than Yaris.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ain't that the truth?
[SPEAKER_08]: And then if I keep selling stuff in Diablo, I can buy the expansion packs, although that's exactly what Blizzard wants.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I bet we're going to see more of this, especially when the Titan thing is revealed, the MMO.
[SPEAKER_08]: I bet there's going to be a lot of mini... I bet there'll be real money woven into that somehow in its own little economy where Blizzard gets a little chunk of it every time.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's an...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's an extremely profitable avenue for them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's move on with more news.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, we will have... Well, it's not a surprise to you anymore because I told you what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will have something special for our fifth centiversary.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's how it would be for hundreds.
[SPEAKER_02]: So here's glorious, beautiful news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, we need to have Ding Dong the Witch's Dad playing in the background.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the CEO of EA, John Riccitello... Is that how you pronounce his name?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: is stepping down on the 30th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Because he has butchered some of our favorite stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, the whole reason he's stepping down, too, is because of fiscal depreciation in the company.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and like,
[SPEAKER_02]: He's basically saying that it has to do, and I'm going to read you the quote.
[SPEAKER_02]: My decision to leave EA is really all about my accountability for the shortcomings in our financial results this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like we will likely come in at the low end or slightly below the financial guidance we issued to the street.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You should have seen the wank on a Tumblr in the Mass Effect fan community.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was glorious and beautiful and there were lots of dancing gifs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, those clothes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it really going to change anything?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the people next in line, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have, right now, the interim leader is going to be Larry Probst, who was the CEO from 1991 to 2007.
[SPEAKER_02]: And likely candidates to replace is Frank Gibbo, who is the president of EA Labels, or their COO, Peter Moore, who was once in charge of EA Sports and worked for Microsoft during the Xbox 360 launch.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could see Peter Moore, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Extifer in chat says, at least he took responsibility.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, yeah, I mean, at least he was, it wasn't as good as the Groupon guy's goodbye letter.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if you guys saw that a few weeks ago, but that was good.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know shit's bad if Valve says no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, Bonds006, I have to agree with this comment in our chatroom, live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, someone will take Jon's place and EA will be EA.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think this is really going to change it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think he's just the fall guy for all this bam, bam, bam.
[SPEAKER_08]: Star Wars Old Republic didn't do as well as it was supposed to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mass Effect 3's ending, just as much as I hate the length behind that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know the whole big rush on that, the pressure came from EA.
[SPEAKER_08]: True.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, true.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now SimCity, you know, and all that.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had to give free games away.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's just the head of the Hydra.
[SPEAKER_02]: On top of that, though, this is coming out right before, well, right after they found out that they're going to be next, again, on the top ten list of worst companies to work for.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: At any rate, I would like to be hopeful to see better things come out, to see a new direction, you know, to see them stop snatching up companies left and right and ruining their... Fix goddamn Origin.
[SPEAKER_08]: I sat there for 30 minutes last night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Myself, Alan, Shane, and Tim all wanted to play multiplayer, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're trying to play multiplayer Mass Effect, but because Alan and I are in the same house...
[SPEAKER_08]: Fix Origin
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want us to take it seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: More like butt gin.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm still gonna... I mean, honestly, I think that Origin in and of itself is a bad business decision to go through.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I mean, it's like I was saying before, you know shit's bad when Valve refuses your money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: but here's the thing speaking of all that we have to remember Steam was pretty bad when it first launched everybody was pissed because it was bundled with Half-Life 2 and you had no choice there's a lot of that so like I want to be hopeful and say maybe there's a light at the end of the tunnel and maybe this will all turn out okay but I'm just I just don't have that same level of trust in EA right now they keep fucking it up end of story and I mean
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the entire Mass Effect series, even if there are... I like to joke around and call 3 a sparkly turd.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's lots of stuff in 3 that I love.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love scenes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love parts of the story.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just the whole lack of, what's the word I'm thinking of?
[SPEAKER_02]: Continuity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really going from game to game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Changing writing staff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know that that pressure came from EA.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dungeon Buster in our chat room, kind of with another perspective.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, what about the good things Riccatello did?
[SPEAKER_08]: Dungeon Buster says the board probably forced him out.
[SPEAKER_08]: EA stock has been on a brutal decline in the last few years.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't disagree with that for sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dungeon Buster says Riccatello was also known for taking gambles backing Dante's Inferno, Mirror's Edge, etc.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, for better or for worse, those were some original games.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I would say for better, Mirror's Edge.
[SPEAKER_08]: For worse, Dante's Inferno.
[SPEAKER_08]: But for better or worse, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's like asking what did Bush do good for the country?
[SPEAKER_08]: I knew you'd take it down a political route.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: But seriously, I think I remembered reading on one other article that their stock increased after the announcement.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ragenator in chat at live.vognetwork.com says, which is worse to work for?
[SPEAKER_08]: EA, GameStop, or Emperor Palpatine?
[SPEAKER_08]: Which would be the worst to work for?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd probably say... That's really tough.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is really tough.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, at least with Palpatine, you don't have to worry about being unemployed because you'd just be dead.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, and as long as you're on the Death Star that they don't blow up, you might have it pretty good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I fucked up every Death Star I don't know, EA's gonna hire me a corporate or GameStop's gonna hire me a corporate office Now, if you're working a desk job on Coruscant, you're usually fine I'm just saying I'm not saying that, you know, they're that bad to work for To register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com use the passphrase, draw Alright, let's move on with more news because Loki, I think you have something very related to this, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I know we're talking about, you know, Origin, but what could they possibly fix with Origin?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Origin's perfect, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, oh, wait, wait, wait, what's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Origin has an exploit where you can use hyperlinks to run malicious code?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's not good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, apparently there is a way that, um... You mean run Origin?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's not just running Origin, it's Origin Plus.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have this, and I don't even know why you would need this in the first place, why this is even part of a feature or something, but they have these URI hyperlinks that basically you click on a link on a webpage or something like that, it launches Origin and whatever game
[SPEAKER_05]: DLL at this IP address.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's not good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Opening some sort of malicious file on a remotely controlled server because that's a thing that they have in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I love their comment on it, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our team is constantly investigating hypotheticals like this one as we continually update our security infrastructure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Constantly investigating, but I don't see a patch for this right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, they know about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's being worked on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Soon, trademark.
[SPEAKER_05]: The best thing you can do is if you have a web browser or something like that, if you haven't yet clicked on one of these URI links or something like that, one, you get a prompt in Firefox or something like that that says, use this program to launch this type of file going forward.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just have it say, let me choose.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, how often are you really going to be launching URI links through your web browser?
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably not very often.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, of course, you know, where they say they're constantly investigating stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I don't wonder, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something very similar now with the Battlefield Play for Free.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very similar with that is they have another thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an exploit for older versions of Windows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything before Vista.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where someone can launch a mod file, I guess it's used to customize games and settings, and that mod file could queue also some malicious code somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_05]: So very similar, but with a whole different game, not necessarily Origin, but that's not good.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I guess they say that it's successful because I guess it overwrites a whitelist as opposed to restrict sites because of this mod file or like a batch file or something like that yeah they upload a malicious batch file they'll execute the next time the computer is restarted
[SPEAKER_05]: Fun!
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll keep your Windows updated, I guess, but not everyone's going to be buying Windows 7 or Windows 8 or Vista.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there are people out there with Windows XP still.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who has it better?
[SPEAKER_08]: The people with Windows XP or the people with Windows 8?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just trolling.
[SPEAKER_08]: Windows 8 apparently isn't that bad, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad I don't have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had to use it on my wife's sister's laptop to try to like... I don't like how everything's arranged in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very odd.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I mean, I'm sure it's a little bit of a learning curve.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, the regular desktop's there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just... It's odd.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the best way I could describe it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I know you play Origin every day, Loki, so you have a lot to be worried about with this.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I have not installed Origin at all, and I know I probably have somewhere like an EA account because I did for Burnout Paradise, I think is Paradise, but I have yet to... You know whose fault it is I have Origin on PC, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Shane's.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I probably would have had to do it eventually because Alan's a big PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: He doesn't really play stuff on consoles anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, let's talk about better news and things that put a smile on your face as opposed to angry little slanted eyebrows and angry face.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a sound for that face.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, mmm face.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is actually really exciting news.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was very happy to hear this.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Final Fantasy X HD remaster on PlayStation 3, it's going to include Final Fantasy X too, which I think is great.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is as reported in Jump Magazine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Both games based on the International Edition, and yes, apparently both are getting that HD remaster treatment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they're both the same engine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: The first trailer for Final Fantasy X just hit, I think, today.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can actually check that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will definitely be picking this up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love that both these games are on one disc for PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, the Vita will be getting both these games, but they have to be purchased separately.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, the games are supposed to come out this year, which is pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yet another reason to not get a PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's all this good stuff still coming out on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe I'll actually beat one of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what my problem was?
[SPEAKER_02]: I breezed all the way through both of them and still wasn't high enough level.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't really play... I mean, I watched you, I think, play some of 10-2 and I've certainly seen my fair share of YouTubes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't really play a lot of 10-2.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm kind of... I'd like to give it a fair shot and play again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I mean, if you had let me know this, I would have just loaned you my copy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I've also got 10 International.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft in chat says Final Fantasy X sucks though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: Incorrect.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see where people take issue to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do get the issues of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What can I do for you?
[SPEAKER_08]: But as the game itself, I really like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's where every gamer has a voice and everybody gets their own opinion even when they're wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even when they're being a butt.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I didn't mean that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only minorly.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um, here's some good news, and I actually have to thank CatastrophicMagi for sharing some nice stuff with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, the, uh, European Wii U eShop lifted the age restriction that they were having, you know, where you could only buy the games after, like, what, 9 o'clock?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it was, uh, no, yeah, you could only buy them after 11.
[SPEAKER_02]: After 11.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the Wii U eShop, all night.
[SPEAKER_05]: All night.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was her name?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ronda Shearer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still remember that show.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: She was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've watched every single Toxic Avenger movie thanks to Ronda Shearer.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, it had to do with German law.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is very important.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, it's Ronda and we'll be watching Hats and Surf Nazis Must Die next on USA Up All Night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it wasn't because of the voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: The 80s hair and the... No, it wasn't the hair.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was not the hair.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even I have to look at that and go, damn.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's she doing now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I'm going to have to Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, great, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Car shows, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rhonda Shearer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so yeah, I think it's really hilarious that we're talking about her and Germany.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, she died.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did she?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I just made that up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, and you said I couldn't troll people.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's had some surgery too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, her last film that she did in 2003, Prisoner Go-Go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: But let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's been doing Sheer Intimates LLC.
[SPEAKER_08]: So she's doing panties, basically.
[SPEAKER_08]: In 2010, Ronda designed the Ah!
[SPEAKER_08]: Bra.
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't that a Pokemon?
[SPEAKER_08]: It makes sense, yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: What does the Ah!
[SPEAKER_16]: Bra do?
[SPEAKER_08]: And the product was an overnight success.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Ah!
[SPEAKER_08]: Bra is the number one selling bra worldwide.
[SPEAKER_08]: That reads like a sales pitch.
[SPEAKER_08]: She plans to add cosmetic swimwear fragrance and Boomer Hottie into... I think that's... Somebody just edited that fucking article.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to know what the odd bra is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just went to look it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, dude, this is things that they sell at the scene on TV store.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys, Loki knows what an opera is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I watch TV, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, infomercials.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also know what a slap chop is.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is a slap chop?
[SPEAKER_05]: A slap chop is a thing that you can chop garlic in.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I had the knockoff brand.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sucked because the garlic is stuck up in the goddamn thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: USA chop all night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, can I go back to the story that I was trying so professionally to discuss?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, because I'm reading a comment from Marissa in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com Marissa, do you have an ah bra?
[SPEAKER_08]: Marissa says, ah bra is a lazy, saggy bra for wusses.
[SPEAKER_05]: According to their website, it says, say goodbye to pinching, binding, chafing, and discomfort.
[SPEAKER_05]: Prevents bra bulge and underarm cleavage.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fits perfectly even if you gain or lose weight.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a chest girdle.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's machine washable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I get an ah brief?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: First of all, I have a comfortable bra.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I can wash it in the washing machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like a tank top made out of spandex or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's seriously what it looks like.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, back to the video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a boob girdle.
[SPEAKER_08]: What gamers really want to know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, look at our demographic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so yeah, basically they made some, I guess they had to have discussed something with the German government or found some loophole to get out of it, but now you can shop for games before 11.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now I imagine she's talking about the Abra.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had to make a deal with the German government in order to be able to sell it.
[SPEAKER_02]: First of all, they had to strike a deal with David Hasselhoff because he secretly uses the Abra for his man boobs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm leaving the room done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: God.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's travel around the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we need to get Marissa to call in and do Uta's brassieres now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we also have the PAX East calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to keep it on topic a little bit, but Marissa is more than welcome to come to episode 500.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, release dates.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's travel around the world and check out what is coming out in a lingerie store near you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Today, Pokemon Mystery Dungeon, Gates to Infinity and 3DS, and I believe today was also... Luigi's Mansion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Luigi's Mansion.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't remember if that was earlier than today or today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, so there's that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, of course, next week, also some big stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bioshock Infinite on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, Army of Two, The Devil's Cartel on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: WRC FIA World Rally Championship 2012 on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fantasy XI, the Ultimate Collection Seekers Edition on Xbox 360 on PC and 360 Final Fantasy XI, Seekers of Alduin Tiger Woods, PGA Tour 14 on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 also the Master's Historic Edition if you really want to spend extra money for a few extra courses and I believe that's it
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go to Japan and check out the release dates over there.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the PlayStation 3 on March 28th, Army of Two, The Devil's Cartel comes out on PlayStation 3, as well as Sengoku Basara Triple Pack.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am assuming that is all three games in the... It's Sengoku Basara 3, Utage, and HD Collection are all the games that are that.
[SPEAKER_08]: What series is this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is this... That would be Three Kingdoms, Sengoku...
[SPEAKER_05]: Sengoku Basara is Devil Kings over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was like, I know it's over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the Capcom Dynasty Warriors game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little more cultish over here, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't release any over here, that's why.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had Devil Kings on PlayStation 2 and then they had Sengoku Basara on the Wii and PlayStation 3 a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Final Fantasy XI expansion makes its way to Japan as well on the Xbox 360 for all you guys playing it on the 360 in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: As well as Army of Two, The Devil's Cartel, Cave Shooting Collection, that ought to be pretty good, and Love Toray Chocolate.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the Cave Shooting Collection, by the way, since it is a cave title, I believe, those are region free.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that something that might come to the store then?
[SPEAKER_08]: Some of them hit the direct download.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Cave, the shooting collection, I mean all the Cave titles have been out on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to say that it's probably, they probably will bring it over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Axis Games might bring it over.
[SPEAKER_05]: Axis or, yeah, it would be Axis Games I think they would be the ones bringing it over.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, I looked up Basara means crazy or over the top, but also stylish.
[SPEAKER_08]: Better than Basura in Spanish.
[SPEAKER_02]: What does that mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Junk?
[SPEAKER_02]: Trash?
[SPEAKER_08]: Trash, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: PlayStation Vita this week in Japan on the 28th.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oboro Muramasa comes out this week from Marvelous Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_17]: Has to do with a sword.
[SPEAKER_08]: Muramasa Rebirth, the remake.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sei Madu Monogatari comes out as well from Compile.
[SPEAKER_02]: Compile!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_08]: Who needs to remake the Guardian Legends somehow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lastly but not leastly on the 3DS this week, Nano Assault gets a price reduction and Shoshinsha Kata...
[SPEAKER_08]: Nai Honichi, Made Soroban, Anzan, Flash Anzan.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a mouthful.
[SPEAKER_08]: What game is this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: No pictures of it, but the related games are all like puppies and kitty cafe and things like that, so it's one of those games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, how about the UK, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Some stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the UK, we have, starting with the 26th, we have Bioshock Infinite.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 27th, Lego City Undercover and Sly Cooper Thieves in Time.
[SPEAKER_02]: The 28th, we have Luigi's Mansion 2 and Tiger Woods PGA Tour 14.
[SPEAKER_02]: And on the 29th, we have Army 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just a couple more news stories for you guys, and then the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: But first, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: WarZ may try to convince you that they were part of this program they actually don't have this program out yet or they just started it it's the early access program it allows you to play and purchase games that are still in development they have a few games starting off with Arma 3 and Starforge also a game I think should be at least a nominee for the best title of a game in 2013 Drunken Robot Pornography
[SPEAKER_05]: Sign me up!
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, and then, let's see, was it Kenshi?
[SPEAKER_05]: Kenshi, an open-ended squad-based strategy RPG.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's too big of a subtitle.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to have to change that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, basically, so yeah, so they're gonna add features and stuff that will be available over time, plus I guess you'll be able to maybe provide some feedback for the titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's kinda cool that you can do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Arma 3, I actually kinda wanna try that, but Arma's so simulation that I just would wanna mod the hell out of it, you know, get laser beams and stuff that are ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: But...
[SPEAKER_08]: I kind of like that whole idea about getting in early on the game's development and kind of getting to give that instant feedback and maybe your angry internet comments really can influence the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Especially in this Kickstarter world we live in now.
[SPEAKER_08]: This seems like a great place to launch a project that started on Kickstarter where your investors, essentially, really can...
[SPEAKER_08]: Have their say on the game's development.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was one I saw.
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was another... I don't know if they were doing it through their own website.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was... Actually, it was a train simulation game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the difference was they were asking people to crowdfund it, but the people that crowdfunded it also get a portion of the profits that they receive from the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you're profit sharing, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be kind of neat to do with Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_08]: I might have missed it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are there any games you're looking forward to being a part of with this?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Arma 3 looks kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I may have to check out the robot pornography game because that's an awesome title and I like giant robot games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be interesting to check out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well one more story for you guys and I alluded to this earlier when we were talking about DuckTales but there was some talk about Mega Man at PAX East at the World of Capcom panel.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brett Elston, the Capcom community manager said that Capcom is developing a new game in the Mega Man series but they're not ready to fully announce it just yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think this is kind of a duh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, despite the canceled projects, I mean, like, would you really just drop something like a Mega Man?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I think you put it to bed for a few years and then it comes back better than ever, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's probably what's happening here.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, since this story first broke on the internet, Capcom kind of came behind the community manager here and said, now, now, now, now, no Mega Man game has been confirmed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: The company is having ongoing discussions about Mega Man but it won't announce anything until something is ready.
[SPEAKER_08]: So don't hold your breath that that's necessarily this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: It could be a long time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, Shane was sending me some private messages when we were talking about the whole DuckTales and WayForward thing and saying, what else should WayForward do?
[SPEAKER_08]: And Shane was reminding me, Rob, WayForward doesn't always strike gold.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's pull up WayForward's resume and see some of the other games that they've done in the past.
[SPEAKER_08]: Godzilla Domination on the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_08]: SpongeBob SquarePants, Lights, Camera, Pants The A Boy and His Blob on the Wii Although to be fair, I never really gave that a try I really wanted to play that too because I love the first one Let's see, the Silent Hill Book of Memories game on the Vita But see
[SPEAKER_08]: Shane didn't like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't think it was terrible.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just didn't think it was great, but it's decent.
[SPEAKER_17]: It wasn't very Silent Hill-y, was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: But here's the biggest sin WayForward has ever committed.
[SPEAKER_08]: You ready for this?
[SPEAKER_08]: A Nintendo DS game called Ping Pals.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you remember this game?
[SPEAKER_17]: I didn't play it, but I remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was like somebody put out PictoChat as a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: But how long ago was that?
[SPEAKER_08]: 2004, glad you asked.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, think about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've done their time.
[SPEAKER_05]: They did their time in jail.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've learned their lesson.
[SPEAKER_05]: They made some bad mistakes as kids, and now they're adults.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do I have Queen's We Are the Champions going through my head?
[SPEAKER_08]: BloodRayne Betrayal
[SPEAKER_08]: Shantae Risky's Revenge
[SPEAKER_05]: I did want to mention, because I do happen to follow them on Facebook, the 100,000 strong for bringing back Mega Man Legends 3, they did post a wonderful update regarding a fan-made game in the Mega Man series.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called The Master System.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an action brawler game based in the Mega Man Legends series.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have two unique characters, and you fight a bunch of the Reaverbots.
[SPEAKER_05]: and you can check it out for free right now it's arcade.legends-station.com slash question mark SP equals master system so check it out or follow the 100,000 strong for Bring Back Mega Legends 3 which they are now 101,000 strong just saying
[SPEAKER_08]: TigerClaw in chat linking us to some Ping Pals gameplay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where you have an actual little keyboard you can type on or you can draw and you have coins to buy stuff for your avatar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: What if, when this game started development, they didn't know that Nintendo was going to put PictoChat into the system?
[SPEAKER_08]: What if there had been no PictoChat?
[SPEAKER_08]: Would we be giving Ping Pals such shit?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: You kids and your frickin' HD reboots.
[SPEAKER_02]: In this case it's, hey, I can't believe I haven't done this one yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go play this pixelated classic and love it.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Eternal Champions.
[SPEAKER_02]: How have I never done this?
[SPEAKER_08]: You say that every week.
[SPEAKER_08]: How have I never done this?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like sitting down trying to go through all of the, oh fuck.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do your, read your thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway, Eternal Champions came out in 1993.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a 2D fighting game and they came out for the Mega Drive or Sega Genesis that same year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was sort of like a Mortal Kombat-y type of thing where there were overkills and special moves and things.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, it did spawn one of the best sequels ever, which was Eternal Champion's Challenge from the Dark Side, which was basically the Sega CD version.
[SPEAKER_02]: And two other spin-offs, there was a, it's just set in that universe, and it's also out on the Wii Virtual Console account, 2007.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically, it's just this typical fighting game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it works a lot like Street Fighter II.
[SPEAKER_02]: It uses the six-button controller, though, so that you can have the different ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the version of this that I have, I got with Sega Activator.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you remember the Activator?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, he had one of those Activators.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was trying to build a para-para machine out of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I think I threw it away.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to tell you how we got our activator.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right before Virgin went out of business, we bought it for $8.
[SPEAKER_02]: A Genesis activator.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's how we have our copy.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was that long ago when Virgin Megastore went out of business?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it was very soon after I moved out here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Longer than 10 years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: you also had a special attack meter so that you could do different specials and then you had your overkills and that was stage specific I'm getting tongue tied today these are basically you have to defeat your opponent where they fall in a certain area of the ground if they land in the right spot the life bars disappear and something in the background kills them to death
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, for example... Wow, this person just got set on fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're... You can get vaporized by neon sign in Shadows level.
[SPEAKER_02]: A Tyrannosaurus can kill you in Slashes level.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good lord!
[SPEAKER_08]: That goes on forever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, not only did the guy get set on fire, but then you see a skeleton, and then the head falls off the skeleton.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a drive-by shooting in Larsen's level.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a napalm bomb in Midnight's level.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, there were a bunch of characters, and I'm going to go through the character lists real quick, just because some of them had some fun names.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there were some of the, I thought some of the better characters were in the second one, but you had Shadow Miyamoto, Rax Coswell, Jonathan Blade, Jetta Max, Slash Trident, Xavier Pendragon, Mitchell Middleton Knight, who was Midnight, ha ha with a K, and
[SPEAKER_02]: Larson Tyler, The Eternal Champion, you had Qin Wo, Dawson McShane, who was kind of fun, Ramsey's the third, Raven Gendar, Senator, and Riptide de Medici.
[SPEAKER_02]: People love to hate on those de Medici's, I swear, but they were all busy killing each other and being Pope.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then you had Blast Chavez, and then some animals.
[SPEAKER_08]: This game looks kind of derpy, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is kind of derpy, but it was classic.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's classic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fair enough, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Classically derpy.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was the slurpy flavor that was Sega Eternal Champions Cherry.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was at 7-Eleven, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then there were game books that came out that were released by Puffin Books.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a comic about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was called Eternal Champions Special that was done by the UK Sega magazine, Sonic the Comic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you remember the group Bone Thugs-N-Harmony?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: They basically sampled Eternal Champions for their songs Eternal and Crossroad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Crossroad samples Eternal Champions?
[SPEAKER_08]: That was like their biggest hit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Courage the Cowardly Dog also used some of the same audio loops.
[SPEAKER_02]: EGM actually sponsored Eternal Champions tournaments, which I remember a few people...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I knew one person who actually was in one of those a while back, but don't quote me on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, like I said, it came with the Activator.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a Special Moves Edition that was a handheld Tiger game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It basically was just a really crappy version of Eternal Champions.
[SPEAKER_02]: and basically it was a pretty mediocre game I mean I thought that the Sega CD one was better and then they were going to do Eternal Champions the final chapter for the Saturn but they cancelled it so that they could push Virtua Fighter in the US I would like to know if there's a prototype of this sitting around because I would love to see it
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, as far as the spinoffs, there was one called Chicago Syndicate that came out on the Game Gear in 95 that was based on an alternate reality where Larson Tyler didn't die in 1920.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there's Xperts, X-P-E-R-T-S.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a side-scrolling beat-em-up that is based on one where Shadow Yamato didn't die.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all champions.
[SPEAKER_08]: Overkill.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this one you get to be eaten by a shark.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm waiting to see if they get to the... They keep pausing it, so I'm assuming they're looking up the fatality or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or whatever it's called in this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Overkill.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was the game that had the ones that were called CineKills?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you remember that one?
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a game that called it that, and I don't remember what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that TimeKillers?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's TimeKiller.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, I'll find out.
[SPEAKER_08]: TimeKiller was the one where you chopped off the body parts.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, there it is, your classic game of the week, Eternal Champions for the Mega Drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were CineKills in Eternal Champions CD, is what they were.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: I knew it was one of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we are going to take a quick break and then we'll be back with more Orange Launch Radio tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have a not-so-serious Google Question of the Week tonight that should be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: A little more news out of PAX East.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully some calls, we're hoping.
[SPEAKER_08]: And yes, Jamie's going to talk a little more about Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_08]: But don't worry guys, not too much.
[SPEAKER_08]: All that and more when we come back with more of Orange Launch Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio, live on this Sunday evening, March the 24th, 2013.
[SPEAKER_08]: Episode number 498 of our program in progress.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello to those of you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently we've got a few folks, I've been messaging IRC and just got some text messages, that are listening to us in the car on the way back from PAX East.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, hello you lucky shits.
[SPEAKER_00]: Drive safely.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, drive recklessly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Faster, faster.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Please drive safe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't be driving drunk either.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura will kick your ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get back into some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, there are things that are more painful to kick than the ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura will kick you in the taint or the ah bra.
[SPEAKER_08]: She will snap your ah bra.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will cut a bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she'll say, you mad brah?
[SPEAKER_05]: Rapid fire news time, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's things locally I wish I could buy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Borderlands 2, they were teasing a while back at South by Southwest that there was going to be a brand new character class.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, PAX East, they finally revealed what that's going to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is Krieg
[SPEAKER_05]: The Psycho, or Kreek the, I guess, I don't know what you call it, the reformed Psycho.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's basically a Psycho from the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: His primary form of attack is melee, which sounds lame, actually, when you think about it, because this is a game about guns, and also because the character I've been actually playing as Zero has a melee attack, and I fucking hate using it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course, there's going to be an Ultimate Vault Hunter upgrade pack on April 2nd.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to raise the game's level cap from 50 to 61.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not 60, but 61.
61.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's so much bigger.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I guess the upgrade pack will be part of the season pass.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Psycho Pack will not be part of the season pass content.
[SPEAKER_05]: and also I guess the upgrade pack is going to have the Ultimate Vault Hunter mode which of course will raise level caps of all the enemies in the third playthrough.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course the Ultimate Vault Hunter mode that's going to be if you don't have the season pass $5 for 400 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also the Psycho pack is $9.99 or 800 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's coming in May at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: and, uh, last piece of DLC, I guess, is coming out in June.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's gonna be part of the campaign.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm laughing because I just got a text from Bobby Blackwolf saying, I'm driving recklessly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yell at Bobby DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yell at him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eh!
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my new word, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, we haven't done anything worthy of cancellation tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: in this half of the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dust and Elysian Tales coming to Steam.
[SPEAKER_05]: And no word on when, but it is coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to be, I guess, not going to be doing a whole lot different than the other versions.
[SPEAKER_05]: but at least it'll look nice if I didn't see them and then the thing I want to know is anyone going to fucking buy this game because I kind of want to buy this game but I want people to play with and you know no one answered me on Twitter so fuck them I'm sure that they had you know more important things to do wait I think that was actually before PAX so fuck you guys for not responding back in the first place and I bet if you ask on Tumblr you'll just get a bunch of likes and no answers
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so, but yes, Duke Nukem 3D has come out on Steam as part of this Megaton edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's basically Duke Nukem, kind of remastered, with all the, basically, you know, I knew that they had expansion packs, but I never knew anything was actually kind of official.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was just kind of this third, like a company making like a skin or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I always thought it was a bunch of homegrown stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, but I have the actual Duke Nukem 3D Mega Edition CD-ROM.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't just use that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to get the Steam version so I can play through Steam, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bitches.
[SPEAKER_08]: How much is it?
$10.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I may have to do this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm tempted.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Duke Nukem 3D, the Atomic Edition, so you got your four campaigns right there, plus the three bundled expansions, Duke's Caribbean, Life is a Beach, Duke, Nuclear Winter, and Duke It Out in D.C.,
[SPEAKER_05]: And I guess, you know, the PC and Mac and they're the OpenGL versions of the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Duke Nukem's in our chat right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, hail to the king, baby.
[SPEAKER_08]: Saying, I used to have the Kiloton collection.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was official, I believe.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the one we have.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, Alan has it and I just stole it.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't have it right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: No...
[SPEAKER_02]: Instant gratification.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want... Here's what I want as part of Steamworks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want custom map supports because, man, I used to make Duke Nukem maps all day long, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was... I had one...
[SPEAKER_05]: I love this story.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had one where it was basically a water park or a water slide.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was just the moving water and you would kind of go along with it and move really fast.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there was a drop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you take no fall damage, you fall in water.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the drop was done with holding Paige down.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would lower the floor.
[SPEAKER_05]: I put a paperweight on Paige down and went and had lunch.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I came back later on.
[SPEAKER_05]: That drop was five minutes long.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Superfast Elevator Superfast Elevator
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't catch everything that's supposed to be in this game, but apparently one of the things they're adding are units from XCOM squads, which is a little silly, but okay, it can work.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to be paratroopers who drop in 40 units away as opposed to 9 units away, so alright, I can kind of see where they're doing that.
[SPEAKER_08]: but I kind of missed what else was supposed to be big about this expansion damn and there's not even the video of the XCOM units there anymore but alright if it's a Civ 5 expansion I'm gonna get it anyway I will buy that just as fast as Dark Tetsuya will be buying this next game it's La Mulana which has a launch date now for Steam it's April 15th just in time file your taxes and then play an even greater enemy in La Mulana or someone can get it for me for my birthday
[SPEAKER_08]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is the version that's based on the WiiWare game, which took forever to come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the Steam version will have the WiiWare DLC Hell Temple, because you know the game wasn't hard enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can plug in a USB controller like your Xbox 360 controller and controller away.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting comment this week from some of the folks behind Super Meat Boy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tommy Refens talking about DRM in the wake of all the SimCity hubble-blue going on, saying that basically DRM is how developers shoot themselves in the foot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Quote,
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_08]: A company will spend massive amounts of money on DRM and the internet will break it in a matter of days in most cases When the DRM is broken, is it worth the money spent to implement it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did the week of unbroken DRM for your game gain you any sales from potential pirates due to the inability to pirate at launch?
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, there's no way of telling and as such cannot be used as an accurate justification for spending money
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, hold on though, as much as you want to go, yeah, DRM sucks, and I do think overdoing DRM is pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Steam DRM doesn't annoy me, but some of these DRMs that we've heard about in the past where you get knocked offline and so forth, that stuff annoys me.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the SimCity stuff, for me, that was really never an issue with the DRM.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't really care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just the fact that you had to play SimCity through Origin, I knew it was going to be bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: But some folks are playing it and enjoying it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: More power to you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm having fun with my games.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have fun with yours.
[SPEAKER_08]: But here's the thing about this whole comment.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did the week of unbroken DRM for your game gain you any sales from potential pirates?
[SPEAKER_08]: See, I would argue maybe because the most critical time for new game sales is that first week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, if a copy protection or whatever scheme can hold things off for a week, then yeah, actually it might be worth it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But at what price?
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's the problem I have is that when that DRM starts to step on the toes of the legitimate player, that's when I have a problem with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when you have a game like SimCity where the DRM is really bad as far as like the launch week was all messed up, you may have people that are just like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just not going to pirate that game because I don't want to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Walking Dead Intro Video
[SPEAKER_05]: I kid you not, and you can even see this in the reviews.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I saw the video.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: The mouse is still there, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: The mouse pointer.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on, that just says... I'm bragging about how little effort I put into this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what that says.
[SPEAKER_08]: and it's so sad that there's like there's bad Walking Dead and there's good Walking Dead like really good Walking Dead and the bad Walking Dead people bought a lot I'm sure a lot of people bought a lot of because or you know stores brought in copies of because the last one did really well and they're like not knowing that the two have nothing in common except that they're based loosely on the same thing even though the good ones from the comics and the bad ones from the TV show right that's unfortunate
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says everyone should play The Walking Dead, the Telltale game, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dungeon Buster speaking about SimCity in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says it has other issues outside of the always online thing let's watch the broken traffic go in circles I find the whole limited space extremely limited space for the city kind of interesting now granted the old SimCity games had that too but the fact that people have broken it so that you can go outside those lines is really curious to me but again I'm
[SPEAKER_08]: I had no interest in SimCity before I really don't now let's move on
[SPEAKER_17]: I like a nap in SimCity.
[SPEAKER_17]: That sounds better.
[SPEAKER_08]: No nap.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is supposedly rapid fire news that's been going on for 20 minutes now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of The Walking Dead, by the way, it's supposed to be coming out on Vita, the Telltale version that is, as in the good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can play it on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't know when, or if it's even going to be episodic or if it's going to be all at once, but it'll be there.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I also picked up DLC Quest.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot to mention.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't play it, but I picked it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was like three bucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to get that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Incredibly short.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: About an hour worth of your time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, for three bucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Three bucks, that's not a waste.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot worse things I could spend.
[SPEAKER_08]: for an hour of my time.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's also Runner 2, Future Legend of the Rhythm Alien, Super Hexagon, Proteus, Retro City Rampage, and VVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVVV
[SPEAKER_02]: but To The Moon though, I am in love with that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm playing it very slowly on purpose.
[SPEAKER_08]: To The Moon, Jamie!
[SPEAKER_08]: To The Moon!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm basically playing a level a week so that I can sort of draw out the game because it's really, I really think it's adorable.
[SPEAKER_05]: As I mentioned, Gary's mine for three bucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Diablo 3 is supposed to be on consoles, but not necessarily exclusive to the PlayStation 3 or PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has been confirmed for both, but they're not saying that that's the only place it's going to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you imagine if they brought it to the Vita?
[SPEAKER_08]: That'd be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Leaving the door open, though, for the Xbox 360 and the Wii U. I could see the Wii U. I want Unicorns and Ponies edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's nothing but that map.
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to go to Whimsyville or whatever it's called.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they need to have the Whimsyville edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's nothing but Whimsyville Quest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whimsyville's kind of hard, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't it Whimsy Shire?
[SPEAKER_05]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ponies and Unicorns and Fairies and Rainbows and Barf.
[SPEAKER_08]: Specific, specific, specifics.
[SPEAKER_08]: Catastrophic Moggy in our chatroom wants to know, are you excited for the To the Moon sequel?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_08]: Called To the Venus.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I just made that up.
[SPEAKER_02]: To the butt.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I will be excited when I finish To the Moon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, that does it for Rapid Fire News tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's go to our Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We ask a question on Facebook and a question on Google.
[SPEAKER_08]: We collect your responses.
[SPEAKER_08]: You slam Facebook and Google together, you get Google.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this week, you guys, not a serious question.
[SPEAKER_08]: We decided to have a little fun with it this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the spirit of PAX East and our upcoming 500th episode, a lot of you have joked in the past that you'd like to see a VOGCon or some type of IRL event.
[SPEAKER_08]: What would a VOGCon or your dream convention consist of?
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're talking about people's dream conventions.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gamer Girl on Facebook starting us off saying, I think it would consist of DDR event in-house, whoever's it would be at, pizza, Mass Effect, and Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's just a Friday night at Jamie's.
[SPEAKER_08]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, that literally is a Friday night at my house because that's exactly what I was doing.
[SPEAKER_08]: VOGCon has suddenly become slumber party at Jamie's.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Haseo Tsuburagawa says, VOGCon should have Loki in the Tingle costume.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get over it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you really wanted it to happen, Eye of Judgment would have worked.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just didn't, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You should actually... I should have made that same... You just should wear your Sackboy outfit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I should have made that same bet with, you know, the freaking Wonderbook, because that thing flopped almost faster than... You should have made the same bet with the Wii U. Oh!
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: That did still mill in copies, so... Oh, it did?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, then, yes, you should have made the same bet with me.
[SPEAKER_05]: In January, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: AZHP responds and says, as someone who goes to conventions, don't we all go to conventions at some point?
[SPEAKER_08]: As someone who goes to conventions, I don't really care what actually happens at the event as long as there are cool people to hang out with, which basically means that a VOGCon would automatically be the second best convention ever behind Fanime.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's be honest, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: James S replies and says, all I know is if Dan and DarkSakura are in the same building, they're not allowed to fight or bicker at one another at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Love you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkTetsuya said I think each show on the network should be represented with a different event like for us I'm assuming meaning OLR it would have to be either a classic game or a music game competition celebrating both our roots and video games roots in general I think we'd have to do the music game and let Bobby have the classic game I can't remember his tagline off the top of my head but he talks about gaming's history and all that
[SPEAKER_08]: Fabrice A replies and says, Dan should host a DDR tournament called Dan's Central.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what Dan's reply to that would be?
[SPEAKER_08]: Dan's Central.
[SPEAKER_08]: He'd make his gorilla face and go, really?
[SPEAKER_08]: That got a like from Tiara, essentially.
[SPEAKER_08]: She replied and said seconded, essentially.
[SPEAKER_16]: She would.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ossifer has an answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_08]: A VOG con would consist of different gingerbread treats and fuzzy red teddy bears named Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your sexy gingerbread legs.
[SPEAKER_08]: The rave would only play disco disco and main dinner entrees would always be garnished with oranges.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: VOG themed alcoholic drinks.
[SPEAKER_08]: A gingerbread legs martini sounds nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some cinnamon rum and butterscotch schnapps.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hanging with the people that I listen to so much and finally, in other words, putting faces to the people that I love listening to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, and of course, DDR, Pinkberry, because I've never had it, Loki in a Tingle costume, and most of all, and I repeat this, everyone that makes VOG a network meshing together and having a great time, because in the end, that's what matters most.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then you follow that up with, oh, and Taco Cabana for Shane, which Shane liked.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, I like Codeman.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who doesn't like tacos?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to give a like for tacos as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like Codeman.
[SPEAKER_02]: Codeman's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're supposed to play Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've been supposedly playing Mass Effect 3 online for like two weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: My next LOL effect picture is going to involve tacos.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everything should involve tacos.
[SPEAKER_08]: In this case, it'll be indigestion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Daniel N replies and says, if I can see the OLR cast and Bobby get back on a DDR pad, and Bobby is in caps, get back on a DDR pad on Heavy as they are now, and a tattoo artist on hand to do Mass Effect art, that would be a good VOGCon.
[SPEAKER_08]: I believe, and I'm sure I'll get a text message in a few minutes here if I'm incorrect, I don't believe Bobby was ever a DDR player.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was way more into Beatmania and all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's actually funny?
[SPEAKER_08]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, since I've been getting on my big fitness kick, we're actually going to be hooking back up the DDR in my house.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would play DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would bring back my alter ego, Dr. Dick, one last time at VOGCon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I liked Mr. Spanky, but you wouldn't cosplay him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember when I did the DDR tour?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you still have the hat?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm too fat to cosplay Mr. Spanky, and if you think these comments from Ossifer are creepy now... Mr. Spanky was bigger than you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw Mr. Spanky, and that was disgusting.
[SPEAKER_16]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, do you still have the hat?
[SPEAKER_02]: That orange fuzzy hat?
[SPEAKER_16]: I might, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I found when I was looking for my art supplies the other day?
[SPEAKER_02]: The orange bat.
[SPEAKER_08]: I still have that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know I have that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nobody else suggesting the location.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, we're in Sacramento, but there's lots of people on VOG, so we'd have to hold it in some type of central location.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, going next to Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_08]: For me, a VOGCon would just simply consist of hanging with all my fellow VOG staffers in the VOG community, playing games, talking or discussing, maybe doing a special show for all the listeners, and doing what friends do, enjoying the moment with each other.
[SPEAKER_08]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_08]: Excuse me, hairball.
[SPEAKER_08]: And lastly, Red Entertainment, Loki in a Tingle costume.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is like three people that said that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got the closest thing, which was a... The Sackboy was pretty epic.
[SPEAKER_05]: An artistic reenactment of what that would look like, and that was it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually read all the answers tonight, but join us on Facebook or Google Plus for future questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll do some more serious ones next time.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I thought that would be a fun question to ask.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's your dream convention?
[SPEAKER_08]: I will say this.
[SPEAKER_08]: VOG may not be having a convention this year, but we're going to be heavily represented at DragonCon this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I would say if you're in that southeast part of the country, or even if you're not, because I'm not, really try to plan on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll be there representing OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Travis will be there representing Under Sedation Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm pretty sure PodCulture usually goes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure they're still figuring it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Critical Myth, I'm positive, will be there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby will be there.
[SPEAKER_08]: British Invaders went last year, so they'll probably go this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only show that probably won't be there, I even think Rama is talking about going.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could be wrong, but he went to Atlanta for something else, so he can go to DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only one that I would know would be Girls Gone Wow, and if we can make that happen, then lordy, we will...
[SPEAKER_08]: Fly one of their asses in from the UK if we could.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, that would be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wouldn't you want to party with Syl?
[SPEAKER_02]: I would love for people to send me a ticket so I can go to DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can get on a bus.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura across America.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get back into some more news about video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Double Fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remember they had that wonderful Kickstarter that kind of brought Kickstarter to the forefront?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Double Fine Adventures now has a name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Broken Age is a point and click adventure game telling the stories of a young boy and girl leading parallel lives.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: Adventure ensues.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the most important part, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hijinks occur.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you didn't back the Kickstarter, you can pre-order the game via the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll have to see when the game comes out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, a lot of people already bought it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be one of the first games to come out that just... Besides maybe, what, Diablo 3, where they just give a million of them away because people already bought them.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow...
[SPEAKER_08]: some updates from Xbox games on demand some reasons why day and date launches don't always make it to games on demand you know there's a big push to try and get games delivered digitally at the exact same time they show up in stores because you know the convenience of downloading them and needing to have that game right now really goes a long way in selling them I know a lot of people bought Luigi's Mansion digitally because it came out right at midnight and a lot of people were like I can't even wait the six hours to get to the store or I guess it's more than six but you know what I mean
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, Eric Jaeger, the senior business manager of Xbox Games On Demand This is why titles don't launch day and date alongside retail releases Quote, we have a lot of strong partnerships with retailers We really need them to do a lot for us They're the ones out there selling the consoles, selling the peripherals And in this time, we're trying to figure out how to fit that into the whole digital landscape shift We're just taking a bit of measured pace with it So very interesting
[SPEAKER_08]: Sort of kind of the converse of what you're seeing with Nintendo That they're actually purposefully giving a little breathing room to the retailers Which is ironic considering those rumors that gained yet again more steam this week We didn't put it on the show roll tonight because it's the same fucking rumor we've heard for a couple months But more stuff out there apparently indicating that Xbox, the new one, will always be online I don't think it's actually going to be online only
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: It's incredibly risky to do that because if they're the only company doing that, remember, they have shareholders to answer to and they can't necessarily just go do this thing where, hey, we're going to go ahead and cut out all of the retail marketplace.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to sell games digitally only or we're going to basically prevent you from selling your game used and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's what they basically said.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is coming from some screenshots of the software development kit on VGLeaks.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And basically they said... I'm trying to find this exact...
[SPEAKER_05]: Durango will implement different power states so it can be powered on.
[SPEAKER_05]: It will draw minimal electricity, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of like the PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says, with this always-on, always-connected design.
[SPEAKER_05]: But see, that's where everyone's like, oh, always-on, always-connected.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said the console will be ready instantly when users want to play and will maintain a network connection so that the console software and games are always current.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that always on, always connected means that it's going to have a standby and it's going to download those updates for your games and system updates when it's in standby so you don't have to fucking wait for an update to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: That makes more sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I mean, this was the same marketing spiel behind WeConnect24, even though obviously that didn't do the system updates and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, the way that reads is an awful lot like they pitched WeConnect24.
[SPEAKER_05]: But see, all these blogging sites and some of these guys that are trying to get these...
[SPEAKER_05]: Headlines, and trust me, I bought into it too until I finally read it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Always on, always connected.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got to always be connected to the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I think if you want to use this feature where your console updates itself in standby so you don't have to wait for these updates and doesn't have to reset and stuff, that's what they mean by this.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a feature so that, because no one fucking likes waiting for these updates to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're trying to play a game and, oh, I got to wait five minutes for this shit to download.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, in the meantime.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: and that there's a statement going out that basically, and I really liked this statement here that's by the creative director for Remember Me, Jean-Maxime Morris, said, if you think that, there's no way this medium's going to mature.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's really a lot of misogyny we need to...
[SPEAKER_08]: Those stats they put out for that Mass Effect 3 panel were pretty eye-opening, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Only 18% of players beat it with Female Shepard.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that is, if you'll notice, the loudest part of the fandom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that 18%.
[SPEAKER_02]: And honestly, I chalk that up to bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kaden is a squad mate less than 2% of the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I couldn't believe that.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's because he was a whiny bitch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: So are you, but you've been on 100% of these shows.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I've been on more like 95%.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still.
[SPEAKER_02]: but the other thing too is that they almost didn't make Tali playable in Mass Effect 3 which would have been a shame basically enough people were passionate about it that they made her playable but I guess it might have to be why she wasn't even available until like halfway through the game but
[SPEAKER_02]: And I mean, I've been running across people who say, oh, she's so irritating.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's so annoying.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, hell, she was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though she's not like a very strong squad mate.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember reading some story and I don't know if there's something you'd put on Tumblr or where, but that a lot of characters weren't playable in Mass Effect 2 because they didn't want you to get them killed before 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, that was it, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were saying because they were part of, I guess, something that they had had in mind for three.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's why they didn't have them playable.
[SPEAKER_02]: But still, I think that everybody should have been playable for the last one.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of stuff that could have gone better about Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: TigerClaw in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says, Some of those PAX East panels weren't broadcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope they post them online like the Bioware one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd love to see that, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we'll get to the mailbag shortly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or no, do we get any emails this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, just the one that was just more for direction.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are we reading it or no?
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I checked.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's nothing else.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, shame on all of you guys for not emailing us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, how dare you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we still have some news stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, Cabstropic Moggy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like Tally as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we still have some news stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a partnership that was announced by Sony and Unity.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, the Unity engine will now have ways to port games to the PlayStation platforms, including PlayStation 4, PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Vita, and Playstation Mobile and using these I guess it'll be easier to take advantage of different system stuff like the cameras and the touchpads and that kind of stuff, Playstation Network and they say also because of that it'll allow people to port titles easier to iOS and Android as well and I guess there's already some games that have used this including Might and Delight's Pid and Fun Bits Escape Plan
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I saw Funbit's escape plan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that was the build of that game?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that was the launch title.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pid and Funbit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Pid?
[SPEAKER_05]: What's Pid?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no idea what PID is but yeah, escape plan looked kind of cool so cool and I know a lot of people use Unity for all sorts of things so porting games will be easier and it sounds like they kind of are embracing indie development a little bit better I think they're finding out that hey, these indie titles that we're bringing over to the Vita and stuff seem to be doing well for us let's get them more involved with other consoles making it easier to get your game on there so I like that
[SPEAKER_08]: Is this something that will be for PlayStation 3 and 4?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's all stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: 3, 4, Vita, and mobile.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, with a new console coming out this year, it seems like there's so much still on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's kind of hard to sell your next console when there's all this stuff coming to your current console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you guys remember Street Fighter X Tekken, you know, and it was okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it was as good as a lot of people were hoping it would be.
[SPEAKER_08]: On disc, DLC.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's one of the things that will be remembered for forever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember, Street Fighter X Tekken wasn't the only game that was supposed to happen there.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was supposed to be another game, Tekken X Street Fighter, which was Namco's version of the game, basically, as more of a Tekken-style fighter.
[SPEAKER_08]: No news on that in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: But producer Katsuhiro Harada, responding to a fan on Twitter, said, quote,
[SPEAKER_08]: that's why we don't say anything so a lot of people are speculating that based on that message oh they're going to move it up to PlayStation 4 and the new Xbox as opposed to the current gen which would make a lot of sense it would also kind of give them a chance to really reinvent some things and hopefully make people forget about the fact that they didn't care for Street Fighter X Tekken so can't really see how this is bad news except the fact that it's going to be a little while longer before this game comes out
[SPEAKER_08]: Dark Sakura, any interest?
[SPEAKER_08]: I know you're a fighting girl fan.
[SPEAKER_08]: You are a fighting game girl fan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you excited about Tekken Cross Street Fighter?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm reserving judgment.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to get it right away.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unless that trailer comes out and you're like, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, Jin.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh my god, Ryu.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like even this little teaser image.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ryu looks great.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like him kind of Tekken style.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I've, you know, I even have to say that I've always been a fan of the Street Fighter characters done in the style of another game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, remember SNK?
[SPEAKER_02]: I loved their renditions of the Street Fighter characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not on the show roll tonight, but I want to say I heard that CVS2 is supposed to be coming out for PlayStation Classics or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can get it on PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would sort of be a big why for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I've already got it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would like to see it re-released so you could do like online battles would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: For matching service.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need more games that say for matching service in the title.
[SPEAKER_08]: We do need.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I've actually got the Vampire Savior for matching service that I forgot completely that we actually owned that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I might sell it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you ever read Gamer Girl's comment in chat here, Loki, about PID?
[SPEAKER_08]: PID is a side-scroller in which you play a little boy who gets lost and gets put on a planet and has to find his way home.
[SPEAKER_08]: And she gives you a link there to PID.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tigerclaw, following up with the Mass Effect information from earlier, saying, There was some mention about the Mass Effect movie during that panel, but nothing like when it's coming out, because I don't think they've even started it.
[SPEAKER_08]: They haven't even started it yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd probably see it out of morbid fascination, but I just wouldn't... For me, I am so deeply entrenched into the game playing as a female Shepard that to think of playing it as a guy is inconceivable to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really hope somebody puts their foot down and makes it a femme Shep.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can support that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I seriously do.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it would be a great character, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I also kind of want them to really fuck with the fandom and do something really atrocious in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like do a decision that like can't even happen in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like have Kayden and Ashley survive Vermeier or like something that just totally like makes fan boys and fan girls just like, what are you doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: I really want that to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want DarkSakura to twitch nervously when she's watching Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, I wouldn't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want Garrus to die.
[SPEAKER_02]: No!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my God, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't believe you'd say something so horrible.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to leave right now to get my soda.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is the part where we would do the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you didn't email us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com Maybe you should do that for next time.
[SPEAKER_08]: So instead, we'll go right into the FUs of the week, even though this is really not a good time to be doing that, but it is what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, my, um, I have two FUs really.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of them is to my iPad for not supporting Java so that I can sign up for something that Rob's going to be talking about later.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, um, my other one goes to this stupid, um, bitch face that, okay, I actually have another one than that.
[SPEAKER_02]: To, um, bitch face number one who was in the car in front of me and one of those homeless guy panhandlers was outside and
[SPEAKER_02]: and she turned on her windshield wipers for the entire period of time that we were at the light and started flinging water at him.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was clearly on purpose because her car was not dirty.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could see all the way through her windshield and back windshield.
[SPEAKER_02]: She just did it to be a bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I gave him 50 cents and said I apologize on behalf of humanity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really, but I did give him money.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then to my former boss bitch face.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care if you fuck with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't fuck with my friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I guess I have to use the fact that my coworker's gone, so I got no one to talk to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck my hand for being weak.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: I opened a bottle for DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm strong.
[SPEAKER_18]: All the pressure builds up inside.
[SPEAKER_18]: And fuck the Mass Effect movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to the freaking wild turkeys in this neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're all assholes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, one of them literally flew right in front of my car today with a death wish, wanting me to hit it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I have to slam on the brakes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank God there wasn't a car behind me or I probably would have been in an accident.
[SPEAKER_08]: I probably would have gotten whiplash thanks to this stupid fucking turkey that lives near here.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, F you to the turkeys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why are you so stupid, turkeys?
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell me!
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you know that actually turkeys were rated as one of the most stupid animals to live?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, thank God we eat so many of them once a year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't eat the wild turkeys in this neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows what the fuck they've been eating.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: They probably taste like radiation.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, that does it for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: A couple more news stories for you guys and then the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: But first, a couple stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, apparently there has been some research into video games and their effects on kids with dyslexia and actually allowing them to be able to read.
[SPEAKER_05]: and this is kind of cool they did a study basically where they had 20 kids 20 dyslexic children playing Rayman's Raving Rabbids which is crazy as it is for a total of 12 hours over 9 days and of course the game has a ton of crazy mini games and that kind of fun stuff and basically
[SPEAKER_05]: Before and after the nine days of game playing, the researchers tested the kids on several different tasks, including reading speed and accuracy, word recognition, and their ability to pay attention to multiple types of input, sight and sound at once.
[SPEAKER_05]: Before playing the games, the two groups were...
[SPEAKER_05]: Both equivalent in these tasks, but after 12 hours of the games, the kids that played the minigames showed significant improvements in their ability to read.
[SPEAKER_05]: They read faster, more accurately, and they recognized more words than they had before the treatment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Meanwhile, the children that had played non-active minigames didn't do any better on the tasks.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's a great story with all the crap that video games get sometimes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm glad to hear something where it's bona fide showing that it's helping in a particular scenario here.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, helping children with this.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's almost like all those years spent telling mom it improves my hand-eye coordination.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like now there's the science to back it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: but the science has always been there I mean for the sake of reading and this is something actually we learn in typography the human brain will read lowercase letters better than it will read anything that's all caps a good reader reads the shape of the words not the individual letters so doing something that's going to improve time cognition for getting instinctive action over slow and methodical picking it out would definitely I think improve that skill when it comes to actually reading a shape of a word
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, that's really funny because when I was studying broadcast journalism, whenever you look at scripts for TV shows and stuff or the teleprompters, everything's always written in caps.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's not, you know, everybody makes that joke like, why are you yelling though?
[SPEAKER_08]: But they actually say it's to make you slow down.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why they write scripts like that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it's the opposite of what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll say one more thing on the subject.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were doing a study of different types of readers, you know, basically really slow, really low-level readers and then higher-level readers.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they timed blink rates and pause rates for when people were reading.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the slower readers would blink and pause more often, usually in the middle of a word as opposed to at the end of sections of words.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Ragnarok Online 2 Legend of the Second Music done by Yoko Kanno
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently this game is now finally almost here.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's supposed to be in open beta in mid-April.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pre-registration is available.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can also check it out on the Facebook page.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to check out this little trailer here in studio.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it goes anything like the last Ragnarok Online, it's going to be in beta for seven years.
[SPEAKER_08]: Most likely.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to look at, is there any actual gameplay in this video or is it just a bunch of freaking like cut scenes?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but there's YouTube video from the alpha.
[SPEAKER_08]: Will I get to fight, what were they called, Prinnies?
[SPEAKER_08]: The little slime people?
[SPEAKER_08]: Pourings.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Prinnies are the dudes from Disgaea.
[SPEAKER_08]: What am I thinking?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, the outfits look so awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, how long did I play Ragnarok online, Rob?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: How long until they banned you?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, they didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually played... Let's put it this way.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I go back and play the International Ragnarok Online right now, I can get all of my characters back and all of my old stuff because I was in the alpha.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you're a super nerd and you have a badge to prove it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I sure do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, let us know if you're able to get in the beta for Ragnarok Online 2 and don't get banned.
[SPEAKER_16]: I've never been banned!
[SPEAKER_08]: You're banned from this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get out.
[SPEAKER_16]: I used to be friends with some of the GMs.
[SPEAKER_16]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are at the end of our news, so we're going to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm hoping we're going to hear from some people.
[SPEAKER_08]: that went to PAX East tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to open up the phones and see what happens.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR is the toll-free number you can use to call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio, all one word.
[SPEAKER_08]: But remember, if you do call us on Skype, you want to call Echo123 first just to test your connection.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, oh, phone's already lighting up.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got a call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm driving recklessly, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, stupid kids.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, about the people cutting through his yard?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: All these kids.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the kids that decided once I locked it that they needed to teach me a lesson by tearing it down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck them.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then didn't you get it all fixed and then like a little mini tornado took it out anyway or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: They took one of the other signs.
[SPEAKER_06]: The mini tornado took my 99 cent no trespassing sign.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Legend of Zaku
[SPEAKER_10]: Legend of Zaku
[SPEAKER_06]: And he's just, he's basically saying, yeah, I'm just chill because I have to work the next morning and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: But like Friday night, he's like, you know, bouncing off the walls and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I just wanted to give that little insight to OLR that, you know, yeah, he's like, No, he actually does have a personality and it's a good one.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you got to meet a lot of people, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100Matt was there, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: I met SSJ100Matt a couple times.
[SPEAKER_06]: I met John from Critical Myth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Met up with him.
[SPEAKER_06]: Met up with Ranma and a bunch of people from the cosplay group that he's in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anime Jam Session.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got to meet Misty.
[SPEAKER_06]: And HitStun found us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: And met some other people from the community.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a good time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't get to see Havoc978.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't go to the Bring Your Own Computer area all that often, so that's kind of where he hangs out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But just comparing PAX East to PAX Prime, I can see why they're saying that PAX East is the real PAX.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just because that convention center is huge.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if the one you went to was in this convention center.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I went to the very first one that was at that other convention center downtown that I don't think they have it at anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the same one that Anime Boston, I think, is at.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think so, yeah, it's the Boston Convention Center, which is, like, really close to the airport, which is great, because I'm so used to, like, in Los Angeles and Seattle, it's, like, a 40-minute cab ride to get from the airport to the convention center.
[SPEAKER_06]: In this one, it's, like, you know, 10 bucks, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had that nice limo ride.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're rock stars.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're taking a limo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, when we did the DDR Freak moderator trip, they sprung for us to get limos from the... Must be nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was fun in Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't you get to ride the limos for the Windows 7, the Microsoft Windows thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: That was after that PAX.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, that was at E3, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that video we made that never got put on the internet, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they stopped at the one that me and Glenn did.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the one they stopped at.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're like, we can send you the raw assets if you want to cut something together.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, no, that's not why we did it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the thing that's kind of funny is because I did a podcast with the Boston Bastard Brigade and Electric Sisterhood and there was a whole bunch of other podcasters and we did a podcast that's going to be coming out this week sometime.
[SPEAKER_06]: We recorded it this morning at 10 a.m.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was actually a lot of fun being in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a roundtable type podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what struck me as interesting, and they had to cut off the end of the podcast because they were losing that room, was that they were treating this a lot like E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: and they're like what do you think of PAX what games did you play on the show floor and I couldn't get in that I'm like I think they missed the point of PAX I mean the show floor is a big part of it but PAX is so much bigger than that and you know some of the stuff that I saw at PAX that really blew me away was not on the show floor I walked in and this just you know hit my nostalgia bone two things hit my nostalgia bone I walked into one room it's really dark
[SPEAKER_06]: and all it had in there, and I'm not kidding, 16 fully functional Steel Battalions.
[SPEAKER_08]: That sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eight of them were system link with the multiplayer game and then they had four playing the single player.
[SPEAKER_17]: That sounds like my house except I have two.
[SPEAKER_06]: 16 all fully functional and they had the one one enforcer who knew everything about the game and he was you know yelling at people kind of like military style and you know giving them you know kind of like the old kind of like the spiel that you would get from like mech core if you're doing the battle tech pods and stuff so that was really neat and then they had the classic console room and they actually did in the corner have like a Commodore 64 awesome with a five and a quarter inch disk drive
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: and that's what sets PAX apart from E3 even though if you listen to most podcasts they're going to concentrate on the E3 aspects of PAX.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nino Cooney Capcom
[SPEAKER_06]: Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate, the worst demo I've ever played.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ni No Kuni is no longer the worst demo I've ever played.
[SPEAKER_08]: You were probably still on the plane when we were doing Gaming Week, but I actually mentioned you and that whole thing in Gaming Week because I hated the demo as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I have friends that love Monster Hunter, and I'm like, I wouldn't know that from this demo.
[SPEAKER_06]: and so, yeah, I think I landed and you were on the classic game of the week when I got in my car from the airport.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, I'll catch the podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I learned, okay, they're doing DuckTales and I'm like, they can't mess this up.
[SPEAKER_06]: How can Capcom mess this up?
[SPEAKER_06]: I just, you can't, I mean, it was perfect and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want to know how Capcom messed this up?
[SPEAKER_06]: They let the Pink Palace developers do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's how they messed it up at PAX.
[SPEAKER_06]: How?
[SPEAKER_06]: There was only one copy of the game in the entire city of Boston.
[SPEAKER_06]: One copy on one single kiosk.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a seven minute demo.
[SPEAKER_06]: The line went around the corner of the booth and they had to cap it because it was already four hours long.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: And so I was up there, and I asked the lady from Capcom, and I'm like, so why do you only have one kiosk of that?
[SPEAKER_06]: And she shot me this look.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, oh my god, I wish you had not asked that question.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is like an hour after they had unveiled that side of the booth.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was covered up until the panel.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so in order to save her, I was like, is that the million dollar question?
[SPEAKER_06]: She's like, that's the five million dollar question.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they knew.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think when everybody started singing in that panel, I think they realized they messed up only bringing one copy of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's because it's running on dev kits and they only have minimum amounts of dev kits.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's exactly my thought because remember, GDC is happening literally, what, tomorrow or Tuesday?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it starts Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, when GDC starts, all the dev kits are probably in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_08]: They can't be in two places at once.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, Rob, Passover starts tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_06]: But what they could have done is since nobody's touching that stupid Dungeons & Dragons game, make that DuckTales.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not stupid!
[SPEAKER_06]: Put on the last stage, you know, cover up the Dungeons & Dragons with like a really, you know, crude notebook paper and, you know, Sharpie saying DuckTales.
[SPEAKER_06]: and just do that and then that four hour wait would have been a two hour wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then you get the one dude come by, where's Dungeons and Dragons?
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard there was a Dungeons and Dragons game, I want to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, okay, the Dungeons and Dragons game is awesome and I probably would have played that if everyone else was over at DuckTales.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you could have walked right up to play that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: but then there's the long line of everybody trying to watch DuckTales and what does it say about I don't know if this is a good thing or a bad thing so this is an open question what does this say about PAX in terms of game announcements considering this was not the only game announced there that the most excited people got over an announcement at PAX was a remake of an NES game
[SPEAKER_08]: IndieCulture
[SPEAKER_06]: Indie Games All these crazy ideas I actually played on an Ouya
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my gosh, they exist.
[SPEAKER_06]: It exists.
[SPEAKER_06]: The controller is terrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's unresponsive, but I actually played a game that actually makes use of that touchpad in a way that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, in the same touchpad that's going to be on the PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game I played there is a Saturday morning RPG.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an 8-bit kind of turn-based RPG, but with a lot of like, you know, like some of the minigames in there, you're playing Simon and...
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's about, like, basically Saturday morning cartoons are this kid's real life.
[SPEAKER_06]: But right before each battle, you scratch off stickers.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's what you use the touchpad for.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: You act like you're scratching off a sticker.
[SPEAKER_07]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, it was a neat game, and it's actually a launch title for the Ouya.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I played that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the buttons on the Ouya controller, it's O-U-Y-A.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so it's like, press O to do this.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I press what winds up being the A button on the controller because that's the circle button on the PlayStation controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to take some getting used to.
[SPEAKER_06]: And even the developer said, I don't like the button placement.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't like the way they did that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should have been some kind of standard or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I did play that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there were some other neat things that I saw that I wasn't able to get interviews with.
[SPEAKER_06]: For the hardcore of the hardcore, I'm talking like, I don't know if Dungeon Buster's in chat because this is up his alley.
[SPEAKER_08]: He is in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, he is in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dungeon Busters, this is straight up your alley.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game's called Artemis.
[SPEAKER_06]: and this is a spacecraft simulator in the sense like the old Star Trek so imagine the Enterprise except it's multiplayer across PC, iPad, iPhone I think even Android and you are basically a crew member and so what they had set up they had them on laptops there and they had five stations you have your captain, your science officer your engineering officer, your navigation and your weapons guy
[SPEAKER_06]: and you're all cross-talking.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have your screen and the way they had it set up there is you had your screen that had like a radar and things you could do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then they had a main screen that actually had the 3D render of what it was doing and they were all talking to each other.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, turn the ship to 160 degrees.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get close.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, comm officer, request docking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Comm officer will say, okay, we've got permission to dock and then the navigation perk guy would actually dock with the station and then battle stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: They would look at, okay, when do I turn on the shields?
[SPEAKER_06]: and the captain would start yelling out orders and it's this social game where basically all of you are working together to fly the spaceship have space battles and I guess deliver cargo and stuff it was amazingly interesting I didn't get a chance to play it because it was a 20 minute demo so it was kind of hard to get in on it but that's actually out now and here's the thing about Artemis is that they don't like DRM
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: and they don't check for this so this is honor system but then you can send the game to five of your buddies as long as they're all flying on your ship so only one person has to buy the game for five people to fly the ship and play the game that's pretty cool it's kind of like a DS title where like everybody can download from the one person I don't know kind of it's kind of what I'm thinking of when you say that that's really cool so that was one of the games that I saw another game that a lot of people were probably talking about I don't know if you ever heard of this game called dive kick
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the most complex fighting game ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's coming out for PlayStation 3 and Vita and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: The way they had it there was that they actually had an arcade style controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are two buttons.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dive and kick.
[SPEAKER_06]: You select your character and there were five characters in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of them is kind of funny because the name of the character was Wolverine.
[SPEAKER_06]: They got a cease and desist letter.
[SPEAKER_06]: The name of that character is now redacted with a strike through it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So basically, in dive kick, it's the standard thing, and you have the little guy go, Okay, ready?
[SPEAKER_06]: Dive kick!
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you can jump with the dive button, and then kick with the kick button.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or if you just hit the kick button, you dive.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's basically, whoever hits the other person first, it's a one-shot kill.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though it shows all these health bars at the stop, but it's a one-hit thing, and you're basically just jumping and diving, and that's all you're doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: and it is the most hilarious, funny fighting game I've ever played.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it sounds like you saw a lot of gems, really, like these little indie gems.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did not see a bad game.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even in the card game, board game section, I did not see a bad game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because there was like, it was, the area was probably just as big as the video game section, but they had the whole tabletop section and the entire perimeter of the tabletop section were vendors and people showing off tabletop games, you know, board games, card games, things like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: and that was in there and that's where I actually played a game that I actually did buy a card game called Flame War which triggered my PTSD of the G4 forums thing because you're playing as a forum moderator trying to create threads, forum threads and then closing them but the way that you attack other players is you flame on their threads and all the cards have internet memes on them
[SPEAKER_06]: and stuff and so I did buy it and you know one of the cards is the Banhammer and so people that were around in the G4 days they actually were selling a shirt of the Banhammer which was basically a hammer that said Ban in it and yes I did buy that shirt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course you have to.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have the Banhammer shirt so anybody that remembers me from the G4 days will appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: and some of the others.
[SPEAKER_08]: Obviously, you say PAX is a lot more than just the expo floor, the community and all that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw some pictures on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like you guys were up very late playing Cards Against Humanity.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, and that was pretty much like... At DragonCon, I'm used to seeing people in a circle playing Are You a Werewolf?
[SPEAKER_06]: And here, everybody was playing Cards Against Humanity.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because they released the third expansion, which sold out on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_06]: but they also had these three Pax East exclusive packs that you could get and if you found them you got them and they were either in the swag bag or if you went to the Kickstarter room you could get it from them and they were handing them out so yeah Cards Against Humanity was huge at Pax a lot of people were playing that everywhere that you looked wow so I think that game took off
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's a Kickstarter success story right there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably street passed with about 11 billion people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I would have street passed with more if I kept at it, but I wound up filling all my pieces and completing Find Me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I now have, I think, over 1,000 street passes total, and that's from all the E3 and all the other stuff that I've done with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm only up to 500, and I thought I had a ton.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you can see I thought I had a ton too, and then I was sitting next to somebody when I went into the rock band panel.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is the only panel I went to, which was the behind the scenes, they named names and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's never going to be broadcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I was sitting there and he had like 2,800.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I remarked on it and he just looked at me and he's like, I'm a cast member at Disney World.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, and so the Rock Band panel was, you're never going to see it broadcast because they actually spent about 10 minutes saying, you know, we could get in so much trouble if you, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're looking right at like the IGN and the Polygon guys in the front row with their laptops out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they kept looking and they're like, don't write this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please don't write this because they actually were naming names.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: And talking about, you know, here's what, here's where we fucked up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pearl Jam Rock Band
[SPEAKER_06]: but they actually showed video of concept video of that and how it was going to be about the Pearl Jam live experience because Pearl Jam is a very active bootlegging culture and live video so they were actually putting it around their and the video in the background was actually going to be video footage from a lot of these concerts iconic Pearl Jam concerts and it just for whatever reason it didn't work out and they then coughed and said Eddie Vedder
[SPEAKER_06]: but then they talked about yes we know you want Mews
[SPEAKER_06]: and they basically kind of explain how Muse something happened and that's why they don't have Muse they actually talked about Pink Floyd and actually how they made concept video of doing dreamscape type of stuff with Pink Floyd tracks the Beatles Pink style stuff and they actually had concept art that they sent off to Pink Floyd and it just didn't ever happen same Led Zeppelin also had a little bit of that they had some stuff like that and then they talked about the Guns N' Roses debacle and this is kind of the highlight of this
[SPEAKER_06]: was where apparently there was a leaked video that came out or a viral video that went out of an unnamed Harmonix employee, which everybody tried to name, saying, hey, we got the entire Guns N' Roses library, Appetite for Destruction, everything, and we're going to do this and this and this and this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dan Rickert Game Informer
[SPEAKER_06]: is the person who actually made that video and made Harmonix's life a living hell for several months.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but I did get to because I do know both Nick Chester and John Drake.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I went up to see both of them during the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I didn't ask them what they were working on because I knew they couldn't tell me about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I asked them, will I think it's cool?
[SPEAKER_06]: And I told them, hey, I've been with you guys since Frequency Days.
[SPEAKER_06]: And John looked at me.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's like, you will find this cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: You will find what we're doing cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're hoping to announce it at E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's like 95% sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: He doesn't want to say anything more than that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I told him, yeah, I was with you in the frequency and amplitude days and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he's like, it's not Rock Band, but considering what I like of Harmonix's past, he says, I will think that what they're coming up with is cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he's very excited about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's all I could get out of him.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well Bobby, it sure sounds like we missed a heck of a show I'm sad, but you know, it is what it is But anything else about PAX East you want to share with us?
[SPEAKER_06]: I got a whole ton of interviews I am going to be probably putting them out on my podcast or some of them on my podcast feed because I don't want to because if I did like one a week every week they would go until like June Tell me more about Saints Row 4 Well I did see Saints Row 4 and I'm going to break this news I told Rob about this because now Deep Silver is handling Saints Row 4 I have a very good relationship with Deep Silver
[SPEAKER_06]: So a THQ never gave me the time of day, but Deep Silver did.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they were showing Saints Row 4 to the press in the hotel that's connected to the convention center instead of having to wait in line.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also that way they weren't bumping people out of the line, bumping attendees.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had press in a different area.
[SPEAKER_06]: and so I went in there and it's the same video the same 10 minute video that they were showing everybody else and they had developers in there and they're like yeah interviews and stuff you know do interviews so I went up to our PR contact her name is Stephanie Shop she is amazing and I went up and Stephanie Shop also if you listen to my show she was responsible for getting the MechWarrior online and the Devolver digital and all those interviews the ones I did kind of in November
[SPEAKER_06]: She was responsible for setting all those up.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I was like, hey, so can I get an interview with one of the Saints Row guys, the developers?
[SPEAKER_06]: And she looked at me and said, no, you can't.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm like, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she's like, because I'd rather you do one of your long-form Skype interviews in a couple weeks with them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ah, nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it would be a five to ten minute quickie interview there, and she's like, I'd rather you do one of your long-form ones with these guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you don't have a date yet though, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: But soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: No date.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, because she's heading off to GDC.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm not bugging her until after GDC.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: But she said she does want to do it in the next couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it could be pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it sounds like you made a lot of great connections at PAX East.
[SPEAKER_08]: You had a really good time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Making us all jealous we didn't go.
[SPEAKER_08]: But hey, there's DragonCon and E3 hopefully.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to have a great time at DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are going to have a great time at DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm seriously looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I probably do have more stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw a lot of other great indie games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some that weren't even on the show floor that I got to see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those interviews are going to be airing throughout the next couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to be getting some review copies of those.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a good time to be a gamer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up with the hate.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of all the stuff, I did not see a single bad game, even looking through all the indie stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did not see a single bad game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Transistor, I think that's the Supergiant games from Bastion.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to know what my game of show is, it's that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: S.J.
[SPEAKER_06]: 100 Matt says his girlfriend agrees with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Transistor's the game of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't the talking sword thing happen in a Mercedes Lackey novel?
[SPEAKER_08]: It actually did.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's distant enough that it's all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Bobby, I know you're going to have plenty to say on the next episode of your show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't imagine there's a person listening to this that doesn't know about your show, but just in case, please plug away.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am the opening band, not the band that you came to see, but I'll only be here for five or six songs and then I'll go away.
[SPEAKER_06]: An hour before OLR, 8 p.m.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eastern, 5 p.m.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pacific on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_06]: Usually it's me doing a monologue for 30 minutes, taking calls from Breakman for another 20 minutes, and then talking to you guys for 10 minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: and that's my show and we've got a lot of great interviews coming up.
[SPEAKER_06]: A game book being put into iPad, an old style 80s game book, Steve Jackson's Sorcery.
[SPEAKER_06]: It plays like an Infocom text adventure as well but looks really great.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to talk to them.
[SPEAKER_06]: An iPad brawler that does not use virtual controls.
[SPEAKER_06]: and it plays more like Fruit Ninja and it actually does work I do get to talk to Phoenix Online Studios with Cognition and the Silver Lining and the next game that they're doing with Jane Jensen I got to talk to Mommy's Best Games about guns, on top of guns and on top of guns Nathan Fouts, he's also been on Fox News a lot recently and we talk about why that happened and what he thinks of that so there's a lot of great content that I've got in my suitcase that is still locked up and sitting in the hallway because I ran in here
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright Bobby, go unpack.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to let you go so we can get a couple more calls.
[SPEAKER_08]: But thanks so much for spending some time with us tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: And remember, if Legend of Zaku calls in and he's all like, that's not him.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really a funny guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's an act.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Bobby Blackwolf Show, calling out the OLR regulars tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, have a good one, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care, bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: The one and only Bobby Blackwolf, everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: We let him go a little long tonight, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm excited to hear from some people that were at PAX East.
[SPEAKER_08]: He always has us on our show, or he always has us on his show, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the least we can do, and he has a lot of great info from the floor.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm hoping we'll get some more PAX East-related calls, like maybe this next one that's coming in right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, it's Legend of Zaku here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, were your ears burning?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because someone was just talking about you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I heard it in the car right over.
[SPEAKER_15]: I heard it right as the car was pulling up to my house.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Zaku, is it all an act?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is this all an act?
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe, but I'm just going to sidebar and focus on the real task at hand, which was PAX East.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well let's talk about the real reason why you called tonight, PAX East.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you were obviously at the show too, because you met Bobby.
[SPEAKER_08]: How was it?
[SPEAKER_15]: I was rooming with him, actually.
[SPEAKER_15]: Were you really?
[SPEAKER_15]: How awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: But then it got shifted when we got into the other hotel.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not going to say as to the reasons why, but...
[SPEAKER_15]: He knows it very well, and we'll leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_15]: But long story short, this PAX, the way I put it, it was average.
[SPEAKER_15]: Last year's PAX, amongst all the swag and the parties, it doesn't hold a candle.
[SPEAKER_15]: Case in point, Curse's PAX East party this year wasn't even open bar.
[SPEAKER_15]: and they oversold it to the point where you only had one free drink and then everything else you had to pay at the cash bar.
[SPEAKER_05]: The economy is really... Sons of bitches closing the open bar?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why I came to this thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what though?
[SPEAKER_08]: Perfectly legit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pax East, not as good because they closed the open bar this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck them.
[SPEAKER_15]: That is true, and then, you know, it was surprising aside from trying my best to play some of these things, given the fact that there were lines just about everywhere.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I only got to play very few things.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was able to get Hawken, you know, play that game.
[SPEAKER_15]: I also tried out the NVIDIA Shield, the new handheld controller device that they have, which is kind of nifty, though, because it's using the latest version of Android.
[SPEAKER_15]: The latest one that you see on a Nexus 4 and the latest tablets, that's exactly the one they're running.
[SPEAKER_15]: It really feels like a top-tier device.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not just bullshitting or anything, I'm just saying it also has touchscreen, but it feels like you're actually playing a recent current-gen console.
[SPEAKER_15]: The graphics are on par.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're like 360 graphics from launch titles.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's gotten to the point where mobile's pretty much at or tailing right now the big boy consoles.
[SPEAKER_08]: You talked about a lot of these lines for games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you wait in any of them?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you stand in that epic line to play DuckTales?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like I was just going around the con, around the expo hall.
[SPEAKER_15]: I did my best to try to score as much free swag as possible, but yeah, it was slim pickings this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're a fan of free stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wouldn't be able to guess from your talk about the curse party.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, okay, what fun nightlife did this PAX East have?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything?
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, I mean, most of the nightlife was either, you know, you went to the local bars near the hotels, which was like the day before the con, which is a pub crawl that basically stayed in one place because it took too long.
[SPEAKER_15]: But other than that, it was just like whatever you had in your room, if you had Cards Against Humanity, you were basically playing not only with your roommates, with your bunkmates, but with random strangers that would just like bring bottles of high-end liquor, like Johnny Walker, like a liter of Johnny Walker for that table.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I was like, we're taking big swigs of it.
[SPEAKER_15]: And as a result, I had to nurse a hangover this morning.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was just about to ask.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to say, you know, your eyes are looking a little bit like you haven't slept in about four days.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, it's like I puked this morning, so yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was going to say you have that sort of prize fighter look about you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I wasn't going to say he got in a fight, but he definitely has that whole, like, I had a hell of a weekend.
[SPEAKER_15]: My face was just crunching up, tightening up because I was lurching over the toilet trying to puke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Were you offering your sacrifices to the porcelain goddess?
[SPEAKER_15]: Porcelain goddess, yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sacrificing my dignity.
[SPEAKER_15]: Aside from the newer games that were out and the fact that they were just like... Aside from the lines and everything else, board games were pretty much another...
[SPEAKER_15]: another huge aspect of it it got to the point where I actually have gotten my girlfriend I know, well for those who probably can't see the camera but that's our weekend Spartacus Spartacus is that based on the TV show?
[SPEAKER_08]: yes how much full frontal is in the board game?
[SPEAKER_08]: how much full frontal is in the board game?
[SPEAKER_15]: none I know my girlfriend would be disappointed yeah
[SPEAKER_15]: That's all she watches it for, full frontal, and then her dad watches along with her for the boobs.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's kind of awkward, but alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I mean, everywhere, like, yeah, board games, like, it got to the point where it was like, at this point it's like, a good third board games, another third indie...
[SPEAKER_15]: or more importantly, probably like a quarter indeed, and then everything else.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm still waiting for Mass Effect Risk.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me ask you one more question, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since you say you weren't as big on PAX East this year as you were last year, what can PAX 2014 learn from this year?
[SPEAKER_08]: How can PAX East 2014 set up to be the most kick-ass one yet, besides open bars?
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: I guess it's the panels that I tried my best to actually go to.
[SPEAKER_15]: This year I did better in the fact that I did like one, two, three, four.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think I did like six panels, one of which I had to duck out because of my hangover.
[SPEAKER_15]: But yeah, it's gotten better.
[SPEAKER_15]: The content has gotten a lot better.
[SPEAKER_15]: Obviously, it still packs up pretty badly.
[SPEAKER_15]: Obviously, the Bioshock panel fills up rather quickly.
[SPEAKER_15]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_15]: But it's just like trying to... I guess they can't please everybody.
[SPEAKER_15]: So the best they could do is stay where they are because their venue is...
[SPEAKER_15]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_15]: The only thing about...
[SPEAKER_15]: The only cool thing about PAX this year was the classic gaming had, well, aside from having the standard setup, like one room dedicated to just classic gaming consoles, they had another one.
[SPEAKER_15]: It had a featured room.
[SPEAKER_15]: And this year's feature was Steel Battalion.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, they had 12 of these.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just playing Steel Battalion is not even fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's just work.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cockpit, start up the Mac's computer, do systems check, ignition.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next time it needs to come with some vodka, it'll be a whole lot better.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zaku, I got to let you go so we can get more calls.
[SPEAKER_08]: But thanks so much for the report.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm glad to hear at least you had a decent enough time so that you were regretting it this morning.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, also they were giving away free Android Bluetooth controllers for Android-owned users.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where's mine?
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Zaku, got to let you go, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Props to Zaku, an OLR gold store.
[SPEAKER_08]: A gold store?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, he can have a whole store.
[SPEAKER_08]: A gold star for Zaku for doing a video call so we can actually see the Spartacus game that he bought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we'll see if anybody else wants to call 1-877-GAME-OLR or I use your name on Skype as Orange Lounge Radio Making us all jealous we weren't there You alright?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just saw something terrifying What's that?
[SPEAKER_08]: A goblin shark That does sound terrifying They have retractable jaws Much less terrifying in this next phone call Hi!
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, what's up?
[SPEAKER_08]: You're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Catastrophic Moggy Nice to meet you I'd never get through You never get through, well you're here now Yay Hold on, the clock on the wall behind you 3.52 in the morning Yes Told you it was going to stay up for us I did say to DarkSakura I would We usually do our chatting when it's 4 in the morning for me And here you are, well what's up?
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to complain about region locking and how I'm so unexcited by the current news about consoles, but I thought, you've already had so much time, I thought I'd bring up something from weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure, go for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: The last, oh, pardon me, sorry, I'm completely fumbling over my words now.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's alright, I do it all the time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, we have to listen to three hours of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_08]: I get to make fun of me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Weeks ago, you were talking, I can't remember what it was about, about your other halves guesting on OLR.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I thought, for either your last episode... Go on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go off, go!
[SPEAKER_01]: For your last episode, you should, um... He's on the internet!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where is it?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's four in the morning.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shh, quiet.
[SPEAKER_01]: For your last episode, you should have, um... Oh, for your E3 special, you should have the other half special with Alan, Dan, and, um... Nellie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nelly, pardon, and with your mum being a guest correspondent.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've talked about them before, and I'm sure Dan and Alan would be down.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would just be about convincing Nelly that it's a really funny idea, but that might be difficult.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nelly would probably punch my husband.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I'd have to be here to see that.
[SPEAKER_01]: You'd have to video it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it would have to be a video thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe the only way I could see that happening is if we promised Nellie it was the last episode of the show ever because she'd be like, yay, Matt can have a life now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, you should do it either for the last episode or for an E3 special.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'd be like we couldn't be bothered to show up, so our spouses do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, we've had a bunch of people calling in to talk about PAX East tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Obviously, you're a little far away, so I'm imagining you didn't make it to PAX East.
[SPEAKER_08]: But what do you think about everything you're hearing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Honestly, I've not heard much news from PAX East.
[SPEAKER_01]: Most of what I've heard is from you.
[SPEAKER_01]: My biggest reaction is I wish DuckTales was coming to PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a policy of not getting digital content on consoles.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can see why.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what though?
[SPEAKER_01]: One time when you can't, it won't transfer over and at least with physical stuff you can trade it in.
[SPEAKER_01]: With digital stuff, he's stuck with it for now.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it does well enough though, if it does well enough, they'll put it on disk.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it's going to be on Xbox though, it shouldn't be that hard to port it to PC.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, I've taken up too much of your time so I'll get off now.
[SPEAKER_08]: No worries.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a pleasure to hear from you and to get to see you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I know you got to shut up because people are trying to sleep.
[SPEAKER_08]: But thank you for breaking all the rules in your household to call us tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm getting shut up tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got someone in trouble.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a great call though.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's true though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I usually, because I'm up around like four in the morning and usually that's right when he's on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we end up chatting like about stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby and Actdeft in our chat room talking a little bit about the DuckTales on PC thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft was convinced it was coming to PC and BlackWolf says his sources say it's a possibility eventually.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not at launch though.
[SPEAKER_05]: After all, Resident Evil 6 I think just or is about to come out on Steam.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sometimes PC's a little bit later so just hold out guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: It might happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, hey, hey, it's Anime Jam Session calling live from the mobile Jersey Mobile.
[SPEAKER_08]: Holy crap, it's all of you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope you're not driving.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I'm driving.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, okay, I was going to say, because if Ranchan had been the one driving, we would have hung up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because you do not talk on your phone and drive.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do it all the time, don't listen to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and you're going to kill somebody, namely a turkey.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm not, no, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, enough of DarkSakura's lecturing.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys are coming back from PAX East.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you have a good time?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I would like to let you know that as Executive Vice Chair of VOGCon East 2013, we went over attendance capacity with the special guest of Cards Against Humanity.
[SPEAKER_04]: We went to a total of 16 guests with special guest stars Johnny Walker Redd.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've had two other callers so far tonight from VOG at PAX East.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're the first one to mention this con.
[SPEAKER_08]: What exactly ended up happening?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_08]: Are we losing them?
[SPEAKER_04]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_04]: We're kind of breaking in and out here.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: What ended up happening at this VOG con?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, JoeVidea did alcohol bingo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zaku went game over because he drank not as much as everybody else.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we did game plus inception equals game-ception.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't say.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, we were playing a dice game.
[SPEAKER_14]: The rules of the game were roll dice, make up rule, drink.
[SPEAKER_14]: Those are the rules of the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Patent pending.
[SPEAKER_04]: The name of the game is called Game.
[SPEAKER_08]: How many minutes were you sober during PAX East?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: More or less, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, what did you guys see on the show floor that kicked ass?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you see anything out there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or even if it wasn't on the show floor, like in a side room or a panel or whatever, what did you see that kicked ass?
[SPEAKER_08]: DuckTales Did you actually wait in that hideous line to play it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hell no!
[SPEAKER_04]: No, DuckTales is one of those games where I will be buying it regardless.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't need a demo to sell you, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will say this, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitch TV was having a giveaway for the DuckTales poster.
[SPEAKER_04]: They wanted people to sing the DuckTales theme.
[SPEAKER_04]: My brother and Jove were there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tried to get Jove to sing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went up there with my bro, and the camera was on us, and after we sang the song, dude in the booth was like, yeah, give the dude with the VOG shirt a poster, because he actually sang the words.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Way to, good job name checking the station, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's always a good thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: We love... Well, we got...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we gotta thank Uk-chan for that because of how big the VOG logo is on our shirts.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I know you guys are on your way home and you gotta get there safe and everything, but since you guys are gonna be talking about this undoubtedly on Anime Jam Session this Tuesday, what do we have to look forward to?
[SPEAKER_04]: A complete review.
[SPEAKER_04]: A whole lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But before we go, a couple of things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another game that's worth picking up is LEGO City Undercover.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, are you a fan of the Shawshank Redemption?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game has a lot of pop culture references, including a scene from the Shawshank Redemption.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of random in a Lego game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a prison break.
[SPEAKER_13]: Basically, you have to go undercover into a prison and talk to one of the characters.
[SPEAKER_13]: The character's name is Blue.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he starts talking like Morgan Freeman.
[SPEAKER_13]: And some of the stuff he says, I was kind of hearing it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm like, why do I know this?
[SPEAKER_13]: And then he said something and I'm like, blue.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm like, oh crap, it's Shawshank!
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_04]: That was bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just as bad as the Nvidia Shield controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, was that on the show floor?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The controls were... The controlling was weak.
[SPEAKER_04]: The outline for doing the directional cross was really bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the demo game was Sonic 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when the song would end, it would pause for a half second and replay the track again.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, yeah, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Lord.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, Bobby was not a big fan of the Ouya controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you get to see that in comparison to the NVIDIA one?
[SPEAKER_03]: I did not know that Ouya was on display.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did not know.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's not enough time to see everything at one pass.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll be getting in like a week.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got to let you go, guys, so we can go wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: But any other last thoughts on PAX?
[SPEAKER_04]: Get your butts out here for 2014 so we can do VOGCon 2014.
[SPEAKER_04]: And unfortunately for ActDeft,
[SPEAKER_04]: since he's a staffer, he does tech.
[SPEAKER_04]: He'll be staffing the con for all three days, so by the time he gets off a shift, all the fun stuff's already happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: Womp womp.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, though, VOGCon 2013 is DragonCon, and you got to Atlanta for one con this year, so I expect you're going to be able to make it twice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, look at it this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I graduate from college, I get those marks, and I land the job,
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be partying our fabulous little asses off Awesome, we can play game Yes!
[SPEAKER_08]: I challenge you to game
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a challenge, that's a fun thing to do!
[SPEAKER_04]: And you had to do it in deep Russian voices.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: It has to be better than what we did at Faname, which was just the one bottle of Malibu and us going all over the place looking for a soda.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about this for the tagline?
[SPEAKER_08]: In Soviet Russia, gameplay you!
[SPEAKER_04]: That was it, and Ukchan, if we're going to do that, Jovidea will be there with our kinky vodka.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, the kinky vodka was so good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I'm getting drunk off this conversation.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ranma, I gotta let you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care, you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Big hello to all you guys at Anime Jam Session, Jovidea, and whoever else might be with you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care, guys, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: You got it, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_08]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sadly, it is time I shut down the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have been taking Skype calls for about 40 minutes, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But most of it was Bobby.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, yes, but, you know, with good reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we had a lot from Zaku and Magi and, you know, Ranma as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I appreciate everybody who called.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you didn't get through tonight, but you have something to say, for the love of God, email us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Give Dark Sakura some work to do next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the meantime, some quick Twitter topics before I go for last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: TigerClaw305 wants to remind us that XCOM Enemy Unknown was announced for iOS.
[SPEAKER_08]: I forgot about this, but I did hear about this.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're talking about they're going to be charging probably a little more money for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not going to be a 99-cent game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Think more along the lines of a $15 game.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that would be in line with Squeenix pricing on iOS, so it would make a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, they say it's going to be just like you're playing it on PC or any of those.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, XCOM makes sense to be on iPad.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would work.
[SPEAKER_08]: iPhone would be a little too tiny.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know about that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even iPad Mini might be a little much.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura wanted to follow up on the rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you bought La Mulana on Playism or Desura, you will get a Steam key after April 15th.
[SPEAKER_08]: So some of you already are going to own this new La Mulana.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also for next week, since we're so close to 500 and with all the old school talk, can we air Best Hits Part 1 next week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't want to promise anything yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: You never know what we might come up with.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Actdeft also posted a story about Dust and Elysian Tale that was covered in our Rapid Fire news earlier.
[SPEAKER_08]: Must have been in the restroom when we went over that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I will say this story does say that a sequel may be in the works.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which, you know, game does well, sequel comes out.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's no big surprise there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Twitter.com slash OLR if you want to follow us there and tweet us for a future week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Last Minute Stories tonight, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have put together this project called the Unleashed Project.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what it is, it's a total conversion for Sonic Generations.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's Sonic Unleashed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sonic Unleashed has been ported to PC completely.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it runs better than it did on console.
[SPEAKER_17]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they're using the Generations engine.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Unleashed, I'm talking about all the actual non-werewolf, werehog levels.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're talking about all the good levels.
[SPEAKER_08]: All the good ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's going to wrap us up for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: This episode's going to have to suit you for two weeks, but we've got an archive of about 497 episodes before this one, so if you need something to hold you over next week, go back and grab it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All the podcasts are still...
[SPEAKER_08]: on our server back through about 320.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there's plenty that are on the feed to grab.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you need something before that, hit up Dark Tetsuya, who's in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's got the link to the OL Archive, where they dug up fucking episodes of Vanilla Sky and guys on a show.
[SPEAKER_08]: They probably have your music show you used to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody probably recorded that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good lord, which was all like, if I had to go out and run errands, I'd just put on Eddie Izzard and I'd come back.
[SPEAKER_08]: People used to bootleg the shit out of Orange Lounge Radio, the station, so it's pretty, now all this time later, it's awesome that they did that, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am also planning this Wednesday to be in Turntable.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I missed turntable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Doing basically what I used to do on my pump of the volume.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I missed turntable.
[SPEAKER_08]: I always forget there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pop in there with me, Robert.
[SPEAKER_08]: I very well might.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just let me know what night.
[SPEAKER_08]: As long as it isn't when, what's the night?
[SPEAKER_17]: I said Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Wednesday's Horde House.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm dead after Horde House.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, after Horde House is fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: This week is actually, I need to give this a shout out, Horde House episode 100 is this Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, big milestone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mazel tov.
[SPEAKER_08]: Giveaways on this week's show.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_02]: Give me some interest in WoW.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've got the secret world.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got it because it was on sale for $22 instead of the full $30.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't blame you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I got yelled at for spending money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that does it for another week here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We just want to thank you guys for tuning in, supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We just do this because somebody brought this up before, just kind of the whole talk about the family issue.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys that are so enthusiastic about this show, there may not be 10,000 of you, but even the fact that there's five of you makes this so worth doing week in and week out.
[SPEAKER_08]: And as we are coming up on episode 500, has really made it worth it and why we've been stuck with it for so long.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't charge for this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're not going to be asking you for $12,000 to do this here in person every other week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am working on a gift for our listeners, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: We talked about it earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tease that in a future way.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I just wanted to say... Unfortunately, though, we have to raise the limit of friends you have to... Or the minimum of friends you have to ask.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to tell 500 of your friends.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're going to have to tell way more of your friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have conventions we want to go to.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't charge you guys to listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can tell you it does not take $10,000 to put on this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: It takes passion and dedication and wanting to do it for the loyal listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that is...
[SPEAKER_08]: What we get out of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so all we ask is help us grow our family.
[SPEAKER_08]: Spread the word about the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell a friend or two about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Give us a thumbs up on Stitcher.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you're on Tumblr, reblog when I freaking post it and not just hit like.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie is just here for her tumbles and wanting more followers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've figured since I've been using my Tumblr to promote the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm also using my Mass Effect Tumblr to promote the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: So don't give me that, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: That does it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to go around and get everybody's final thought for these two weeks, and then we'll be back on April 7th.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have a headache.
[SPEAKER_17]: Stupid sinus infection.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought is hazelnut frappuccinos.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to go get one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that Starbucks on the way?
[SPEAKER_08]: Any of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's open.
[SPEAKER_08]: Use the app.
[SPEAKER_08]: The app will tell you when they're closed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have the app.
[SPEAKER_08]: Girl, get with the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Last but not least, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a grind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though I'm not a huge fan of these games, it's really unfair that there's a Beatmania 3 final and a Keyboard Mania 3 final in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_05]: They want $100 for both.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, do you just want to split the price?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll take the Beatmania and you take the Keyboard Mania?
[SPEAKER_08]: Where am I going to put a Keyboard Mania in this house?
[SPEAKER_02]: In my backyard.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you can hold on to the other machine for me until we get a house, then yes, I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll talk to Dan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Someone's already bid on it, on one of them, so you gotta outbid them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on, it's at $99.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll do what we can.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a great week, everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: Be safe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't be a dick online.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know you guys won't be.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope all you guys had a blast at PAX and have fun at Game Developers Conference if you're one of those guys going to that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pixar didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we'll see you back here in a couple weeks on Orange Lawn Tradio episode 499 when we come back on April 7th.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a great week, everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_12]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_12]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_12]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_12]: See you next week!