[SPEAKER_00]: Sakura, Sky, and Loku Tonight, March 3rd, 2013 Two companies promise new games at PAX East Gran Turismo 6 will be out before year's end And could Shenmue 3 happen via Kickstarter?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Who claims it has not worked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nah, it has not worked.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has not worked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you've been... How long have you and Nellie been together since the start of OLR, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys were together.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, around there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, so... I think 2001.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you and Dan have been together that long, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we've been together for 15 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_02]: As of the 23rd of January.
[SPEAKER_04]: This show just, you know, fosters long-term relationships.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, over the course of the show, I think I've had four or five different... I did get married after we started the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the one I'm on is the last one, because he's listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you know he's a keeper, because he's supportive and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, and he's officially my hero for re-reblogging one of my posts on my Mass Effect blog, because I totally agree with him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you guys and your Mass Effect lulzy stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You were talking about Shitadel earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we already dogging the DLC before anybody's played it?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just my special nickname for the Citadel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Shitadel?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's very clever.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's very creative.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Becky and I call it that sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Funny you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby Blackwolf Ken Allen
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a confession, Rob I really didn't play many of them
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and I did like Phantasmagoria, but I played the LucasArts games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Loom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well that was all kind of around that same time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it was around that same time, but I just wasn't as into it myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh God, I loved it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was a console girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will admit, I was not as into Space Quest as I was into Heroes Quest, and especially King's Quest.
[SPEAKER_04]: That series was so amazing to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think everybody remembers King's Quest IV, Rosella, because that's the one that incorporates all the old fairy tales and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my gosh, great, great classic game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just didn't get into them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the only real thing I played on a PC before that were the text-based gemstones.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then of course your favorite, Civilization, the old school one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got into that early on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was never into Civ.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I should give a plug for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm curious what you guys think about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, Microsoft is doing a huge sale on their games on demand right now where you can get a lot of these...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: If I was going to try and get Jamie into Civ, I would be all like, poke, poke, here's a $10 gift card.
[SPEAKER_04]: Poke, poke, here's what you go spend it on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Poke, poke.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I know that won't work, so I'm not even going to bother.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not giving her money.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you gave me money right now, I'd probably just pay bills with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think about Microsoft responding to this really deep cut sale thing of sorts?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I think they're just trying to push digital sales, trying to figure out, you know, how to get people interested in that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's all about getting them more exposure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe, you know, kind of trying to, I don't know, hype up stuff and, you know, as we approach a supposed announcement of some sort, you know, so maybe...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it seems to have worked for Steam and stuff to help drive sales.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe that's why they want to... Hey guys, you know we do sell games digitally as well, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not just Sony and Steam.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do that as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, hey, buy something.
[SPEAKER_04]: A tiny correction to what I had stated earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby says it was Space Quest 4 was the one in the series that Ken Allen did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oops, my bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will say that I know this one for a fact because Bobby and I are both fond over this one and our mutual love of an old-ass Sierra game I bet none of you have heard of.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Jones in the Fast Lane.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to know something, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why people on Tumblr think that I want to see animated gifs of Caden's butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you're following those Tumblrs.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all about what you want to follow on the Tumbles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't there one called Caden's ass?
[SPEAKER_02]: This one's called Shepard's butt.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because it's like, hey, we saw that you viewed alien penises.
[SPEAKER_03]: You may like Caden's butt.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's also one that's called Shepard's left boob.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, going to our chat room at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Black Wolf, yet again trying to correct me here.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only difference between the disc and CD version was the CD version had full spoken audio.
[SPEAKER_04]: The animated characters were still there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought in the CD version, they were actual like digitized characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: And in the disc one, they were cartoons.
[SPEAKER_04]: And on the disc version, there is a fuck yes, I boob tumbler.
[SPEAKER_03]: And on the disc version, it came on like 48 discs, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, that's the equivalent of a CD.
[SPEAKER_04]: The disc version of Jones, I think, was only like four.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like four discs or so.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I remember, what was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Willy Beamish, I think it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a game I was playing way back in the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was on like 12 discs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I had an anime fighting game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was called...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember what it was called.
[SPEAKER_03]: Something lace.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember what it was called now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was like metal and lace or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got into like software, et cetera, you know, back in the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never did get that game to run correctly, but damn, it took a long time with like eight plus disks installing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the whole reason you needed a hard drive was because you had to have something to install the stinking disks to.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, the 14 disk descent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's where you had to have like a rubber band to bind all the discs together.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still have it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: My stack of Descent discs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Classic Gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: What a trip.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get into what we've been playing this week as far as modern games go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that classics are bad by any means.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I've been playing Capcom Arcade a lot lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't we just start with Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no, I was going to say... No, that was last week, not this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I was going to say, you missed last week, and I was talking about Capcom Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you know that the freebie game that you can just get for free on PlayStation 3 is Black Tiger, which you've talked about on the show before?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: and you can flip between the Japanese and the English versions.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was so excited to tell you last week and then you weren't here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think Dan might have already gotten it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's a neat game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one of Dan's favorites.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next week they're putting out Gun.Smoke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gun.Smoke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gun.Smoke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a demo for Gun.Smoke.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: What were you going to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Something sassy over there, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder, you know, because now that they're allowing you to get all these weird URL names, I wonder if someday we will have Gun.Smoke.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Mass Effect, The Reckoning DLC, The Last Multiplayer DLC, The
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: But the multiplayer is so good.
[SPEAKER_04]: The multiplayer is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys wonder why we don't shut up about Mass Effect 3 ever, ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: For DarkSakura, it's a lot of this fandom and all this stuff she keeps perpetuating.
[SPEAKER_04]: For me, it's the multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can keep going back and playing that and it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been playing a lot of multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_02]: The bulk of my playing has been multiplayer because I...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: That was good of Bioware, by the way, to give everybody a free character new.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looking back, I wish they'd done that for each piece of DLC they did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand their whole little microtransaction model is to make people save up the in-game credits or be tempted to spend three bucks on a pack to maybe get a character.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think it was a good gesture to give everybody a freebie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got Hawkeye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, I have one of him too, the Zayid wannabe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, but like with the bow and arrow, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: The omni-bow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love engineers, but I wasn't, like it was cool for a little bit, but I went back to my human because I don't have a quarian engineer on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I finally, though, like, this is the first time I've actually gotten a character up to 20 and promoted my class.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now I have to start over, and I, like, I hate the starting over, because, like, they put us on a collector map right when I just started over, and we all know the collectors are bullshit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, the second one, thankfully, was a Cerberus thing, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first game I was in, though, I had to roll my eyes because we had a Collector Adept, we had a Gath Juggernaut, and we had a Krogan Warlord.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it was almost all of the new classes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was amazed.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was such a balanced party.
[SPEAKER_02]: We just flew through everything like it was no big deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was like a hot knife through butter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Technus in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says he's kind of done with the Mass Effect universe for now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, but I get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, is it time?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this is the last multiplayer DLC.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have the last single player DLC next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it time?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, nothing good lasts forever, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it time to move on to whatever's next for the Mass Effect series?
[SPEAKER_02]: Three words.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Still going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still going.
[SPEAKER_04]: It took a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: It took a while, though, to come back.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there was all the movies and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you want to share or should I move on to Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's really all I played.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm probably going to be canceling a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sad face.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just for a little while until I get a job.
[SPEAKER_04]: Makes sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: My gaming week was all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: It started off okay, at least.
[SPEAKER_03]: I started, we were playing Borderlands 2 and kind of going through that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then that wonderful add-on content pack came out from 2K.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I was like, okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to go ahead and get this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I know I could have saved some money by buying the DLC, either the season pass or buying just the DLC straight from the marketplace.
[SPEAKER_03]: But here's the thing, though, is that I want to put it on more than one system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I play with a friend, and I don't want to play DLC twice.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the add-on content packs do not have DRM on them.
[SPEAKER_03]: They also apparently don't work very well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because the true nature of Gearbox is finally coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, huh...
[SPEAKER_03]: Borderlands is such an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did they really fuck up Duke Nukem Forever and Aliens Colonial Marines?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because it's a fluke.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they fuck up everything, apparently.
[SPEAKER_03]: Borderlands is just, I guess, some weird fluke for this company.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe they took some of that Duke Nukem money and Aliens Colonial Marines money and made the game better or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the disc broke the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: The disc broke the DLC.
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, I couldn't get any of the DLC to work on either system.
[SPEAKER_03]: The people that did get it to work, they're having problems with the DLC not quite working because they can't pick up any of the weapons that are exclusive to the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get in there saying, this weapon is for this piece of DLC which you don't have.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that kind of sucks for everyone else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I mean, we could probably just remove the DLC and probably have to, I don't know, clear our cache or something, re-download something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's still annoying, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to have to go through this process and try to figure out, okay, which series of events do I have to do to get this to work?
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyways, so I was trying to get this thing to work, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: Shadow Next Gen has an opinion on Gearbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shadow Next Gen says, Gearbox cannot be blamed for Duke Nukem.
[SPEAKER_04]: All they did was they put their existing material and made it playable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gearbox is totally to blame, though, for aliens.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Meeting you halfway.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll accept that.
[SPEAKER_03]: but the thing is so okay so it's all fucked up in one way or another and for me it's a little bit more fucked up than some of the people that have the game and just like can't either access certain DLC or can't access the guns in certain DLC or you know the waypoint's not showing up and their solution is well we're just gonna have to put out a patch for it the disc is for people that don't have fucking online how are you gonna download this patch to make the fucking offline thing work correctly oh that makes total sense
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you guys test this at all?
[SPEAKER_03]: Does that mean you have to do one of those weird things where you download it to a USB stick?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, there is no way.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can do that for system updates.
[SPEAKER_03]: The console firmware, you can't do that for game updates.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't do that legitimately.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can get tools to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're telling me that the technology's there, it's just that for whatever reason they don't let the publishers use it.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: So for now we've been playing like emulator stuff because I have these modded Xboxes that we were messing around with and so we've been playing like Super Nintendo and Nintendo games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also started trying Far Cry 2 because my thought is, hey, you know, I remember Far Cry Instinct's Predator had a pretty awesome map editor and you can make your own levels and stuff like that and the game's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: So I would have probably picked three first, but two seems to be pretty good price point-wise.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm recreating my favorite maps from other games in the Far Cry map editor.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I've got, I've started from Grand Theft Auto IV, Bellative, Gay Tony.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got the Ziggurat map, which is the ferry terminal that's under construction.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I've started that, and it looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: So hopefully I'm going to just take all my favorite levels or I'll just download some if I'm too damn lazy because it is quite a process to get that stuff looking right and actually getting it to work correctly.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I may just download some other maps and stuff like that and hopefully maybe we can switch over that because I think right now we bought another map pack for Call of Duty a couple weeks ago and we're kind of already sick of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Dicks like, hey, I got to see Grand Theft Auto V being played twice because the guy died midway through one of the missions.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I got to see it all over again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, I fucking hate you.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyways, it sounds really awesome though.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just talking about how you can switch between the three characters during the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: They showed off one of the levels that... I don't think it was in the trailer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was a screenshot.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was basically where the guy's rappelling down the side of an office building.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so he's like, oh yeah, so one of the guys you're controlling is flying a helicopter and another one's a sharpshooter on one of the other buildings.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the other guy's the one that's rappelling.
[SPEAKER_03]: And actually as you're rappelling, the detail in the game, you have people coming in the offices and going, hey, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_03]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's just...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it sounds really awesome and of course he reiterated the size of the game and stuff and he just says it looks fucking amazing so I can't wait so fuck the next gen, I don't care, I just want this game that's right but what about those games analysts that say oh for sure Grand Theft Auto 5 will come to next gen consoles
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, here's what he said.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll come to next-gen consoles eventually.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the only way I believe that is if they do a PC port, which they're not doing right away.
[SPEAKER_03]: They may do one later on, or they may go the Red Dead Redemption route and say, fuck it, we're not going to do one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially if they're worried that the game's going to get hacked, because that's where you get your fucking keys for... Well, they're stupid enough anyways to put the fucking keys for Grand Theft Auto and have it be all the same across platforms.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why they do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's assume that they don't do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when they do put out a PC port, it would enable hacking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or at least that's how it's been.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think that, yeah, they could do a PC port.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if they do that, then they'll probably do a next-gen port because they're going to be up-resing everything or making it run better, have better particle effects and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: but it's not going to be at launch and it would be like eventually like maybe next year or a year after that depending on what their release schedule is as far as what Rockstar is going to be working on next probably DLC for Grand Theft Auto 5 which would be pretty awesome so I don't know they're going to be busy for a while so I don't think they can really split the resources I am kind of surprised that it's not on the Wii U but I don't know whatever
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's see ShadowNextGen in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com He wouldn't take Loki and then was bragging about getting to see Grand Theft Auto 5 That ain't right Well, it's just, you know, they took our buyer and stuff and, you know, our Well, he was the vice president of sales, now he's some new business guy So it's just all the management people and the buyer Don't worry, I'm working on getting rid of the buyer
[SPEAKER_03]: Soon enough, I'll be going.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll just be a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I did say, I'm like, so, you're taking me along with, you know, DPS, because they're going to have Grand Theft Auto there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, we don't need to send this VP guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: He doesn't know anything about games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, anything else you want to share about your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Played a little bit more Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_03]: How's the server going?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's empty.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played some last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very empty.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hardly see a soul on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do check the logs every now and then to see if people are actually connecting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to thank whoever built the ginormous N7 in front of my house.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that wasn't you?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it wasn't me!
[SPEAKER_03]: I do keep an eye on it every now and then.
[SPEAKER_03]: I read the forums and I also check my 3D map every once in a while to see if something is new.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, hey, that's different.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I was working on... I don't even know what it is now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was trying to create this little airship thing that I have a picture of.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not necessarily create it exactly, but just something similar.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I was like, okay, I'm going to make this giant castle inside this mountain.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was like, I'm wasting so much damn time in Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could be doing something more productive, but I just didn't want to be productive that day.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to build Hogwarts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I remember what it was now, why I was playing Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because my wife was watching Hulu, which is being streamed through my Xbox, and I wanted to build maps in Far Cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so I was waiting for Far Cry to download or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I bought it on PC as well, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: instead of buying stuff on the sale on Xbox I bought PC games.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100 Matt says I'll be getting Minecraft soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know I saw at Target those little like it's mixed in with all the cards for the crap online stuff you're never going to play like Club Penguin and all those you know how like they sell tons of those cards.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a card for Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So like you can buy Minecraft at like Target and stuff now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am eventually at some point once I get motivated enough to finish the website and stuff to
[SPEAKER_03]: Settling up nights to do things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't quite done that yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know Codeman's going in there and he's doing videos of some of the Mob Arena stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: That needs to be fixed and balanced.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I've actually just been having fun digging my holes, which is pretty much all my houses are.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're holes in the ground.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like you do on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just dig your own holes all night.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've seen my house, haven't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: My prairie dog?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, your Minecraft house?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Minecraft house.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a series of underground tunnels.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't been on Minecraft in like a month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shame on me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get yelled at all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yelled at over it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, I keep looking at your half-finished house all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I need to finish it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anything else you want to share for Gaming Week?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait until you hear what I have been playing and you're going to be like, God damn it, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so my Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I was driving around town hoping somebody broke street on Tomb Raider, because I heard a lot of places were selling Tomb Raider early, but I couldn't find any, so I guess I'll have to wait like everybody else.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_04]: How can you not want Tomb Raider after the Conan review?
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, Conan, I love his review thing, it's kind of hit and miss and stuff, but my god are the deaths in that so violent and frequent.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of, I think Jamie would like the game actually for that reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: What game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, the new one?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, because there's stuff, you know, okay, you gotta go left, oh, you gotta go right, oh, you didn't go right fast enough, and now she impales her neck on a stick very violently.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I wasn't... One of our listeners got me the last one, the Guardian of Light.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: So, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't... Well, Guardian of Light is so different, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Guardian of Light, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a great game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, yeah, I wasn't really prepared.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I should have known better because, like, you know, I know Tomb Raider was all about the death scenes back in the day, but it was a little more cartoony back then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Locking the butler in the fridge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of that stuff now, like, when I saw that whole, like, impale scene, I was like, oh, maybe, maybe, I don't know, maybe I'm having second thoughts about this purchase because, you know, I'm not huge on the violence, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll deal with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: From what I hear, it's limited.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wonder if you can still make her break her own neck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sure you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wouldn't be Tomb Raider if you couldn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I still want to lock the butler in the freezer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that was the only thing I ever did in 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wouldn't surprise me if they have throwbacks to...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then again, her mansion's not really in this one, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's a reboot.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a prequel.
[SPEAKER_03]: She doesn't have a butler yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll have to hope for a new one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe at the end of the game when she gets to her mansion or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: She gets a letter from her butler.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dear ma'am, I'm still in the freezer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please let me out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sincerely, your butler.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, that is gross.
[SPEAKER_04]: You paid $60 for this, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should be trying to rape her.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should be saving your money, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get a 401k.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSG 100 Matt said the best.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should reread that in your mom's voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, that's gross, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Through her neck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would totally be her.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's talk about what I... I adore your mom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Diablo 3 Diablo 3 Diablo 3
[SPEAKER_04]: What am I smoking?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the fact that I've been into Path of Exile lately made me go like, maybe I should go back and try Diablo 3 because I was enjoying Path of Exile.
[SPEAKER_04]: People say Diablo 3 is... Extrofer was like, you need to go back because a lot of it's patches and all this.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I've actually been enjoying it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got to admit, I think part of that is the fact that nobody else is playing Diablo 3 right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't get people jumping in on your game?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and I said you know what I'm going to play this through one time just me at my own pace because I think part of what broke the game for me was that having people jump in your game as much as it's nice to be social and all that like it paces the game a lot differently because people will be off kind of doing their own thing you got to go back to town and sell stuff but you don't want to miss some of the exploration and the XP and you know I don't know like so I kind of want to just I want to play this game by myself for a little bit one time but always connected to the internet
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, but it's always connected to the internet, which is ridiculous in its own right, but hey, at least I got the game complimentary with the whole Warcraft Pass thing, so I can't complain too much about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I may have to reinstall it and give it another go.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't dislike it, I just didn't like not being able to rotate the camera and getting a better view, so that was really my biggest pet peeve.
[SPEAKER_02]: That and people jumping in my game, which I had turned it off and people were still jumping in my game.