Orange Lounge Radio
We're your hosts, Dark Sakura, Sky, and the Lowkey Arcade
Tonight, March 25th, 2007, Black Xbox 360s turn out to be real, Devil May Cry 4 is no longer an exclusive, and an old 80's arcade classic comes to Blu-ray
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello everybody out there and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
We are that video game podcast dedicated to what you, the gamer, really want to know
You know, gaming culture, gamer lifestyle, and all that fun stuff
My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky if you check our forums or whatever
That's S-K-I-E, Sky
Joining us, as always, say hello to Tech Master Loki
Hello
How you doing Tech Master Loki?
I'm doing okay
Alright, you might wonder where Dark Sakura is at tonight, unfortunately she's not joining us tonight
She's very sick, she sends her love to all of you guys, but she has a sinus infection
I spoke to her on the phone briefly before we started tonight
And she apparently slept for 14 hours yesterday, which is, you know, a pretty surefire sinus
Someone's pretty sick, so, sorry Dark Sakura, rest up, feel better
And I was all excited too because I saw a Doctor Who pinball machine this weekend, which I'll get into in a little bit
No, but seriously, I was like, oh my gosh, this is like, this is Jamie times two
These are like two of her loves rolled up into one
Sort of like what I thought of, like Loki, I've had this thought about you before
The first time I ever went to that restaurant in the Bay Area that serves the slabs of meat
And they served the chicken wrapped in bacon
That made me think of you, because I was like, it's two of Loki's love
I might add, the chicken wrapped in bacon wasn't that great when I had it, so
Sorry to hear that
Alright, well we do have a female perspective on tonight's program
You know, not that we really need one, but we have one anyway
Just teasing, to all the ladies out there listening
Say hello to Rice Princess
Hello everyone
How are you doing Miss Rice Princess?
I'm doing well, how about you Rob?
Oh, pretty good, it's been an interesting week
Yeah, I agree
I agree
So you were talking about movies before we came in tonight, what did you see this week?
I saw Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
Now how was it, because I read a review in some magazine that said it was absolute crap
Well that magazine's absolute crap, because it was so fucking awesome
Like it was fucking epic, it was great
Was it better than the old school ones from like the 90s with the ninja wrap?
There are two different things, that's apples and oranges
I just, I loved it, and I loved the old movies too
Chime in Matt
I did see it yesterday as well, and I, because I was a little scared
Because when I first saw the first trailer that came out, it looked badass
It was like, oh yeah
Then I saw these new trailers that they're showing on TV and stuff
And they kind of made it look stupid
But I swear, go see it, it's fucking awesome
And the reason why, they did make, it does tie in with the other three movies
And they do make some changes to the storyline
You know, it basically takes place after everything
And so, you know, April O'Neil's not a reporter anymore
And Casey Jones isn't exactly like he was in the other movies
But that's fine, you kind of forgive that when you see it
It's just, it never lets you down
It was one of those movies that I was watching it, and I was just like, fuck, this is awesome
You know, it wasn't, really I haven't had that much of a satisfying movie experience in a while
And this was one of those movies that just, it was awesome
It brought me back to what made Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles so cool in the first place
It just, it was very satisfying
And I really suggest, just ignore the negative reviews out there for it
Because it really is good, and I cannot wait for the sequel
Are you on somebody's payola, like New Line's payola?
I'm not, I'm not on anybody's payroll for this kind of stuff
It was awesome, and yeah, I would love to see it again
It really, there's a lot of parts that even have, you know
I was telling Irene about one scene towards the end of the movie or something
Which has to do with my Cage Man song, by the way
That, it's just, when that scene kicked in, it was like, fuck yeah, that's awesome
So, highly, highly recommend this movie, especially if you're a fan of
You know, the original Ninja Turtles movie, maybe not so much number two and definitely not three
But, you know, even the old series and stuff, it really works
And it sounds like that this is going to be something that kind of jump starts the whole movie series all over again
I'm looking in our chat room, the always present fourth guest on our show
Because, you know, part of what makes this show so unique, shall we say
Is that we always encourage the live interaction with our chat room
And the phone calls, which we'll take later, chat.orangelaundry.com if you want to join in
If you're listening live on this Sunday night
Let's see, we have Blaze from the O.L. Army says TMNT was fucking amazing
Joshi16 says one of the turtles is gay, is there a gay turtle now?
There's not a gay turtle in there, not at all
Let's see, Wonder Dog Harold says are they really still teenagers at this point?
Okay, well maybe not, yeah, because they're pretty old by now, but I was kind of thinking, well maybe teenage for, like, turtles
I don't know how long turtles live, but, you know
Yeah, I've never done that
Maybe it's like dog ears or something like that, you know, I don't know
Well, I mean, not to, I don't think this is spoiling anything, but they've all, like, kind of, I guess, taken on, like, responsibilities
Or have, like, moved on past, like, how they used to live before
So I guess it's kind of showing that they've, like, grown up a little bit, but
I don't know, they still, I guess their mentality is still kind of, like, a teenage mentality
There was a lot of adult humor in it, which is great, like, a lot of funny stuff
It was just awesome, I mean, I mean, if anyone that's going to see it obviously doesn't have to do a shredder anymore
This is kind of after all that, they've defeated them, the Foot Clan's kind of been disbanded a little bit
Where at least they've gone underground, and then it's kind of what they've done since then
They kind of went on with their lives, because now they don't have to really protect, you know, New York from anything
They're just kind of living, and so now they have to kind of come together
And, you know, it's just, it was really awesome
Even the opening scene where they're showing kind of that flashback with the battle and stuff
That was awesome
That was great, oh my gosh
Right now I was like, oh my god, this movie's going to be cool
Because it was just, it never let you down at all
There was a little bit of humor, you know, from the show
Because, I mean, they were kind of, you know, Michelangelo, of course, is still goofy and stuff
But it wasn't, like, detracting, and it was, it fit, it fit with the characters
And I'm just really glad they kind of respected the actual characters
And didn't make it so retarded and all one-liners
I mean, there were one-liners in there, but it worked
Yeah, it did, like, a lot of them were puns, but I absolutely love puns
I think puns are, like, the greatest jokes ever
And, like, it really worked, I mean, if you were a fan of the old cartoon series
Or if you watched the movies, I mean, you saw that anyway in the movies or the series
So it's, like, it was just more of that, you know, and it was appropriate to the times, too
The only thing that really kind of annoyed me was Splinter's voice
I know, I know, like, I'm all, did, like, some Chinese dude, like, do his voice or something?
No, he sounded Jewish
Really? You think so? I'm like, wow, Splinter
Oh my god, Turtles
I know, seriously, it was kind of weird, but
Well, alright, we can talk movies all night
Did any of you guys play the games yet? The Ninja Turtles games?
No, no
I played the old one on Ninja Turtles
That, unlike the movie, did kind of suck
Alright, well, let's get into a little bit of How Was Your Gaming Week
Where we talk about the video games that we've been playing this week here on the program
Rice Princess, what have you been playing?
Um, I have actually not played anything this week
I, like I said before, I cancelled my WoW account for the time being
Ouch
So I kind of have been not doing, I've been, like, doing stuff around the house
Did you watch anyone play something that looked cool and that you wanted to have?
Oh, no, you know what I played? I played DDR
Did you? Alright, there you go
In the arcade, yes, for the first time in, like, two years, it was awesome
What was it, Supernova, Extreme?
Um, I played, um, Supernova and I played a little bit of, um, whatever's that golfing?
The other one, Extreme, I think it was
Max 2, I think
I played that, yeah, it was good times
Memories?
Yeah, like, I was surprised because I could actually do, like, 7 and 8 footers again
Whereas I couldn't do that, like, two years ago
And I was like, sweet, I don't suck anymore
So, yeah, it was good times
Cool, Loki!
I finally, I've been waiting for this game for a while
And it's just a really weird game to wait for
But Earth Defense Force 2017, it is awesome
It is so stupid and so ridiculous and the voice acting is so horrible
But it's so fun to play
It's just, basically, at least
I know nothing about this game, what is this?
It is basically these aliens come and start attacking Earth
And it is so B-movie, cheesy and stuff
I mean, for example
Like, Destroy All Humans?
Not exactly, like, we're talking, like, robots and giant ants
I mean, that's giant ants
That's what you're fighting for the first few levels is giant ants
And it works
Well, in Final Fantasy, you fight giant slimes to level up
Okay, but still, though, I mean, it's giant ants
And the voice acting is so horrible
Like, for example, they're all, look, it's flying
Or, look at those alien spaceships
It's like something out of the science fiction movie
Not a science fiction movie, the science fiction movie
Like, the one and only that's ever been made
Exactly
And so, I don't know, it's just, I can't stop playing
Basically, you have, you can collect up to 200 weapons in this game
By replaying the levels over and over, you can level up your characters
Or whatever, get your stamina higher
And you can actually, you can play it through five different difficulty levels
I've been playing it through, like, normal and easy
And even normal is starting to get hard now
Playing it on hard, which is not even all the way up to, like,
They have, like, extreme inferno or something
Hard is fucking impossible
So, inferno's gotta be, oh my god
Oh my god
But, it's pretty fun though
It's two player co-op, which is kinda cool, split screen
So I'm really looking forward to playing that at work
But, it's just so cheesy though
It's really worth picking up
The achievements are not easy in it
It's basically beating the game on each difficulty
And unlocking every single weapon
That's your achievements
Six achievements for 1,000 points
But, it's, you know, it's one of those games though
You have infinite ammo
And you have some weird weapons that are in the game
In fact, there's one missile that I unlocked in the very beginning
It's a piece of shit
It's the slowest moving missile I've ever seen
I mean, the thing is going, like, less than five miles an hour
Just crawling across the air
And it doesn't hardly do any damage
But, it's fun because you can pick, you know, one of two weapons
To use each, throughout the whole game
So you just select your weapons, play your mission, and that's it
And the best part about it though, you can blow up everything
Buildings, doesn't matter, no one gives a crap
Because you're saving the earth
So, what do I do? I just start launching random missiles
Into every single skyscraper I see
And watching them all fall
And it's entertaining because they're there at the next level
Because there's no continuity whatsoever
So do you recommend the game?
I highly recommend the game
Let me tell you, the frame rate's crap
The graphics suck, the sound is awful
And the voice acting's horrible
And the AI is pretty retarded as well
So are you saying it's so bad it's good?
It is
It's the showgirls of video games?
It's so bad, it's so bad
But that's the thing, you gotta play it
Realizing that it's gonna suck in these areas
And to be honest, the graphics don't need to be that great
It's like an old arcade game
I mean, old arcade games, they're not that many polygons and stuff
But it works, it's just fun to play
So it may look like crap
It may be very fucking hard at times
The AI can be dumb
Because I saw some soldier or whatever
I was trying to find these people
So they would join me and help kill the alien ants
And this guy was shooting a shotgun into a building
Because he was stupid and couldn't figure out how to get around the building
That's awesome
I don't know, it's funny
But it's still a lot of fun to play
It does not stop getting fun
So really highly recommend this game
It's only like 40 bucks for the 360
Definitely worth picking up
Even if you can find it used, that's even better
So I recommend it
It's a lot of fun
Definitely a lot better than from what I've heard from Armored Core 4
And other than that, I played Crackdown a little bit
That's about it though
I've been just trying to get the last few achievements and stuff
Kind of getting a little bored with the game
Because now that you're at the end of the game and stuff
There's not much to do
Oh, and Grand Theft Auto Vice City Stories
We've been playing that
At work we put custom firmwares in all of our PSPs now
So we're all playing it overclocked, which is fun
It actually looks a lot nicer
We have a guy that's working
Actually he's a pretty famous cheat designer for the Vice City Stories
Durga Durga Man
He's working on a multiplayer code to switch out some of the weapons
And get some different stuff
So hopefully that'll happen
And I am so looking forward to this week when the Grand Theft Auto 4 trailer hits on Friday
That is going to be awesome
I am going to watch that thing like 16 times on Friday
Analyze every frame
Oh yeah
Alright, we'll be looking forward to your thoughts on that trailer on Sunday then
Alright
Miggletov, I noticed you snuck in here while we were starting the show
First off, hello, how are you doing?
Hello, I'm fine
Alright, how was your gaming week? What have you been playing?
Only been playing two things
World of Warcraft, I made my alternate character
His name is Agathon
And his pet is named Helo
Oh my gosh, that's awesome
Because I'm a big Battlestar nerd now
Because it's so good
It is so good
It's the best and Helo's hot
And then other than that, finally at work
Thanks to being at a developer place
I've been playing a lot of Boom Boom Rocket
And it's the best game I've ever played in my life called Boom Boom Rocket
And it's pretty and I love it
I'm not sure how to take that
It's the best game you've ever played in your life called that
I could say Big Mother Truckers was the best game I ever played in my life
That's a lie, because it wasn't a good game at all
But Boom Boom Rocket, if I didn't have a 360, would sell me on a 360
Because it's really just that much fun
What the hell is it? Because I still don't know that much about it
Are you allowed to tell us what it is?
I won't mention specifics, I don't know
It's not our game, I don't care
It's a music game with fireworks
So it's like Fantavision meets DDR with a touch of Beatmania
Because the fireworks make noise for Beatmania
And if you hit arrows when you're not supposed to
It penalizes you like Beatmania does as well
So you can't just mess around
But the track list is not stellar, but it gets the job done
And if you like Fantavision and you like pretty things
It's really, really fun and lots of explosions
High def, good stuff?
Yeah, oh my goodness
I don't know, I must have played that a lot this week
I got all the achievements, they're all really easy
Especially if you play music games
And it's just a whole lot of fun
I don't know, it almost convinced somebody at work to get a 360 too
Because he was really enjoying it
Interesting, so the music game fans will be all over this
Maybe, it depends on if you care about the quality of music you're playing the game to
Alpha Canogram says it sounds like every Xtend Xtra
No, because this game is good
I liked every Xtend Xtra, whatever
Every Xtend Xtra
Music was a part of it, kind of like Rez
But Rez wasn't really a music game
The music was an important element
That's what every Xtend Xtra is like
This is a rhythm game, it's not a game where you blow something up to cause chain reactions
Every time you hit one of those arrows, fireworks explosions happen
It's like DDR once you hit a hundred combo
You get a little flashy explosions
But there's timing issues with the game too
And I don't think they'll be fixed before
I'm pretty sure what I was playing is the release candidate
I just need it to come out now really bad
That's it
Alright, we'll see what happens
My gaming week, interestingly enough
I don't know if you were listening last week
But I mentioned I was going to be going on vacation for a little while
So I have been on vacation the past four days in the middle of nowhere
I was up in the Mendocino, Fort Bragg, coastal area, Northern California
No internet, no phones, no games, really nothing
So it's just nice to have a break away from everything
I'll get into what effect that's going to have on tonight's show in just a minute
But yeah, I just took a break
But before I left, I did get to sneak in a little bit of Castlevania Symphony of the Night on Xbox Live
Oh my heck, it is awesome
It's so great
Just the fact that they brought back one of the greatest video games of all time
And they didn't change much
They do have that enhanced mode
Which basically means somewhat smoother, cleaner sprites and changed sound effects
But really they didn't change that much
Don't let that talk of a new high def mode thing fool you
It still looks like the old PlayStation 1 game
But that's not a bad thing
No, obviously
Especially for Xbox Live Arcade
Yeah, if it ain't broke, don't fix it
Exactly, and really they didn't change anything
It's an awesome deal for $10
I mean, great, if you still have your old PlayStation hooked up
And you've got your disc available to play the PlayStation games or whatever
Then have fun, go play the old version as you remember it
But for the rest of us, our PlayStations were thrown in the closet a long time ago
We lost our copies of Castlevania Symphony of the Night
This is awesome
Didn't you mention something about no loading times or anything?
Oh yeah, there's no loading times
You don't have to wait for anything
They kept all the voice acting intact
It's great, I mean, I definitely recommend
Especially if you've never played it before
Oh my gosh
It's got a lot of hours that you can put into the game if you've never played it before
There's no excuse to have never played that game before
Like, I don't care
I'm looking in chatroom, Blay says Sky was a hippie for four days basically
Yeah, basically
When it comes down to it, I was
Yeah, so back to Symphony of the Night
Well, I'll be playing plenty more Symphony of the Night now that I'm back from vacation
And another game I picked up today was Tetris Evolution on 360
But I've literally played it for 15 minutes, so I don't have enough to say on it
My initial impressions are, why didn't they just put this on Live Arcade?
But then again, it was only $30, so it was a cheaper title
And the idea of being able to play Tetris on Xbox Live is pretty cool
But I'll give you my full thoughts on that next week
Because it doesn't seem bad, but it doesn't seem as great as Tetris DS either
And those are just my initial five minute thoughts
But I'll look at it more in depth later
It looked okay, they had videos playing in the background
The HD videos looked pretty hot, so I'll give you that
But what was kind of interesting though is they also had
You can cheat in it just like you can with the Tetris DS
You can rotate blocks or whatever and then you can actually
Basically kind of hover them there forever until you decide where you want to put them
That's pretty sweet
Alright, so I'll give you more thoughts on that next week here on the program
Alright, let's get into some housekeeping tonight
While I was out for four days, apparently some stuff has gone down on Live 365
And it has to do with this new CRB, the Copyright Royalty Board
If you want to know more information on it, go to www.live365.com slash choice
And of course, Live 365 is where we broadcast our live feed
Obviously the live element is an important part of our show
We don't want it to go anywhere, so we suggest you guys all check this out
I know our buddy Travis Donovan went into detail on this on his program on Saturday night
I haven't had a chance to listen to it yet, so if you want to go check him out on iTunes under Travis Donovan
You can check out what he has to say on it
We don't know what we're going to do about this yet
We understand it has changed some rules already on Live 365
Which may be kind of a pain in the butt to listen to us on Live 365
Long story short, we don't play enough ASCAP, BMI type music on this program
To justify if they're going to raise the rates much more of keeping Live 365
We don't know yet what we're going to do
We do have other offers on the table we're going to be looking at
And if we have to go underground, we may just do that as well
But obviously the live element is an important factor of our show
And we don't want to lose that anytime soon
This shouldn't affect the podcast feed
Worst case scenario, if the rates of Live 365 had to go through the roof
We might have to go a couple of weeks with no live element
But we would find a new home, set up something on Shoutcast, I don't know
But seeing as we're Orange Mountains Radio is a bit of a network now
Because we have some other great shows like STFU on Thursdays
And Travis Donovan on Saturdays
We don't want to lose any of those other shows that we've built up over time
More to come on that when we have some time to sit down and take this all in
What's going on with us
Because again, I'm just getting back and kind of hitting all this news
And I want to check out what the rest of the OLR staff has to say about it
So we'll see
Travis Donovan is in chat and says
Urges folks to visit Live 365.com slash choice
And says you all need to contact your local congress person
And let them know they need to level the playing field again
Over the air radio does not pay royalty rates
But internet and satellite radio must
Doesn't sound very fair to me
And it's going to hurt the little guys like us and other great Live 365
And just internet radio stations in general
So that kind of sucks
So we'll have more info on that next week
We'll see
Also, as far as housekeeping goes
Tonight we're going to change things up a little bit
Dark Sakura's not here
And I, of course, have been out of town for the last four days
So I'm a little bit out of the loop on gaming news
So Loki's going to be news boy tonight
And all of our news tonight will be presented by Loki
So we are going to break our usual format a little bit
So take it away Loki, what happened this week?
Hooray, well the big thing that happened, of course
At least if you're in the UK and most of the other world
The PlayStation 3 finally came out for you
That time has finally come
You can finally buy your overpriced gaming machine
And there were some interesting stories coming out about that
Of course, one that pretty much sums everything up
Phil Harrison
Basically was saying that Europe is the most important continent
For the gaming industry
Which is funny because it was also the last one to get the PlayStation 3
But apparently the third is also the most important
And he was told
You know, this gameindustry.biz
Big industry site
It's got the most countries and it's got the most people
It's also got the most cultures
The fact that we've got the launch here
With more consoles shipped on day one
Than we've ever had in our history
Is a compliment to the most important market
Of the world, the European market
I don't know, that sounds a lot of sucking up to me
Especially since
What?
They've had so many delays, they've had to pay more
They didn't get the 20 YIG model at launch
Oh, and which we'll get into a little bit later
Their backwards compatibility has kind of been
Hurt a little bit
So
I don't know, I think it's kind of stupid
This strikes me as nothing more than fluffy PR
Nothing less, nothing more
This is just nice little sound bite statements
Made by official Sony people to get all over the Europe press
About how freaking important they are blah blah blah
And believe me, listeners abroad
I'm not trying to belittle the situation
But obviously
If Sony cared that much
They would have done things a little differently, correct?
But oh wait, it doesn't stop there
To prove that point
They even went out of their way to give out free TVs
To the first 100 people purchasing the Playstation 3
At their London launch event
Free 46 inch HDTVs
And a free taxi ride home with those
Jesus, that's not a bad deal
Where's my damn TV?
I want to know
Wait, the 100 people that sat out online
Like this incentive to wait in the cold or whatever?
Yeah
So in the US, you have to wait two days
And dodge bullets
Maybe have to race and slam into a pole
And get sent to the hospital in a coma
Exactly, and then in the UK you get free TVs
To go with your gaming systems and stuff
Yeah, Raven's Dolphin in chat says
We get shot, they get TVs, what the fuck?
That's a big PR
Is that just because British people are nicer, or what is that?
Maybe
Is that to encourage people to actually go outside and wait in line or what?
Well, they didn't know that this was going to happen
This was just something that they did
I mean, if they said, hey, by the way, we're going to give away free 46 inch TVs
Everyone would have been there
It would have been like the opening of an Ikea
When Ikea's open, everybody knows
The first people in line get huge certificates
And suddenly the lines are around the block
Yeah
Well, that's interesting, though
That they didn't announce that
Because why wouldn't they announce it
And get the long lines for the media to photograph
So they can go, hey, look how popular the PS3 is in Europe
Even though they had to wait six months for it
But here's the thing, though
If they did something like that, they'd be like, yeah, but it's only because you're giving away free TVs
I mean, it's not because of the PlayStation 3
And they would have just spun it that way
I think this is just kissing ass
It's a whole lot of kissing ass
It's like, please don't be mad at us that we waited so long
And you have to pay more for a system that actually does less
Please don't be mad
Joshi16 says, Sony was eating crayons
They weren't eating crayons
They were just kissing ass
That's all it was
Now, GS68 says, doesn't free stuff, bundles with something up the price
But you're saying these are absolutely free TVs
That they gave away to the first
Absolutely free
Is it the UK Retailer London store?
I think so
It was where they were doing their launch event
Where the Sony president would be heading out the first PS3 type thing
Something like that
I don't know
Anyways, along the lines of that
The UK Retailer game
They were quoted as saying that they were very happy with the amount of supply and demand that they had for the console
And it was actually the first time that they were actually able to fulfill all the demand in short term
So that's something that's never happened before
Sony withheld the release of the PS3 in order to build up stock levels for the launch
The situation with the Xbox 360 was terrible
And the Wii doesn't even hit the sides when it comes in
I think it's a very good move on Sony's part, it won't have that negativity of not being able to supply enough units
So that's good that they're able to supply enough units
I don't know if that's really an issue though
I think the demand is just less for it
Cool that they have enough units out there
Unfortunately though
And it kind of gets into that whole demand thing
Because outside of the launch event
It wasn't so pretty for Sony
In fact, there was a few situations where you only had a few people lining up for the system and no one cared
For example, Virgin Megastore
They had some campers outside
But it was really only about three or so people that were waiting in line for the system
And a lot of other stores, there were some situations where they were breaking street in Italy and stuff like that
And there's also stuff where people were just not coming in pre-ordering or even buying the system at all
So a lot of people said, who cares at this point
I don't know, so it's kind of negative a little bit
What do you think made the UK folks not want to line up for it?
Do you think it was because of what happened over here?
Do you think maybe they just don't get excited like this?
Although I seem to think that I remember the UK folks were lining up for the Wii and everything
They don't want to line up for it because it costs too much and it's a stupid system
There you go
Why? Why is it a stupid system?
Because it has no games on it
It has everything you can get on the 360 except resistance
But Gundam!
Jokes
And the only thing cool about the PS3 is that stupid home thing that's coming out this summer or fall or whatever and I want that
But other than that, it's stupid
Yeah, I think it's a little bit what Shane said, maybe not so harsh
It's not a lot of games out there right now
Not a lot of exclusive stuff that's really must have
It's really one of those systems that maybe it's better off to wait when the price comes down a little bit and there's more of a library
Also, they were kind of getting shafted for a while
A lot of people that were waiting the six months or whatever
Not six months
Four months
Three months to get the system
Probably say, hey, you know what?
Maybe 360 is a little bit better
Maybe I should just pick this up now
Because I can get it now and there's a big library of games out there
Or get the Wii
Making them wait for a while
If they're really itching to get their grasp of the new game systems
They're just going to go someplace else and get something that's out now
I don't know
They're really having a hard time distinguishing themselves as why you need this system
So that's one thing
The UK didn't have the only problems with launches
Australia, the launch wasn't very great over there
In fact, their launch event only drew about 40 people
I had read that a lot of these launch events were getting cancelled
Because of the fear of gunshots and all the crap that happened here
I didn't hear too many of that
But I know the ones that they were talking about in Australia
They had about maybe 40 people show up
Another 30 that were press
And it was pretty much like kind of
I don't know, just people weren't really excited about it
I don't know if it's just because not a lot of people were pre-ordering them
Or just no one really wanted them
Rice Princess, you'd want to comment earlier but got cut off
I know, I was just going to say they're all busy playing Wii bowling
They're too busy to go stand out in line and wait for Sony?
Yeah, because they're playing a good system
Because they're playing Wii bowling, okay
Would you have camped out for this?
No
Let's say you had the money
Let's say you had 600 euros, dollars, whatever right now
Would you go camp out?
No, because I probably already have a Wii
And I don't have a desire to have a PS3
I'd be spending my time on the Wii
I've got a question for you
You've been very vocal about your hate for Xbox on this show previously
Would you buy an Xbox at this point before Playstation 3?
If I had?
In terms of if I had to
Because obviously I wouldn't buy it on my own
But if I had to
Probably
I probably would
Huh, that's a very interesting thing
Miklotov wants to comment, he's dying over there
Why would they be playing Wii bowling?
Because the Wii sucks
I don't like it
Wait a minute, wait so you hate the Wii and the Playstation 3?
Yes, I like the 360
I seem to recall though on this program you were very excited about the Wii
I was
When did this change in heart happen?
Well it was when Nintendo decided that they were too good to release games anymore
And I don't want to play crappy games
And that's all they've been giving us lately
You do this all the time though, to be fair
I distinctly remember you sold your Xbox 360 back for the same reason
How many PS2's have I had?
When Final Fantasy 11 came out you bought a new one eventually
Because you were like, ooh I have to be a corsair because they're pretty
I mean, have you sold your Wii back at this point?
No, but my Wii has been broken since I got it
And I have my little return sticker for Nintendo
I need to call and get a new one actually
But I have no desire to send it back because
What am I going to play on it right now?
Sell it, I mean seriously you can sell it
They're going for a lot of money right now because they can't find them
And people want them
So if you don't want yours, might as well sell it
But at the end of the year you're going to get your Mario Galaxy
Your Metroid, you're going to want one anyway
I have no desire for Mario Galaxy thanks to Sunshine
But Metroid, yeah, Smash Brothers, yeah
Maybe they'll have another color by then
I'm a color whore anyway
I want something you'll talk about later
Let's see
Joshi16 says the exact same thing happened on the DS, don't act surprised
What, the
Oh, I was thinking the color changes, like yeah
But oh, the lack of games
Lack of games
Yeah, but you know what, I could play some good games on like
From Game Boy Advance
I could play GameCube games on this and not be fulfilled
Because GameCube games aren't that good either
Blaze says die, Miklotov die
You can die too
Tetsuya says Miklotov's Wii's been broken
Which SakuraMax follows right up with
Don't worry, Mama will fix it
That's creepy and so quit talking please
For the record
If you listen to last week's program I was all excited about playing Cookie Mama this week
I went to Toys R Us today to try to get it when I bought Tetris
Because I had something to take back so I had a credit there anyway
And they told me it didn't come out until next week
It came out last week
They're retarded
They're just lying to me, to my face
Yeah, they have old information or their shipments didn't come in
Bitch!
It's not, it was not something that was delayed
It's been out there
I've heard the games being crap reviews anyway
I'm a little worried
I saw it, let me put it this way, I saw Blockbuster yesterday
So I know it's out there, I don't know
It just, I looked at it and I'm like
Mama needs to fix her shipping dates, that's what she needs to fix
I'm like, I'm not even going to rent this
No thank you
I know I'm going to buy it because I'm dumb
Cookie Mama on the Wii
Oh my god, that looks so great, I want it
But it's been getting negative reviews everywhere
It looks great but it controls like crap
Why would you be excited for it?
Because you're a woman and you do that already
But not on a DS
On a Wii, stupid!
Or on a Wii, shut up
It's really disappointing that it controls like crap
Because I was hoping that it would be, it looked fun
And the DS one looked fun too
It's just, well there were some control issues
And it really, that frustrates the hell out of you
More comments from chat, I'm really relying on chat tonight
Because I have not been reading the internet this week
Zappy says the original Cookie Mama got bad reviews too
Because it had control issues
It has control issues
Let's see, Skylark makes a good point
And says, luckily Super Paper Mario comes out in a few weeks
What, you're booing Super Paper Mario, Mikotov?
The crap, what's wrong with Super Paper Mario, it looks great
I don't like it because it is a Paper Mario title
And I don't like Paper Mario games
And I know it's a freaking platformer game
But I'm sick of platformers
And I hate everything, so there
Well you heard about the Power Rangers game that's coming out
Just kidding, I got you
Sucker!
Blaze wanted to point out, Mikotov just won my love back, lol
No one makes Power Rangers games anymore
And GS68 says Cooking Milf
Maybe that'll be the sequel, Cooking Milf
That's wrong
Something else is wrong
Is removing the Emotion Engine out of the Playstation 3
To cut down costs
Granted, okay, I will give them this
It does now, they have with the new version 1.6 firmware
The original Playstation 1 and Playstation 2 games
Actually I think more Playstation 2
Are emulated now with the Emotion
Like kind of a software emulation instead of hardware
So of the 2,451 Playstation 2 titles in the European region
Only 1,782 titles work
Which to be honest though
That's a lot better than the 360
That is a lot better than the 360
Of course, what does that really mean?
Because that's a lot of titles
But maybe it's a lot of barbie horse adventures type stuff
Really how much of this stuff am I going to want to play
And which games are working, not working, etc.
And I'm trying to remember here
I want to say of the list that they were saying that weren't working
I want to say Final Fantasy VII, Resident Evil 2, Ratchet and Clank, Metal Gear Solid 2
Those are some of the PS1 games that weren't working
And let's see, big name issues
There was 550 of the games that had noticeable issues
According to Sony
Among the big name titles like Metal Gear Solid, Tomb Raider 2 on the Playstation 1
Final Fantasy X, Kingdom Hearts, Sing Star, Grand Theft Auto, San Andreas on the Playstation 2
Those are all ones that didn't work
Those are all ones that had noticeable issues
Lame
To be fair though
1700 titles for your system that are backwards compatible
A lot better than over 300 for the 360
I guess that's true
They're working on it
So give them some credit, that's a lot more than I was expecting to work with the system
They're doing something right at least
But I still think it's kind of crappy that it's software emulation now
Who cares though, I have one of the original Playstation 3's and it plays on hardware emulation
So who cares
Pardon me for a minute, I have a sidebar issue completely unrelated to take care of
Why is it when I got up to sneak to go use the bathroom
The magic of radio I can get up and leave and you don't even know
But yet I noticed in chat I suddenly said I'm Rob, I'm so flamey blah blah blah
Wow Rob you're amazing
I'm going to let you take a guess who said that
Yeah it was probably Miklotov
You're probably right
They're pointing back and forth at each other
You guys are jerks
Banned from the show forever
It was funny though
With the Playstation 1.6 firmware for the Playstation 3
You got some other stuff
Not just some backwards compatibility
Wait hold on I want to comment on the whole backwards compatibility thing
It sucks
That's all
Well here's the thing
What else is there to say
I don't know it's weird
But at the same time I do feel like if you're going to buy a Playstation 3
You know I called in to All Games Radio very randomly on Tuesday or Wednesday
One of the days before I leave to talk about this
And I kind of made a little joke
Because I don't know they were doing something on there
They were joking that the whole cast of OLR was at the Sony factory doing backwards compatibility
Don't ask I don't remember what it was
So I called in pretending to be at the Sony factory
I made this little joke about
If you're going to buy a Playstation 3 to play all your old Playstation 2 games
Maybe you ought to save $400 fucking dollars and buy a Playstation 2
Right fair
So I don't know why
At one point I do want to go well that kind of sucks
You can't play all your old games
But seeing as the system doesn't really upscale it yet
Like it was supposed to right
Actually the software emulation will allow it to upscale
So that is good
But it's not that big a deal
It's not that big a deal
It's not going to suddenly make your games HD beautiful blah blah blah
It's just going to be a little bit smoother
Honestly ask yourself
I mean really if you've got a Playstation 3
And you're really gearing to play some next gen games
Are you really playing Playstation 1 games?
I'm not I have Playstation 2 games
I have a Playstation 2 as well
I don't touch the thing
I don't play any of those games
I'm playing new stuff
If I really want to go back and play Kingdom Hearts 2 or whatever
I'll play it on my Playstation 2
I mean Playstation 2's are still selling really well
Exactly
They're sort of readily available out there
And they're not that expensive
And they'll probably drop in price again
Once we get down to Christmas time again
At the same time though
I do get a little irritated
Like when Xbox 360 talks about how they're going to abandon
Pretty much the old Xbox stuff come 2008
I think we had a story on that last week
And I know people go
Well why don't you just play it on your old Xbox blah blah blah blah
But I don't know
Sometimes I don't feel like cooking
I don't feel like cooking the game systems
So it is kind of convenient sometimes to be able to do the backwards compatibility thing
It is
And it's a nice thing that they've added
I mean since I think was it
The Playstation 2 was the first system to actually do that
And it was a great selling point
It plays all your Playstation 1 games
It actually makes them run a little bit better
You can do better graphics or you know
Better load times
So that was kind of cool
Which I might add
Playstation 3 load times kind of suck on certain games
If you were going to install it through the hard drive that would be really nice
But either way
It's still
I would say though
1700 games working for your system is a lot better than 300
Okay
That's something that they've got
But the Xbox did not have as big of a library as the Playstation 2
Because they didn't have anything before Xbox
Microsoft didn't compete with Playstation 1
And really I'm hoping that they do stick on
You know
The backwards compatibility instead of just saying
Ah fuck it you know we got this mini to work so
That's it
We're done
SSJ100Matt says it's funny that Microsoft killed the Xbox One right away
And Playstation 1 and Playstation 2 are still around
I don't know so much about Playstation 1
But certainly Playstation 2 still got quite a bit of life
It seems left in it
Oh yeah
I don't know if God of War 2 is like it's last gasp of air
Or if that's going to be the last big game
That may be the last Sony game
That may be the last games throughout the year
That are coming out for the Playstation 2
And I'm sure we'll get Sudoku Master for years to come
On Playstation 2
I played a lot of Sudoku
When you don't have a PSP or a DS
It's all about Sudoku
It's cheap to develop for
That's what it is
It's the one system that has the largest user base out there
Over three times of what the 360 has
And of course they're going to still make games for it
I mean 30 million people have the damn system
It would be dumb not to make games for it
But I mean certain games like the new Ghost Recon games
And stuff like that
You just can't do them on the Playstation 2
You've got to cut your costs
Either make the next gen version look pretty
Or just skip the current gen one
Maybe do something like EA is doing
Like Medal of Honor Vanguard for the Wii and Playstation 2
And then make a new one
Medal of Honor Airborne
For the Playstation 3 and the Xbox 360
That way everybody's happy
And they've saved their costs a little bit on the games
That don't necessarily need the huge graphic budgets
And stuff like that
Let me quickly go to another sidebar comment
And then we'll get back into the news here
The comments from the chat room
This is an interesting conversation
JVmon says, if you have a Playstation 3
Why the hell are you still playing Final Fantasy 7?
And then ShadowNextGen says, JVmon Final Fantasy 7 is a classic
That I will always play
And then moving on
Let's see, JVmon says then play it on your Playstation 2
And Hippolytus says this
He says, I for example never owned a Playstation
I think he means PS1
But now that I have a Playstation 2
I can play Playstation 1 games
But that begs the comment
How many people do you know that's actually going to go get a Playstation 3
Who never had a Playstation 2?
But I do know of one person
I do have a friend who's considering getting a Playstation 3
And he never had a Playstation 2 or a Playstation 1
He's thinking about getting it
Because he can play all the backwards compatible stuff
In this country you still can
If this is a big concern for them
I would recommend that they do
And it's going to be a different SKU
Or a slightly different item
Not item member
They're Sony item members
Either way, you're going to be able to look on the box
And tell which version of the Playstation 3 this is
The one that has
One of the original launch ones
Or one of the ones that got the
65 nanometer chips in them
And it's software emulation now
So if it's a real big concern for your backwards compatibility
Make sure you get one of the older ones
And that's all you really need to do
Or buy an older one that's used or something
I'd recommend that's the case
Because really it's going to drop in price
Probably in the fall
I mean they probably will need to
Especially if Microsoft drops their price
But the thing is
That it's going to come at a cost
You're not going to have that chip on there
And they've already said they're going to take it out
For the US ones
So if it's a real big deal for you
Maybe spend the extra money
I mean it's either that or you're going to spend another
$99 on a Playstation 2
So pick your poison
I mean this way you get a larger hard drive
With it at the same time
You can buy a more expensive system or something
I don't know
Anyways
So back to the Playstation 3 1.6
Oh firmware that's out there
Finally they've added
Background downloading
Something that they should have had from the beginning
Because this thing downloads like
Fucking slow
Well to be fair 360 didn't have it at first
It badly needed it too
But I would have hoped that since
The Playstation 3 came out a year later
That they would kind of learn from
I'll give you that
Either way so now it does work
And it is confirmed that it will work
While you're watching a blu-ray movie
Or playing an offline game
Not an online game
Basically the same rules as a 360
So that's kind of cool
Another thing
Well and also kind of another thing
Why would you really need background downloading
Because there's not a lot to download on the store right now
So anyways
Another thing that does add
And this is kind of neat
Is that folding at home
That basically the kind of program
That runs in the background to help
Crunch numbers to figure out
How to come up with cures for diseases and whatnot
Interesting enough
This was released this week
The firmware update
And already the Playstation 3
Is processing a lot more
Numbers than anything else
In fact even more than
Most of the Windows PC's out there
Right now they are currently
Doing what was it
251 teraflops
Which you know that's
100 trillion
More than
They were saying that
The Playstation 3 machines are delivering
Over 251 trillion
Floating point operations per second
100 trillion more than
10 times the number of
Active PC CPU's
Is this folding at home thing
Forgive my ignorance a little bit
Because I don't have a Playstation 3 so I haven't been really following this very much
But is this something that you
It automatically kind of stealth installs in your Playstation 3
And just runs without you knowing it
I think you have to download this
Or it's basically a
I'm not sure if it's included with the update
If it is included with the update it's a program you have to run
It runs almost like a screen saver
And it will crunch numbers
But yet for a PC
You would have to elect to download this
And kind of seek it out right
Yes but the thing is though you have to run it
In order for it to actually run
It's not something that will run automatically
So
Kind of like distributed net
Because I used to run that back in college
It's basically like the old study at home
Little cow icon
Except you know now instead of searching
For extraterrestrial life
Because I guess they gave up on that
Instead of that they're looking to
You know
Cure cancer
I can't wait for the press release
When one of these Playstation 3's
Happens to crunch the magical number
To cure cancer
Sony cures cancer
I mean I can see that PR right now
Joshi16 in chat says
Cure cancer
1000 gamer points and a home trophy
There you go
Yeah I want the cure cancer trophy
Anyways
On to a completely different system and subject
This rumor of the
Black Xbox 360 just will never die
And it's now confirmed to be real
Probably why the rumor never died
And the latest issue of Game Informer magazine
Which further goes to show
Microsoft rumors 90% of the time
Unless you made it up yourself
Microsoft rumors are always true
Always true
It has been announced at least through
According to the article in Game Informer
Not officially announced yet but anyways
An HDMI enabled black unit
Is coming out for $479
It's going to be a limited edition
In black it will be in white later
But limited edition for
Yeah $479
And
It's supposed to have a larger hard drive
120 gigabytes
And other rumored options with this
Is that it's supposed to also have black accessories
Coming out for it
So eventually you'll see different colored controllers and whatnot
And one thing also they were talking about
Is the IPTV is supposed to be enabled in it as well
So that's something interesting
If you've already spent the money though
On your 360
You'll be happy to know there will be a larger hard drive
Coming out for under $200
And the other rumor with that is
That there is going to be a data cable included with the new 360
And a new hard drive that will allow you to be able to hook up your old hard drive
To transfer any saves you have
So I hope that's true
Well Microsoft rumors usually end up being true
So that would make sense
But interesting
I don't know I can't get too excited about the black Xbox 360
Because I think well the first Xbox was black and nobody cared
Well it's going to be called the elite
I mean that's what they're calling it right now
The core system is not going away
The premium system is not going away
It's basically this is just going to be another skew that's added on
And eventually it will become a white system
I'm not sure if it's going to replace the premium system or not
But they're going to eventually all be white
So I don't know it's interesting
Hopefully we'll see a price drop for the core
Because that would be kind of nice
I heard they're ditching the core
I don't know
I would think they would because they want to urge people to download movies and stuff
So that means you have to have a hard drive right
Yeah but at the same time they want to still be able to compete against the Wii and stuff
I mean they've got to have that lower price point out there
Drop the premium to $299 there you go
Yeah that would be good
I think if they do a price drop to drop it to $299
They could keep the core around for like $199 or something like that
If they're not going to keep it around then so be it
So they'll have a unit that's not out there
Shadownextgen says a new Xbox 360 hard drive for under $200 equals $199.99
If I were to guess actually
I can't remember because originally the core system
It was $299 and the hard drive is $99
So that would equal $399 roughly
This is $479
So I don't know
Core system plus new hard drive
I'm guessing the hard drive is $179.99
That would be my guess
Blaze says Sky new colors always make people go ooooh
I don't know I kind of like the white because for my setup it's kind of nice
Because my Ikea TV table is a light color
And then you have the white Wii on one side and the white Xbox 360 on the other side
Everything looks nice
Rob you got to understand though people are stupid and they will buy different colored stuff
I can understand for the HDMI cable the bigger hard drive and that stuff
I don't know I'm not going to get it
I might get the new hard drive or something if I really need it or something
But I don't need the HDMI my TV doesn't have HDMI so that's a big deal
Black I couldn't give a crap if the thing was bright green or pink or something
Who cares
Ravenstaufen wants to know if you've seen this through your insider sources
Nope because certain companies will not talk about stuff before it needs to be out there
Certain companies are a little better about keeping tabs on that stuff than others
Microsoft, Nintendo, Sony they're an expert in the PR department
And they will not leak crap like this out there
In fact I'm surprised that it would even be out there in some of those system stuff
Unless they're doing like test stuff I don't know
But yeah this stuff will not be out there until they want it to be out there
Anyways
So other stuff about that
Well actually they don't really have anything else other than that
Hopefully April I mean it's not that far away so
If we're going to hear an update about this it's going to be pretty damn soon
So keep your eyes peeled for an actual press release about this
And hopefully more exciting stuff to come from
Does Microsoft have any events coming up in April where they could drop this bombshell
No but I think they're getting close to the end of their fiscal year
So I don't know
That might be good to make boost stock prices or something
Anyways on to the final new system out there the Wii
They are getting the final version of the internet channel towards the end of April
And it's supposed to be having some more features added to it
I believe they're improving the
Like getting rid of that goddamn bar that sits at the bottom of your page?
I hope so I can't remember I have to find the exact details for it
But I remember improved zooming auto resizing of text
I think they're improving the little virtual keyboard that's on there
So that has like some more preset stuff like www. and html and stuff like that
So that stuff on there
Hopefully they're removing the little bar on there
And I think they're extending the free web browser until June now
Well that's a nice thing to do considering a lot of people that want to get Wii still can't get them
The web browser is five bucks when they start charging for it
I don't know I can't see how that would be
You know the Wii web browser has been getting a little bit of play in this house
Because we use it for YouTube
When there's like seven people over we want to show something funny on YouTube
Like hey look at this Kelly video on YouTube because you're the only person on the planet that still hasn't seen it
We'll go to YouTube and bring it up on the TV and it's kind of cool except for that bar
That sits at the bottom of the page and kind of eats up all the space
Or porno tube
Or porno tube is also yeah I remember the New Year's party good times
Good times
Yes it's a gateway to porn
Anyways
Back on the subject of the Wii here
EAA announced a brand new game for the Wii called Boogie
This was I think we had covered a story
They were talking about how there was going to be a 70's style music game coming out for the Wii
And I believe this is it
Is this the harmonix partnership?
No
Because there's that going on too right?
I seem to remember last week there was some sort of from game developers conference
EA said we're going to get in bed with harmonix for one game type thing going on
Is this related?
I don't think this has anything to do with harmonix
Alright just curious
It's basically a Wii exclusive game and you're going to be using the nunchuck as well as the remotes to disco dance
And your character kind of looks almost like I don't know definitely not human
But there's these evil looking peak men things in the background
Everybody disco dancing
So it's interesting what they're doing with that
Could be kind of fun I don't know
So I'm looking forward to it
That should be out later this year of course no specific anything
Still a little vague for me
I want to know more about like you know were there videos out there of people playing it
Pictures
Looks pretty good
Another thing that was announced or at least reconfirmed
Guitar Hero for the Wii is supposed to be coming out
And they're saying that they're going to actually be doing controllers as well that look like guitars
Not a big surprise
And yeah kind of going back to when they were talking about
Wait they're going to make controllers that look like guitars?
That's what they were saying
But wouldn't that be a given because Guitar Hero uses a guitar controller
Or are they saying that feasibly you're going to be able to play this game with no special controller
I think they're actually making new controllers for it
Because
Yeah they said it says the Colt rhythm game Guitar Hero is on its way to the Wii it comes with a guitar shaped controller
And plays convincingly enough to make you think you're making real music
Hopefully we'll get the actual guitar and not pretend we're up
So it's speculation never mind
So no idea if they're going to actually have a real guitar thing
I would hope that they're going to if they want to cut costs you know
Just make a plugin for like the Wiimote you know stick it in there
I mean because the things made to build off of it you know that's why they have that stupid little
Almost like a USB thing on the bottom for all those attachments
Build something that works onto it like slide the guitar or the Wiimote into the guitar
I don't like this whole thinning of the Guitar Hero franchise amongst all the consoles you know
I already passed on Guitar Hero 2 for Playstation because I knew the 360 version was coming
And now I don't know I don't know what the Wii version is going to have to really have something special to make me want to buy another guitar controller
And another you know I kind of wish they would put out a guitar that would just work on all the systems
Kind of like you can get DDR pads to do that
Yeah
I'll be nice
Then let's see here have one more story and I think you talked about this a little bit last week Rob
And it's been finally confirmed a Nintendo rep has confirmed individual friends list for the Wii titles
So yes they have worked they have done nothing to change the fucking hassle that was DS friends list system
And basically they've said I can confirm that the friend code system in the Wi-Fi connection service for the Wii will be the same as it was for the Nintendo DS
Meaning game specific friend codes and separate friends rosters are used in each game where players can play with identified friends
As with the Nintendo DS the system was created to ensure gaming environment is kept fun for everyone
Except for the people that have to enter in the 5000 codes for each damn game
Retarded
I just I don't know I talked about this so I was blue in the face last night I just don't get it
Rice Brothers you weren't here last week what do you think of this whole friend codes thing on the Wii
That you're going to have to basically enter in your friend code every time to get new players
What that's dumb
Like you do on the DS right you know how you do that on the DS you enter a friend code now you have to do the same thing on the Wii
Even though we already put in friend codes to send the messages back and forth you have to do it for every single game
Because heaven forbid you get a I don't know a predator on Wii or something
I hope I hope that these that this is something that's not required for like third parties or something this this could be fun
I'm fine with the first party stuff if they're doing what they want to do that great but I you know so far with like Konami
They have a little bit so we connect 24 stuff you know I'm I don't know I don't well I guess that's not really playing with anyone online though
That's just exchanging like levels or something so I still think it's retarded though it why would you want to be a friend in one game and not another
I why it doesn't make any sense no sense whatsoever I don't understand why they have to complicate things
And I'm sure they got an over you know what was the response to the DS one I mean no one I think actually was positive on it
Everyone was like this fucking sucks so what would make you decide hmm people really hated it before let's do it again that'd be awesome
I mean really what was the thought behind this I don't get it
Maybe there wasn't any thought
I mean people aren't really being kidnapped with the goddamn DS I mean seriously
Skylark says friend codes are horrible haven't Nintendo learned anything I'd rather take the risk of meeting child molesters than not be able to play online at all
And really how hard is it anyways to add someone I mean you just put in a friend code it's basically like accepting like hitting yes or something
I mean people you they won't people can add you to their friends list but you have to add them back first so it would be just like you know if I send a friend request to somebody they don't have to agree to do it
So why just leave it as yes no instead of numbers I don't know why you have to complicate things
Maury in our chat room live on this Sunday evening at chat.org.com says it's a really flawed system especially considering Nintendo's justification
Qwhat5565 says Nintendo can't be that stupid they have to be coming out with an easier add-on maybe a report button
Well I mean here let me put it this way we still got time until the first you know online game comes out this could change before then
But not really because we've had Elibits and that worked fine but I know you don't play versus or whatever but
I'm just saying right now though they could change I hope they change it I mean I really do because it's just a pain in the ass it really is
I'm glad that they want to protect the children out there from you know child molesters and stuff to be honest I don't think you're really gonna have that problem
Because you don't have video chat you don't really have voice chat you don't have even normal chat it's just fucking exchanging messages back and forth like you know email
I don't see what the big deal is just just put yes or no I mean is that so hard instead of having to enter and people put their damn friend codes on websites anyways
And they exchange them that way so how is that any different than you know yes or no
You know what we should do is create a website childmolesterfriendcodes.com and like encourage you know people to use the friend code systems to meet child molesters
Obviously I'm joking people but you know I mean Loki brings up a good point you can trade codes online with complete strangers who might turn out to be people you don't expect them to be I don't get it
I don't get it either because if you know someone ends up being creepy or something you delete their friend code or for example with Xbox Live you just befriend them
Whoa that's
Or push the button that reports them it's not that hard although I know a lot of people don't use it
I mean how hard is it I mean people oh no people are gonna send you like stupid messages oh it's so hard to just delete them I mean
I just don't understand why they have to make extra hoops to jump through for a system that can be so simple
Rant rant rant rant rant jumpman says historically Nintendo hasn't been great with new technology look at the virtual boy
Skylark says how do they honestly think friend codes are a good idea if they do anything they prevent us from playing together totally not we
Making a little play on that play together line get it GS68 says how to meet child molesters come down to the Silicon Valley area and take the line 22 bus after 10pm
Well here's the thing it's like okay I have a huge list of friends or whatever that you know I've got in my Wii system right now
I get you know not that I would actually play Pokemon I get Pokemon battle revolution or something like that great I want to play against my friends
Oh no wait no I can't do that because I have to email all my damn friends now with the Wii system and say hey what's your friend code for Pokemon battle revolution
Because I can't play you until you know I get this so it may take me a couple days before I'm actually able to play the game online with friends
Hooray mission accomplished you've really you know embraced online
Well I think there's only one thing left to say about all of this
That would be the FUs of the week for the second week in a row inspired by Nintendo friend codes
No dark soccer tonight so Loki you get first dibs
My FU goes to drama I hate drama and I hate drama that's unnecessary I'll leave it at that for now
My FU goes to bullies they come in all shapes and sizes and fortune 500 sizes and bullies are not cool
And double standards suck as well I really hate double standards I really really really really hate when you see one thing applied this way here
And then it's applied totally or a blind eye is turned over here I think that's stupid
That's all. Rice Princess do you have anything you want to share?
Well I second both of your FUs but yes so FU to immaturity yes that's pretty much it I'm not going to get into specifics yep
Oh and one last thing some very vague FUs this week FU to the last Mimsy because it just got ridiculous towards the end really ridiculous
Some chat room folks are entering honorary FUs on behalf of dark sakura for not being here
Joshi16 says dark sakura FU to fucking drivers drivers suck I hate them they should die in a fire Kingdom Hearts rules no FU to them
That's great oh drunami says FU to e-sluts on myspace yes amen you know I've been gone for 4 days so I logged into myspace I swear to god 15 e-sluts that is going to kill myspace just like slowness killed fredster it really is
It would not be that hard for myspace to institute some way to get around that
I think they kind of are right now
Well they have that whole thing where you can know my last name and get around it that way so I'm thinking about putting this big thing on my profile that says my last name is roberts
You know because I've used my fake last name that I use on the radio on myspace profile so that people in my real life I don't want to find me can't find me because they don't know my stage name
So I'm thinking about just putting that really big so that the cam girls are cool and they can't at least shut it off turn it on for a little while and hopefully it will get them to stop hitting my profile I don't know
Just do what I do robin just not check myspace after you know once every 2 weeks or something because by the time you get back there most of the profiles have been deleted anyways
I like getting the ads from listeners of the show and things of that you know and people that I you know meet in my real life who I tell how to find my profile and all that stuff
You know I like getting that I don't like having to wait through the cam horse to do it but that's you know there's that all games community site which is pretty rad as well
Rice Princess you should sign up for that because they talk games on there a lot
Did you? I don't know well maybe you did it while I've been gone I haven't checked the site in a few days there could have been some great blog posts I don't even know
I have some game review haikus I have to catch up on for the community site so that's community.allgames.com our buddies over there at all games have set up there their answer to myspace minus the cam horse plus all the gaming chat
Really? Yes it's good times
But I might have to go there
You'll probably get a lot of friend ads because OMG a chick
Oh ok
I'm going to go in as a dude
You get a lot of cool people over there it's a good community because all listeners of this show and all games and you know all the other shows that are on allgames.com about the six or seven other indie podcasts they have that are on that network so it's cool
Yeah I'll check it out
Good times
Ok Tigerclaw wants to know if I check the games and porn community site as well apparently all games has these two spin off community sites one of them is rhythm nation which is for like music based games and the other one is games and porn
I've not looked at games and porn yet but rice princess that sounds right up your alley
It totally is
You might have to check that out
Or just the porn
So no more news this segment Loki?
That's it for part A
Saving the good stuff for part B?
A little bit yeah
Alright well then we're going to take a little break here on Orange Lounge Radio we'll be back in a little bit with more including our part B and if you listen to us on the podcast feed keep in mind you have to wait just a couple days for part B
That way you get your OLR spaced out throughout the week so we get a little bit to get you through the work day or the commute or the jog however you listen to us you get a little bit on Mondays and you get a little more on Wednesdays
For those of you guys listening live though you only have to wait a few minutes and we'll be right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio
Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcasted to the world twice a week
Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio