[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft,
[SPEAKER_12]: And how Sony's winning a lot of people back over thanks to their announcements about home Well, what about Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, Nintendo basically made only two unveilings in their conference at GDC And that was a new Mario Galaxy trailer and the fact that it would be out this year And a type of, I don't know what you'd want to call it, Mii Idol or something like that Basically a, do you like this Mii, it's like a Mii popularity channel
[SPEAKER_12]: has been announced for the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not a lot of announcements outside of that, but then again, a lot of people are saying, ah, Nintendo, you guys suck, Sony made all these announcements, and Nintendo, you didn't do crap.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, keep in mind, folks, it was Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_12]: What did Miyamoto talk about?
[SPEAKER_12]: He talked about the waifu meter, he talked about how Mario 128 kind of evolved into the game Pikmin, he talked about game development types of things.
[SPEAKER_12]: On that end, Nintendo really didn't disappoint, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, you know, if you were there looking for the E3 Bangin' Fireworks press conference, I guess you were going to be a little disappointed.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, of course, we remember that story last week that said, hey, Nintendo's got some stock things going on.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're not going to be able to make any big announcements at GDC, whether they want to or not.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, unfortunately, the only little trinkets you got there from Nintendo were those two things.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, curious, what do you guys think about that?
[SPEAKER_12]: Did either of you guys watch the new Galaxy trailer?
[SPEAKER_12]: What did you think of it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_12]: Mario Galaxy because it looks like you can flip 2D to 3D at a touch of a button like if you're playing the 2D thing and like you see a wheel thing like there was one video I saw like a wheel spiked wheel was coming at you you hit a button to go to 3D and then you can run around the wheel and then you go back to the 2D mode it's so crazy I liked it it was very cool so that was something I'm looking forward to way more than any of the other stuff that was talked about unfortunately I don't know Smash Brothers I'll give Mario Galaxy a try of course I want my Smash Brothers we'll see
[SPEAKER_12]: Again, if you want to give your comments in chat, it's chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the second time I've done this show.
[SPEAKER_12]: Chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm out of it tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Something's wrong.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's something in the water I'm drinking tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actdeft says, Super Paper Mario for the win.
[SPEAKER_12]: Blackwolf was at Game Developers Conference and played Super Paper Mario.
[SPEAKER_12]: He says, Super Paper Mario equals fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: The A button goes to 3D.
[SPEAKER_09]: Joshi says Super Paper Mario is when I get a Wii so it looks like a lot of folks are very excited SSJ100Matt says yay more channels but how about Galaxy, Smash, and Metroid there's your comments from chat anyways this week we saw some pretty good stuff coming to the virtual console including Super Ghouls and Ghosts and that was of course very fucking hard as usual and of course Sword of Vermillion um
[SPEAKER_09]: and Elevator Action for the, well, that was on the NES.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this week, though, what are we going to be getting?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, from what I've been hearing, I think Sonic Spinball was among those.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know it was on the Japan launch there, at least what they're getting this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if I remember correctly, they also were getting Excitebike and Legend of the Mystical Ninja.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that was on the website, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: So maybe that is on its way.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they saw Spinball there too, if I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, you're going to expect about three games tomorrow or Monday.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anything on Virtual Console that you were dying for still not out?
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I got Kid Icarus, so I kind of got my wish.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have R-Type.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I know, but anything not out that you still want?
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, obviously Guardian Legend, but realistically something from either Nintendo itself or one of their very close third-party developers.
[SPEAKER_12]: Snow Brothers.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's an interesting choice.
[SPEAKER_12]: I remember that game, actually.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would like to see, and I know Jamie hates this one, but I really like Strider on the NES.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't say I hated it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was actually, the game was based off of the Strider manga.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought you told me once you hated it because the arcade one is so much better.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't say I hate it, just the arcade one is so much better.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wouldn't it be neat, though, one week to get Strider on NES and Strider on Genesis?
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be kind of cool, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mega Man would be my other wish.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, they need some Mega Man games on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: It would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, Capcom just needs some more stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would think it would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was a fan of this game, at least.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uniracers?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: No one really played that game for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm looking at chat room here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course, you bring up Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_12]: Everyone makes their list of demands.
[SPEAKER_12]: James Patrick says Secret of Mana.
[SPEAKER_12]: Secret of Mana, and Evermore.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mori says Earthbound, please.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ryoma says Ice Climbers.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, Ice Climbers is already up.
[SPEAKER_12]: Go check it out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Unless he was referring to something else, but I think that's what it was.
[SPEAKER_12]: Salamander.
[SPEAKER_12]: Life Force in this country, but yeah, that would be cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actdeft says Kirby Superstar.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mel B on our staff says Tecmo Bowl, but will it be licensed?
[SPEAKER_12]: Not likely.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think they should just leave it in there with the old, like, 88 lineup or whatever that game had in it.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_12]: Then you could still play us the 49ers and actually be good because it's 1988.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was a sports joke.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't make those very often.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was a sports joke for you guys out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, for those who are disgusted with Rob's sports jokes, no, not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: This has absolutely nothing to do with sports.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have Chocobo Tales coming out in...
[SPEAKER_05]: May in the UK, that is, it's coming out April 3rd here in the US, but you play as a chocobo, and you have to, you know, stop the bad guy from, you know, I guess being all evil, even though he's all evil.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you go around and you do minigames, and you build up a deck in card battles and save the universe on your DS through the Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, um,
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fantasy 2 U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: Forge of Japan
[SPEAKER_12]: You would have to use the big carrot when it came up on the screen and said, Smells like Chocobo.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you kind of always wondered, what the hell does a Chocobo smell like?
[SPEAKER_12]: Does it smell like farts or roses or what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Smells like chicken shit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Kentucky Fried Chicken?
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's Kentucky Faraga Chocobo.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: No price announced here yet, but I guess based off those prices, you could speculate $34, $39.99, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be a fair statement.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess something to compete with the PSP a little bit, although this is not included with the DS.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's kind of something extra.
[SPEAKER_12]: But if you've ever wanted to surf the Internet while on the go on your DS, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would not buy that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not feeling this.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm really not.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what would have been cool?
[SPEAKER_12]: If I had the internet channel on my Wii, then I could beam it over to my DS.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever happened to that functionality?
[SPEAKER_12]: Wasn't that something they said you could do at one point?
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that the DS would interface with the Wii?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they're going to have that with some future games, but they may add that later.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have a feeling that's something up their sleeve.
[SPEAKER_12]: DS demos on your Wii a little later on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But one thing I was going to say is I think that they've done this probably better at homebrew.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_09]: Really, the only problem and the reason why they don't have a lot of the Flash support and stuff is because there's not enough RAM in the system and there's no storage.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just pretty much the cart itself, which doesn't hold that much.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you would probably need to have some sort of Game Boy Advance thing plugged in the bottom.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, I think that's what they did in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: A couple different versions of that, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: Joshi16 wants to know, is there going to be an OLR DS page?
[SPEAKER_12]: Since we have the PSP page and a Wii one in the works.
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think that many people are going to be using that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe like five people would use it, if even that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do we even have five listeners of Orange Launch Radio?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think we do, actually, so I don't think there'd be a lot of point to do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Five listeners of Orange Launch Radio?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we have more than that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe a handful, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: The first episode we only had five listeners, but my how we've grown since then.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you guys so much for supporting us over the years.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know our fifth anniversary is coming up in just two months.
[SPEAKER_12]: Two months is the station, but I think we're actually going to celebrate it with the first live show, which was June 23rd, 2002.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: So last week we talked about how the Wii didn't have me support for third parties.
[SPEAKER_09]: And now this week, SNK's president says that they're not letting third parties have online capabilities either.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which is funny, because Sega's got a Pachinko game coming out that does have online and does have Mii support.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I basically ask, are they just not letting SNK have online support or Mii support?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because to be honest, I mean, and I'm sure everyone can agree with me,
[SPEAKER_09]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well, let's go on to another topic, shall we?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this is something that we've been, of course, talking about since the announcement of having our E3 taken from us.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there is going to be E3 this year, if you were invited, it's July 11th through 13th.
[SPEAKER_05]: To quote the invite, it says, The opportunity to engage in one-on-one meetings with leading game company executives in an intimate setting as well as network, socialize, and test pilot major company offerings.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I got invited.
[SPEAKER_12]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, if it works out for me, I'm going to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm actually...
[SPEAKER_05]: I sort of do see more now of the logic and them changing it to more of a meeting base.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we're still going to have the demos and such.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just not going to be the big over-the-top production that E3 was in the past.
[SPEAKER_09]: And not really many people have figured out why people are getting invited.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was actually looking just earlier today.
[SPEAKER_12]: Joystick ran an interesting story on the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: And apparently they're saying, they said here in the story, this week that some journalists received their invites, but many did not.
[SPEAKER_12]: And interesting enough,
[SPEAKER_12]: Jamie did get an invite, and so did someone else on our staff who works behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_12]: But Loki and I have not.
[SPEAKER_12]: So where's the love, you guys?
[SPEAKER_12]: I know there's some developers out there that listen to us.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sniff, sniff, cry, cry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Send us an email.
[SPEAKER_12]: We want to go.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll interview you, have you on the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll play Beat the Host with you.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll bring our rig.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, but I do hope...
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just like a lot of times we didn't go to... I mean, we went to meetings for some things, but I got a lot of accomplishments with booth tours and stuff like that and actually meeting people face-to-face instead of just actually having meetings and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob went to meetings with me.
[SPEAKER_12]: At this point, it's really all speculation.
[SPEAKER_12]: We just don't know how they're picking it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It might also have to do with how you registered.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: Shifting gears completely here, going from E3 to talk about politics a little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Game Politics ran a story earlier this week about the video games made me do it defense.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, apparently what happened is that this 19-year-old Patrick Morris actually shot his 15-year-old boy with a shotgun and used the good old excuse, the video games made me do it.
[SPEAKER_12]: and his mom even tried to go in there and say, he would just go into his room and play those video games.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, the prosecution brought out Dr. Michael Knapp from Ashland, Oregon, and he said it was ridiculous to blame video games.
[SPEAKER_12]: Moreover, he said while you usually can't predict violent behavior, other risk factors in Morris' life, such as his drug use and emotional disorders, were much stronger factors.
[SPEAKER_12]: So after 30 minutes of deliberations, the judge sentenced Morris to life imprisonment
[SPEAKER_12]: in prison.
[SPEAKER_12]: The video games made me do it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Defense carried no weight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha!
[SPEAKER_12]: As well, it should have not had any weight because that's a stupid defense.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because it was the hip-hop music that did it.
[SPEAKER_09]: No one made you press the power button, asshole.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was the hip-hop music game that made me do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all Def Jam Icon's fault.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was Def Jam Icon, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, if anything makes me want to go out and get a shotgun and shoot people, it would probably be Sonic on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know about you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Please don't take me literally.
[SPEAKER_12]: I hope you guys know I'm joking.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, sometimes we talk about harming the certain beta testers of online functions in, say, portable Grand Theft Auto games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you fucking sucked at it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyways, one thing, though, that's going to make people, especially Sega, make some more games is this online poll that they have where they're trying to figure out the interests of...
[SPEAKER_09]: Night would be awesome
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, I think it would be really good, though, to move on to something else that doesn't have to do with video game news.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, Rob?
[SPEAKER_12]: What would that be?
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ah, but don't our emailers sometimes email us with video game-related things?
[SPEAKER_12]: I would hope so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometimes, but I ignore it.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, well, let's open up the old mailbag and see what's in store.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to email us, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Today's first email actually comes from GrinWithoutACat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: and 45 million sold in Europe.
[SPEAKER_05]: The slimline model is actually sold better in Europe than anywhere else, with 18 million against North America's 16 million and Japan's 6 million.
[SPEAKER_05]: Europe also seems to be the one who takes a mis-interest in their casual and innovative games such as iToy, SingStar, and Buzz, a quiz game with buzzer peripherals.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: It seems like every week we're getting some type of email from a European listener, and understandably so, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_12]: But a European listener who's a little bit upset because they're constantly getting screwed by the game companies.
[SPEAKER_12]: So unfortunately I don't have an easy answer for you on that one.
[SPEAKER_12]: But thank you for the insight.
[SPEAKER_12]: We do appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that was actually a very well thought out email.
[SPEAKER_05]: So thank you for sending it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next one comes up is from BearWhoDriveCar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please make Sky stop attempting accents, especially British.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is all.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I don't know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob, your accent really is awful.
[SPEAKER_11]: Carry on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Would you like to go out and have some tea?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's really awful.
[SPEAKER_11]: BearWhoDriveCar, would you like to go out and have some tea?
[SPEAKER_11]: A spot of tea?
[SPEAKER_11]: Or are you going to continue to be a tit?
[SPEAKER_05]: Next up comes from Cy.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is DearOLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, Grin.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, on my World of Warcraft server, there's a guild called LessQQMorePewPew.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys rock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: The OLR guild is on Ravencrest, by the way.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want more information, go to the forums.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although that is a great name for a guild, LessQQMorePewPew.
[SPEAKER_12]: I should look that up on the armory.
[SPEAKER_05]: So how about this?
[SPEAKER_05]: This one comes from Ali.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I thought I would voice a few opinions on your cynicism toward the PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: My brother had the opportunity to play a PS3 a couple of days ago, and he told me it was really a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe he played Resistance, Fall of Man, and Gran Turismo HD.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now granted, my brother is a pretty hardcore gamer.
[SPEAKER_05]: He pulled strings to get himself an Xbox 360 at launch, got a PS2 at launch, etc.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now I thought I would remind you of the PS2 launch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everyone told us we were crazy for spending that much on a game system, and the Dreamcast was so much better.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also remember reading that the emotion engine was nigh impossible to program for.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, once time passed, the PS2 gained traction price-wise.
[SPEAKER_05]: The price stayed even as Flint inflation went on, and people cracked how to get the most out of their EE.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, look at the PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everyone says the 360 is 100 times better, that the cell is near impossible to program for, and that it was too expensive.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that will happen in a year or two.
[SPEAKER_05]: The PS2 will see a revival and will take the market.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other than that, I literally got my 360 a half hour ago, and I got Crackdown, Call of Duty 3, Gears of War, Saints Row, and Test Drive Unlimited.
[SPEAKER_05]: The reason I'm telling you this is that I want some music games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard that DDR for 360 wasn't too good, and as far as I can tell, Guitar Hero 2 is not on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Will Guitar Hero come out for the Xbox 360, and is DDR any good on 360?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it is coming out on 360.
[SPEAKER_12]: I believe April is the big month for Guitar Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Insert usual love the show drivel here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Boom Boom Rocket, I don't know much about, but people that have gotten their hands on it say if you like music games, you're going to like yourself some Boom Boom Rocket.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know when that'll be out, though, knowing the release schedule.
[SPEAKER_12]: It could be summer.
[SPEAKER_12]: It could be the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_12]: DDR on the 360 is actually, it's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just components of it are bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: But the game itself, the main core element of the game, I mean, what's DDR?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's songs and steps.
[SPEAKER_12]: The songs are great, and the steps are great.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a fine game.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just all the other stuff around it, like quest mode, sucks, and some of the other stuff is not so hot.
[SPEAKER_12]: But the game itself is fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: It depends how much do you love DDR.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, are you willing to spend 80 bucks on it?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the question.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it's some good songs, and they'll keep you in shape and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And our last email of the day is from AZHP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey guys, just had a comment, possibly a very long comment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did I miss some?
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry, LankyStyle was here and leaving, and I was trying to kiss him on his bald head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the email you guys got last week on the topic of piracy affecting game development, first of all, I'd like to say that the fact that Nintendo puts out arguably higher quality games than Sony and Microsoft is that they simply care more about the fun factor in the games than any other developer out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shigeru Miyamoto said in his GDC keynote that if at any point during the development he feels they have lost sight of the fact that this game is supposed to make people happy, he scraps it and redoes it from the ground up.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's devotion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Secondly,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: This is purely marketing and financial-based decision and is probably not affected at all by the piracy issue.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendo is not like other companies in this regard.
[SPEAKER_05]: They spend as much time as they want or need pushing back release dates if necessary to ensure the highest quality games, not the highest quantity.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lastly, Nintendo's consoles are not much harder to pirate.
[SPEAKER_05]: are not any harder to pirate games on than the PS2 or Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a mod ship in my GameCube and I burn my original discs to many DVD-Rs so that I don't have to lug around giant DVD cases that GameCube games come in as I travel a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are also mods that allow you to use full-size DVDs for your games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the argument that Nintendo games are harder to pirate as a reason that Nintendo is succeeding is not valid.
[SPEAKER_05]: A-freaking-men.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would agree that piracy is something really that not the masses really gets in on.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, very few people would know how to put DDR fifth mix on a PSP, Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: or would know how to do some of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: They would know how to pirate or mod a GameCube and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not an easy thing to do.
[SPEAKER_12]: Your average person is not going to be able to do it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I kind of think about when piracy got really busted and got out of control and I think about Napster and when did Napster really cross the line?
[SPEAKER_12]: When like every media outlet started reporting on it and then every college kid in the nation was using Napster to download music off each other.
[SPEAKER_12]: and to some extent, yeah, the piracy still goes on today, but it's not as easy as it used to be, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, remember it used to be like you just download Napster, type in Metallica and bam, you get like any song you wanted, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, now you have to download LimeWire and type in Metallica and then you can... And hopefully you connect to the server and you have to configure, and the thing isn't as user-friendly and you have to configure all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not as easy as it was.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all about BitTorrent and use groups or Usenet.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not saying just because it's not easy makes it right, but I'm just, you know, that
[SPEAKER_12]: That is true that, you know, you're probably never going to eliminate piracy completely, but you can make it difficult enough where that most people aren't going to figure out how to do it or care.
[SPEAKER_12]: Right?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki, you're just an exception.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're a special child.
[SPEAKER_12]: Face it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's give him some donuts.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that it for the mailbag?
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Einhander is awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Send more email.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mailbag at Orange Lodge.
[SPEAKER_12]: You have Einhander on your PSP?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: God damn you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mailbag, OrangeLaunchRadio.com Well, this is something else we can get mad about because we didn't have this.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is kind of old news because it's ending like now.
[SPEAKER_12]: But Australia actually had a free Xbox Live Gold service all weekend long.
[SPEAKER_12]: That ran this weekend, March 9th through March 11th.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if you're an Xbox Live Silver subscriber in Australia, you got three days worth of gold.
[SPEAKER_12]: So pretty cool there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Discovery Channel gave the Gears of War maps.
[SPEAKER_12]: It wasn't Discovery Channel.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was somebody else.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it was some type of network or TV show or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sure somebody in chat room remembers.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm trying to see.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe not.
[SPEAKER_12]: History Channel?
[SPEAKER_12]: Dark Knight says it was the History... No, I don't think it was the History Channel.
[SPEAKER_12]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, so people love free Xbox Live Gold Weekends.
[SPEAKER_09]: People don't like Bullet Witch.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Bullet Witch...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: No lock-on, cheap deaths, horrendous voice acting, cumbersome systems for casting spells, which I might agree that is pretty bad, camera angle too low to the ground, and invisible and visible barriers all over the place.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, it just sounds to me... It's a giant brain.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's sloppy stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, a giant brain's kind of cool, you know, because that's just an enemy that you fight, and the fact that it's a giant brain makes it easier to hit with their crappy targeting system.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it was one of those games, though, that probably shouldn't have been brought over here for, you know, the full price.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe, well, it was $49.99, so maybe $39.99 would have been a better price.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe, like, they have to pay us to play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, maybe free would have been a better price.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, at least it wasn't as bad as Bomberman Act Zero.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is one thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, great, they could put that on the sticker, a little sticker, so, you know,
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki from Horizons Radio says, hey, it wasn't as bad as Bomberman Act Zero.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I have something that should make everybody happy in regards to Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have the classic Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles game going to Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's going to be actually out, I believe the date was March 21st, which is right before the movie comes out on March 23rd, guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: Isn't that speculation still?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because...
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, also, you can still play it alone, and it's like co-op if you want it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's still Turtles.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dibs on Leonardo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dibs on Donatello for me.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, you know, I want to address this real quick before we get into our next segment, but I noticed this coming up quite a bit in our chat.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've seen this like twice now tonight, and it's coming up again.
[SPEAKER_12]: and the person who's posting it has an OL Army recruit number in front of him, so I can't credit it.
[SPEAKER_12]: But somebody is spreading around this story about Mushroom Kingdom Hearts coming to the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's got to be fake, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Every year they do an April Fool's joke and it's April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_12]: God, I hate April Fool's Day.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_12]: So the upcoming April issue of Electronic Gaming Monthly and they always do some stupid-ass April Fool's thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, I get it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's gotta be a joke, come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a joke.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is a joke.
[SPEAKER_09]: They even pointed it out that it's a joke.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a nice idea, but I don't... I would like a new Mario RPG.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it's never... It's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that's why it makes a pretty decent joke, but no, sorry guys, it's not a reality.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well, since Jamie brought up Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles being confirmed for Xbox Live Arcade and all, we thought we'd take this opportunity...
[SPEAKER_12]: LISTLESS
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's been brought to my attention by a long-time listener and staff of the show, Dark Datsuya, that we may have actually done this topic once before, but we've deemed since it's been at least a year since we've done this topic, and so much has changed, and we have a lot of new listeners since the last time, we're going to go ahead and do a list list for this topic tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the list list would be, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles was one of the most sought-after games for the Xbox Live marketplace, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: So...
[SPEAKER_12]: What arcade game now do people want to see on Xbox Live Arcade?
[SPEAKER_12]: Now that Ninja Turtles has made its way over, what game should be next?
[SPEAKER_12]: So this is the way Listless works.
[SPEAKER_12]: Each of the three hosts and our special guest who's joining us for this segment, Miklatov.
[SPEAKER_12]: Can we give Miklatov a mic so we can say hello to him?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, good job dropping the mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, Miklatov.
[SPEAKER_12]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Miklatov's going to help us build a list.
[SPEAKER_12]: So each of us are going to give our top three so we get a list of 12 games.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then we're each going to go around and knock one thing off the list, leaving a list of eight games.
[SPEAKER_12]: After that, the chat room will vote on their favorites, and we will get the definitive top one, two, and three list of the arcade games you would like to see ported over to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, let's start it off.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who wants to start off tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: I shall.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, ladies first.
[SPEAKER_12]: What would be your pick for the game you would most like to see on Xbox Live Marketplace?
[SPEAKER_12]: Arcade games, folks.
[SPEAKER_12]: Number three, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: Number three.
[SPEAKER_03]: R-Type.
[SPEAKER_12]: R-Type!
[SPEAKER_03]: The arcade R-Type.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why arcade R-Type?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's fucking R-Type!
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, Loki, what would be your number three pick?
[SPEAKER_09]: The arcade version of Bionic Commando.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow, that's kind of obscure.
[SPEAKER_12]: How is the arcade version of Bionic Commando different from the NES, for those who don't know?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hopefully not by much.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Better graphics.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can just tell you, like, I haven't played Bionic Commando in the arcade, but I can tell you that, like, Rygar in the arcade and on the NES were completely frickin' different.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, Mikotaba, why don't you go next?
[SPEAKER_12]: Your number three pick.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would say the X-Men game.
[SPEAKER_08]: The big screen one.
[SPEAKER_04]: The six person?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that was a good game.
[SPEAKER_12]: We talked about that last week here on the show, the X-Men game.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's a very good choice.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, X-Men.
[SPEAKER_12]: My number three pick would be Quiz and Dragons.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I can take on Bobby Blackwolf through Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_12]: Quiz and Dragons was this game and it had like, I think they used pretty much the same engine that Magic Sword and all those other games used.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's Magic Sword?
[SPEAKER_12]: God, okay, um
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura Planet Harrier Space Harrier
[SPEAKER_05]: Which was a really freaking awesome game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I've played Planet Harrier in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really, really fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think that it deserves some sort of home release.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: What next?
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki, what would be your number two pick?
[SPEAKER_09]: My number two pick would be... You know, actually, I would like to see... I see the image of the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just going to have to go with, you know, the Beyonce Metal Slug, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, why the hell not?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, they're going to put Metal Slug in everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd rather have some achievements for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, Metal Slug.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't believe you of all people just said that you need more Metal Slug.
[SPEAKER_12]: You obviously are drawing a blank.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, Miklatov, you're number two.
[SPEAKER_08]: Turtles in Time.
[SPEAKER_08]: because it's the superior one.
[SPEAKER_12]: Turtles in Time, the sequel.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sounds fair.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Turtles in Time.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was so much fun to, like, throw the foot soldiers at the screen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's the one you do it in.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, like, it was like Battletoads.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could do it in the first one, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was originally... This is a case where the chat room yelling out random things can have influence on us because I'm actually going to pick one from chat for my number two because I originally was going to say Rampart because that game was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's Rampart?
[SPEAKER_12]: We...
[SPEAKER_12]: You don't ever play arcade games, do you?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm young.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was kind of Tetris-y because you would rotate pieces to build a wall.
[SPEAKER_12]: But they have it on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't see why they can't have it.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I'll take it off since it's on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to say, I love this idea, NBA Jam totally needs to be on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: It needs to have the codes, though, for the Mortal Kombat characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game was so good.
[SPEAKER_12]: That could totally work, too, because Midway puts a bunch of stuff on Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want NBA Jam.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm putting NBA Jam down.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you, Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_12]: Number one pick, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Radiant Silvergun.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ooh, good pick.
[SPEAKER_12]: Radiant Silvergun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's freaking treasure.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's treasure.
[SPEAKER_05]: And by the way, I do agree with GS68 for Blazing Star, but no.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got to be Radiant Silvergun.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki, your number one pick.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know...
[SPEAKER_09]: I had a couple things, and I just thought of my second pick, but I can't remember what the game's called, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: So my number one pick's going to be Simpsons, the arcade game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, good pick, good pick.
[SPEAKER_09]: My number two, instead of Metal Slug, should have been, and I can't remember, those hentai puzzle games I kept playing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because those are fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: The hentai kicks thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember what it was called, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: You should have just said Gal's Panic.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what it was, Gal's Panic.
[SPEAKER_12]: Will we allow Loki to remove Metal Slug and put in Gal's Panic?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: We will allow Metal Slug to come off the list in favor of Gal's Panic.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Gal's Panic.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the first time we've ever done that on a listless segment, by the way.
[SPEAKER_12]: Allowed that to get changed.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mikotov, you looked a little pissed off when Loki took Simpsons, the arcade game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you come up with a new number one?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying so hard, but that's all the arcade games I played.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shall we go to the chat rooms for some ideas?
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me look at them.
[SPEAKER_12]: Would you like me to read some to you?
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't credit all these because a lot of folks are just yelling them out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Super Offroad, Moonwalker Arcade, Dungeons & Dragons, Shadows Over Mysteria.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can I pick a ticket game?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, you can't do a ticket game.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, there was this... Crazy Climber.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, there was this game that everybody played.
[SPEAKER_08]: Street Fighter 2 without getting fucked up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was by Midway, and it had like a joystick and a trackball, and it was like a third-person shooter type game.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Grid.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Grid, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: You want The Grid?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I want The Grid.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, The Grid.
[SPEAKER_12]: We just talked about that earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: Where were you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I was drooling over a guy at Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: My fault.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Shane comes back in here and goes, you guys want anything from Starbucks?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm like, they're going backwards.
[SPEAKER_12]: My number one pick would be Super Puzzle Fighter 2 Turbo, because that game was awesome!
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially with Dance Puzzle Jojo.
[SPEAKER_12]: And why not?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because they have Street Fighter 2 up, why not give us Puzzle Fighter 2?
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably because the joystick sucks?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's funny, because Actdeft said that again in chat, but I actually had that written down before he said that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actdeft and I are on very similar wavelengths tonight, apparently.
[SPEAKER_12]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's the list as it stands so far before the elimination part of this list.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have Arcade R-Type, Bionic Commando, X-Men, Quiz and Dragons, Planet Harrier, Gauss Panic, Turtles in Time, NBA Jam, Radiant Silvergun, Simpsons, The Grid, and Super Puzzle Fighter 2 Turbo.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which of these games is not worthy of being on the list?
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Grid.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, The Grid gets denied.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not very fond of that game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nikolatov says, you know what, I pulled that out of my ass anyway, so I'm okay with that elimination.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki, which of these games does not deserve to be on the list?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I would actually say...
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, NBA Jam, just because there's no way they would be able to... I mean, it would be nice, but they can't do it!
[SPEAKER_09]: Blame EA!
[SPEAKER_09]: They have the rights to the NBA franchise for years and years and years.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, actually, no, they do it to... No, that's the NFL, not the NBA, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, you're right, you're right.
[SPEAKER_09]: My mistake.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, it should stay!
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, fine, it'll stay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_09]: Radiant Silvergun, because there's going to be already Ikaruga and a bunch of other shit coming to LiveRK.
[SPEAKER_12]: Radiant Silvergun is unique!
[SPEAKER_09]: It's gone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_12]: Any more, please?
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: No donut for you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye-bye, Radiant Silvergun.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nice knowing you.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's funny because chat room was like, fuck you, Loki, fuck you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then I retract that, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Miklatov, which of these comes off the list?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Miklatov, which one of these does not deserve to be on the list?
[SPEAKER_08]: Quiz and Dragons because it's too nerdy for that list.
[SPEAKER_12]: I kind of...
[SPEAKER_12]: I kind of accepted the fact that Quiz and Dragons would come off the list, so I'm okay with that.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I will help Jamie out and take a little revenge on Loki, but not how you think.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to take off Bionic Commando, because come on.
[SPEAKER_12]: He couldn't even tell me what was different from the NES version.
[SPEAKER_09]: It had better graphics, that's it.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, the NES version is awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like, what's the difference between Contra and Contra in the arcade?
[SPEAKER_12]: It has better graphics, that's it.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the only one you need.
[SPEAKER_12]: Arcade R-Type X-Men
[SPEAKER_12]: Planet Harrier, Gal's Panic, Turtles in Time, NBA Jam, Simpsons, or Super Puzzle Fighter 2 Turbo.
[SPEAKER_12]: The way this works is you're going to send your number one and your number two pick in a private message to Sky in our chat room, only if you're listening live.
[SPEAKER_12]: You send your number one and your number two pick clearly labeled.
[SPEAKER_12]: That helps us break any ties.
[SPEAKER_12]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Arcade R-Type, X-Man, Planet Harrier, Gal's Panic, Turtles in Time, NBA Jam, Simpsons,
[SPEAKER_12]: Super Puzzle Fighter 2 Turbo, what arcade game should they port next to Xbox Live Arcade?
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll have the results later in the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a good thing you said the X-Men game because the other game I would have mentioned was the Avengers game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the Avengers game, I've been, like everybody knows I've been getting back into my whole obsession with Captain America and I love the Avengers.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I've been like actually downloading them.
[SPEAKER_05]: We actually played that the other day, the old game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to say, I don't think they would put Gals Panic on Live Arcade because it's too pornographic for them.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a fun game, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: They could do Girls of Xbox.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they have the one that's not Gals Panic, but it's like Gals Panic, but in 3D.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not nudity, but it's just scantily clad animation.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Bra and Panties.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Bra and Panties game.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should have just called it that.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you can have Dead or Alive, Extreme Beach, Volleyball, whatever, then you can have that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have an engagement somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll tell you offline.
[SPEAKER_12]: because you're more than invited, which I told you about before.
[SPEAKER_12]: OLR Extreme Beach Volleyball.
[SPEAKER_12]: OLR Extreme Beach Volleyball, I think not.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to see me in a Speedo, you need help.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played volleyball in high school.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I don't know why they always make me the server because I was short and I couldn't spike.
[SPEAKER_12]: You played volleyball in high school, Shane?
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_12]: But was it sunny enough in Kansas to actually play volleyball?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, it was indoor volleyball.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played Marching Band.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was my sport.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was in Marching Band, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: And your book.
[SPEAKER_12]: Something else I played a lot of in high school that I haven't played a lot of since is Earthworm Jim.
[SPEAKER_12]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Dave Perry, the shiny entertainment founder, has hinted that a new Earthworm Jim game is going to, quote, happen eventually.
[SPEAKER_12]: Apparently, they have put together the pieces of the development team...
[SPEAKER_12]: to revive this game that originally came out in 1994.
[SPEAKER_12]: You might remember it was the game where you could launch cows.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I remember the burping theme song.
[SPEAKER_12]: It went, Earthworm Jim.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like somebody burped the title and they recorded it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because that's how mature Earthworm Jim was of a game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it would be kind of fun to see that come back.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why do I have a feeling this might be an Xbox Live Arcade title?
[SPEAKER_12]: Does it scream Xbox Live to anyone else?
[SPEAKER_12]: Is it just me?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: It does.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, um, they did, didn't they do like a 3D remake of it or something like that that came out on the PSP or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: You're thinking of Bubsy, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no, I'm thinking Earthworm Jim.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was like a quasi 3D remake or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, somebody, I just, yeah, ew, 3D Earthworm Jim, the new Earthworm Jim better be 2D.
[SPEAKER_12]: So apparently there was one, I just never played it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess that's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, so, um, well, Earthworm Jim, you know, it's a great game.
[SPEAKER_09]: The question is, how do you get your girlfriend to play games with you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Speaking of which, you have excellent timing.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is a list that's been posted on the internet.
[SPEAKER_09]: How to get your girlfriend to play video games with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You put lots of naked people in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You put things that she likes in it and not things you like in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number one, they say find out if your girlfriend has ever played video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: She may not be a full-blown gamer, but she may have played Mario games when she was younger.
[SPEAKER_09]: and she may play games on the internet and stuff like that to remind your girlfriend that if you both play games you'll be able to spend even more quality time together bullshit pick out games she might like if you're not 100% sure she'll enjoy it you can rent it try to choose a game or system that isn't too confusing and doesn't require short reaction time because girls are feeble minded apparently
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I was just thinking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, because my female brain can't figure out these buttons.
[SPEAKER_12]: The voice you're hearing, by the way, is Loki's wife, Nellie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, I'm Nellie.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm retarded because I can't figure out buttons.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do I do with this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where does the thingy go?
[SPEAKER_09]: If you can, get a game that is multiplayer, optimally co-op.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it says, consider your girlfriend's personality when picking out a game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some girls may prefer brightly colored, all-ages games like Katamari...
[SPEAKER_09]: Bustamove, Lego, Star Wars, Sims, or any Mario game.
[SPEAKER_09]: But remember, if your girlfriend is an individual who could just as well go for Halo, Resident Evil, Grand Theft Auto, or Nelly's case, Dead or Alive Extreme Beach Volleyball 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't get games that involve things like strippers, prostitutes, sex, unless she has a sense of humor about the subject.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, yeah, it's a good thing that they added the sense of humor thing, but I was about to disagree.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have fun when you play with her.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you make a good time, she'll enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even if she's not into games and yadda yadda yadda.
[SPEAKER_09]: And basically, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: So they have a whole bunch of tips out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's on wikihow.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get your girlfriend to play video games if you're really interested.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just say, like Nellie said, make sure that there's porn in there or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Incentives.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get Rez with the Transvibrator.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, every week on this program, DarkSakura likes to surf the Internet up and down and left and right and back and forth.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever the DDR steps are that she's dancing to this week will be the World Wide Web Surfing to find the website of the week to share with you all here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, DarkSakura, what is your website of the week?
[SPEAKER_05]: You picked it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I helped.
[SPEAKER_12]: You asked for ideas.
[SPEAKER_12]: I gave you ideas.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it would have been one that I would have used.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's PotterPuppetPals.com, which I think was down for a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: And really, it's just the ones that came out in the actual puppet version.
[SPEAKER_05]: With the sexy Snape animation and the muggle pants animation and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: PotterPuppetPals.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Snape!
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's bother him!
[SPEAKER_12]: Bother, bother, bother, bother, bother, bother!
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that just PotterPuppetPals.com?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: as well as some episodic content, new modes and maps and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: And apparently on March 23rd, coinciding with the European launch, they're going to launch the two multiplayer modes, which is team conversion, basically the conversion mode with teams, and assault, where you destroy your team's defending base.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they're also adding a spectator camera mode as well,
[SPEAKER_09]: And, um, later on we should be getting some more story elements, um, in the form of episodic content.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I'm glad to see that they're actually doing some stuff with this game, because it is pretty awesome game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just, you know, once you finish with it, I guess multiplayer is the only thing left for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, you can go back through the game and get some more weapons, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fun, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alrighty, well, we're going to open up our Skype line here very soon, so you guys can interact with our program.
[SPEAKER_12]: We had a couple people calling in during part A.
[SPEAKER_12]: 877-GAME-OLR
[SPEAKER_12]: Super Puzzle Fighter 2 Turbo.
[SPEAKER_12]: Number three was your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_12]: Your number two pick was NBA Jam was the number two pick you would like to see.
[SPEAKER_12]: And number one, honestly, this isn't much of a shock to me.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it was based on the same hardware, lovable characters.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Simpsons is the number one game you guys want to see on the Xbox Live market.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they're still talking about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: They might do that, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, because with the movie coming out and everything.
[SPEAKER_12]: It might happen.
[SPEAKER_12]: By the way, I just want to point out, Turtles in Time, very, very close.
[SPEAKER_12]: One vote away from making it onto the list.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that was another one you guys wanted to see.
[SPEAKER_12]: But every entry on the list at least got a little bit of love.
[SPEAKER_12]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Tonight's list list.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you, chat room, for playing along.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you're listening to this on your iPod, your Zooms, your PSPs, whatever the case may be, and you want to play along next time, you've got to join us live for a taping.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Sunday nights over at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: Shall we open up the Skype line and take a look at what our callers have to say?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's shall.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's do it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, we're back.
[SPEAKER_14]: Paradox Vincent.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, Paradox Vincent.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just got another Beatmania game, 10th style.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I just want to shout out a quick review for it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, sure.
[SPEAKER_12]: Beatmania 10th style.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, this is an import game, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it's an import game, so I have to use Swap Magic with it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well, tell us, or you have to own a Japanese PlayStation 2, like I actually own one.
[SPEAKER_12]: It has a lot of dust on it, but I have one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, tell us your review.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, uh, Be Many a Ten style, well, it has my favorite song list in it, and, uh, I heard a lot of complaints about it on, uh, just some of the various Bimani communities, but...
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't really see it.
[SPEAKER_14]: What were some of the complaints?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just heard that it was bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just people going, this sucks.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can't ever take that for an answer, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can't let somebody go, this sucks.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why?
[SPEAKER_12]: Why does it suck?
[SPEAKER_14]: The only thing that I ever heard about that was legitimate was that it's where the difficulty really started ramping up.
[SPEAKER_14]: There are a few songs in there where the difficulty just starts getting a little intense, but overall, I mean, I think it has the best song list out of the releases that I've played.
[SPEAKER_12]: It does have a pretty solid song list, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_12]: What types of songs would Bomani fans be happy to know are in the game?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, there was Ixion by Leadlight, and there...
[SPEAKER_14]: There was a lot of Sampling Masters.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sampling Masters was really heavy in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: There was both Rattle the Mercury and Rattle the Sun.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some Sampling Masters, ISF, 108, Daddy Daddy.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was really... It was a talk heavy...
[SPEAKER_14]: There was a lot of talk songs in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: It depends, because I'm training somebody right now, and they seem to really like it and be able to play a lot of them.
[SPEAKER_12]: But if you've never played before...
[SPEAKER_14]: I'd say maybe this one's just a little too hard, because after maybe the first five songs, the difficulty starts to ramp up a bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, maybe not TenStyle, but TenStyle would be an awesome second or third game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well there you have it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Any final thoughts for our listeners, ParadoxVincent?
[SPEAKER_14]: On a comment on the getting girls to play games segment, I just said,
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, some of the games that I found worked really good were Katamari and DDR, actually, but no Rez.
[SPEAKER_12]: Rez didn't work?
[SPEAKER_14]: Rez doesn't work for anything.
[SPEAKER_12]: Even with the attachment?
[SPEAKER_14]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_12]: Even with the trans-fibrator attachment?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I don't know about the trans-fibrator attachment.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe you need to have her take a second look.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I will.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess there's just a difference, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think when we read these stories about how do we get girls into gaming, they mean the casual gaming girl, I think.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not the hardcore gamer nerds, you know, like you and I, regardless of sex and all that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, let's go back to the phone lines, take another call.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Good evening, this is DMN.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, DMN.
[SPEAKER_12]: God, you get through every week.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: Not so much as On Tour, which I really didn't like.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's $50.
[SPEAKER_07]: Definitely recommend it.
[SPEAKER_12]: What if I've never played SSX before in my life?
[SPEAKER_12]: What do I have to look forward to?
[SPEAKER_07]: If this is your first SSX game, it may be a little difficult for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: The thing that's really difficult is... Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_07]: The thing that's really difficult in that game is moving around and doing tricks, because they do it a lot differently than you would with a DualShock 2 controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: Once you get accustomed to that, though, as the tutorial does a great job of having you get the hang of it, it's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: When will SEX Tricky come out?
[SPEAKER_12]: An SEX blur.
[SPEAKER_07]: When people don't give a shit about AO ratings.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anything else that you've played this week you want to share with our listeners about?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm getting back into a leap-eat agent, so I'm getting psyched for Owen Don, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's supposed to be coming out later this year.
[SPEAKER_12]: Looks pretty sexy.
[SPEAKER_12]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_12]: That news just came out recently as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was going to ask you, you have not been the biggest Sony fan in the past, from what I remember.
[SPEAKER_12]: What did you think about their announcements this week?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm excited for them.
[SPEAKER_07]: The PlayStation Home looks fantastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I could play the rip-off card, but I'm not going to.
[SPEAKER_07]: LittleBigPlanet looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not something that's going to make me drop $600 on a PS3, but it's a great idea, and I really hope it gets off the ground.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, anything else you want to share with our listeners, DMN?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're introducing over the next month a new segment, a new recorded segment after SDFU.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is the month of March, March Madness of Basketball.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I thought I'd throw together a little tournament called DDR Madness.
[SPEAKER_07]: 64 DDR and In The Groove songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys vote to determine which is the best one.
[SPEAKER_12]: But if it's DDR madness, why do you have In The Groove songs in it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Shouldn't it be like Dance Game Madness or something like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll call it Dance Game Madness.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I had an effect on the world.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Listen to STFU Thursday night, 7 o'clock, right here on OLR.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: and it's podcasted now, so you don't have an excuse not to listen.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sweet, is it really?
[SPEAKER_12]: Do we finally get that on our servers?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have the pilot episode and episode 12 up right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Are we going to get all the episodes on the stream?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I'm going to release an old one and a new one every week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, check that out, Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's the podcast feed?
[SPEAKER_12]: Is it in iTunes yet?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, stfu.orangelunchradio.com slash rss, I believe.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll find the link and post it in the chat.
[SPEAKER_12]: Great.
[SPEAKER_12]: That will do us no good for the folks listening on the podcast right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Can they search it in iTunes or somewhere yet?
[SPEAKER_07]: I believe it's up in iTunes now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, good luck to you, DMN.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks, man.
[SPEAKER_12]: Later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's go to at least one more call here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_00]: Just ranting on the Internet.
[SPEAKER_00]: In particular, how people are just bitching and moaning about how one PS3 game, Unreal Tournament 3, is actually getting keyboard and mouse support.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would like to see that as an iTunes review, by the way, as an iTunes review of this program.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just ranting on the internets.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_00]: As you know, they're saying that it's going to give, you know, PC gamers who basically grew up on keyboard and mouse, myself, it's going to give them an advantage over the folks who use Nexus just to play the game, and there's just some back and forth arguing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_12]: Is it really that big a deal, or should people just shut up about it, or what?
[SPEAKER_00]: The only exceptions to, you know, the only good controls that I've seen so far, you know, in console first-person shooters...
[SPEAKER_00]: His golden eye in Perfect Dark.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because they had the benefit of the joystick on the N64 and it actually felt nice on your hands.
[SPEAKER_00]: Whereas, you know, stuff like Halo, honestly, you know, personally I found it really hard to just, you know, to actually aim.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I found that very difficult with every other first person shooter that I've seen on the console.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was just horrible.
[SPEAKER_00]: But now that they had a keyboard and mouse, it's easier for me to transition.
[SPEAKER_00]: But then on the other side, you could actually use 6-axis to basically aim up and down, and then you could just use the D-pad to move forward, backwards, side to side.
[SPEAKER_12]: Since you brought up Halo, there are current existing 360 games that will use any USB keyboard.
[SPEAKER_12]: Final Fantasy XI is what I'm thinking of.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you think that Halo 3 ought to accept a mouse and a keyboard, USB mouse and USB keyboard as possible control devices?
[SPEAKER_00]: Just to throw the PC gamers a bone, at least.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because, you know, they're still out there and that would pretty much be on getting Halo 3 if it had that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I could just hook up a mouse and keyboard and then I could just play in my own comfort zone without having to go through hell trying to learn the controls and trying to be good at them.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well, any other thoughts for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: Maximum Tune pawns Initial D, that's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_00]: What, Maximum Tune?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I thought you said you wanted to comment on Initial D. No, I said Maximum Tune is greater than Initial D. Certainly when it comes to the soundtrack, I would agree.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh yeah, that too, and the fact that it's more real than Initial D.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well, Racing Game fans, if you disagree with Zaku, call him at home.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I can't give you the number.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks, Zaku, for your call, as always.
[SPEAKER_12]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, let's go to the next call.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Ranma, the official spoken at a chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's up, everyone?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hello, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_12]: How are you doing, my friend?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_02]: How is everybody else over there?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: The other two are kind of quiet tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: They don't want to participate in phone calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm doing fine, just have, you know, a lot in my mind.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're having chat room sex online, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: No!
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm trying to take calls here.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: But then, you know what, DarkSakura, you talk to Ranma.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have to go pee anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: You talk to Ranma.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's really fucking good radio, Rob.
[SPEAKER_12]: Way to go.
[SPEAKER_12]: He needs to go pee.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, he's just, yeah, way to go, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a wuss.
[SPEAKER_05]: So hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a question.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a question for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I read an article on Consumer sometime back about people complaining about GameStop, the fact that they open up the video games and put it on display, and then when they sell them, they sell them at the full price, they'd rather knock a couple bucks off.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think about that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, first of all, I have no affiliation with GameStop whatsoever anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's fine, I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: But honestly, they don't do that with all of their games.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's like the last one.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it hasn't been played.
[SPEAKER_05]: The disc has not been physically touched on the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It has not been inside of the system.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is an unused game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is only that the case has been opened.
[SPEAKER_02]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're right on that, but
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess from my point of view from working retail, it seems like it belongs in an open box status where you want still new, it's open, and technically you really can't say it's new so you're going to knock a couple of dollars off.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's sort of like a shades of gray when you think about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think open box really should apply to like hardware, like appliances.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the same thing with demo machines as well, but I remember a friend of mine, my friend Patty, we were looking for a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: We found it.
[SPEAKER_02]: but they wouldn't knock like a couple bucks off because it was like a display box you know they took the game out and all of that and the boxes are a little bit faded I mean they could at least get something well I think that um
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, okay, look at it this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: If ever you go to the bookstore and you have books that are shrink-wrapped, you know, but you have books that are unwrapped, they're still going to sell you the book at the same price unless the book itself is damaged.
[SPEAKER_05]: If the game is not damaged, if the case is not damaged, then there's no reason for them to make any differentiation between it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're right, but it's just that some people argue about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's one of the reasons I try not to shop at GameStop unless I really have to, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I don't shop at GameStop anymore at all, so don't blame me there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go to GameCrazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no GameCrazy down here in New York.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that I know of.
[SPEAKER_05]: This should be attached to a Hollywood video.
[SPEAKER_05]: if you got them.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have a Hollywood video, but there is no GameCrazy there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, GameCrazy sells old games, and that's why I love them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not just because Dan works there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it works for me, definitely.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well, is there anything else, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to call you out, Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm tired of you talking trash about Vista.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't, I'm tired of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not really talking a lot of trash about Vista, I'm just not that interested in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but the thing is, Windows XP, every box of XP is coming out, oh, new upgrades, brand new hardware.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the time the new OS came out, it's definitely time to upgrade, because it's been like maybe two or three years since the last upgrade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Since it was Vista, it's been a while since, you know, the last operating system was XP, so you got newer hardware for Vista to support.
[SPEAKER_02]: and people complain about bugs left and right.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of those bugs do not even apply unless you're like a hardcore higher end user doing stuff you shouldn't even be doing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why should I upgrade to Vista?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, personally because there are newer hardware that's coming out that XP may not be able to support and the fact that XP and Vista
[SPEAKER_02]: is more secure, is more stable.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're perfectly honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't say now because if that was the case, I'd be very updated.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drew, he's already updated.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm waiting a month before I get all my hardware ready to go because I want to really try out this copy that's out in stores because I shouldn't be really saying this, but I was a beta tester and I've been playing around with it since it was mobile and I've seen...
[SPEAKER_02]: The changes from 2004 all the way up to now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ranma, I got to be honest, you're not selling it to me.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, you're telling me that because everyone else is doing it, I should do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing the best that I can.
[SPEAKER_02]: I work retail, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you don't work for... Look, let me tell you straight up, honestly, if you don't want to upgrade to Vista, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, to each his own.
[SPEAKER_02]: Me, personally, I plan to do the upgrade in due time.
[SPEAKER_02]: XP is still going to be around for a couple of years.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to read some chat comments on this and then wrap up here.
[SPEAKER_12]: I see James Patrick says, you can control audio for every separate program in Vista.
[SPEAKER_12]: Trying to help you out there with some good reasons.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_12]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Somebody said they are on Windows.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, NM64 says, Vista?
[SPEAKER_12]: Heck, I still prefer Windows 2000.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well Ranma, we've got to let you go, but thank you so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_12]: Any last words for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_02]: Listen to Uni's radio on Shoutcat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember the name of it, but she should be posting it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, I'm sure she appreciates the plug.
[SPEAKER_12]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_12]: But don't listen to it right now, because we're on the air.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, thanks so much for the call, and...
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going to go ahead and shut off the Skype line now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you so much to those of you that got through tonight and participated in the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: We appreciate it, as always.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to go around and ask if there's any last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, anything?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not particularly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just, you know, I'd like to remind everybody that I'm really awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not a story.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was a thing that's coming out in Japan that's actually kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a painting program for the DS, and you basically paint, like,
[SPEAKER_09]: A Japanese man has blamed his 6-axis for a new impotence problem.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, Mr. Owie, what's his name?
[SPEAKER_12]: Owie Bailey says he cannot get an erection anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: He says having his controller in his lap in close proximity to his penis has left him unable to perform.
[SPEAKER_12]: He thinks the controller is sending out a Bluetooth frequency that can cause bodily harm.
[SPEAKER_12]: He has contacted Sony to find out if he is not the only one having a problem from the PlayStation 3 controller, but has yet to get a response.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bailey plans on going to the doctor this week to try to get some answers.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, Bluetooth gives you...
[SPEAKER_12]: Impotence, apparently.
[SPEAKER_12]: What the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's not... I think he just has emotional problems, and that's why he's impotent.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why is he trying to play the game with his penis, anyway?
[SPEAKER_12]: It sounds like he's trying to put the controller right there to maybe, like, look at a picture of a pretty girl.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know about you, but when I play the game, I don't have my hand down there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have the controller in my hands.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the Al Bundy way of playing video games.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, one hand down your pants, one, yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, that's awfully lazy, and to be honest, I don't see that...
[SPEAKER_09]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: How old is this guy?
[SPEAKER_09]: It didn't say.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that's what I thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I'm betting it's not anything that has to do with... Well, you know, here's what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's because the fucking imagery from the PlayStation 3 is so fucking sexy, his wife just doesn't do it for him anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: NintendoManiac64 wants to know, why would you put the 6-axis on your dick?
[SPEAKER_12]: There's no rumble!
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess that's a good question to ask.
[SPEAKER_12]: One of the OL Army recruits, meaning they haven't changed their nickname yet, says, That's how the Power Glove was invented.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now you're playing with power.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's so bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, let's go around, if there's no more last-minute stories, and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll start with you tonight, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_04]: Give me money.
[SPEAKER_12]: My final thought is Guinness World Records.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's my final thought.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I've had like three glasses of it this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's good stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki, your final thought, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: My final thought is it's a lot harder to put PlayStation 1 games on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_12]: Were you successful in your attempts?
[SPEAKER_09]: I put it on there, but the thing is you need to have a bunch of different files from Hot Shots 2 actually from the PlayStation Store.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then because with each firmware update they change the encoding on the PS1 games, so
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, thank you guys so much for tuning into and supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_12]: You guys are awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Remember, we do this for free for you guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if you like what you hear, please tell two friends about Orange Lounge Radio because that way if you tell two friends, then they tell two friends and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_12]: We slowly take over the world.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's how it works.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's how we get our name out there because we don't have any big corporate magazine or game company or website that backs us.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're just us, three gamers like you guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks so much to our chat room for joining us tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: And thanks so much to all our callers tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Are you going to be here, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_12]: I know you had a week off coming up.
[SPEAKER_12]: Are you here next week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: There was some week you had off.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't remember if it was this week or next.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, hopefully we'll all be here next week.
[SPEAKER_12]: But if not, then some of us will see you here next week on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_12]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_01]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!