[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_08]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is March 18, 2007, and you're on Part B of our podcast series.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Best Buy, Best Buy, Best Buy
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, here's an interesting spin on it, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our company, we haven't been able to get 20 gig systems for a while now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they are basically have been discontinued in our system as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this has been, I think, going on for about over a month.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I wouldn't be surprised if this is true, if they're discontinuing the 20 gig system, probably because they're making more money off the 60 gig system.
[SPEAKER_06]: And not a lot of people were snatching up the 20 gig system.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think 20 gig was still pretty fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: 20 is enough space for right now at least.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not for the Xbox 360 with all that movie stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm almost out of space.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think about that with the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: When I jump ship, I probably will get the 60 gig model just because I'm a consumer whore.
[SPEAKER_04]: And how?
[SPEAKER_06]: I will just upgrade my hard drive in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's something cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of, we had talked about Tecmo earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tecmo is bringing out Ninja Gaiden Sigma and
[SPEAKER_04]: as a has new backgrounds, enemies, characters, animations, textures completely revamped for the next system.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can partially or fully install the game on the PS3 to help with load time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will run at 60 frames per second, self-shadowing, and in 720p.
[SPEAKER_04]: So lots of Ninja Gaiden action.
[SPEAKER_04]: You also get a playable Rachel.
[SPEAKER_04]: You, uh, apparently supposed to be very bouncy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, it's Team Ninja.
[SPEAKER_04]: So.
[SPEAKER_10]: My question is, will I actually be able to get anywhere in the game without getting frustrated so that I throw my controller through the screen?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody can help that you suck at it, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, everybody sucks at Ninja Gaiden.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a fucking hard game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan was pretty good at it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Dan is a god among men then, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know what to tell you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I only marry awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, a game I'm really looking forward to on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: And how sad is it that this is one of the games I'm really looking forward to on the PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki's wagging his finger already because he knows what I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: SingStar on the PlayStation 3 is coming out, of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of people thought it was going to be something that was like a network download, but no, I think at E3 they said it was going to be a full game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it is coming on a Blu-ray disc and there's going to be HD videos on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: 30 songs on the disc.
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't know exactly what 30 songs we're talking about yet, but I seem to remember E3...
[SPEAKER_10]: Survivor by Destiny's Child
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll get that on the internet for all our listeners to download.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or just Bobby Blackwolf because he's Loki's only friend on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have like seven friends now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not his only friend.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's not my only friend.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're very popular.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, something that's kind of popular on the PC is distributed... What is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Computing.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have a similar thing with Folding at Home.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Stuff to cure cancer.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you might have a part in curing diseases such as Parkinson's, Alzheimer's, Cystic Fibrosis, and many cancers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, well, let me write that $600 check right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's for a good cause, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: That whole, you know, distributed, I think that that website distributed net had something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a very interesting concept.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, as it is, the PlayStation 3 does suck a lot of power out of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, if this was something on the Wii, I could have it in standby and it would do this.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's Wii Connect 24 for you, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if I really want my PlayStation 3, this giant screensaver on an HDTV, just sitting there all day long, even if it was for a good cause.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck that shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: It should be calculating what the winning lotto numbers are for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the kind of computing I want to see the PlayStation 3 doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to see, you know, it earning money to pay for itself.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what it should be doing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go out and get a job, PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go out and wash some dishes somewhere.
[SPEAKER_10]: Get a job cooking french fries someplace.
[SPEAKER_10]: Work the streets if you have to.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just help me pay the rent, PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pimp that Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_04]: $600, make you holler.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, make you holler.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why did I spend $600 on this goddamn Blu-ray player?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: In other news regarding the player itself, the 1.6 firmware update for PS3 has a remote play function, so you can...
[SPEAKER_04]: Bring up any audio, video, photo stored on the PS3 using your PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, just anywhere you can find an internet connection.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Porn, porn, porn, porn, porn, porn, porn, porn, porn, porn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mighty porn, mighty porn, porn, porn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, anytime you talk about sharing photos and movies and all that stuff, I can't help but think of porn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that so wrong?
[SPEAKER_10]: I also can't help but think of Killzone on the PlayStation 3 coming out in July.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, there's a lot of other things I can think of.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just needed to transition.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, anyway, Phil Harrison revealed some footage of Killzone on the PlayStation 3, of course, at Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, you know, it was...
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess one of those things where the feedback from the journalists was not so hot, so they didn't end up showing it at the full Sony conference, even though folks were reporting they could see it on the screen, like in the PS3, they didn't play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a tease thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: But according to IGN, the game will, I guess, come out in July.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not coming out in July, the demo will come out in July.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the game itself is nowhere near done.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we'll probably see it at E3 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another game that we can be looking forward to pretty soon, well, a few months off at least, but Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it is thought, the rumor is that it's going to be set in a New York City setting.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this rumor comes from a couple of people that have been
[SPEAKER_06]: um contracted to come up with New York City themed music for the game so um you know possibly hinting that a New York City type theme if I were to guess I would say it's Liberty City because that's supposed to be New York City anyways so I don't know I would think Liberty City all over again is where it's going to be but whatever they could surprise us and have a real you know city in there either way it's um
[SPEAKER_06]: The game's not expected out until October, however, the first ever trailer of the game will be available March 29th.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I cannot wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it better not suck.
[SPEAKER_10]: Correct me if I'm wrong, but in the previous Grand Theft Auto game you could fly planes at some point, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, now, isn't putting the thing in New York City, look, I'm trying not to be wrong here, but just, you know, thinking aloud here.
[SPEAKER_10]: By putting Grand Theft Auto in a town very similar to New York City, doesn't that kind of open it up for folks at home to do some really unpolitically correct things in their game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Y'all know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't have to say it, but you know kids across America are going to try to imitate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, you can already, to be honest, you can't fly 747s or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't fly giant jet planes.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can fly biplanes and stuff like that into, you know, towers or make, you know, jets and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell, if you want to do that now, go buy San Andreas because you can do that right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: San Andreas was funny because you'd be driving along on a motorcycle and then all of a sudden a plane would crash into you.
[SPEAKER_06]: So random plane crashes are kind of fun in that game too.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Tack Johnson is going to have his ego all over this crap with another lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I can have Sex with the Hooker in a jet flying towards a building and then set a nuclear explosion off that wipes out the entire city, that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everybody seems to agree here that it's going to take place in future.
[SPEAKER_10]: A, it's not really New York City.
[SPEAKER_10]: B, even if it was modeled after New York City a lot, it would be a future New York City where that landmark I was previously referring to would be removed.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, still.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't help but think, you know, if they might put something in there where folks would be able to make it look like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: All that would happen is you crash into the building and your plane explodes.
[SPEAKER_06]: The building does not explode or fall apart.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all that would happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is your plane would explode and people would be like, Ha!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like 9-11!
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you would, you know, get it out of your system and you'd go back to playing the damn game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or you'd be like me and do it a few more times until you got it out of your system and then... But can you not see...
[SPEAKER_10]: Tack Johnson in a courtroom playing this footage telling the judge how Rockstar is evil and they're Al-Qaeda sympathizers and the game should be banned from the market forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're expecting him to actually show footage of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, he's trying to sue them now about games that haven't even come out yet that he doesn't know anything about other than that they are making a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's an idiot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're not talking about it anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Done.
[SPEAKER_04]: He Who Shall Not Be Named
[SPEAKER_04]: We should send him one of the pink PS2s that are out in Australia on the 15th.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you mean over at... I had to censor myself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that what you mean, my arch-nemesis?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I was actually... Well, he's not necessarily an arch-nemesis.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's more like a lackey.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: He would be like Toad is to Magneto.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I was referring to He Who Shall Not Be Named.
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, I swear to God, I am sick and tired of hearing about Warhawk and whether it's going to be on a fucking disc or downloadable title.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, because of that, during Game Developers Conference, because this is back when they said, okay, downloadable only title, great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, some people are a little bit pissed off.
[SPEAKER_06]: A few people left the actual development team because, you know, they were frustrated like this and basically saying, you know, crap product will sell like crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: If it's on the shelf or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's kind of my take on this thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game looked okay, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I couldn't give a shit about whether it's on a disc, it's on the PlayStation Network, or both.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just release the damn game, because I swear to God, the longer it takes this game to come out, the worse it seems to get.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, that is it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm done with Warhawk.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will never read another story about the game coming out on disc or on the network.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, why are we bothered putting together an outline if you're just going to skip my stories?
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Didn't we talk about it last week anyway?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: PlayStation 3 is getting episodic games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I remember us having a conversation about this last week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who has put together successfully an episodic franchise
[SPEAKER_10]: Except for Sam and Max.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like the only one I can think of in the past little while that's been successful.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care about episodic games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know why they're doing episodic games?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's because they go, cha-ching, cha-ching, oh, I can make some more money off this shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Great, let's put some more episodic content out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the last stuff's done so well so far.
[SPEAKER_10]: Flaming Bozo in chat room says, Grand Theft Auto 4 is going episodic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Has added content, but it has a full game before it.
Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura will put some hand sanitizing rubber gloves on
[SPEAKER_10]: Dive into the mailbag and pull out her favorite emails and her least favorite emails to read here on the air.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you can't send average emails because they don't get read.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: We try to read as many as we can, but since, you know, we're so popular and all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, but sometimes we just get too many.
[SPEAKER_10]: We can't read them here on the program.
[SPEAKER_10]: But DarkSakura does read them all.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sometimes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I read most of them, too, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: So unless you're a spammer, then do not actually send us email because we're banning IPs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's open up the mailbag, shall we?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we have three.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dear LLR, I recently got a new gaming machine and thought I'd send in a review.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple weeks ago, I bought myself a shiny Commodore 128.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been wanting to play a 64 for some time largely due to the opinions expressed on your fine show, but eventually the used market prices dropped on the 128 model and I decided that it was worth a dollar to get a newer machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure glad I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: What, Rob?
[SPEAKER_10]: I love whoever wrote this already.
[SPEAKER_10]: Finish it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just read the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is beautiful.
[SPEAKER_04]: So having lesser system specs, the C128 still holds up well feature-wise against other consoles on the market.
[SPEAKER_04]: It offers backwards compatibility just like each of the major consoles on the market and even supports homebrew just like modified PSPs do, which so far only Microsoft seems to be interested in with their consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: The C128 offers more buttons than any current console and it is available in a stylish off-put color similar to the DS Lite, Xbox 360, and
[SPEAKER_04]: and Wii, although somewhat less glossy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, it still lacks some of the features of the other consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: The 128 does not currently support HD output, but it is not believed that Commodore will be addressing that problem through firmware or otherwise.
[SPEAKER_04]: The command mode basic interpreter is also a little bit more difficult to use than, say, channels on the Wii, where everything is laid out for you and you just point at what you want instead of typing load, quote, asterisk, quote, uh,
[SPEAKER_04]: Comma 8 and cursing whenever you hit the wrong key or the file list is longer than one screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember that for freaking Lode Runner.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, a system is only as good as the games that are on it, and while there are very few C128 games, backwards compatibility means that I can enjoy any C64 game I can get my hands on, of which there are many.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you know the discs haven't disintegrated over the last two decades, which I understand is a problem, I cannot seem to get Impossible Mission or The Last Ninja to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: I even tried blowing into them, but no such luck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Overall, however, I find the Commodore 128 to be a fine addition to my game console lineup, and I intend to have many more hours of fun with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: By right sucks, Warrior Bob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously, Warrior Bob, I want to have your baby.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was an awesome email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Imagine, we could have a little house full of little VIC-20s and Plus 4s and 16s running around everywhere.
[SPEAKER_10]: That email was beautiful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, he also sends another email to you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're a rock star.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, we're so going to get it on.
[SPEAKER_10]: with our Commodore.
[SPEAKER_10]: We should do some Commodore live gaming and we could play... God, what the hell could you play over the modem on the Commodore 64 on my 300 baud modem that plugged into the back of the Commodore 64?
[SPEAKER_10]: What kind of games could I play?
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess over the local bulletin board systems.
[SPEAKER_10]: God, no, not even... Even then, I didn't really hit until I had an IBM.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was there anything you could play over the modem on the Commodore 64?
[SPEAKER_10]: Surely we had a modem for some reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd play a whole shitload of kicks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe there was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kix was my game.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll get together and play some Kix.
[SPEAKER_04]: The last email comes from... Wait, you said three emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know the second one was also from Warrior Bob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: This one's from Philly Girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you are the best podcast ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't know how much I appreciate you guys, but onto what I'm emailing you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got a dirty joke for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's six to eight inches long, goes in and out of your mouth, and leaves the white stuff around your lips?
[SPEAKER_10]: A penis.
[SPEAKER_10]: A toothbrush.
[SPEAKER_04]: A toothbrush.
[SPEAKER_04]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've already signed up on your website because you guys are so great.
[SPEAKER_04]: My screen name is VanityAngel from DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for putting this on the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: The email had nothing to do with video games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Somebody just emailed us going, hey, I want to tell you a dirty joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_10]: God, I love our listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, that's even better.
[SPEAKER_06]: What you need to do is call our Skype line or our...
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR
[SPEAKER_10]: UK sorry you guys are screwed you gotta you're Australia you guys gotta use the regular Skype method of doing it Orange Lounge Radio on Skype that's a beautiful idea if they're video game jokes that's even better I would love to hear some really more points if it's video game themed like Dirty Princess Peach jokes that would be great this is also great and it has nothing to do with porn or emails or any of that wow there really wasn't that many emails this week that's kind of sad I cry yeah aww
[SPEAKER_10]: Mailbag at orangeonstrider.com Send us more stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Great, great news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Vivendi is looking to actually revive Sierra.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, this is great news because Vivendi, you know, years ago, they bought out Sierra or whatever and they're offshoot Sierra online.
[SPEAKER_10]: And now it looks like Vivendi is going to be reviving Sierra somewhat.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Vendy CEO Bruce Hack
[SPEAKER_10]: The revival of the Sierra brand comes from product.
[SPEAKER_10]: Over time, as our products become better and establish themselves as perennial franchises, the name Sierra will be given a stronger life.
[SPEAKER_10]: As we move forward, our products get stronger, and as they are established as franchises, the name Sierra will be strengthened.
[SPEAKER_10]: No news yet, though, on a new Police Quest game, which kind of makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or Leisure Suit Larry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I guess, then again, Leisure Suit Larry went somewhere else, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: He went to a dirty, dirty place.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Sam and Max and it will be available in August of 2007 comments in the chat room on the last story sorry to deviate a little bit but some interesting things on Sierra James Patrick in chat says please Sierra is dead Sierra Studios were in the Sierra Mountains that studio is closed therefore Sierra the real Sierra is dead and the adventure company is the one bringing it over here to the United States so
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Sam & Max, and I don't know why I haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, Sierra and Sam & Max have nothing to do with each other, but I was... Well, the chat room's a little bit behind.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a little bit of live lag, so there you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I had a complete and utter brain fart.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why?
[SPEAKER_10]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_10]: Were you daydreaming during the show?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that what's going on?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I did my Reiki class today, so I've been sort of out of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe me and Captain America can run off and have a family together.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll pursue my massage therapy and he can have a successful business as a crime fighter.
[SPEAKER_01]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, so how about a story?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd like to see that in a comic.
[SPEAKER_10]: How about a story?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, how about more Jamie and Captain America slash fanfic?
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll name our family the Avengers.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the custom license plate we'll have on our minivan.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I please see this posted on fanfic.net or whatever that site is?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, because anyone who writes any fanfiction at all involving any characterization of me will be sued for libel or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: No sense of humor.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I have no sense of humor because it was stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then make a character named Sark Dakara.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can see it now.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're barbecuing on a Weber grill that's painted to look like the Captain America shield.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: So how about the next... Hey, you're the one that had a brain fart and derailed the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: No pie for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to get you pie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: For anyone who likes their MMOs, Turbine is offering the former subscribers of the Dungeons & Dragons online game a free weekend of gaming, actually, which is over right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for those in Europe, you're going to get an additional bonus for 10 days.
[SPEAKER_04]: of Free Gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can enjoy their Module 3.3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's supposed to beef up their character stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, for those who are currently subscribed, you will get 50% more experience and a plus one to loot found and lots of live events.
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically they're saying, we don't want to go out of business.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alrighty, well, changing gears completely here, talking about, well, maybe, I don't know, maybe they'll show D&D online at this, who knows, but of course, the E for All Expo is being held October 18th through the 21st at the LA Convention Center, which is where E3 used to be, and of course, E for All is supposed to be kind of like that public version of E3, but we're not sure exactly how much like E3 it's going to be, because part of us are
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo and Sony were traditionally in the West Hall.
[SPEAKER_10]: So therefore, we know that Sony and Nintendo's boost will be a little bit smaller than what we know from E3 past.
[SPEAKER_10]: But still, the fact that they are going really gives a boost, I think, in some regards to the E for All Expo.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to go, hey, it's only $100, but the tickets are not currently on sale.
[SPEAKER_10]: They will be made available in the future, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: But certainly, Sony and Nintendo signing on does really help out this new show.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_10]: Will they be using Kensha Hall?
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll probably have a gun show going on in Kenshiya Hall while this is going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: One time... No, for real.
[SPEAKER_10]: One year I went to the Rocky Horror 25th Anniversary Convention in Las Vegas, which is at the Las Vegas Convention Center.
[SPEAKER_10]: We had the right side of the building for the costume contest, the live speakers, because they had people from the movie there and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then the left side was a gun show.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you had
[SPEAKER_10]: People in fishnets and full, you know, doctor, for those that have seen the movie, you know what I'm talking about, like full Dr. Frankenfurter garb and, you know, little Columbia's and sequined outfits and, you know, people just basically dressed like fucking freaks intermingling with the gun show people.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the most hilarious part was that the ATM was in the gun show room.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if any rocky people wanted money to buy their crap, they had to actually go into the gun show and get pointed at and stared at by the folks there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Guns Next To Games Just What He Who Shall Not Be Named Once
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, so there's a brand new game coming out now that's probably one of those serious games that will help kids deal with the complex emotions surrounding marriage or divorce in this case.
[SPEAKER_06]: Earthquake and Zipland
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: No way you can fix a marriage.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might as well throw yourself into the ocean and die.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, does the game tell you that, too?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's really pleasant.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but that's where I took from it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could be wrong, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then again, I'm not a 12-year-old that's played this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm neither of those.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, do you think we need a game to help kids understand divorce?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, people just shouldn't get married.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should have an expo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, think about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If there was no marriage, none at all, and everybody had a common law deal, then there wouldn't be a problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well, Daddy decided that he and Mommy were going to break up, so he just moved out.
[SPEAKER_04]: No problems.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should find out that the reason that the island split in two is because the king was having sex with some other chick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Daddy's moving in with Uncle Bob.
[SPEAKER_04]: I personally, I basically, my parents were divorced before I had any memory of them being married.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: From that point of view, I couldn't really say if a game would help with that, because I just always grew up understanding what divorce was.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously, my parents have been together ever since I was born.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were together for like 15 years before I was born, and they're still together today, and I need a game to help me understand why they're still together after all these years.
[SPEAKER_04]: What I don't get is why people who obviously hate each other's fucking guts, Oh, we're staying together for the kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, you're giving them a fucking complex because you hate each other.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why does Mommy and Daddy fight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do they hate each other?
[SPEAKER_04]: You'd all be happier if you'd just go ahead and get a divorce.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm sure we'll be getting some emails on that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't believe in staying together for the children.
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe in giving the children a healthier environment to exist in.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we'll see what kind of Pandora's box that comment opens.
[SPEAKER_04]: I grew up just fine with my divorced parents, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: You're not giving it the proper context.
[SPEAKER_10]: You heard about it from me on a radio program a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just play me my damn music.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to go run and hide.
[SPEAKER_04]: The website of the week, again, is one that Rob mentioned a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mantis.net Mantis.net
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mantis are panties made for men.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're frilly and lacy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can get them high cut.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can get briefs.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can get nylon or lace.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they have all kinds of designs.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they have seven day ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're really pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: And plus they're made spacious in the front for special needs of men.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Guys, if you want to be pretty, if you feel like being a little dressier than usual, you should go to mantis.net Chat room, the answer to your question is no.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be no.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's so wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel dirty.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you can still feel dirty, yet pretty underneath, and no one knows but you.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I'm looking at the embroidered ones, and they have hearts on them or balloons.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, PowerShop Pinball Constructors coming out for the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oxygen Games just announced this coming out very soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, cause Metroid Prime Pinball did pretty well, so here we go, Pinball, Powershot Pinball Constructor So I guess it sounds like you can make your own table in this game, which sounds kinda cool, yeah, it has a table editor in it And of course that makes me think of Pinball Construction Set on the Commodore 64 Pinball's fucking awesome!
[SPEAKER_10]: So now you can make your own table, so that means if I wanted to make a table of nothing but like 50 bumpers, I could do that Do you remember the Hyperball machine though?
[SPEAKER_04]: All it was was nothing but multiball
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I don't remember that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would just shoot out a bunch of balls and you'd have to shoot them back down on the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, if I want to build pinball machines, I just get Dan to buy one and fix it for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, well, now you can do it all in the palm of your hand on the DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, so Zelda co-creator Eiji Aonuma, I guess, Aonuma, confirmed in an interview with Game Informer
[SPEAKER_06]: Phantom Hourglass for the DS will feature in online multiplayer mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they didn't really say what it's going to feature, but he did answer yes when they asked if there's going to be online battles over the Nintendo Wi-Fi service.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's interesting, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe, I'm thinking it's going to be something like Four Swords, maybe?
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: 4 Swords was actually a really, really cool game.
[SPEAKER_10]: 4 Swords was a much fun game, like on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_10]: That game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: When you could find people that had the advances and the chords to play the damn game with, it was a fun game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought I heard... Now, I can't remember... Correct me if I'm wrong, because I never played 4 Swords Adventure or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did it have an online mode or something where someone...
[SPEAKER_06]: There's like a couple Triforces on the map or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we talked about this maybe last week, where you basically drew a path that this warrior thing follows or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the multiplayer in the Zelda Phantom Hourglass.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that was Bobby telling us about him playing it at GDC.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what he was saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what we were hanging out with him last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, anyways, so as Bobby was telling us from GDC, it's basically...
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a couple Triforces on the map, and you can't, I think, see the player if they have a Triforce or don't have a Triforce, something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And basically, one player controls, there's three guards, and you draw a path that they follow, and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of like that Pac-Man multiplayer game that was on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pac-Man Versus, which they so need on the Wii and online.
[SPEAKER_10]: or on Xbox Live then, because if Nintendo's not going to do it, then fucking put Pac-Man vs. on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what we should have gotten instead of old school Pac-Man, but that's just my opinion.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do I know?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: How about some stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a little bit of information, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know I'm not visiting your website of the week this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_04]: So there is an unholy union between In The Groove and Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like they got together after taking a lot of LSD and bread.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now there's a Pump It Up Pro.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to say anything else about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: God, where do I begin?
[SPEAKER_10]: A.
[SPEAKER_10]: Those of you that were saying that In The Groove was going to somehow be absorbed into Konami and Dance Dance Revolution No!
[SPEAKER_10]: It was going to have In The Groove songs, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: And here's further proof that that ain't happening because it's been absorbed into Pump It Up, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty much all the songs that were done by Kyle Warder now on Pump It Up, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, in other words, Andamiro threw a bunch of money at Kyle Ward, and that's it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because Andamiro... But Andamiro and Roxor had, I guess, a working relationship, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because those In The Groove 2 cabinets, of which I've still never seen one in my entire life, were... Well, wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: I take that back.
[SPEAKER_10]: There might have been one at that 8 on the Break place in Jersey when I went there a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_10]: But regardless, Andamiro made those cabinets for him, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: They already had a little bit of a working relationship.
[SPEAKER_10]: So this actually doesn't surprise me so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you're going to see songs like, for example, Oasis, as well as... There's a bunch of other stuff I recognized on there when I was watching the videos of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exotica, Esperanza, let's see here, Destiny.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a bunch of songs, I think, from In The Groove that were in there, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't get me wrong, I like some of Kyle Ward's songs.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really like the stuff he does under, was it Banzai is the name?
[SPEAKER_10]: The Zodiac and Anubis and all those songs.
[SPEAKER_10]: But still, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: Miklatov wanted to come on the show tonight, but he had to leave.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know he's a hardcore Pump It Up fan.
[SPEAKER_10]: He ain't happy about this.
[SPEAKER_10]: He does not like the In The Groove thing crossing over to Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's really crossing over.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's more of just they have him now as an artist.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So he's taking his songs with him.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the guy's got to work, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: That doesn't necessarily mean he's just, you know, it's in the groove now.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did, I like what they've done with the interface.
[SPEAKER_06]: The interface is not retarded as it usually is on Pump.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's kind of nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: But other than that, I don't really think it's in the groove.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just that it's got, you know, Kyle Ward doing music for him.
[SPEAKER_06]: Great.
[SPEAKER_10]: In the group, DDR, right.
[SPEAKER_10]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see, if you would like to call us, we're going to open up the Skype line here very shortly because we encourage your interaction here on this program as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio, and our 800 number if you want to call us that way, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: Looks like we have some Ain't On The Break fans or folks that live near there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blaze says, Ain't On The Break for the win.
[SPEAKER_10]: DDR Dollar Bill says, yeah, Ain't On The Break.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rama says, Sky, that was a beta in the Groove 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chinatown Fair has in the Groove 2 and a Pump It Up box.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been to Ant on the Break.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to say I've been there a couple times, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I went out there once randomly when I was in the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_10]: I went there again for some DDR tournament.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I played some game that was some beat game I'd never seen in my life.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't remember, sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: ShadowCharlie wants to know what happened.
[SPEAKER_10]: Speaking of Zodiac, what happened to the Zodiac remix that Loki made that was during the bonus segment of last week's show?
[SPEAKER_10]: Check his community page on all games.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's there.
[SPEAKER_10]: and apparently 8 on the Break has two in the group, two machines now.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, let's go ahead and head on over to the Skype line and start taking some calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Raven Stolfen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me turn down the thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, Raven Stolfen.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_10]: I got a podcast now.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have a podcast now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everybody and their fucking mom has a podcast now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why should we listen to yours?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because he's a tech podcast guy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Something different.
[SPEAKER_10]: A tech podcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: This week in Raven's Dolphin?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's it called?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's called Raven's Tech Review.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: And where can we access Raven's Tech Review?
[SPEAKER_03]: On the All Games Forum.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's being submitted to iTunes soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be up there.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully coming soon to the iTunes store.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Raven, talk games with us.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because we don't... Well, I mean, we do talk tech, but we talk video games.
[SPEAKER_10]: What did you think of some of our stories tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they're interesting, but you're missing one more, and I viewed it on my site.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the Commodore computer coming back.
[SPEAKER_10]: We talked about it last week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, we did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_10]: As a tech-inclined individual, what do you think of Commodore making a comeback in the competing with Alienware or something market?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if it's going to be an operating system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you remember the Commodore had a different operating system than the DOS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know what they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if it's going to be Commodore just placed in there with a Windows operating system, or they're going to go with something different.
[SPEAKER_10]: Something tells me, since Commodore Basic is very antiquated, I think you're going to just get a normal Windows PC in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just interesting about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'll tell you, I'm not going to miss syntax error one bit or load, quote, star, quote, comma, eight, comma, one.
[SPEAKER_10]: I ain't going to miss that shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't miss it at all, but two more things.
[SPEAKER_10]: The fuck did comma, eight, comma, one mean anyway?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two more things.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just their command line.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it was like the device number or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, why was the disk drive eight?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was always eight.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think like once in a blue moon you might have seven.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: This would be This Week in Raven from 1984.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, what else?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, you have to listen to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, what else is on your mind, Raven?
[SPEAKER_03]: Two more things on my mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Vampire for the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_03]: You ever play Vampire?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm familiar with the title, but I can't remember the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fun game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's on GameTap.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was going to say, I think it's on GameTap.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that's where I've seen it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have not played it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you do in Vampire?
[SPEAKER_10]: Last thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: And don't say you're a vampire.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am not a vampire.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I meant in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: This one goes to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Flintstones Pinball.
[SPEAKER_03]: You ever heard of it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I was very interested in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was it based off the movie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it was.
[SPEAKER_10]: I played that table once, and because it was the movie, it felt like I felt unclean after playing it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I had to go change out of my mantis.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, bye Raven's Dolphin, take care.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, if you want to give us a call, it's 1-877-GAME-OLR or you can always call us on the Skype line, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's go to the phones and take another call.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll give you three guesses and the first letters are J-A-N-S.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, it's Jazz.
[SPEAKER_10]: God, you haven't been on the show in a long time.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, hi Jason, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_07]: You fail at spelling, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mr. VXJasonXV himself, our webmaster extraordinaire.
[SPEAKER_10]: Extraordinarily extraordinary.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, VX, our website held up amongst being on the front page of Dig and Joystick and Kotaku and all that stuff, Destructoid and all that this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, good job.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really good to know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've kept looking and I've kept checking.
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw when you guys...
[SPEAKER_07]: Rumor noise up, Sal.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would love a new Space Quest game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would absolutely love it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Haven't kept up.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just heard it, and I thought it was cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Six.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, so there were that many games in the Space Quest series?
[SPEAKER_10]: I always thought there was only like the three or four that were in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was, the first four were all the keyboard navigational, the fifth actually introduced the mouse, and then the sixth actually introduced the announcer, and even more interactivity.
[SPEAKER_07]: Five was awesome, that's the first one I played.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got the anthology and played the old ones, and then I played six, and I was blown away, because it was a big difference, and it was so good.
[SPEAKER_07]: For the kids today...
[SPEAKER_10]: What makes this game so freaking great?
[SPEAKER_07]: Humor.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to read, but it's all in the humor.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's a great puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_07]: I was just saying, I mean, that's the best part about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is a funny game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is very witty.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's great to read.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is a game that puts you through a book adventure.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I loved it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I beat Turtles Arcade at 5 o'clock in the morning Were you by yourself or did you have a bunch of other people?
[SPEAKER_10]: I was by myself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, but you get unlimited continues by yourself.
[SPEAKER_10]: How many continues did you have to use?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Call me back and brag when it's three or less, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, just teasing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, actually, there's a YouTube I saw somewhere of a guy running through the entire game on one credit.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know how anyone does it.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of people claim about, you know, single credit arcade runs.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I know I don't have any game I could say I've done such a thing with.
[SPEAKER_07]: Me neither.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, Jason.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, thanks for all you do for us.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we're going to let you go so we can take some more calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: All righty?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_10]: You too.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to call us, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember, it's your show too.
[SPEAKER_10]: We want to hear what you guys have to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: So let's go to another call here on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, this is Dark Shy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, Dark Shy?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, Dark Shy.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_05]: First, I want to say it's kind of amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the first time on the air.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was going to say, I don't recognize your name as calling in before.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know your name from chat, but you've never called in before.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, welcome, noob.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: So, well, first off, I just saw 300 today, and I heard of a game coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my friends all, so I saw like, oh, it should be on PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so amazing it deserves to be on PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I've never heard of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, what?
[SPEAKER_10]: It does sound a little bit like a fanboy's wet dream, such as Kill Bill, the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: If there's any game that's slated to come out, Loki would know about it.
300?
[SPEAKER_10]: Are they really making a game out of 300?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they did a PSP game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it wasn't very good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm thinking... Did he not get his PSP and his PS3 confused, maybe?
[SPEAKER_05]: I told him that he said it deserves to be on PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's saying, like, oh, it's so amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But at the same time, the PS3 wasn't all that great, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: It could be possible you get another game or two out of this a little later on down the line, especially with the movie being as popular as it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have one more thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure, what's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I remember so many years ago about hearing about Phantom Hourglass, and it just came out now, or coming out now, and I'm like, is this like a tradition for the Zelda games or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty much, sadly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, the Phantom Hourglass, they debuted at what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Didn't they first show that off at E305, I almost want to say?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it was E306.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it was either E306 or it was either that or Tokyo Game Show or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it has been a long time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's pretty much tradition for the Zelda series at this point.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, except the CD-i ones came out pretty quickly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, are you looking forward to Phantom Hourglass?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm a big fan of Zelda.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you think of the multiplayer mode we were talking about?
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you think it's going to be fun on the internet?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm hoping so, because I can't really think of Zelda online, so maybe they'll surprise me.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's hard to think about Nintendo online these days, but yeah, I mean, Zelda's definitely a step in the right direction, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, DarkSakura, thanks so much for the call, and call again sometime, all right?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have fun with Phantom Hourglass and all those hours you're going to be putting into that.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry to those folks that did not get through.
[SPEAKER_10]: We apologize.
[SPEAKER_10]: But everybody's trying to hammer the line there, so it happens.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Going to the chat room, trying to read the comments there to some of those previous calls we took.
[SPEAKER_10]: SSJ100 Matt says, I hear the 300 game is awful.
[SPEAKER_10]: GS68 says, bring on the max 300 jokes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see, SSJ100 Matt says, you could have 302 electric boogaloo.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll take more calls next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, again, Loki's Challenge to leave us a dirty joke on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's open, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can do that all week long.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm going to go around and see if there's any last minute stories anybody would like to share tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been trying to find the information on it, but I can't actually find it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's actually a new pinball table coming out later this year that's a Monty Python theme.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're actually going to get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like a Spamalot table?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it's Spamalot, because there's already a Holy Grail table.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that they were either going to do Meaning of Life or Life of Brian.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's Meaning of Life.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Always look on the bright side.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Life of Brian.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I know, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meaning of Life had, um... Had, um... The, uh... It's just a waifu thin mint.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wasn't the Meaning of Life the one that was in, like, the office building in the beginning?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was actually a different... It was supposed to be a lot shorter.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, unfortunately, they let Terry Gilliam have his way.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was the, uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Crimson something assurance.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember that scene going on forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: With all the tax preparers.
[SPEAKER_10]: All forever a scene went on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that scene.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't it great to charge your own accountant?
[SPEAKER_04]: That one.
[SPEAKER_10]: TheRobD says about the Amani Python table, every time you hit a bumper, I fart in your general direction every time you hit a bumper.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_10]: LegendZaku says, and now for something completely different.
[SPEAKER_10]: and Monty Python Pinball Table.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a good name for a table.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, anything from you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just a couple small things.
[SPEAKER_06]: One, Splatterhouse is confirmed apparently for Virtual Console this Monday.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to be seeing that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to tell you right now, Splatterhouse is one of those games you're going to think back to your childhood and go, this game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: But when you all download it on Monday, the game was not that good.
[SPEAKER_10]: It really wasn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember how bad it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's still funny though.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want that Friday the 13th vibe to it, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see what else here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, apparently it started now on the PlayStation 3 on one of the previous firmwares.
[SPEAKER_06]: Up until 1.51, they're seeing holes and they've exploited a TIFF exploit.
[SPEAKER_06]: basically causing a buffer overflow like they did on the PSP to run their own code.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's only a matter of time before they break the PlayStation 3 and have piracy rampant on there as well as homebrew and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm waiting.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I don't have anything either, so I guess we're here to the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're finishing pretty fucking early.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, this is a short show tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of weird for us, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been a, you know, compact and
[SPEAKER_10]: Good show.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of information.
[SPEAKER_10]: We talked about a lot in Part A and Part B. We'll do it all again next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: In the meantime, thank you guys so much for tuning into and supporting Independent.
[SPEAKER_10]: Internet Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys are awesome, and it's because of you we continue to do this show every week in and week out.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we'll see you next week here on Orange Lounge Radio, March the 25th, for episode number 225.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that like a landmark number?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because it's like, you know, multiple 25?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not so much.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: 250 maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or our five-year birthday is just around the corner.
[SPEAKER_10]: I say we get a stripper for the fifth birthday.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, anyhow, in the meantime, that's it for this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see you next time on Orange Lounge Radio and tune in next week to find out which website calls us a liar next.
[SPEAKER_10]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week.