Orange Lounge Radio
With your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Waroko
Tonight, March 11th, 2007, as Sony won back some fans with the unveiling of PlayStation Home,
EA and Harmonix Forged Deal, and has an online poll foreseen the return of NiGHTS
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
We are that podcast dedicated to video games and the gamer culture and gamer lifestyle
My name is Rob Roberts and joining me as always say hello to DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
Hi
How are you doing?
I has salad
You have a salad, a yummy salad?
I has a salad
I has a fresh choice earlier today, it was good
I has Quiznos
Do they have fresh choice all throughout the country?
I don't know, is that a local thing?
No
Basically it's an entire restaurant that's a giant salad bar
The only way you get salad bars is if you go to Shoney's
Or Sizzler's
We don't have Sizzler's in Alabama
I know what Shoney's is, but they don't have that here
Shoney's is nasty
Well so is Waffle House, yet it's still popular
Waffle House is not nasty!
Waffle House has special drugs that they put in the hash browns
Anyway, say hello as well to Techmaster Loki
A whole place dedicated to salad is nasty
What the fuck?
They have pizza
It's a pita's dream, I mean seriously
Or pita's dream, yeah
They have pizza and soup too
Okay, well soup is okay
Fucking, why the fuck is pizza there?
That's just so random
I guess it's healthy pizza, I don't know
Well I remember, god I went there a long ass time ago with an ex
And I had pasta there, pasta was okay, but salad is just nasty
They have the best bread ever though
That's what food eats, I don't eat that, I eat food
Alright, well let's get into tonight's program
First off actually I want to say, Techmaster Loki, did you notice
We did not get the FUs of the Week music automatically start playing
I was a good boy this week and made that not play
That's because he told you to
What?
No, I thought of it all by myself
Stupid Jamie revealing stupid behind the scenes stuff
Alright anyhow, also I do want to plug the chat room
chat.orangelaunchradio.com
We have lots of boys and girls that come there to chat with us
Kind of the fourth guest of our program
When we don't have any other regular fourth guest such as tonight
We don't really have a regular fourth guest, that kind of sucks
I tried to get Dan to come
Oh really?
And his loud friends
Probably for the best they didn't come then
Yeah, they're playing some card game
We had a guest and then he left
When's Marissa coming back?
Maybe next week
Sweet, how about Chris?
Because I'm horribly broke
I have to have Chris and Marissa come up here for doing the birthday stuff
I think that might be when Rice Princess and Eddie come here too
So we could get everybody in here in one week
You know what, we could just all leave
Honestly, three of us could just take the night off, let them do the show
What do you say chat room?
Let Chris, Rice Princess, Marissa, and Eddie do the show instead of us
What do you say?
We'll take the night off, we'll go out to eat
Let's do that
We'll go to Country Waffles
Our knockoff of Waffle House we have out here
No, we'll go to Fresh Choice
They closed at four
The entire chat room's at no, no, no
And they're only open breakfast and lunch
Oh damn it
Oh, we got a hell yeah from Zappy, there you go, DDR dollar bill, hell fucking yes
They don't love us anymore is what it boils down to
That's sad
Alright, well let's start off tonight's program the way we usually start it off
With a little bit of How Is Your Gaming Week
Where we talk about the games we've been playing this week
If anything at all, Dark Sakura
Marvel Ultimate Alliance
Still, huh?
Yes, and then Dan had to take it back so he's just gonna buy it for me after Pay Day
The only freaking PS3 game I will play, like, regularly
I love my PlayStation 3 now
It gives me Captain America and Wolverine
In the same game
Although the damn thing is on the Wii and the 360 as well
I don't care
360 get achievement points
That's true, the Wii you could do
Flippy, floppy movie things
You know what, I don't like doing that
I do not like doing that
I have to say, as much as I love the Wii
I think that when you have games
That are made for play like that
That's one thing, but when you have a fucking platformer
I just fucking put a controller in my hand and let me play
One thing I actually don't like about the PS3 one
Is that it has you flip the controller to pull
I was gonna say the PlayStation 3 uses that six axis
But it's stupid
Six axis, like a normal word
Because, you know, Sony wants that big marketing oomph behind the words
Six axis
It sounds like an alien race from Doctor Who
Kinda
Exterminate
God damn it, Tigerclaw
Why do you have to drive the knife in my heart?
I'm assuming, I haven't even looked at chat
I'm assuming Tigerclaw is talking about
How your Wednesday must have been
How did your Wednesday go?
I hate you Marvel
You bitches
In case for whatever reason this is your first week listening to Orange Launch Radio
You know, Sony is talking about our personal lives as well
And one thing that Dark Soccer is also a fangirl of
Is comics, namely
Captain America
Which is funny because really on this program
I know you've liked Captain America a long time
But it really seems like, especially in the past six weeks
Your fandom seems to have rekindled
Because I started reading all the Civil War comics
And I was like, dude, he's cool
But then, so it was kinda funny
I mean, not like funny haha
But funny like, don't call Jamie today
Like when I saw it in the news
That they'd killed off Captain America
So how was your day when that happened?
He will be back
You think he'll be back?
Oh come on, it's a fucking
You know, Marvel needs money
So they do a gimmicky thing
So I was looking at your
All games community page today
And somebody decided to jab the knife through your heart
A little more there and say, going
Basically somebody put a comment on Jamie's page and said like
Haha, Captain America died
What do you say to those people that say
Haha, Captain America died?
Die in a fire
That's what I thought
Is there anything else in your week you want to talk about?
Um
I really like my salad
Loki, how was your gaming week?
Salad the game
It's alright, we don't have to worry about Captain America dying
Because Afghanistan is going to come and replace him
So
Wow, that's a very unpolitically correct comment
And he's going to be far more awesome
My gaming week was filled with lots of stuff actually
I played quite a few different games
Starting on the 360
Of course played Crackdown
Because Crackdown is awesome
I did play
What else did I play?
Oh, Armored Core 4
Which is pretty cool
It's going a lot faster than
ChromeHounds
Looking forward to that, I'm not sure if I want to pick it up yet
Because I'm trying to cut back on the amount of games I buy
But it's still pretty cool
On the Playstation 3
I downloaded Flow
Tried that
It was pretty good, kind of relaxing I guess
I didn't realize that there were actually
Stages in the game
So it's kind of neat they get to become different things
Including like a dolphin looking thing
So that's kind of neat
And then I played Motorstorm
Which Motorstorm is pretty awesome
Graphically and it's pretty fun to play
My only gripe on it
Split screen multiplayer for one
That would have been nice
The other thing is
The game looks so awesome
And there's like some pretty cool
Animation in the menus and stuff
But during races
The fucking spectators are cardboard cutouts
And they're not even animated cardboard cutouts
They're just like stuck in a pose
And I'm like
I understand that you know you probably couldn't animate
All these people in the game
Even though other games can do that
You know
That's how I was in the Gran Turismo HD concept at E3 right?
Oh yeah and I still thought I was retarded there
Huh
Granted they're probably trying to save on
You know calculations and stuff
To make it run smoother but
The least you could do is make them animate
A little bit so I can kind of go
Okay at least that doesn't look
As hokey you know
It's 2D but at least it's animating
Or doing something you know cheering and stuff
Why is it just a person standing there frozen
It just looks retarded that's something you would do
On like the fucking Super Nintendo
Or something and even the fucking
Super Nintendo had animated sprites
That were cheering in the background
Yeah but those little dudes aren't sprites anymore
Sprites are so last gen
Okay well it's still
Something that's sitting there at 3D spaces
2D okay whatever
So they could have done that
That's my big gripe on that
Otherwise the game's fun
You know I had a lot of fun playing it
Speaking of last gen Alpha Canogram in chat says
Loki split screen multiplayer is so
Last gen
Oh yeah it's so last gen that's why
Halo 3 is gonna fucking have split screen multiplayer
That's why Call of Duty 3
Has split screen multiplayer
That's why Gears of War has split screen multiplayer
So fuck off it's still
In town okay
No last gen it's because you can't
Fucking program a game that can have multiple
Instances of it running at the same time
So that's just lazy
Programming which you know
Oh I'm sure Motorstorm wasn't lazy
Programming it wasn't like they downgraded from
1080p and 60 frames per second
To 720p and 30 frames per second
Which I still say though
The game looks fun
And it looks pretty awesome
Some other things that they probably didn't think about though
When you're playing in first person like say
In the cockpit type of thing
And it's not really in the cockpit
The camera's just on the front of the vehicle
Which is still stupid
But if you happen to crash into something
And your hood gets bent
You could actually not be able to drive in that perspective
Because it's blocking the whole camera
Which totally makes sense
But anyways
So other than Playstation 3 stuff
Let's see here
On the PSP I was playing of course
Grand Theft Auto Vice City Stories
Which is fun
I also put some homebrew stuff on there
Including this game called No Gravity
Which I might say that this game right here
They could totally sell at retail
And it looks a lot better than most of the PSP games
Out there
And so the fact that most of those games out there
For the PSP are getting their asses kicked
By a homebrew game
That's pretty sad
A demo for a game looks way better
Than a lot of stuff like Konami
Capcom, whatever
Put out on the PSP
It can be done
I just would like to see some more independent games come out there
Maybe something like XNA
Or something like that for the PSP
Would be pretty awesome
But that's about it
I'm about to load the Thrill Kill
And DDR Fifth Mix on my PSP
During the show
Keep us posted on that
So you're not actually going to be participating in tonight's show?
Oh ok
Do that in between
Hitstun wants to know
Does the retail MotorStorm crash every five minutes?
Nope
Wasn't it determined that the crashing of MotorStorm
Was the resetting of the system gone wrong
When people were supposed to...
It was because it was overheating
I don't know
Download the demo, it doesn't crash on the PS3
Fine, whatever
My Gaming Week, surprisingly enough
I actually played a little bit of Crackdown this week
Which is usually not the type of game I would get into
But Crackdown is kind of fun
It's like Grand Theft Auto
Only there's no hookers to have sex with
And you jump really really high
And flying all over the place
But I find there's a lot to discover
I kind of like just walking around doing random stuff
I don't really like having to fight the gangs
And get into that whole thing
No, I like to jump around the Ferris wheel
And do the little race around the Ferris wheel
That stuff's fun
And finding the orbs and all that stupid crap
Good times with Crackdown
A couple people tried to challenge me
In co-op or whatever
Or I guess you don't really challenge someone in co-op
They wanted to play co-op with me and I declined
Because I suck at Crackdown
But this week I'll probably actually play
Because I was still trying to learn Crackdown
I don't want someone to come into the game with me
And I'm like, I don't know what I'm doing
Did I just shoot you? Oh shit, I just blew you up with a rocket
I don't know
I kind of want to have a little skill
Because sometimes I feel weird playing listeners
On the Xbox friends list
But I think the listeners sometimes expect us to actually be good at games
Because we talk about them
We really don't know about you
Oh, hi Rice Princess, you came out of nowhere
Oh, sorry
They really don't know much about you then
No, they don't
I was a jab at you
JeremyTau1 said, Rob didn't want to play co-op with me
He denied me when I asked to join his game
Actually that may not have been me
Because the other thing you have to keep in mind
Is that Shane has been playing my game without asking
I wish he could set a password
On the Xbox Live accounts
Maybe he can, I just haven't done it
I don't care, but Shane has been signing on to my account
And playing Crackdown
I only let him do it because he's been getting me achievements
So it's all good
Because I'm still trying to get those 1500 points
So I can win, what was it?
Like a gamer picture and a copy of a game I already own
Contra, something like that
Because I want my e-penis to grow by 1500 points
With the whole Xbox Live contest thing
So that would be fun
What?
So you're having an e-penis fluffer take over
Yes, Shane is fluffing my e-penis
Maybe right now as we speak
Don't make a face, Rice Princess
Rice Princess, how was your gaming week?
If you have anything to share
Hey, guess what? I was playing WoW
Wow, you played WoW
Wow, that's the same as every other week
I play a lot of World of Warcraft as well, actually
I know
Almost every time I come on, I see you
I made a troll
You're a troll
That wasn't nice
Well she is, she said she made a troll
I made a troll
Jamie's a troll
You're a dirty napkin
Totally should
So did you do anything fun in WoW?
Aren't you one of those twink players?
You don't level past level 19
With all your gear?
It's 29, get it right
Oh, it's 29 now
Because you told me when I played on your server once
That you play nothing but Warsong Gulch for the rest of your life
Yeah, that's what I did originally
But then I discovered the world of 29
And I was like, wow, you get poisons as a rogue
And you get Arathi Basin
Which I think is an awesome PVP
Exactly
Because Warsong Gulch is so
Last gen
Oh my god, yeah, like who does that anymore?
God
It's all about Isla Storm
The other thing I want to know, where exactly did the term
Twink come from? Because when I hear
Twink, I think about something very different
I don't think about
World of Warcraft, I think about
The gay porn that you see advertised
The twink porn
I don't know, it's a little weird
That's where the mind goes
How did a World of Warcraft
Term come up to match up with a
Gay term?
I don't know for certain, but I have my
Theory
Twinks are like
The young, hot
Boys, right? Like the good looking
Ones that
Beauty is in the eye of the beholder
But sure, I guess I get what you're getting at
Like magazine looking guys
Well why don't you elaborate on what exactly a
Gay twink is?
I don't know if all the listeners want to know
It's basically a person who
I would think, a guy who kind of looks
Underage, who isn't
Like your blonde hair, blue eyed
That whole thing
Completely waxed everywhere
Type look
So like the best looking
No?
It has to do with like an
Age thing?
Do we really have to keep going with this topic?
Maybe my perception of what a twink is
Is different
I thought it was like
It had something to do with old men
Liking twinks
So they would be their sugar daddies
And give them a lot of money
And I'm thinking, okay, well to be a twink
You need to pay for your stuff
So maybe twinking is like
Horing yourself out to get money
To get all these awesome enchants
But that's just a theory
I don't really know
I just heard a bunch of people say, oh, twink, twink, twink
And I was like, okay, sure
That's exactly what I am
If by twink you mean awesome
Alright
I'm trying to see if there's anything in the chat room here
That says what's going on
JV Mon says, welcome to Gay Slang Chat on OLR
Let's see
Squeenix says
In the gay slang
Twink is a term that describes a young
Or young looking male, usually of slender build
With little to no body hair
Often they are described as blonde hair and blue eyed
To many gay men
The term is pejorative
And implies shallowness and stupidity
Twinks are typically contrasted with bears
And that's from Wikipedia
So there you have it
But that doesn't say anything about, how the hell then
You know what, I have no idea
I didn't realize there were so many gay players
And wow, right
That they would come up with the term
I'm done with this topic
I'm done with that, let's talk about other news
But I only stopped by to say hi
Someone leave now
Bye, get out, we don't like you anyway
Get out
Yes
Most of the podcasts you're listening to this week
Are probably going to be talking a lot about
Their experiences at Game Developers Conference
But not us, we didn't go
Nope
That's right, we sat home on our big butts
And read about it on the internet
Just like most of you guys out there did at home
I was originally going to go to Game Developers Conference
But some things came up
And I didn't end up going
But we did get to
Go to San Francisco yesterday to meet
Some people that we, you know
If I had gone to Game Developers Conference
It would have been like a networking thing
Like I would have gotten to meet a lot of people
So what we did is we drove to San Francisco
Because some of our buddies over at All Games
Were in town and of course we rebroadcast our program
Over on All Games on Monday nights
So we went over and met with some of the
All Games folks, we met with Bobby
And we met with Lawrence, although Lawrence we were
Basically taking to the airport so we didn't get to spend a lot of time with him
But Bobby who does the
Other Sunday night show you might listen to over
On All Games, we spent some time with him
When we went to Sunnyvale Golf Land
Which, you know, is a pretty big
Arcade, kind of infamous
In Northern California for the many fighting game
Tournaments it's had and
DDR music game tournaments it's had
Kind of sad to go
In there and see the place as
Basically turned into like the entire middle
Where they used to have tons of classic
Games, like you know
They had like the old school fighting games
And stuff were all up in the middle section
All gone and it's all ticket spitters now
Which kind of made me sad
I don't know, I made this big long rant over
At my All Games blog
Over at community.allgames.com
About
How kind of sad it is just to see that
The arcades are kind of
Really giving way to the ticket spitters
And although Sunnyvale Golf Land did have
Some pretty cool music
Games, they had, you know, Be Me and You
2DX Happy Sky which I got to play and they had
Pop'n Music 8 which was cool and they had some
Nice racing games, they had
Like everything in the little niche genres they had
I don't know, it was kind of sad to see
That most of the arcade is turned into that whole
Gambling for kids thing
So it kind of got me thinking
What do you think it would take
For us to really go back to arcades now
Because you know a lot of folks say that arcades
Are dying because
You can get the same experience at home
And you can get a lot of them on Xbox Live
What do arcades need
To do business again?
New games and well maintained games
And just something
Because even still you can play DDR at home
But it's not the same as playing in the arcade
And you need the atmosphere back
That's pretty much it
If I were to be opening an arcade
It wouldn't have any ticket spitters
At all
I don't care if that's why kids come in there
But you need to bring people in
That are looking for the arcade experience
Not just have arcade games
So that little Billy can run in there
And say mommy mommy I want to spend money
And play games and stuff
And win crap with tickets
They just kind of have that stuff
Out of golf land
Keep people there longer after their game of golf
Or before their game of golf
Dave and Busters
Dave and Busters is kind of like that for adults
I mean do you really play a lot of the arcade games
Dave and Busters? Maybe a few
But a lot of us kind of succumb to the whole ticket spitting
Thing at Dave and Busters because we're drunk
Right?
No I usually go often
You know when they had the
What was the meca salt
I know that that was always what
Whenever I'd go with Dan and the guys
That would be what they went right for
And I always played my deluxe games
But they got rid of meca salt
Stupid fuckers
I'm not really angry at the ticket spitters
Necessarily it's disappointing to see
But if that's where the money is
It's not like I'm totally mad at golf land
Because if that's where the money is
That's what they're going to buy
Granted those ticket spitters probably make them a ton of money
But I try to think about
What's really been new in the arcade lately
That I've had to get excited about
DDR Supernova?
Well I'm sorry Bomani fans
But DDR Supernova
Was pretty much just a DDR 9th mix
It didn't bring a whole lot of new stuff to the table
Really
It was just kind of the same game all over again
And even you could say the games like
In the Groove and stuff that tried to fill in the gaps
Same thing it was 4 panel dancing
It was the same damn game you always knew
But even DDR alone was not going to save an arcade
You know what I mean?
There hasn't been a lot of new stuff in general
I mean the last big new arcade release
I can think of was Soul Calibur 3
But that was already on the home consoles
So I don't know
It seems like they're really starting to go away from making arcade games
It's kind of sad
Because if it weren't for that arcade community
This show would not exist
Period
We need more Planet Harrier
I don't know if that's going to save it
We'll see
I'm trying to go to the chat room
Chat.OrangeLawnsRadio.com
See I had all games on the brain
Because of our little discussion with Bobby
Don't go to that chat room, that's the wrong one
Chat.OrangeLawnsRadio.com
Let's see
I'm trying to see what kind of chat is going on here
Fireboma says the arcade by me
Is just having games that are more like rides now
Some of those can be okay though
Remember After Burner?
With the freaking thing that you would sit in
That would practically make you sick?
Let's see
NM64 says
Arcade Halo
Sadly that would probably bring them back
You know, I kind of tend to agree
Something like that
Do they have that?
Do you remember The Grid?
They have Half Life in Japan where you can play that in the arcade
Really? I think about a game we saw at E3
A couple years ago
I remember it was 04, 05
And Amiro of all companies was showing off
This arcade game that would actually interface with computer versions of the game
It was like a first person shooter
Yeah, that's pretty cool
OL Army Recruit
I'm sorry, James Patrick says
Virtua Fighter 5 should come to US arcades
I don't know
That would be interesting
Alright, so I don't know if there's an easy answer
To how arcades can be kind of fun again
For all of us
Not just, you know, kids
8 through 12 or whatever
We welcome your feedback
Mailbag at OrangeLawnsRadio.com
And bloggyblog
Over at the community.allgames site
And leave a comment, that would be awesome
And I just want to say thanks to Bobby
For hanging out with us yesterday
And you should check out his show
He's on allgames.com at 5 o'clock pacific time
About an hour before we go live over here
At OrangeLawnsRadio.com
He also does a podcast
It's a different show over there
Because it's just him and his chat room and his callers
So the chat and the callers
Really drive that show
He's a pretty good moderator
And he actually moderated a panel at GDC
That Loki and I listened to on the car ride home
It was pretty good. Good times
And I forgot to mention
I played a lot of games over at
You know, Sunnyvale Golf Land
Loki playing popin' music was fuckin' hilarious
I hate popin' music
But I had like $10 in tokens
And I needed to get rid of them
And I was too tired to play DDR
Yet I did play more of it
So I played popin' 8
At popin' music
I'm not surprised because I knew I sucked
It's just I really sucked at popin' music
I played the Star Trek theme and that sucked
And then I played some random song
And that really sucked
And then I played 2DX, Happy Sky
And I sucked at that and that was fun
And I played Supernova and Supernova was pretty good
Until I picked a random double song
That was like a cata or something
And I was too tired to play it
I played part of it though
I'm just getting too out of shape for this
I'm out of practice
BlackWolf
Is actually in chat right now and says
Sky might have taken video on his phone, actually didn't
I did take a picture though, I'll put that on the community site later
Of Loki playing popin' music
Good times
James Patrick's continuing on the Virtua Fighter 5 thing
That would be great
Knowing you could fight anyone in Japan or America
Who's using the Virtua Fighter 5 arcade
Kinda going with that whole thing about
Being able to interface with computers and stuff
Pretty cool
Illusion says that Pachinko machines could revitalize arcades
That's an interesting thought
Alright
So anyway we had fun at the arcade the other day
But going back to Game Developers Conference
And starting off tonight's news
I want to talk about of course
Huge news in the Sony department
In fact this news is like so big
We might actually want to take calls on this
Just this a little later
Sony unveiled this week
At the Game Developers Conference
It's very interesting
And we'll talk about Nintendo's conference in part B
But a lot of the stuff that you saw
Like the big companies do
Was really about the game development
They didn't turn Game Developers Conference into E3
Like a lot of people thought
Which is a good thing I think
Game developers need their hangout
It was not E3
But Sony kind of used their keynote
To drop E3 like bombs at
Where they need to right
They're getting the bad press right now
Everybody kind of gives them a buy
To use Game Developers Conference as their platform
And some would say they hit a home run
I think so
Key word there is home
They revealed PlayStation Home
Of course we talked about it last week
But even when we talked about it last week
And the whole Kotaku drama that resulted
I don't think I was expecting anything like this
I don't think any of us were
When I heard it was going to be like Animal Crossing
I'm picturing to myself
Oh cutesy, cartoony
Animal Crossing with your me's
No no no no
What they unveiled instead
Is a service that looks like Second Life
It's like a virtual world
And here's a screenshot we have here in studio
You can see all these people with their customizable outfits
Kind of walking around this virtual world
But not only that
When you're in this virtual world
You can invite people over to your virtual apartment
And you can look at your virtual trophy rack
They've basically taken Microsoft's achievement system
And kind of evolved it into
Hey you can get trophies that you put in your house
Look at my stuff
Come over and look at my stuff
But not just that
Let's say you want to put a TV in your apartment
Then you can run videos on your TV from your PlayStation
Put pictures up on the wall
That you have on your PlayStation drive
Walk up to a pool table that you put down your place
And actually start playing pool
They're going to have some games included with this
All of it, free
It's going to be part of
That's basically what they're saying
What Microsoft is giving you in Xbox Live
We are now going to give you this service
Called PlayStation Home
And it's free
Of course the money that they're going to make
Advertising on all the billboards throughout the place
And people love to customize
So unless you want the raggy
Cheap Ikea furniture in your apartment
If you want some of the nice
Bling couches and stuff
You're going to have to probably pay for those
People will probably do it
People will do that because they buy shit in Second Life
So this will all roll out
In a closed beta
Of about 15,000 users
Between April and August
The open beta, about 50,000 users
August through October
And the service will go live with everybody
Probably about October
The best part about those
They're saying different games
Kind of like how they have with the gamer pics
And the games that you play on Xbox 360
Right now, you're going to be getting
Custom outfits and crap for your house
Basically by playing games
Or unlocking achievements
You'll get different things that way as well
So that's kind of neat
Alright, and that wasn't the only thing
Sony unveiled at the conference, correct?
Yes, there's another game that they were
Touting, it's basically a game called
Little Big Planet
And it's basically a community made game
You create your own levels
The entire thing is physics based
It's kind of similar to like Gary's mod
In Half Life 2
And you create these little
Almost like platformer levels
That you and your friends will play
And try to find their way through
And so it's totally customizable
You'll be able to download them
Rate them, and so on and so forth
But it's just, it looks like
A lot of fun
And it's actually selling a lot of people
On the whole
Playstation 3 experience
What they were definitely pushing
With their keynote was
This game 3.0 where
Most of the content out there would be
User created, which is kind of ironic
When you think about it because
They have all these firmware updates and stuff
For the PSP to stop user created
Content for that
I think that's kind of funny
But yeah, definitely
Cool little game
Hopefully it will come out soon
Definitely
One of the types of things that Sony
Is going to need
It's kind of like
I think we've all been waiting for something like this
Out of Sony
I don't know about you guys, but this is definitely
This put the brakes on the negative Sony press bandwagon
And now I think Sony's turned around
In another direction
But I would say the question is how much
I've heard people say everything from
Eh, whatever
To I'm going to go out and buy a Playstation 3
Now this is exactly what I need
If you guys are Playstation 3 owners
What do you think about this news?
Well it's awesome because their current service
Sucks
By the way, everyone wants to know
Is BlackWolf still your only friend?
No he's not
I do have about 7 now
So thank you for those people that sent requests
That's awesome
It's just basically
With the whole friend request system
You don't really know who's on there unless you talk to people
Thank you, I have more than one friend now
That's awesome
So the surface
Since I already own a Playstation 3
I personally probably wouldn't buy
A Playstation 3
For just this stuff
But it's definitely helping it
It makes their service look a bit nicer
It fleshes it out
Because before their network service was like
Well fuck, we don't know what they're doing
And to be honest, as of right now they haven't done anything
So this home service
Is going to be pretty awesome
It's going to be a great way to actually meet people
And to be able to add more friends that way
And just a really cool community thing
And I think it's going to have the same appeal
As Second Life or Sims
People are going to be customizing their own
You're going to see
Home places that are going to be themed around
Your websites
And you know
It's going to be crazy
You're going to have people reporting from home
Jamie, any thoughts on this?
I have MySpace
And LiveJournal for getting in touch with people
I think all I would do
Is just sit around and mess with stuff in it
Like I do with The Sims
I hate Second Life by the way
But
It wouldn't be any
It wouldn't make or break it for me
But since I already have it, I would use it
That type of thing
For me, I don't own a Playstation 3
And I've actually had several people ask me
Is this going to make you go buy a Playstation 3?
No
But it helps
But again, what is the golden rule of gaming boys and girls?
A system is only as good
As the games that are on it
Trust me, this is a huge step in the right direction
Because I love that
You know, they've kind of done something
You know, come to think of it
I think we had a caller last week or the week before
And I'm so sorry to the caller
Because I can't remember who called in and said this
But somebody called in and said
Sony is really good at ripping everybody else off
And doing it a little better
That was actually on a podcast
Somebody else said that
But when I heard that on the podcast
I remember somebody calling in
And saying it as well
And I thought to myself
You know, when we took the call on air
I was kind of like, oh yeah, okay
That's a cute thing
But I was kind of thinking when I saw this
God damn, they're right
That person, whoever called us, stand up and take a bow
Whoever did that
Because that was absolutely right
We all thought
Microsoft's achievement point system was genius
It's great, it's wonderful
And now we look at what Playstation 3 is doing
And we go, hmm, the Microsoft thing kind of seems
Kind of not as good as it could be now
Next to that
They just have the problem of being there first
Yeah, I guess so
It's just interesting
I still like achievements
I still love 360
But it's just kind of interesting that Sony could still do that
Even with all this negative press
Wow, they really kind of did rip something off
And make it better
One thing to keep in mind is that with the
As we progress
As more and more and more ideas come out
After a while it's very hard to innovate
Once you've already thought of what you can do
The only other thing you can do
Is expand on the idea
We've never seen Nintendo doing this
Because they can't embrace online
So
Who cares?
Well, I'm still thinking
I will probably end up
Breaking down and buying a Playstation 3
When some of the games I want
Come out like Final Fantasy 13
But I don't
Think I still want to run out and buy a Playstation 3
Just yet for only this
Although I think it's really cool
And if you are thinking about buying a Playstation 3
For only this
You need to wait until this stuff comes out
Because a lot can change
They can promise the moon for you
But they can deliver shit
Honestly
I think E3 this year
For Sony is so critical
Because I think they need to make up
For Zonkin out last year
And I think this year at E3
Now that they've kind of set the stage
Because that's kind of what they do with the game developers
Is they've kind of set the stage
Everything around, the big case
That Playstation 3 is going to
The big central thing now
That Playstation 3 is going to have
It's going to be about the games
That needs to come out at E3 and say
Here's the exclusives
Here's the first party stuff we're developing
Here's the stuff that's going to really make you want
A Playstation 3 now
Because I think about all these trailers and things we saw
At E3 last year
That we really have never heard about again ever since
Maybe little bits and pieces here and there
Africa with a K
Can we find out why I need Africa
And why this game is going to be so flipping great
Because when we saw the trailer before
We were like, I don't get it
I think about that game
I can't even remember what the hell the name of it was
Remember the trailer showed the gas station blowing up
Or something in the cars
What was that with the two guys
It looked kind of neat
What the hell was that?
Where did it go?
I guess so
I went to vaporware land
I just think it's so important
For Sony to come to E3
Now saying, now you know the box
That we're putting this in
The box off with games
And that truly is going to get me rah rah rah
About Sony again
I'm kind of curious
Has your guys' opinion of Sony changed at all
From the home run they hit at Game Developers Conference
Loki?
It's about time that they did something right
So that's great
Originally when I heard about home
I thought it was going to be a rip off of
The Miis
No, not at all
Now it's a rip off of Second Life
They took a business model, at least they took the right one
Because Second Life is
Really successful
As far as people making money off of it
As soon as I saw
Oh yeah, you're going to be able to buy clothing and stuff like that
On the service
And actually customize your characters
I'm like, oh well, cha-ching
Basically
They're going to make a lot of money
I think it's great
I do like the way that you can jump in
And play multiplayer games
Just by meeting people
So that's kind of cool
I don't know
They just wait to see what they do with it
Because they've been talking to a lot of online communities
With their games coming out
It's just going to be
Interesting to see how they implement everything
We are going to open up our Skype
Line in a rare occurrence here
Just to get your feedback on this component
Because I think this is so big
Especially with all the
Whining
Just kicking of Sony while they're down
People have been doing
I'm really curious to see what our listeners think
About this whole thing going in the other direction
We are going to take some real quick calls
Before that though I want to get some chat comments
If you want to call us 1-877-GAME-OLR
Or Orange Lounge Radio on Skype
And then I want to hear what Jamie has to say on this as well
First let me get some chat comments here
Let's see
I was saying that somebody here
Said something really good up above
Sorry guys, live radio scrolling around
There it is
Rob D said
This doesn't matter to me
I need games
Not a Trojan Horse Media Center
Give me games
It would be a good bonus
Let's see
Allusion says yeah a new Sims game comes out
And someone says I like the Sims better
When it was called PlayStation Home
I think kind of making a joke about
How Sony kind of rips things off and does it better
Let's see
The game is shallow and sucks except for resistance
Even now
Zappy I believe saved the day there
Earlier in chat Zappy believes that the game
I was talking about was called 8 days
That sounds right
That does sound right to me as well
Dark Soccer do you have anything you want to
Say about the whole Sony
Has your opinion of them changed?
Or you still think they are eating crayons over there or what?
I still think they are eating crayons
But this is a step away from the crayons
I think that they have moved away from crayons
They are eating paste
Because paste at least
Is flour based
They are eating
Paste in those little
Star shaped
String cheese nuggets
Let's go to the skype line
And see what people think on this
Who is this?
Ravenstaufen
What do you think about Sony at
GDC?
It's definitely a step in the right direction
Are you a Playstation 3 owner currently?
I wish, no
But you say you wish now
No I have been wishing
So does this make you want it even more?
Yeah
What do you think
Is going to be the coolest thing
About everything that came out of GDC?
What are you looking forward to doing with
Home or with LittleBigPlanet?
I thought Home was a
Very good idea
The only thing I want to do is stream porn from my hard drive
To my TV
You can kind of do that anyway
I don't know about the hard drive on your computer
I think you can stream the movies on your TV
But I'm looking at some FAQs
That came out about it
One of the questions that was posed about Playstation Home
Can I launch and watch a
BD movie from within Home?
Launch yes, watch no
I think some people were thinking that you would be able to put
A porno on the TV in your apartment
And that would play
Well you could go to that and launch the movie
But it won't actually play the porno in your apartment
At least that's the impression I'm getting
Which seems, the logistics of that seems like it would be
A real bandwidth eater anyway
So it's probably for the best, right?
I got bandwidth
I think it will actually stream whatever it is
On that TV because they said they had dynamic
Well, I forget if it was like
Dynamic sound or something like that where
As you walk closer to the source it will get louder
And that kind of thing
What do you think should be
Sony's next move, Raven's Dolphin?
What should they do at E3?
I don't know
I think they should definitely put Home
In a good response but I definitely agree
That any games
Like to support the Home
More games that support Home would be a home run
So maybe some games that incorporate the Home thing
Because one thing that's interesting about what Sony
Is doing versus what Microsoft is doing
Is Microsoft requires developers
To put achievements in the games
Sony is just kind of letting it be there
And if the developers want to
Put things in it then great
If when you beat Final Fantasy 13
Let's say if Square wants to
Give you a little cloud sword
Even though cloud's not in Final Fantasy 13
I don't know, humor me here for a minute
A little cloud sword that you could put in your PlayStation Home
That would be up to them completely
So kind of interesting
Yeah, two more things
Alright, hurry
You have to buy a Bluetooth headset and a USB
Are you?
I already have one for my 360
It's going to be a tough sell on Sony
Sony will need to tell me why I need it
Okay, and
The next thing about the trophies
Did you see that room?
I saw some of the videos
It looked like one room had a crap load of trophies
Maybe from all the arcade titles
I don't know
And one thing from Second Life
Am I going to launch pink dicks at people
That I don't like?
I have a feeling since this community is going to be a little more moderated
Probably not
With Second Life you can kind of user create things
I haven't done a lot of Second Life
But there's more user creation in that
I don't think you really get that so much here
You get user customization
But not so much creation
Alright, thanks so much for the call Ravenstaufen
You're welcome
Alright, we'll take one more call and some feedback with the Sony stuff
1877 Game OLR
Our username is OrangeLoungeRadio
Over on Skype
Of course we encourage you guys to interact with our program
That's what we're here for
We're just three folks that like video games
Just like the rest of you
We want to hear what you guys have to say as well
Let's take another call
Hi, you're on OrangeLoungeRadio, who's this?
Hey, it's SSJ100Matt
Hi SSJ100Matt, what do you think about this whole Sony home thing?
Actually, I'm liking it a lot
You're liking it a lot?
Were you somebody that wanted a Playstation 3 before Game Developers Conference?
I actually know originally I was split between a 360 and a PS3
So what do you think now?
Well now I've got to start thinking about the PS3 now
Before I was like majority 360
Now I'm back in the middle
So I'm going to wait until this home thing picks up around October
And then I'll make a decision
What about home that puts you back in the middle with all this?
Originally I used to play The Sims a lot
That was basically my guilty pleasure
That thing was like crack
This is kind of like The Sims
I know I'm going to be on this thing customizing buying crap
To make my place look good
Speaking of customizing LittleBigPlanet
Is that something that appeals to you?
It looks really nice, I think it will be great
Because I think they said something that they're going to come out with a full version
Where it's just going to basically be user created courses
And bring that out in retail or something
I think it's going to be very interesting to see how that plays out
When it's actually out there on the marketplace
Because now it seems like Sony is starting to listen to people
And they're going to be more welcome to user created things
Thanks so much for the call SSJ100 Matt
We've got to get back to the news
But take care
Take it easy
We'd love to take more calls
But we will take calls later in the show during part B
And if you want to talk about Sony home at that time
Certainly you can
But we need to get back into some news, right Jamie?
Yeah, news would be a good thing
I need to cleanse the palette of Sony
I sense a little bitterness about Sony within you
The bitterness is strong with this one
It always has been
But speaking of things that are a little less bitter
Is that in Fable 2, which will be coming out
You can have a dog
And he walks around with you
And he growls when he smells the people sneaking up on you
And you can't really tell him what to do
But you can gesture to him and he'll learn to follow
Well, he'll always follow you
But he'll go along with you and be your puppy
And lick your face and eat your chickens
And that type of thing
Wait, he'll eat your chickens?
I don't know
That's not good
Do the chickens fight back like they did in Zelda?
I don't know
But I wish they had cats
That was kind of disappointing
Because I'm more of a cat person
But then again I suppose the cat would control you
Apparently you can also be a pregnant woman
And catch diseases
You can get knocked up within Fable 2?
You can have sex, you can have unprotected sex
And protected sex, you can get STDs
That's making the fantasy out of my game
How many different kinds of sex can you have?
Is there going to be a whole Kama Sutra?
Hot Monkey
Will butt sex be involved?
They had gay relationships in the first game
Butt sex is not just a gay thing
Well, that's true
Good point
The dog is pretty awesome
They're saying that you're actually going to care for this dog
It loves you
And it will try to keep you safe
And stuff like that
It's pretty cool
They have some videos on gamevideos.com
Basically talking about the whole dog aspect of the game
It just looks awesome, I really want it
It's way better than in 10 Dogs
DDRDollarBill says
I want to have sex without E-Herpes
And DDRDollarBill says
Surprise butt sex?
I guess that's something you could do in the game
Surprise butt sex on people
I don't know, probably not
I just don't know
If I were going to have something useful I'd have a pet wolf
SSJ100Matt says
Do we get extra points for donkey punching?
I want a pit bull
And NM64 says
Everyone has AIDS
Because if you're allowed to run around and have unprotected sex in the game
That's the likely conclusion
I wonder if you could start an epidemic in the game
It's kind of weird
But I suppose this answers the question now about
What was the big secret about Fable?
It was puppy dogs and diseases
I guess so, there you have it
DDRDollarBill says
You're going to have to buy your condoms with your MS points
That's funny
Little microtransactions out the wazoo
Yeah, maybe you'll be able to get a cat
But you'll have to pay some points for it, I don't know
Alright
Well, there was
You have to change the litter or you die of methane poisoning
There were some other announcements that came out of Game Developers Conference
And I love me some Mizuguchi
Of course Mizuguchi, the fine fellow who created Rez
I believe Space Channel 5
Luminous
Meteos
Some of the greatest games, 99 Nights, not so much
Feeling the love there
But everybody's allowed to make a mistake
Well, this Make No Mistake here
Every Xtend Xtra Xtreme is coming to Xbox Live Arcade
And it looks like the audio and visual sex capade
That you would be expecting from Mizuguchi
I mean, just kind of look at these screenshots here
Of course, every Xtend Xtra was a game that was out on the PSP
They're going to be making this version as well for Xbox Live Arcade
And of course they're calling it E4 for short
Because every Xtend Xtra Xtreme get it, there's all the Es there
They're going to be able to battle others in an online versus mode
And that's kind of something that's a little new there for Xbox Live
Of course, just look at how trippy that looks
I mean, this is going to be an amazing seizure playable game
But I really like every Xtend Xtra on the PSP
It's kind of a unique sort of game
It's not really a puzzle
It's like a
I mean, it has puzzle elements
You have to think about what you're doing
But it is kind of an action game
So it's unique
And I'm a big supporter of unique games
So this is a perfect announcement for Game Developers Conference
So check that out on Xbox Live Marketplace
When it becomes available
Probably later this year
At least as far as we know
Yeah, late later this year
Christmas
Anyways, one thing though that's making games like this possible
Is the fact that Microsoft has officially raised the file limit
Of the Xbox Live Arcade games
Originally it was 50 megabytes
To fit on that wonderful 64 megabyte memory unit
Of course, now that they've also announced a larger memory unit
Which is going to be 512 megabytes
Now they can have games that are even bigger
Including games up to 150 megabytes
And even higher with permission
So that's excellent
And I know one of the first games to actually utilize that
Was going to be Symphony of the Night
Because I think that was like 98 megabytes
Yeah, that's when these rumors started
Because of Castlevania
I had thought that Microsoft already confirmed this
So I was kind of surprised to see this making the rounds on news sites again
Well, they sort of confirmed it
And then they made a press release about it
So now it's official official
These stages of gaming news
Especially Microsoft gaming news
Because Microsoft news always starts out as a rumor first
Because Microsoft rumors 99% of the time are true
So there's a Microsoft rumor
And then it evolves into random dude at Microsoft
Or a Microsoft blogger said, yeah, we're working on it, shh, don't tell
And then it evolves into like a press release
And then it's like, oh, it's official now
Microsoft has said, hail the larger Xbox Live arcade games
I'm sure every XtendXtra will benefit from that 150 megabytes
Here's the other thing I want to know though
Now that the arcade limit has been upped
Mr. Mizuguchi and everybody over at Q Entertainment
Whatever happened
It's been like a year now, whatever happened to Madonna in Luminous?
And I'm not just saying Madonna specifically
Contrary to popular belief, I could give two shits about Madonna
But I'm talking about the licensed music in general
We got one song, Heavenly Star, which was an in-house thing anyway
Where's the rest of the content that's supposed to be in Luminous?
No content for you
I guess not
Sorry, I got on a tangent there
This is supposed to be about the thing
Talking about Mizuguchi made me think about that
What the hell ever happened to Madonna, etc.
The puppy ate it
I guess so, the dog ate it
Well, you know something that you don't really have to worry about
Well, I don't know, I'm sort of worried about this
Peter Jackson is doing some episodic content for a couple of Xbox 360 games
And one of them is Halo
And I'm wondering, dude, what's he going to do for Halo?
That'd be very interesting
There's not too many details about it
And I don't think anything on what the other game is
It looks like it's still in development
But I don't know, is it going to involve giant monkeys?
Well, if you know Peter Jackson is doing it, you know it's going to be long
Like three and a half hour, butt-numbingly long
Like certain movies that he's made
In fact, most all the movies he's made in the past few years
God, seriously
Don't get me wrong, Lord of the Rings is cool and all
But damn, those are some long movies
It seems like episodic content has become this real buzzword of the past couple of years, hasn't it?
It seems like everybody and their mom is doing episodic content
What could they really do for Halo episodic content, you think?
Do you think this is something they'll do like two and then say, oh, there was your episodic content?
Or is this something you could see actually going on for a while?
I mean, God, if any community could support something like this though
The Halo community is huge and loud
I would see this happening like after Halo 3
And it would be for Halo 3, not its own game
Just like additional story, single player stuff
Or co-op missions or stuff like that
It's kind of similar to the co-op missions in Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter
Or something like that
It's not really episodic content, it's just downloadable content later on
Because to be honest, there aren't that many episodic content games out there
I mean, even Half-Life or whatever
They're only up to episode two and two hasn't even come out yet
You know I'm going to say Sam and Max
Sam and Max, yeah, that's one that's actually pretty good
But what else besides that?
I agree, Sam and Max is the only ones that seem to be doing it right
It's a buzzword thrown out there a lot and it's not being done
I mean, it's just like digital distribution for movies and stuff
Everyone talks about it, but it's hardly done
We've got to check in with the chat room because there are some funnies
Of course, going back to me bitching about the whole Luminous thing
Joshi16 kind of combined the stories together and says
Madonna would give you the Herpes achievement, Sky
So insinuating that maybe Madonna will actually be in Fable
To give you the STDs that you can get inside the game
So that's certainly an interesting thought from Joshi16
Let's see, Lazer is a winner for this reference
Maybe the Dingo ate your content
Ahh!
Now I'm getting all Meryl Streep
The Dingo ate the baby!
Anyway, let's see
You're so a winner for that comment
What else was there about episodic content?
I thought it was very interesting here in chat room
Well, Firesafety says there are already giant monkeys in Halo
So I guess you can't really say that that's what Peter Jackson is going to bring to the table
Let's see
Firesafety also says hopefully it's nothing like Half-Life 2 periodic
yearly maybe content
Funnydale says episodic content equals 3 hour games every year
Yep, that's basically what it's been so far
So I'm hoping Halo will break that mold
We'll see
Well, this is not a happy story here
But some news came out about Castle Crashers
Loki, you were all excited about Castle Crashers
Because this is the game that kind of looks like
It looks like an old school arcade
Hit the buttons, hack and slash type thing
Like a brand new one, this looks awesome
Well, when approached
Behemoth's Dan Paladin
They won actually an IGF award
Dan Paladin actually commented on the game
He noted that the Xbox Live title still had
About a year of development left
Meaning the Castle Crashers
Looks like it will now be out in 2008
But now the good news about this is that since the size limit has been increased
One reason that's been kind of a conclusion
That's been jumped to over this is that
Oh, they're going to go back and make the game bigger
Thanks to the size increase
So maybe good things will come to those who wait in terms of what's there
So I know you were really anxious about this game, Loki
Are you okay with this delay if it's going to make the game better?
Are you pissed?
Do you wish they just released something now and maybe do a Castle Crashers 2?
Oh, I'm fine with them delaying the game
Most likely even if it wasn't because of this
It would be delayed for some other reason
I mean, who cares?
There's supposedly more content coming out now
So I'm fine holding off on that
I mean, it's one of those games that look neat
I wasn't like, oh, I gotta have this now
I mean, big deal
I don't know, I can wait
Alright
Well, I don't know
But game delays, they kind of get me a little bit angsty
I don't know about you, DarkSakura, but you know
Anytime a game I look forward to gets delayed
Whether it be for the right reason or not
I get a little pissed off
What about you?
Um, sometimes
So that means that because we're pissed off
Well, this is one of those times, DarkSakura
Help me out here, because we got a segue
Roar!
Thank you, and to the FUs of the Week
Music
My FU of the Week is, as usual, traffic-based
Fuck you to men with small penises who drive big trucks
And also fuck you to sacramoms who drive SUVs
I leave it at that
Moki!
Fuck the fact that I can't find two files for Pop Station
For the PSP
And those are two important files that I need to make things work
I did find, however, though, there is one game that I have
That I really should put on my PSP
And that is Einhendr
Because that would be fucking awesome
That's it
Alright
I didn't have really anything that
Oh, fuck to the fact that this room is like a scorching
I don't know
I think somebody turned the fan off
I'm gonna go check that
It's like fucking hot in here
It is
It's just me
No, I know
I'm bringing them here too
I'll go look at the temperature in a minute
But I want to say my FU of the Week would go to
Daylight Savings Time
Oh my god
Ugh, I hate Daylight Savings Time
How dare you rob me of an hour of my sleep
I don't care if there's farmer kids with school
Or whatever the hell reason they say
Energy consumption
Whatever the hell excuse they have
FU Daylight Savings Time
I'm dying of fire
Hey, that was a pretty short FUs of the Week segment
I'm kind of sad a little bit
Well, don't be sad
Anyways
There's one reason you shouldn't be sad
Xbox Live hit six million users
They apparently did this four months earlier than they had expected
And not a big surprise
Because, you know, they offer those two day subscriptions
And pretty much anyone that plugs in
You know, their console into the internet
They are logged into Xbox Live
So, and they didn't really say what the six million mark meant
I mean, whether that's going to be silver or gold or whatever
Um, I don't know
So, take it with a grain of salt
But yay, there's lots of people on live
That's all you need to know, I guess
More people to flash us their ass, you know
On the camera
Hooray
Yay ass
Speaking of which, how have you noticed?
The camera for the 360
Completely useless, like the iToy
I have kind of noticed
What about Rayman Raving Rabbids on the 360?
Oh, I'm guessing that's going to be about as good as any iToy game
That's a damn good point
When was the last time anyone said anything about the Xbox Live camera?
And why is it we haven't gotten more games like Uno?
You would think, based on the success of Uno
That we would have seen like, you know, we would see like Old Maid
And like freaking Skip Bow
And I don't know, whatever else card games and casual games they can come up with
On Xbox Live by now
Is it just a rights thing? I don't know
It's lame
Well
There are though some things that are not quite as lame as that
Although there's not many things that are really as lame as that
Um
Some news for our European listeners though
You know, we've been talking about Blue Dragon
It's going to be released in very likely September in Europe
As was announced at a game developers conference
Isn't that cool?
And I'm thinking that I've actually been really excited about this
You know
I mean, I'm still sort of back and forth
But we have to wait until August to get it
And so I think by then I'll decide whether or not I really am going to be able to dedicate the time to another RPG
I think it's going to be awesome
I think there were a couple more details on Blue Dragon this week
Because I thought about, Loki, you said
Already on this show like a month ago that Blue Dragon was coming out over here
I think you might have said July
But whatever, it got delayed a couple weeks, big whoop, right?
But we all knew it was coming over here
But I seem to remember one cool thing that I remember reading about Blue Dragon
Is that they're going to have both the English language and Japanese language tracks in it
Kind of like how Enchanted Arms had
So if you're one of those people that's like, I hate it when they dub this stuff in English
Because blah blah blah blah blah
Then fine, you can watch the Japanese stuff with subtitles
Everyone's happy
So I'm actually really looking forward to Blue Dragon
Just because, you know, how could you not be?
It's, you know, the team that made the original Final Fantasy
Kind of, I don't know
I'm very excited about it
Looking at chat room to see what's going on there in chat
Let's see
Joshi16 will not let the Madonna thing go
Because Joshi says Madonna needs a live arcade camera game
Dude, you need to get your issues worked out there with Madonna
Let's see, what else do we have here?
Blaze says simply fuck the Xbox Live camera
There you have it
Mori agrees, Xbox 360 skip bow would be amazing
You know what would be more amazing than Xbox 360 skip bow?
And props to you if you know this game
I might be horribly pronouncing it because it's French
But this is like my favorite card game ever
Xbox 360 Millborn
You ever played that game?
With the roll and stop and punctured tires
It's like a racing card game
No
Oh my god, it's the best game ever
I love that card game
Bring me my Millborn on Xbox Live Arcade
Sorry
I'm ranting tonight
I'm a demanding little bitch tonight
I'm sorry
I'll be good
Alright
Oh I'm sorry, we got a release date to talk about
Wow
Live Radio
See I get all ranty and then I completely forget about talking about release dates
But I suppose we should talk about the Japanese release dates
Because these are usually the things that we're going to see over here in the US before too long
Or over in Europe as well
Well coming out on the Xbox 360, not a lot
Except some games are going into the Platinum Collection on March 15th
So you can now get Battlefield 2, Burnout, Chrome Hounds, Perfect Dark Zero
All at a lower price over in Japan
Coming out on the Nintendo Wii, you get G.I. Jockey Wii is coming out
Sonic 2 Himitsu Ring is coming out on March 15th
That would just be Sonic and the Secret Rings
SpongeBob SquarePants also making its way to Japanese audiences also on March 15th
We're sorry Japan
Yeah, sorry Japan for that
Sometimes things from our culture will stink up your things
On the Playstation 3, Fight Night Round 3 making its way to Japan on March 15th
As well as a game called Dust Cap 3
I don't know about you, but I've never heard of Dust Cap 3
That's not a game, that's why
Wow, I need help tonight
Dust Cap 3 is just an accessory
Because I was like, whatever happened to Dust Cap 3?
I was like, what the hell is Dust Cap 1 and 2?
Sounds like the name of some weird RPG or puzzle game
I've never heard of Dust Cap 1 and 2, apparently Dust Cap 3 is literally that
Yeah, forget it
Also coming out
Let's not submit this show for podcast award consideration
Because it's just not that good tonight and it's all my fault, I'm sorry
Coming out on the Playstation 2
Konjiki no Kouda 2 is coming out, also from Koei
Big week for Koei Entertainment
A game that's going into best hits, I love this title
Princess Maker 4 is coming out
So if you've ever wanted to be your own princess
Now you can for a much lower price
I don't think that's exactly what that's about
It's called Princess Maker 4
Look at the box art
Doesn't that look like princesses?
Having a good time there?
Look at the description
Princess Maker 4 is the fourth installment of the popular promotion simulation game
In which you become the father guardian of a young girl
You must raise her to become a princess in eight years
See? It is Princess Maker
STFU, you don't know what you're talking about
Anyways
Wait, I have more
Dust Cap 4 is coming out in 2008, look for it
No, on Nintendo DS real quick
Bionicle Heroes, the Konami Arcade Collection is coming out over there in Japan
Also, Kuro Kuro Princess
And Lost in Blue 2 is coming out on March 15th as well
And Fingerprint Guard Film Light
I love that one
Just kidding, I knew that wasn't a game
Alright, I'm done
Anyways, US, pretty much as far as games go
There's really one big one this week
And that would be God of War 2
Coming out in PlayStation 2
PSP is not seeing much else either
Call of Duty 3 Road to Victory
That's going to be coming out as well this week
The 360, we're just getting a re-release of Call of Duty 3
The Gold Edition, now with downloadable maps
Actually included in there, I believe you get tokens for that
And some special behind the scenes DVD or something
Lame
For the PlayStation 3, you're getting College Hoops 2K7
Hooray
And let's see
For PC, quite a bit of stuff coming out
None of it looks very good though
Some highlights, the Top Spin 2 is coming to the PC
Battlefield 2 complete
And the rest sucks
For the Wii, Tiger Woods PGA Tour 07
Get your golf on, and then for the DS
You have Mind Quiz
And that's another ripoff of Brain Age
Can I say another game I played this week real quick?
I played Quiz and Dragons with Bobby Blackwolf
And we were so horrible at that game
Words cannot describe the handicap we will need on future games of Quiz and Dragons
Which is now on UltraCade apparently
Even though UltraCade, you know, we're a little meh
But yeah, Quiz and Dragons will own you
Herbie Rescue Rally DS
Which is a port of a crappy movie
Made into a crappy game
Now on the DS
And it looks crappy
That's it
I just have to say real quick, sorry chat
No Rob
It's chat, it's chat
The chat room was making fun of my fuck up earlier
DarkTetsuya says dustcap 3, dustcap's revenge
Fireoboma says dustcap 3 gets more incredible
And Illusion makes the mandatory dustcap 3 electric boogaloo
That would be dustcap 2
Anyway, how about our European releases?
How about it?
A Bunch of Crap on the 16th
Yeah, maybe some of it's kind of crap, some of it's kind of cool
We have Call of Duty 3, Championship Manager 2007
Free Running, Legend of the Dragon
Lunar Knights, Vampire Hunters, Phoenix Wright Ace Attorney, Justice For All
Puzzle Quest, Challenge of the Warlords
Rayman Raving Ravids
Rome Total War, Saint Seiya the Hades
Samurai Warriors 2 Empires
Spectrobes, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles on DS
Test Drive Unlimited, Tiger Woods PGA Tour 07
And UFO Extraterrestrials
And also coming out this week in Europe
Sorry guys, you're only going to get dustcap 2
Because you always get screwed on the release dates and having to wait for things
But enjoy dustcap 2, we have been for the last 3 years
Sound fair?
Very fair
We love you overseas listeners, we really do
Well another love affair that's going on right now is Electronic Arts and Harmonics
And it was just a real brief thing that came out, was leaked to the media this week
That Electronic Arts announced they have penned a deal with MTV Networks and Harmonics
To publish Harmonics' next game
However what that game is, is a secret for now
So it's interesting though because obviously Guitar Hero was something that Red Octane published
But now EA is going to be filling that role for whatever Harmonics' next game is
I seem to remember previously said, and it looks like this article makes reference to it too
Harmonics once said that Guitar Hero is just the tip of the iceberg, just the beginning of what these games can become
And I seem to remember Harmonics saying that their next project was way bigger than Guitar Hero
Like a real thing
And a lot of people speculated it's going to be a game that really teaches you how to play guitar
I don't know
I'm still waiting for Sax Maniacs
I kind of wish they'd bring back the Amplitude thing in some new evolved regard
Because I did love me some Amplitude
They could evolve the game, make it next gen somehow, a little more competitive
Crackin' DJ over here
Crackin' DJ was not even a Harmonics, that was a Sega game
I don't care, it's still fun
Crackin' DJ, I haven't heard that in years
At least Crackin' DJ sort of made you feel like you were actually remixing stuff
Because you were going through the same motions as an actual DJ would
So that was kind of neat
And I will be kickbanning users in chatroom who said that the game Harmonics is making is Dustcat 4
Let the joke die you assholes
I think we have the start of a brand new joke to beat into the ground
Dustcat 4 bust a cap
I saw that in there, that was funny
Ha ha ha
Anyways, so more EA news of course
They are kicking off an online music competition featuring singing sensation Lily Ellen
Who the fuck that is?
I am not hip to these artists out there
Anyways, apparently Lily Ellen, they are doing, I guess this is coincidentally
Let me just put this in perspective for people
If the music doesn't sound like
Puch pooch meow meow meow meow
Puch pooch meow meow meow
Then Loki doesn't listen to it
If it's not cat techno, it's not for me
So, anyways
Apparently she is doing a version of her song, Smile, for Sims 2
Which is going to be in Simlish, which makes it sound even more retarded
So, very excellent
Just so you know, Lily Allen is a newer artist who has recently peaked at the number 2 position in the UK
With her single, Alright, Still
And it actually peaked at number 20 here in the US
And that is who Lily Allen is
And I've seen this, I've probably heard this song before
Don't make me pull up a clip
To which I would say, alright, still don't care
So, but if you do win this contest though
You will be winning a prize package worth approximately $1,390
And have a chance to record a song in Simlish for possible inclusion in a future Sims 2 game
So, great, you get to sing a song in gibberish that's going to appear in a game
That probably no one will actually pay attention to the music
That sounds awesome
I want to sing a song in gibberish
That's my song, Lily Allen, are you listening?
You could totally sample me on your next record
Isn't that like the Strong Bad Lights which rave all of a sudden?
So, how about SingStar?
Oh, yay, there's another thing I'm looking forward to on the Playstation 3
Well, we are having, for SingStar there's going to be a release in the US in fall
It's going to be early June in the UK
And they are going to be doing this thing called Game 3.0
It's a very interesting thing
Basically, you're going to be able to download new content
But upload content as well using your USB camera
You can record videos
And then everyone will look at it
Like a Numa Numa kid or something
Dear God who is in heaven, please listen to this boy's prayer
I've been a very good Rob this whole year long
Please, please, please God Almighty who art in heaven
Please, please make Loki get really drunk one night
And record some videos on SingStar
And upload them to this Game 3.0 service
So that the entirety of the internet can download and make fun of him
Thank you, amen
What?
God doesn't listen to you
Come on, Loki, you know you want to do it
No, you want me to do that
I do
I don't want to do that at all
I am not touching that fucking game
Karaoke will not be entering my house
Fuck that shit
GS68 says
I don't know, it makes me think of a Caturday macro
It says, I'm in your OLRs, drunk in your hosts
Maybe that's God speaking
We all know we're all going to hell
Probably
Except not me because I don't believe in hell
We're going to wherever pagan people go
Let's not turn this into a religious
We're not a God cast
Go look up God cast in iTunes if you want religious stuff
We've got to talk about games
And one game that we'll talk about here is Warhawk
It's interesting because Warhawk went that it was going to be downloadable only when it went over to the Playstation 3
Here's the other thing you need to know
Warhawk is not going to be single player now
It's going to be a multiplayer only battle arena
Since the game has moved into the Playstation Network
It's a downloadable title
It's only going to be something that you can play online
But the cool news is that you don't get to just do planes
You can do jeeps, tanks, infantry units, and the whole works there
So you need to get some other online modes as well
But if you don't like to play online games, too bad
Warhawk will not be for you on the Playstation 3
It's just like Star Fox 64
It's like Star Fox is all about flying
Now I have to run around and I have tanks and shit
Why can't it just be about the flying?
Eh, whatever
Anyways
So when you think about high end computer systems, you probably don't think of Commodore
But they're hoping to change that
Because now they are back and they are trying to make a name for themselves
If the year was 1984, I would be thinking about Commodore
Because the Commodore 64 was my first gaming platform, really truly
Commodore 64 is an amazing piece of machinery
Amen
So yeah, now they're launching a new Commodore PC
Geared for PC gaming, and it's supposed to launch at Germany's SeeBit show
Actually this week, March 15th
I don't know
They're basically saying that's going to provide what gamers need and want
Excellent
Can I play Last Ninja on it, yes or no?
Better
Because if not, there's going to be one hell of a syntax error coming out of this angry gamer
That was a Commodore joke
Don't laugh at once
Yeah, that's why no one got it
That's why we're on the internet, boys and girls
Not satellite radio or the real deal
Maybe we should call ourselves Video Obscura
That'd be an awesome name
That's actually not a bad name for a podcast
At least Video Game Obscura
At least people would know we're a video game podcast as opposed to when people go
What the hell is Orange Lounge Radio?
Are you guys a lounge music podcast?
Yeah, we just had Richard Cheeze on last week
Speaking of cheese
There is a Lego MMO that is in development coming in 2008
It's being developed by NetDevil for auto assault
You go around building stuff and talking with people
It's just an MMO with Legos
It's for kids, but I love Legos so I'm probably going to play it
I love Legos too
I remember when you tried to make the charging cradle out of Legos
I did make a charging cradle
Speaking of which, I broke the charging cradle this week
Because Nelly wanted to play Elite Beat Agents
Because she's been playing that game now
I had to rip the cable out because it doesn't work very well plugged into the
For those that didn't hear the shows a while back
Loki actually built a DS charger out of Legos
So it was like a docking bay
He built one out of Legos
I like Legos too
Actual Legos
Not so much all these games
I measure my Legos in gallons now
And I still have 10 gallons of Legos in my closet
Let's build the next OLR studio out of Legos
We don't have enough Legos for that
I did one time build something
I used to have this desk that stretched one whole wall on my room
And I used every single Lego to build one giant, like, base thing or something
It's just like a really cool, like, I don't know
You remember Classic Gaming Expo though
Where they built the Space Invaders thing out of Legos
Hey, is Classic Gaming Expo coming back this year?
I heard they were going to be in Vegas this year
They're supposed to do, I think, the 10th anniversary
I want to go, I want to go, Jamie, let's go
But I'm going to something else
I'm going to Pinagogo
I heard a rumor you were going to
I don't know if I can say it on air, but
Yes, I'm planning on, if I can at all manage it
I'm going to be going to Dragon Con
Okay, she said I didn't
I want to go to be there at the podcasters panel
Just, you know, right now it's like
How am I going to afford that?
But, you know, I'm working on it
I played Monopoly Pinball
And I was actually kicking ass over at Sunnyvale Golf Land yesterday
What the fuck does that have to do with anything Dragon Con?
She mentioned pinball
Pinagogo
It's going to be a hard time
I don't know if I told, you know, everybody
But we did get a new machine
And we got a bride of pin-bot
And we are actually
Dan has my Rocky and Bullwinkle working now
Which makes me intensely happy
And our Guns N' Roses is now for sale
Aww
Will you sell it to someone on the internets?
Oh, but shipping would be an arm and a leg
If they live in the area
Or want to come pick it up
And pay us a lot of money for it
Then I don't think we have a lot
Define a lot
How much are you selling the Guns N' Roses for?
I don't know, it's up to Dan
He actually may have a trade worked out on it
But I think we are also selling our Johnny Mnemonic
It's a good pin, but I hate Johnny Mnemonic
You should let us know some prices
Well, I'll talk to the hubby and see
If he wants me to use our independent
Non-corporate sponsored podcast
To sell my pinball machine
Why not? You got to get something out of this deal
Seriously
Alright, well something else you can do
If you love Orange Launch Radio
We'll give some cheap plugs
For some of our other stuff right now
You can always leave us a review on iTunes
Because we could definitely use some more 5 star review on iTunes
Because it helps spread the word about the program
Also, you can visit our MySpace
www.myspace.com
Slash Orange Launch Radio
And be our friend on there
Because who doesn't love having a thousand friends on MySpace
And being attention whores over there
Also, we are now
Participating in the new All Games Community site
Over at community.allgames.com
Most of us are so far
You will be as of tonight
We will all have profiles on that site
And I'm actually using my blog over there
It's kind of fun
And I've been doing official
Well, not, I don't know, official
Whatever, but Orange Launch
Video game review haikus
Where I review games in haiku form
So if you want to see what the hell that's all about
You gotta go find my page on
The Community All Games site
Because I review video games in haiku form
Anything else we should plug
Before we take a break
I don't know
I can't think of anything
This is kind of a short show tonight
I have a weird story
But it's not gaming
Well, it's
No, it's not gaming really
There's some weird reason
Like, this is weird
Usually our shows have been running
Almost to the two hour mark
We haven't even hit 90 minutes
For part A this week
Why not?
A short story from Loki
Okay, this is kind of weird
I was watching Comedy Central today
And Spike TV absorbed Comedy Central
Like, at least on my Comcast box
So two channels were Spike TV
Which were playing some really crappy
Pros versus Joes
Or something like that
Thing, which is
I don't have any interest in sports TV
But it was funny though
Because all of a sudden
It was like Spike TV
Also last night I was watching G4 TV
Because they had cheaters on
And that was kind of funny
What else are you going to watch
Like, you know, at midnight
I don't know
I guess I could have watched Saturday Night Live
But that's not funny
So
Actually, hey
But Saturday Night Live did bring us
Laser Cats this season
It is getting better again
It's not
It ain't
It's Dana Carvey
Chris Farley
Or, you know
Especially not
It's Gilda Radner
Or Dan Aykroyd
Days
But
It is still pretty
It's getting better
Than it was last year
Of course, usually I try to go out
On Saturday nights
So I don't know
I don't get to watch it at home a lot
But I do see, like, the YouTubage and things
Come on, what did this year bring us?
This year brought us Laser Cats
It brought us Dick in a Box
Some good stuff
Good stuff
I actually
When I went to New York in October
I got to see the set
That was kind of fun
In a touristy way
So, hey
Any other
Do you have any short stories
You'd like to share with our listeners
Um
I'm starting a
A fund that's called the
Send Dark Sakura to Dragon Con Fund
Either that or buy me a Dolphie
Why don't you massage your way to Dragon Con?
You know, I would
But I have to take a whole lot more massage classes before then
Oh, that sucks
But, um
I'm actually
You know what
Two weeks to go, Rob
No, three weeks, sorry
Three weeks to go
I will be a fully certified massage therapist
And then I can charge everybody
Cool
I guess
Well, I mean
Massage is good for your health
Maybe they need
You know
Conventions are a lot of walking
You should massage people's feet
I'm actually thinking about
Um
Cause my friend
A lot of my friends are on the
Fanime staff
I'm actually thinking about asking them if I can
Get an event license
God, Fanime's right around the corner too
May, end of May
Yeah
But I'm seeing if
I'm gonna see if I can
Get like an event license from
Wherever I have to in San Jose
And set up a
Set up a
Massage at
Fanime
There you go
Fun
I don't have a chair yet
But I can rent a chair
Alright
So for the weary
Fanime con-goer
Do you know how often
I've been in
Fucking costume
And wish someone would rub my feet
Cause I was in
Freaking
Five inch
Platform heels
Oh my god
My Mad Hatter costume
I've worn many an uncomfortable costume
But my Mad Hatter costume was the worst
Because of the wings on my back
And the fucking heels
So
I think massage therapy
At
Anime conventions
Is brilliant
Alright well we'll see what happens
Holler if you hear me
Alright
Holla
We better go ahead and take a break
So we'll be back
After this short break
With a little bit more
Orange Lounge Radio
In part B
Orange Lounge Radio is taped live
On Sunday nights
And is podcasted to the world
Twice a week
Stay tuned to our podcast feed
For the conclusion
Of this week's
Orange Lounge Radio
We'll be right back