Orange Lounge Radio
With your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky and Loco
Tonight, March 18th, 2007
All next-gen systems are set to roll up
A beautiful Katamari
Halo 3 is set to arrive in September
But on what day?
And what happens when two popular dance games get together and have a baby?
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello everyone out there on the internet
And welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
We are that podcast dedicated to video games
Video gaming, gaming culture and the gamer lifestyle
My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky
Joining me as always, say hello to DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
Yo
And also joining us tonight, say hello to Techmaster Loki
Hi
Alright, if this is your first time listening to Orange Lounge Radio
We'd like to welcome you to our little program
DarkSakura, Loki and I all met a few years ago at an arcade
And decided, hey let's start a radio show talking about games
And we've been doing this internet program for the past almost five years
It'll be five years in June
Talking about for a while music-based video games
And a couple years ago expanding into podcasting
And talking about a general variety of games
We're going to deviate from our usual forum a little bit
Usually we start off the show talking about how is your gaming week
But tonight, we want to get right into this
Because we think this might be possibly what might draw some new people to our site this week
Is this particular story
I'm going to cite a particular story of this site
QJ.net ran this story
So let's take a look, shall we?
Rumor, release dates for beautiful Katamari for Xbox 360, PlayStation 3
Before we go any further, we'll take this moment to warn everyone
That this particular topic is currently marked with a huge red rumor flag
This is a report about something that has somehow made the internet implode
But until we get any official word from Namco Bandai about the whole issue
We suggest taking the following details with a grain of salt
Okay, good
Blah, blah, blah, there's reports going around about beautiful Katamari
Blah, blah, blah, it's going to come out on the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360
October 17, 2007 for $39.99
On the Wii, November 14, 2007 for $29.99
The report goes on to say that the PlayStation 3 version will feature 6-axis support
Though fails to elaborate on how exactly this will be implemented
And also points out that the release dates they gave actually coincide with a trademark
Namco Bandai filed back in January
A screenshot has said trademark has been provided as proof
Now as much as we want to start doing cartwheels of joy over this piece of news
There are several things we need to keep in mind
At the moment, the only source of these reports seem to be Orange Lounge Radio
Who are they? I've never heard of them
There's this really annoying guy and then this other really annoying guy and then this really awesome girl on it
A bunch of liars is who they are, they're a bunch of damn dirty liars
Although they must have some pretty solid reasons on how they came up with this bit of news
Skeptics can say that there are still some gaps that need to be filled in
We all have yet to receive official word from Namco Bandai
Which either confirms or denies the existence of beautiful Katamari
Trademarks get filed almost every day
But that doesn't necessarily mean that they actually get used
I don't know, they're really poking some holes in this theory here
This is something else
The team behind Katamari has already been disbanded
And as far as everyone knows, no sequels were planned
Although Katamari trademarks were registered towards the end of 2006
Well we just so happen to have the man who started this whole thing right here in studio tonight
Loki, you goddamn liar
Is this some type of April Fools joke you're playing on all of us?
No
Is that what it is?
Tell me Knights is coming to the Wii? What the hell?
That's not my story
Alright, no
Seriously though, it wasn't just Katamari
In fact, we have the whole lineup for Namco
Which we'll be revealing a little later in the show
So it's not just Katamari
I got excited by Katamari because I love the game
So I figured, share the story with everyone
That and I gotta get a jump on those big corporate sites
Because, you know, they like to beat everybody to stuff
Anyways, so
Beautiful Katamari
It is set for this fall
The Playstation 3 and Xbox 360 versions
Are set for October 17th
$39.99, which is great
You know, nice price point for a game like that
And if you remember, the original Katamari
Also very inexpensive
And then of course the Wii version is coming in November
And that's also $29.99
Now, we do have a big time span between now and the fall
So, I can confirm this much
Okay, the game is coming out
That is for sure
Whether Namco decides to release it on those exact dates
Because, you know, dates change a lot
You know, especially with six months gaps in between them
I would say that yeah, it's gonna come around the fall for sure
Those exact dates, who knows
But those are street dates, not ship dates
Ship dates are a day before
Because, you know, most retailers out there
And most distributors out there
They work on street date systems
As opposed to ship dates
As, you know, most publishers work on
So
Let's say that someone's listening to this show for the first time
Because they want to hear what a bunch of liars we really are
Why should anyone believe you?
Tell me, tell us
How you got, tell us what happened Friday morning
What took us from you finding out about this
And how you found out about it too
Posting it on the site and so on
Well, I do a lot of work on order forms and stuff for my company
I'm a, you know, I work at a game distributor
One of the big ones in the United States
And so, because I work on this show as well
And because I'm, you know, a huge freak
When it comes to making sure I have accurate dates
And all my, you know, order forms and stuff
I check our system for new stuff
Almost twice daily, if not more
Because I'm crazy like that
And so, I will look and see if there's new stuff
Especially next gen stuff all the time
And when I saw, you know
Actually, I think the first title I did see was
Ace Combat 6
Which we'll be talking about later
I saw that and the system was like
Hey, that's kind of neat, new game
So I, you know, said
Okay, well probably got some Namco title downloads
And sure enough, pulled up
Oh, there's Katamari
So I was like, okay, I gotta let people know this
Because I was literally like jumping up and down in my seat
You know, when I saw this
But anyways, as far as how I get these dates
These dates are actually straight from the publishers
Usually their sales department, purchasing department
Wherever you may call it
Are they secret?
Are you breaking an NDA by posting these?
Can you get fired?
Can we get sued?
No, no, there's no
This is public information
Any one of our, you know, customers
Has access to this information
I'm assuming that most of them probably
Don't, you know, work in internet radio as well
But at the same time, I mean, you see this stuff all the time
Also on like, you know, GameStop or Amazon
Or something like that
They get title downloads as well
Sometimes, you know, GameStop and stuff like that
They'll put in arbitrary, you know, titles or dates
Or whatever, you know, for preorders
But since we don't really work on a preorder system
We don't have anything like that
We pretty much, if they give us, you know, the information
To set up an item
We will set it up in our system
And with whatever information they give us
Well, interestingly enough
One thing that we observed is that almost at the same time
And I don't know who posted it first
You, these guys, but this other site
Xbox IC had some guy renegade with a cell phone camera
At a blockbuster who took screenshots in their system
Also of Ace Combat and beautiful Katamari
And so it was very weird because, you know, we don't talk to that site
They don't talk to us
But yet we posted almost very similar stories
At the exact same time
It's very interesting
And if you look at their dates on there
Their dates are all Friday dates
Whereas ours are all Wednesday dates
Wednesdays are typically when, you know, most companies get their games released
Of course games come out every single day of the week
But for the most part it's usually Wednesdays, Thursdays or Tuesdays
Usually in the middle of the week
Now blockbusters, they're one of two things
They're either gonna, most likely they're gonna be
Not direct with a publisher
So for Blockbuster
They would be getting their product received into the distributor
Or their corporate office or wherever
And shipped out to the store
Usually about two days ground or whatnot
That's why they have Friday street dates in there instead of Wednesdays
It just, you know, makes the system nice and neat and stuff
So, yeah
That's basically how we come about most of our street, you know, street dates and stuff like that
It's from actual sources at these companies
The problem is though their marketing departments
And the sales departments don't always talk to each other
And so in the case of like, you know, Konami last year
When we released all the information about their E3 lineup
They apparently didn't really want that information to be, you know, leaked out
But unfortunately somebody in their sales department went and did that
But, you know, that's life
That was a very interesting thing
Because, you know, we have friends that work at Konami
Several friends work at Konami
And they almost got a little heat
Because Konami thought they blapped
And that isn't the case
It was this whole roundabout thing that went on
Which was very interesting last year when that all went down
Yeah
Now you say that this news, you know, the dates could change
The prices could change
And a lot of websites who've been blocking about this
Have been kind of saying that
Wow, this is really ballsy of them to post some dates and some dollar amounts
When it's so far out of advance
But you're kind of admitting that that could change
If it changes, it won't be by much
I mean, usually, you know, Namco as far as I'm familiar with
They don't really change dates too much
As far as stuff releasing
You know, some companies, for example, some of the smaller ones
You know, there's titles they'll move each month
And, you know, we'll see a date change like six or seven times
You know, some companies are a little bit better by that
When they put a street date in the system
They'll actually stick to that
You know, Rockstar with Grand Theft Auto IV
That's been October 17th since it's been announced
But I think about Bethesda and Oblivion
And that date always falls back
Yeah, exactly
And it can be, you know, a couple things
They can be trying to postpone it to a later date because it's not done
Or because they want to time it with, you know, certain releases or lack of releases
You know, it's really up to the company
But I, you know, I don't really kind of
If that were the case and if I was always afraid of dates changing
Then I'd never be telling you guys news
But the reason is you, I mean, even if the date changes
That's, you know, whatever
But the fact is this game is coming out
Next question I'm going to ask you
Yeah, and I think of
Let's think of some cases on this program where this was correct
And you named games through the distribution system
People didn't have yet that ended up coming out
We may not have blogged about them on the site
Because we don't have the resources to have people
Crawling blog sites 24 hours a day, 7 days a week
And the distribution thing and the way the other sites do it
We don't, we have day jobs
We do this for fun in the evening, you know
Like Logie said, his day job is distribution
So we don't have the resources to blog about it
And have it, you know, in writing that we were the first every time
And the fact is sometimes, you know, like I said
The marketing departments and sales departments of these companies
Don't always work together
Some of them do, like for example Nintendo
They know not to say anything about anything
And even when you feed them a lot of alcohol
They still will not say anything
But yet I seem to recall that you were the only one
That was willing to say that the Wii was going to come out
After the PlayStation 3
Because at some point earlier in the year
Nintendo had said, no, we're going to beat the PlayStation 3
And they didn't, remember the Wii came out a little bit later
And you called that, I remember that distinctly
Not that I'm trying to inflate our own ego here
You know, it's not a big deal, honestly
But it just, I don't know
For me, I get a little bit frustrated when I see all these website headlines
And say, rumor, rumor, rumor, rumor
Yet when EB Games and GameStop will post dates
They'll block it with, EB Games says this is going to come out
And they don't say it's a rumor
Why couldn't this have been blocked saying, distribution leak says, blah, blah, blah
Why does that have to be rumor, rumor, rumor?
Well it's because, you know, our website doesn't have the word game
In it or a company name like Nintendo or something like that
And that's why
For example though, I mean, look at the Konami releases and stuff
Or for example, I think someone, I can't remember if you did this or not in the story
But the whole Wired article saying, Karaoke Revolution, American Idol
All these guys are a bunch of liars
And this thing is never coming out
And then it comes out
Do we see, you know, a story run later?
Oh, they were right, no
Everybody forgets that we mentioned it
And once, you know, a big site runs the press release
Then everybody forgets that we even mentioned anything
And this is how it's happened in the past
I mean, full out of two on the PSP
I kept seeing this weeks and weeks and weeks and weeks after each other
But no one remembered when, you know, was it one up ran the fucking press release
Or ran the story that's coming out
I was like, oh look, it's coming out on the PSP now
The other one I think of is Oblivion on the PSP
Because when you first said that on the show
I was like, what? How the hell are they going to do Oblivion on the PSP?
But sure enough, we find out later on
A scaled down dungeon only version
And you know, sometimes they'll release press releases
About game announcements before sales will find out
Like I said, it all depends on, you know, what the marketing department wants to do
And what the sales department wants to do
The sales department wants to make sure that the retailers and distribution