It's so easy, happy go lucky, we are the world, we deal with you, you, you, you, us, us, us, us
Thank you for watching!
The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_23]: Orange Lounge Radio Live, episode number 145, coming up at ya.
[SPEAKER_23]: Tonight's episode, we're going to talk about greasy breadsticks, yummy tiramisu cake, and diet soda.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_23]: Orange Lounge Radio Live
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_11]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_23]: And this is episode number 140 for this, June the 5th of 2005.
[SPEAKER_23]: You're tuned into Orange Lounge Radio, radio that gamers really want.
[SPEAKER_23]: And this is Orange Lounge Radio Live, your home for all the news and discussion on rhythm and music games, as well as the gamer community and the pop culture world.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're plugged in and fully interactive through our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_23]: My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_23]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_23]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: Suicide girls suck!
[SPEAKER_21]: OMG, I want to kill myself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's got a razor?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm so emo, watch me slit my wrists and bleed my angst all over the world.
[SPEAKER_23]: Does anyone actually self-declare themselves as emo?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, I hear a lot of... No, because that's not cool.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't... I thought emo was, like, the hip thing to do right now, you know?
[SPEAKER_23]: But I don't get it, because everybody makes fun of emo people.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know anybody that's standing up for emo rights.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, I don't know anyone that's, like, saying, you know, I'm emo!
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, but see, the things that you make fun of now are hip, like, next year.
[SPEAKER_23]: So are you saying that, like, VH1 will do the I Love the Emo next year?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember, kids, down the block, not across the street.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wow, think about that one for a minute.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, also joining us, TechMath's Loki.
[SPEAKER_23]: I love Pizza Hut.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's becoming a tradition for you to come over and bring Pizza Hut every Sunday.
[SPEAKER_23]: Twice.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, twice is enough.
[SPEAKER_23]: I can swear, like, every week you've been in this new studio, you've brought over Pizza Hut.
[SPEAKER_23]: I've only done twice!
[SPEAKER_23]: The new studio, by the way, is right across the freeway from Pizza Slut slash Taco Bell.
[SPEAKER_23]: Toxic Hell!
[SPEAKER_23]: It's more like Taco Bell with some pizza.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, it really is what it is.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyway, also joining us tonight, we have a very special guest.
[SPEAKER_23]: We haven't had many guests in the new studio, so we're very pleased to welcome a staff member of DDRFreak.com.
[SPEAKER_23]: Say hello to Islander.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_23]: One of the original ddrfreak.com members Yeah, can you believe that?
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm over five years Shit, that's a long time I know, it's a very long time Oh, you know, before I forget I need to give a shout out to OhMyGodIt'sDubes because when I first saw that name I thought it was OhMyGodIt'sBoobs I want to know if that person stole the name from my live journal And so I was just like, wow And then I think somebody else changed their name to OhMyGodIt'sNoobs Which I thought was kind of funny too
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh my God, it's something that rhymes with oobs tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to say one more thing tonight, though.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, what's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Happy birthday to Murdoch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because he's 39 and ancient.
[SPEAKER_23]: But that's, in U.S.
[SPEAKER_23]: time, that's actually tomorrow, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: 6-6 of 66?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's June 6th in the U.K., so happy birthday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't he a fictional character?
[SPEAKER_09]: I can still say happy birthday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okie doke.
[SPEAKER_09]: If Mickey Mouse could have a birthday, okay?
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, we'll be back after this with more happy Skippy Orange Lingerie.
[SPEAKER_23]: If you want to join our chat room and, you know, hang out with OMG, it's Doobs and Boobs and Noobs and Scoobs and whatever else they come up with, head on over to our website, www.orangelingerie.com and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_23]: In this break, we're going to hear some music from Poppin' Music Iroha, also known as Poppin' Music 12, because somebody wanted me to play this song last week and I never got to it.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think it was Siggy or something.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't even know if he's listening right now, but can't say I didn't honor that request.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, what are you giggling at over there?
[SPEAKER_23]: You're giggling like a little girl.
[SPEAKER_23]: You actually found an animated graphic.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, somebody posted in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_23]: Somebody posted that in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's brilliant.
[SPEAKER_23]: Somebody posted a picture, for those of you that aren't in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_23]: Somebody actually posted a picture of a hand showing the razor.
[SPEAKER_23]: And it says, remember kids, what is that?
[SPEAKER_23]: Down the street.
[SPEAKER_10]: Down the road, make it count.
[SPEAKER_23]: Down the road, not across the street.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to have to find Sherlock's icon.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, we'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_23]: Poppin' music.
[SPEAKER_23]: Orange Launch Radio.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for watching!
S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_15]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge Radio, Bomani Music, and more.
[SPEAKER_18]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: In that break, Shizuku, the new StartMine remix.
[SPEAKER_23]: The new Akira Yamaoka song, Usoki Hyper Rock, and Virokana, all from Papa Music Iroha.
[SPEAKER_23]: Or if you're lazy like me, you can just say Papa Music 12, but technically it's Papa Music Iroha.
[SPEAKER_23]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: and all the, and Goonies.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, the Goonies was in Pop Music 10.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, and I played Star Mine.
[SPEAKER_23]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_23]: I thought you hated that remix.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do hate it, but I had to play it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was actually pretty fun and easy.
[SPEAKER_23]: I like poppin' music an awful lot.
[SPEAKER_23]: I sometimes resent it because it seems like there's all these new poppin' music games coming out and then, you know, whereas Guitar Freaks, well, I guess we do have... I keep thinking PS2.
[SPEAKER_23]: But, like, no new DDR lately.
[SPEAKER_23]: So I guess I gotta resent poppin' music for being so damn successful.
[SPEAKER_23]: But it really is a cute game.
[SPEAKER_23]: And it's really weird that not a lot of arcades here have it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, I mean, it is and it isn't.
[SPEAKER_23]: I mean, let's face it, the music in poppin' music...
[SPEAKER_23]: is a little scary to, I think, a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_23]: But, I don't know, to me, it's cute.
[SPEAKER_23]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think more people should be into it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hi, we're here on Orange Laundry Radio, episode number 145.
[SPEAKER_23]: Somebody in chat told me I said 140 in the opening.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oops, my bad.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's actually 145 tonight.
[SPEAKER_23]: I thought I said 145, but somebody said I said 140.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: 145 tonight, that means we're very close to 150.
[SPEAKER_23]: Isn't that scary?
[SPEAKER_23]: You know what else is this month?
[SPEAKER_23]: The three-year anniversary of this show.
[SPEAKER_23]: Three years!
[SPEAKER_23]: Come along with us on that BART ride, huh?
[SPEAKER_23]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_23]: And this show is now old enough to attend preschool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, when I was three, I had a good vocabulary.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think that our vocabulary has grown quite a bit from shit, fuck, damn, you know.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, but I still like my dick and fart jokes.
[SPEAKER_23]: Pfft.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still like burping on the microphone.
[SPEAKER_10]: It guarantees that the microphone stays in my possession.
[SPEAKER_23]: Listen to the opening.
[SPEAKER_23]: It still has the fart noise in it.
[SPEAKER_23]: And I don't think anybody that was listening to us episode one still listens, which is kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wasn't Dark Tetsuya there for episode one?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think that's about it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wasn't he in the room for episode one?
[SPEAKER_23]: Puppy listens still occasionally.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Puppy needs to actually do his correspondent job.
[SPEAKER_23]: Bradley, Arcadian42, he was there episode one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, he was.
[SPEAKER_23]: So we do have a few people.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have some of our old schoolers.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyway, so we'll be having our three year anniversary special thingy sometime this month.
[SPEAKER_23]: Don't know when yet, because I could be out of town one of the weeks this month, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well that's poopy.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, I'm going to be going to LA this month, and then actually in August I'm going to be going to the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_23]: I actually have two trips to the East Coast planned right now, which is really weird.
[SPEAKER_23]: One for work and one for leisure.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was going to go to the New York area around Labor Day, and now I'm going to be going to Pennsylvania in August.
[SPEAKER_23]: So that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, I heard about, you know, it's kind of empty, there's not a whole lot there, but I heard about some classic gaming store out there.
[SPEAKER_23]: Somebody had sent me a tip over email, so I'm really curious to check that out.
[SPEAKER_23]: I just hope it doesn't suck like a certain classic video game store we have here in town.
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I will give a short history on that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Leah, who was the ex-wife partner, went into business with Dan to keep the store alive, and so it became Game On.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then she kind of screwed him up, because she wanted pocket money, because she was dating a rich guy.
[SPEAKER_23]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: My week was work, and of course having Monday off, like all of us who work for a bank did.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I really didn't do a whole bunch of anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Played some PSO, of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: Played some Silent Hill, didn't get too far, so I'm actually at the same save point I was at before.
[SPEAKER_10]: Played a lot of Puyo Puyo, watched Dan beat Fire Emblem.
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_23]: The weekend was okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: I played a little Final Fantasy yesterday.
[SPEAKER_23]: And then pretty much I had to do stuff for Nelly's birthday.
[SPEAKER_23]: So we went to Red Lobster.
[SPEAKER_23]: I hate seafood.
[SPEAKER_23]: But I got steak.
[SPEAKER_23]: Steak's good.
[SPEAKER_23]: And then, um... What else?
[SPEAKER_23]: Uh... Not too much.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think during the week was just kind of... Eh.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was kind of slow.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was nice having a short week, though.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, I've got to go back to Red Lobster at some point, because there's a waiter there, and I think he's gay, because he was giving us all this free food.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was me and two of my gay friends went over to Red Lobster.
[SPEAKER_23]: He started giving us, like, all this free food and didn't charge us for it.
[SPEAKER_23]: We didn't get charged for drinks.
[SPEAKER_23]: He brought us, like, double sides and stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'll just... Highlander's getting all kind of gay as he says, I want to go with you.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, I swear, there's like this pink mafia out there.
[SPEAKER_23]: And, you know, I'm going to expose the secret here.
[SPEAKER_23]: If you get the slightest inclination that somebody at a particular service industry, like, you know, at a store, at a restaurant, might be, you know, gay...
[SPEAKER_23]: Flirt with them because you'll get a discount or something.
[SPEAKER_23]: Or if they suspect that you're at least like a gay rights supporter, you can get like breaks and stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's really weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: Does that mean we need to go into Red Lobster wearing a shirt that says hag on it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'll tell you which waiter it is too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: I swear there's like a pink mafia out there.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_23]: But anyways, other than that, really, nothing has been going on.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's pretty much just been work stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: I know we've got our Dallas people coming out in the week of the 20th, which I think is a couple weeks away now.
[SPEAKER_23]: So they're gonna come out to which I guess I have to play them at some games or something, kick their ass, just because that's
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, standard company procedure.
[SPEAKER_23]: And then today I went to Pizza Hut and I got two things of breadsticks and the pepperoni pizza.
[SPEAKER_23]: I've eaten half of that.
[SPEAKER_23]: I still have one thing of breadsticks left, which I'm debating about keeping for later on.
[SPEAKER_23]: Because they're damn good.
[SPEAKER_23]: Fascinating, really.
[SPEAKER_23]: It is fascinating.
[SPEAKER_23]: Then today I had to build a computer for my sister and
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know where half of my motherboards went, but I have a lot of crappy computer parts, so she's going to get a computer that's about comparable with what we used to run the show on.
[SPEAKER_23]: The reason I say it's comparable is because it's almost out of the same parts.
[SPEAKER_23]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_23]: I have a complaint about that movie.
[SPEAKER_23]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_23]: I haven't seen it yet, so no spoilers.
[SPEAKER_10]: General Grievous.
[SPEAKER_10]: I heard how just kick-ass he was in the Clone Wars cartoon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, he... Damn it, it's hard for me to make my major complaint or else I'll spill it for Rob.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's just something about Obi-Wan riding a giant iguana.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, there was some iguana writing.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_23]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm supposed to see it Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: Me and some of the Pink Mafia are going to check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why aren't you listening to Pump Up the Volume?
[SPEAKER_23]: Maybe we'll get in free.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: Because I'm trying to revive my own show at some point.
[SPEAKER_23]: So between that and karaoke, I don't have a lot of free weeknights.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't make me, like, haunt you or something.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'll TiVo it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Speaking of haunting, we're supposed to be scheduling another trip out to some remote cemetery that's down by Dry Town in Sutter Creek.
[SPEAKER_23]: And apparently it's on some guy's land and we won't get bothered out there.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, whatever happened to the ghost hunting?
[SPEAKER_23]: It's been on a hiatus for a while, just because A, I'm moving and everything, and B, we've been trying to get in contact with local members of, I forget, there's an actual organization that people sign up for, which I really don't think there's a big deal behind it, but it's just like, they have standard protocol to take or something like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: So when you go ghost hunting, is it like Luigi's Mansion?
[SPEAKER_23]: No, it's not like Luigi's Mansion.
[SPEAKER_23]: Did you take a vacuum cleaner?
[SPEAKER_23]: I know!
[SPEAKER_23]: No, it's not like that at all.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's mainly, it's just kind of like surveying, basically just take readings of areas and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_23]: The thing that I would probably be doing, though, that most normal people would be doing is they usually don't try to disturb the area, whereas I believe it's like if you want the rat to come out of the woodpile, you've got to start shaking the woodpile for that to happen.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, same sense in this.
[SPEAKER_23]: If you want something to happen, you gotta piss it off.
[SPEAKER_16]: Mario!
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyways, but no, supposedly we're just gonna go chill down there.
[SPEAKER_23]: We were gonna do an all nighter thing, but my fiance didn't like that idea.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, instead we're gonna go down there at dusk and hang out during the night for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Should we go ghost hunting in Alabama?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because we actually have old cemeteries.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, this is an old cemetery, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: These are from, like, the 1700s and 1600s.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't want to talk to old people.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's all fun.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, anyways, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a picture of a ghost.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, but you know everyone has a picture of Michael Jackson, so it's okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyways, that's all.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_23]: Islander, how was your week and how was your day?
[SPEAKER_24]: My week started off at Fanime, actually.
[SPEAKER_24]: A big anime convention down in the Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_24]: And woke up, unfortunately, with a hangover.
[SPEAKER_24]: Too many tequila shots, not a good thing.
[SPEAKER_24]: And either my roommate or someone down there got me sick.
[SPEAKER_24]: So the entire week I've been fighting a cold.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm pretty much getting over it at this point.
[SPEAKER_24]: Today, I was in the mood for Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_24]: Another dance simulation game.
[SPEAKER_24]: Pump It Up, really?
[SPEAKER_24]: I've never heard of it.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_24]: For those of you who don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think most of our listeners know Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm pretty sure they do.
[SPEAKER_23]: I hope you do.
[SPEAKER_23]: If you don't, Korean five panels.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's all I need to know.
[SPEAKER_24]: So I had to drive all the way down to Florin Mall.
[SPEAKER_24]: They still have Pump It Up there?
[SPEAKER_24]: They still have Pump It Up there, and they have a Dance Freaks.
[SPEAKER_24]: OMG!
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes, the Korean version of Dance Mania X.
[SPEAKER_24]: OMG, I have to go play this.
[SPEAKER_24]: Do they have different songs in it?
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, it's basically DMX1 with a few K-pop songs thrown in.
[SPEAKER_24]: Are any decent K-pop songs?
[SPEAKER_24]: Um... There's a few good ones.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, unfortunately, Caution is not in it.
[SPEAKER_24]: How about Starion?
[SPEAKER_24]: It's in every other K-pop song.
[SPEAKER_24]: Is Starion in it, really?
[SPEAKER_24]: No, Starion's not in it, but there is a Baek Ji Young song called Dash.
[SPEAKER_24]: There is a few songs... I know it was in another game.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um...
[SPEAKER_24]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_24]: I was watching it going, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_24]: I was expecting it, because...
[SPEAKER_23]: Bakwa is such a kind of like, I don't know, it strikes me as a very angsty kind of song.
[SPEAKER_23]: And I was expecting her to be kicking some ass or something, not freaking sitting on the rock being the Little Mermaid.
[SPEAKER_23]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was expecting her little crab friend and fish flounder to pop up and start singing along, you know?
[SPEAKER_25]: But yeah, that's pretty much it, and now I'm here.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, I'm glad you could make time for us.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's very nice.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm actually trying to read up on what's going on with that Pump It Up tourney.
[SPEAKER_23]: I know there was one a couple weeks ago in Dallas, Texas.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was going on.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was one of those qualifiers for the big Pump It Up tournament in Korea.
[SPEAKER_23]: But I haven't heard anything else about future qualifiers since then.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'd be really mad if that's the only qualifying tourney in the United States.
[SPEAKER_23]: That would suck.
[SPEAKER_23]: But there's got to be one that happens in the...
[SPEAKER_23]: in the bay at some point.
[SPEAKER_24]: Dallas is right in the middle for this big country for everyone to go to.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was looking over on Mastiff's site to see if they have anything on it, and they are still plugging a smidget being at the Metreon on February 11th.
[SPEAKER_23]: Which, by the way, I didn't even know the Metreon had Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't think they do.
[SPEAKER_23]: So they must have wheeled in a machine for that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Unless they replaced one of their other machines.
[SPEAKER_23]: Not sure.
[SPEAKER_23]: Now I'm trying to check out Amaro's site and see if they have anything going on.
[SPEAKER_23]: And I don't see anything.
[SPEAKER_23]: But I'll keep looking.
[SPEAKER_23]: Maybe somebody in our chat room knows.
[SPEAKER_23]: If anybody in our chat room knows, feel free to share.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll read it on air and try to get what's going on with that tournament.
[SPEAKER_23]: Because I'm sure a lot of people that aren't just in Texas want to qualify what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_23]: That's the spirit.
[SPEAKER_23]: The goth club was actually quite a bit of fun.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was wearing one of the brightest shirts there.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was wearing my shirt... You could see you from across the room.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was wearing... See, because most people at the goth club wear all black, or sometimes, like, the gothy goths wear white, because, you know, they're going to be different.
[SPEAKER_23]: I wore a bright-ass red shirt, because it was my English.com shirt, and it said, I hate myself and I want to die, because I thought that would be appropriate for the goth club.
[SPEAKER_23]: Team America World Police
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm so ornery.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you were watching South Park.
[SPEAKER_23]: South Park, the movie, yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, I went and saw Crash.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think that was on Monday, which was good.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's just very unapologetic and in-your-face type thing where some of the language is very raw.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's a movie that deals with racism, so if the N-word makes you uncomfortable or any of the other various racial slurs, Loki, you'd have no problem with this movie.
[SPEAKER_23]: If any of those various racial slurs make you uncomfortable.
[SPEAKER_23]: But actually, it was a really good movie.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was really good.
[SPEAKER_23]: Really well done.
[SPEAKER_23]: So I recommend it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Otherwise, not a whole lot going on.
[SPEAKER_23]: I went out to play In the Groove, actually, twice this week.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_23]: I just... Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm loving the USB support thing because...
[SPEAKER_23]: One reason I like the way In The Groove has its workout mode set up is that you don't have to do a special mode to have it count your calories.
[SPEAKER_23]: It actually counts your calories while you're playing a normal game.
[SPEAKER_23]: This kind of bugs me about DDR.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's such a little-ass problem.
[SPEAKER_23]: But I wish that, and I think the only game that ever did this was Disney's Rave.
[SPEAKER_23]: Funny enough, Disney's Rave is the only DDR game that did a lot of things correctly.
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's say Dance Magic...
[SPEAKER_23]: and then it counts your calories no matter what mode you're playing in.
[SPEAKER_23]: The reason why I don't like workout mode in like PlayStation 2 and Xbox versions is that if you play in workout mode, you don't unlock new songs, you don't technically save your grades or your scores or anything, so there's no point in playing in workout mode unless you are strictly there to burn calories.
[SPEAKER_23]: But I like to unlock songs as I play DDR.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know about the rest of you, but that's part of the fun of it, so...
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyway, so In The Groove has the fantastic USB support.
[SPEAKER_23]: Say what you will about the game, but the USB support is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, I've been having fun with that.
[SPEAKER_23]: The game itself, eh.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's just kind of holding me over until there's a new DDR, which, I don't know, I'm not going to hold my breath at this point, but maybe some home versions this fall.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, we know there's home versions, but you know.
[SPEAKER_23]: I want new arcade stuff really bad.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's see what's going on in the Bomani world news-wise.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought we had a... I know two things.
[SPEAKER_23]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Jack and... No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's really a slow... Video gaming altogether is kind of a slow news period right now.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's on vacation after E3.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, it really is.
[SPEAKER_23]: Checking some of the headlines recently over on TED-DDR Freak, which, by the way, replays our show on Friday nights.
[SPEAKER_23]: Those lovely folks over there.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_23]: Um...
[SPEAKER_23]: They actually had like a legal perspective, explain the Konami vs. Rockstar thing.
[SPEAKER_23]: Which, if you were totally confused by the lawsuit, I would hope that if you listened to our program a couple weeks ago when that subject first came up, that we helped explain things for you.
[SPEAKER_23]: But if you're still lost, they kind of had somebody that is in law school or recently finished with law school try to kind of explain it a little more.
[SPEAKER_23]: So it's a fun read, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_23]: Also very interesting that's brought up in there is that Roxor is supposed to have like 20 days to do a response to the lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_23]: So it'll be interesting because sometime this week, even though it's been over 20 days, it might be 20 business days.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know how it works.
[SPEAKER_23]: But somebody, we're thinking this week we might get some more information on exactly what Roxor's comment's going to be to that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Or as I predict, the out-of-court settlement will happen very soon.
[SPEAKER_23]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_23]: And then of course there were some new trailers posted over on IGN.com for DDR Extreme 2 and Ultramix 3, which really don't show anything new as far as I remember from looking at the trailers.
[SPEAKER_23]: There's really nothing new in it.
[SPEAKER_23]: and then a Beatmania trailer is available over on Games Are Fun but it's the same damn thing they showed at E3.
[SPEAKER_23]: Exactly the same thing.
[SPEAKER_23]: Really not a lot new.
[SPEAKER_23]: New news possibly on Xtreme 2 at Comic Con if it's going to be anything like last year.
[SPEAKER_23]: You remember last year at Comic Con in July in San Diego they actually brought a build of Xtreme.
[SPEAKER_23]: Last year it was Xtreme and we found out some new songs that way.
[SPEAKER_23]: So we're hoping that this year they'll do the same thing and we'll find out some new stuff for Xtreme 2.
[SPEAKER_23]: We shall see.
[SPEAKER_23]: It will be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_23]: and then we'll also get into tonight's cage match very soon as well as your calls via the skype line www.orangeloungeradio.com by the way we're looking into this new thing we might do I actually this is the first time I have even said this to the others because Jason brought this to my attention just like two days ago but there's actually this new thing called skype in where we could get a phone number and then if somebody calls the phone number it'll come in on skype
[SPEAKER_23]: So we'll probably be looking into that.
[SPEAKER_23]: So possibly in the very near future, Orange Lounge Radio, for those of you that don't get the Skype thing or don't want it, we will have a phone number that you can call to be on the program.
[SPEAKER_23]: So that will be a very cool addition.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_23]: After this break, we'll be back with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: And this break, music from 2DX Night Style.
[SPEAKER_23]: Started off with a popular song from 2DX Night Style that we haven't played in a while, so I thought you kids would enjoy this.
[SPEAKER_23]: Lionski.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: And now it's time for Erotic Pop Idol, where we will find the next singer for everyone's favorite perverse Bomani band, Erotic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do it all night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do it with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, that was awful.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bloody terrible.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you take vocal lessons?
[SPEAKER_08]: Kill your teacher.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the heat of the night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, God, I think my ears are bleeding.
[SPEAKER_08]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shut the bloody hell up, Paula.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, that was cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you even know why you're here?
[SPEAKER_08]: That was just bloody pathetic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next!
[SPEAKER_01]: Come on, do it with me.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, yes, that's it!
[SPEAKER_16]: We have a winner!
[SPEAKER_12]: A Star is Born, here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: God, that promo's old.
[SPEAKER_23]: I thought with the whole American Idol.
[SPEAKER_23]: That is really old.
[SPEAKER_23]: I thought with all the American Idol stuff, it's not even that good compared to some of our other promos.
[SPEAKER_23]: But I thought with the whole American Idol thing going on this past couple weeks that it was time to play that again.
[SPEAKER_23]: So congratulations to Carrie Underwood, your erotic pop idol.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm sure we'll be in Playboy in a matter of years.
[SPEAKER_23]: Because that's where most of those pop idols are at.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't even followed it since Carrie.
[SPEAKER_23]: Carrie Underwood is useless.
[SPEAKER_23]: I can sing country music, but can you sing pop music?
[SPEAKER_22]: Country?
[SPEAKER_23]: No, pop music.
[SPEAKER_23]: Pop!
[SPEAKER_23]: That's all she could do.
[SPEAKER_23]: Every song she sang was a country song.
[SPEAKER_23]: She's so going to be on The Surreal Life in two years.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't followed it since I bought Clay's album.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did buy Clay's album and I was proud of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because he has a good voice.
[SPEAKER_10]: But he has a really good voice.
[SPEAKER_23]: What happened to Clay Aiken?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, but he's pretty.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's invisible.
[SPEAKER_24]: We don't know what happened to him.
[SPEAKER_23]: You have to understand, what happened was, is there was a rival, you know, between, you know... Ruben and Clay?
[SPEAKER_23]: Biggie, Ruben, and Clay, you see, and, you know, they gunned him down.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, I figured that Ruben just ate Clay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, Ruben was having, I think, to visit a nutritionist because he was saying he was comfortable in his own body, but he was actually starting to develop heart issues and things last I checked.
[SPEAKER_10]: We saw people going to die?
[SPEAKER_10]: He's the people who's going to, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: But there's been a big health concern regarding the fact that he's basically put on 100 pounds since he won.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's too bad.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dang! 101?
[SPEAKER_23]: He needs to start playing some DDR.
[SPEAKER_23]: The bigger I am, the bigger I am on the charts.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know that he's gained a lot of weight since then.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look at the comparison pictures.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's a big boy now.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_23]: Who was that rap artist way back in the day that used to be like... Heavy D?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, Heavy D. Dude, Heavy D was cool.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dude, Biz Markie was on that VH1 Get Fit show.
[SPEAKER_23]: Celebrity Fit Club.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love Biz Markie.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the Snapple Lady.
[SPEAKER_10]: She was on that too.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, she was.
[SPEAKER_23]: As well as Mia Tyler and
[SPEAKER_23]: VH1 shows
[SPEAKER_23]: In the same house with Omarosa from The Apprentice and Janice Dickinson for America's Next Top Model.
[SPEAKER_23]: Which, by the way, if America's Next Top Model is not your guilty pleasure show, it should be.
[SPEAKER_23]: Because that show, what a bunch of bitches.
[SPEAKER_23]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_23]: Nelly was watching this one show yesterday on VH1.
[SPEAKER_23]: I guess it's called Strip Search.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm surprised, Rob, you haven't heard of it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Actually, my roommate watches Strip Search every week.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, I was like, this is weird.
[SPEAKER_23]: He's probably watching it right now.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was overhearing it while I was, you know, uploading my MySpace site, which I'll have to cover later.
[SPEAKER_23]: And, um, so, it's just like, I guess they make these guys do, like, their strip dances in, like, the middle of, like, wherever they're working or whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: And I guess they can go and compete to become, like, the next, um... Thunder from Down Under.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, Thunder from Down Under show.
[SPEAKER_23]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_23]: I've got thunder down under, it's called my fat thighs.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know about you.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_23]: What the hell are we talking about before?
[SPEAKER_23]: If I clap them together, it might make a thunderous noise, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_23]: What the hell are we talking about before we get on this weird tangent?
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, American Idol.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think I made Islander just throw up in his mouth a little bit, though.
[SPEAKER_23]: American Idol.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, since we were talking about American Idol, have you seen the previews for that show, You Think You Can Dance?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, is that the dance show on ABC?
[SPEAKER_23]: That's the dance show that's going to be on Fox.
[SPEAKER_23]: Fuckin' all these reality shows.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's going to be, imagine American Idol except dancing.
[SPEAKER_23]: I should go on that show.
[SPEAKER_23]: Including the people that can't dance.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, you know what show actually I should go on?
[SPEAKER_23]: Beauty and the Geek.
[SPEAKER_23]: I saw that show.
[SPEAKER_23]: You would think this show is a, no seriously, from the previews, I thought this show was going to be a big pile of trash.
[SPEAKER_23]: It actually was a really cute show.
[SPEAKER_23]: I thought.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know about you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_23]: Which one again?
[SPEAKER_23]: It's all these really nerdy guys.
[SPEAKER_23]: I mean, more nerdier than Bill Gates.
[SPEAKER_23]: Like E3 goers.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, like E3 goers.
[SPEAKER_23]: I haven't bathed in a few days.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, but you bathed.
[SPEAKER_23]: They put them against Playboy models.
[SPEAKER_23]: but the thing is that then they go in competitions and they pair off and they have to do competitions so the geeks have to teach the models like how to like spell and then the models have to teach the geeks like how to dance and how to do like social things so actually in the first episode they had a dance competition for the geeks and the models were in what a fifth grade spelling bee or what were they doing?
[SPEAKER_23]: yeah that has to be hilarious it was so great because the one girl was like
[SPEAKER_23]: Tattoo.
[SPEAKER_23]: T-A-T-O-O.
[SPEAKER_23]: She got all excited because she won.
[SPEAKER_23]: And then they're like, no.
[SPEAKER_23]: They're like, no, it's not like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: But it was really, like, the way they do it, they do it without it being demeaning, I think.
[SPEAKER_23]: Like, it's poking fun without being malicious.
[SPEAKER_23]: But a shot like that would be followed up immediately with the girl who actually wins it.
[SPEAKER_23]: She's going, I feel so great right now because I've never won an intelligence competition in my entire life until today.
[SPEAKER_23]: And you're kind of like, that's so cute.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's so sad.
[SPEAKER_23]: Congratulations!
[SPEAKER_23]: You're at the fifth grade reading level there.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: But, yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_23]: Sorry, yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: That was my reality show tangent.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, but seriously, Beauty and the Geek, it's actually really cute.
[SPEAKER_23]: You should watch it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyway, Loki.
[SPEAKER_23]: Loki has some actual Bomani news for you kids.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, it's not Bomani news because... Is it one of Bomani?
[SPEAKER_23]: One of Bomani, I guess.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyways, let me see here.
[SPEAKER_23]: Basically, I decided, you know, it's been a while since we heard something about those other games that are out there, so I figured I'd go take a peek and see what's actually being worked on.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, Neon FM is where all the news is right now.
[SPEAKER_23]: Apparently, they've had a kind of an invitation-only, you know, debuting of their machine and stuff, which looks pretty cool, and considering it's all being done by scratch, it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_23]: And what they've got so far...
[SPEAKER_23]: Um, basically you've got something that looks kind of similar to DDR, not really, um, it's, uh, basically you've got five panels on each side, arranged kind of like, um, a normal Beatmania controller, you know, back in the five key days, um, and- Without the turntable.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, yeah, obviously without the turntable, that'd be a little weird if it had- But that would be fun!
[SPEAKER_23]: Ice skating revolution!
[SPEAKER_23]: Exactly, um, so basically, uh, we've got those, and, um,
[SPEAKER_23]: It's basically, they were showing some of the screenshots and more of the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_23]: And they, I guess, debuted this at Betson.
[SPEAKER_23]: For those who don't know, Betson is an arcade parts supplier.
[SPEAKER_23]: And they're the ones actually building the machines for Neon FM.
[SPEAKER_23]: And they actually debuted it, I guess, at one of their warehouses there.
[SPEAKER_23]: So that was kind of interesting to see.
[SPEAKER_23]: Some more interesting stuff that's happening right now.
[SPEAKER_23]: I guess Thomas Howard, the same Thomas Howard that may be featured in La Seniorita and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: He's actually going to... Captain T!
[SPEAKER_23]: Captain T, yes.
[SPEAKER_23]: He's actually going to Japan right now to film a live performance with the other artist that sings Girls Butts.
[SPEAKER_23]: And they're doing the live video that's going to be in the background for that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_23]: Girls Butts is going to be the reason to play...
[SPEAKER_23]: and honestly, what else?
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, they've got, there's, what else?
[SPEAKER_23]: Damn, where did my clip of girl's butts go?
[SPEAKER_23]: I used to have it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll be able to get you some clips in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm going to download this other thing.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's basically 20-second samples of a bunch of different songs.
[SPEAKER_23]: But we actually have some of the full-length songs, not obviously the same cut that's going to be in the game, but from Poppin' Co., which is one of the artists that does the music in the game.
[SPEAKER_23]: And it's some pretty interesting generic stuff right now.
[SPEAKER_23]: Are we going to play clips from these songs here?
[SPEAKER_23]: I suppose we should just play clips, yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's just play clips, because these are kind of long.
[SPEAKER_23]: So here's a clip of...
[SPEAKER_23]: Are all these songs in the game?
[SPEAKER_23]: Because there's two songs here called Complete Shot.
[SPEAKER_23]: Complete Shot, I think the Greek Fire mix is not in the game, but the other one is.
[SPEAKER_23]: Then let's play a clip here of the Club Blend mix of Complete Shot.
[SPEAKER_23]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_23]: This is going to be a Neon FM.
[SPEAKER_23]: Is this like their version of Max 300, or what is this?
[SPEAKER_23]: No, I think it's probably just, it's more stuff to it.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, it's because it's a long version of the song.
[SPEAKER_22]: Death Metal!
[SPEAKER_22]: Worship Satan!
[SPEAKER_22]: No, it's just like, you know, a techno song.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, that might be a Max 300 song.
[SPEAKER_23]: Not too shabby.
[SPEAKER_22]: Not too shabby.
[SPEAKER_23]: Better sound than in the groove.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, they're different.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's hard to say.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, here's a clip of the other song.
[SPEAKER_23]: This is Electro 8.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Enjoy this one.
[SPEAKER_23]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_23]: May 13th prototype party where they had it at Betzen and you can actually see pictures of the cabinet and actually if you go to NeonFM.com you can check out they have more screenshots or actual shots of the cabinet that you can see the actual buttons and stuff and it looks pretty cool actually so far and they've done a pretty good job with the game I believe I wish they'd just call it Feet Mania because that would be funny because it looks really cool from what they've got so far I mean
[SPEAKER_10]: That just makes me think of Stepping Selection.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I have bad, bad traumatized memories of Stepping Selection.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Boo Jaleco.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm actually excited about Neon FM.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think they're doing a lot of things right.
[SPEAKER_23]: And sadly, I think the reason why they're doing a lot of things right is because they've been able to learn from everything in the groove did wrong.
[SPEAKER_23]: And here's the other thing, too, which is going to be before everyone starts going, well, they're going to get sued!
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, they're actually working with Konami of America throughout the entire process of developing this game.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's what I think is, like, really kind of weird, in a way.
[SPEAKER_23]: Not really, because it's not bad, it's just weird.
[SPEAKER_23]: It makes sense, because they're getting feedback from them, what they think, and also they're making sure that all their bases are covered, like, you know, hey, is there anything we're infringing on that we need to be copyright, you know, paying you for licensing and stuff, and they're taking care of all that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, you should be giving us 50 million dollars.
[SPEAKER_23]: But, honestly, I don't think this is going to be much of a problem compared to, like, say, you know, in the groove, which looked exactly like DDR, this is at least, doesn't resemble DDR.
[SPEAKER_23]: New cabinet, new dance pad, they've kind of, even in the screens, it doesn't look anything like DDR because of the way they've rearranged things, so.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, it's very different.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's why I give the game a lot of credit.
[SPEAKER_23]: I hope it catches on enough so that we see this in a sizable number of arcades.
[SPEAKER_23]: Honestly, I'm glad to see something that's different than, say, DDR Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_23]: Something that'll be a little different.
[SPEAKER_23]: Also, good comment from our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_23]: Ron Chan says, maybe the FM in Neon FM stands for Feet Mania.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: So Neon Feet Mania.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have a genius.
[SPEAKER_23]: And here's another thing also, in case you're interested.
[SPEAKER_23]: There's a link on Neon FM's site here where you can actually download ringtones for your cell phone.
[SPEAKER_23]: One of them being Girls Butts.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_23]: Fun.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dude, I'm so downloading that for my... Does it support Sprint, or do we know?
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, they have a picture here that shows M-Mode, so... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: M-Mode would be, I believe, the AT&T... That's not Sprint.
[SPEAKER_23]: Sprint is...
[SPEAKER_23]: But it's just, they're MIDI files, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_23]: I mean, any phone should be able to download that.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_23]: So that's your... I can't find my clip of Girls Butts.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm downloading, I have a thing downloading right now, which I will actually give to you if you give me my flash drive back.
[SPEAKER_23]: Thank you, I will.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's a 20 second clip of about 13 to 20 different songs, and you'll be able to hear a lot more of what's going to be in there right now.
[SPEAKER_23]: So I guess I'll throw it on here, and we'll play it later.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, we can do that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_23]: So we'll play that later.
[SPEAKER_23]: More Neon FM.
[SPEAKER_23]: Any idea when they're going to release this?
[SPEAKER_23]: Any word of a release date yet?
[SPEAKER_23]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_23]: We need to talk to somebody over on the team over there and try to get somebody on this show to give us details.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: and I also want girl's butts dedicated to me.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was going to say some other stuff non-related.
[SPEAKER_23]: I have a Myspace site, another one now, that I've been plugging in our LiveJournal community.
[SPEAKER_23]: Actually, it's Myspace.com slash LokiFusion.
[SPEAKER_23]: You can actually listen to brand new songs on there as they come out and I don't upload them to my really shitty site.
[SPEAKER_23]: And plus I have a really cool logo that looks just like the DDR Ultramix 3 logo.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's spiffy.
[SPEAKER_23]: Um, so go check it out, befriend me, do all that wonderful stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: Um, also, if you play Step Mania, um, someone actually made a sim file for, um, what was it, uh, The Legend of Trance 2005, so go check that out, Bomani style.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's a few pages back in their sim file section there.
[SPEAKER_23]: And... Which technically would count as another max sim file.
[SPEAKER_23]: Good job, guys.
[SPEAKER_23]: Bastards.
[SPEAKER_23]: The background art, though, kind of sucks, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then, other than that, really, not too much else going on.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think I found it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob found girl's butts.
[SPEAKER_22]: On his computer.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is it, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think this is it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_17]: Wanna know what I did today?
[SPEAKER_17]: I was looking at girl's butts.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hanging out in the subway.
[SPEAKER_17]: Looking at girl's butts.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is right here the song of the game.
... ...
[SPEAKER_23]: Now how can you not be excited about Neon Feet Mania after hearing that?
[SPEAKER_23]: Now that's not the same mix though, because that doesn't sound like Thomas Howard.
[SPEAKER_23]: That sounds like DJ Potato singing that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Am I wrong?
[SPEAKER_23]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think that's DJ Potato actually singing that.
[SPEAKER_23]: It might be DJ Potato singing.
[SPEAKER_23]: But the new one, I mean, I've got to say that they're doing quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_23]: I mean, they're putting quite a lot of polish in this game.
[SPEAKER_23]: I mean, getting a live performance of Thomas Howard in Japan with the other artists.
[SPEAKER_23]: And apparently there's a female artist that does vocals on that song as well.
[SPEAKER_23]: I want, like, really, like, 80s porn, like, close-up shots of her butt in, like, tight clothing and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: It has to be porn style.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even DarkSakura agrees with me.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_10]: Picture this.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's got to be all pimped out.
[SPEAKER_23]: This one yells at me every time.
[SPEAKER_23]: I even mention they should objectify women in one form or another, and she agrees with me on this one.
[SPEAKER_10]: This song has to have it, and the guy has to be all pimped out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then the girl has to turn around and shoot him.
[SPEAKER_23]: I've got your video right here.
[SPEAKER_23]: You need to have a really quick close-up shot of a door opening.
[SPEAKER_23]: and Thomas Howard singing the song is the pizza guy.
[SPEAKER_22]: That would be fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: I still think the girl needs to go around and shoot.
[SPEAKER_23]: They should parody a bunch of different porno videos.
[SPEAKER_10]: The pimp should be a girl.
[SPEAKER_23]: Just when I thought it was going to be a train wreck of a show.
[SPEAKER_23]: I found girl's butts.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm going to be happy.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're going to have the Skype line open very soon.
[SPEAKER_23]: www.orangeloungeradio.com Click on... Interact with us for more information on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_23]: I almost said click on girl's butts, but I... We don't have that on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_23]: We need a girl's butts button.
[SPEAKER_23]: That should be the marketing for the game.
[SPEAKER_23]: They should have that printed on bumper stickers.
[SPEAKER_23]: It should just be Neon FM and really tiny print in the corner.
[SPEAKER_23]: Neon FM featuring Girls Butts with a Z. That song.
[SPEAKER_23]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_23]: That song needs to go on the radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: Maybe we should help them out.
[SPEAKER_23]: We've got some artistic people on staff here.
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's make some Neon FM promo banners.
[SPEAKER_23]: And we'll do that.
[SPEAKER_23]: A little Neon FM featuring Girls Butts.
[SPEAKER_23]: Really huge.
[SPEAKER_23]: And then have the 80s porn butt.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think we should do that.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll do it as a favor to Neon FM, and then maybe some of them will come on the show and talk about their game.
[SPEAKER_23]: I like this idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: It has merit.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think we'll go to a quick break.
[SPEAKER_23]: When we come back, we are going to take your calls over on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_23]: www.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_23]: That might not be a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_23]: I have a feeling that if we do that, we will be taking an inside joke or a joke that was five minutes ago and just be ramming it into the ground.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, in this break, I thought maybe what we could do is actually play some In The Groove music this break, because we've kind of been mean to them this week.
[SPEAKER_23]: Has In The Groove come out yet?
[SPEAKER_23]: Because apparently, and this is interesting, apparently, someone I know at work, they're like, you know, I'm looking for a DDR game that has some Britney Spears songs in it, because my daughter, daughter's a 10-year-old, okay, now she's into the Britney Spears, Christina Aguilera crap,
[SPEAKER_23]: Um, they're looking for a song that had some of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: So I'm loaning her DDR Extreme Max 2.
[SPEAKER_23]: In return, she's loaning me In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_00]: What?
[SPEAKER_23]: For the home console.
[SPEAKER_23]: Apparently she already has it.
[SPEAKER_23]: She says that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_23]: She says it looks exactly like DDR, except it does, you know, I showed her pictures of In The Groove and she's like, I'm almost positive that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_23]: If it is, that's very odd, because I haven't heard of it coming out yet, and it would be all over if it had come out.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_23]: Let me check, let me check.
[SPEAKER_23]: In fact, let me just make sure I haven't missed something, okay?
[SPEAKER_23]: ITGFreak.com, because this site would have it, right?
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_23]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_23]: No news on the home version coming out.
[SPEAKER_23]: Your co-worker's insane or has gotten some huge break somehow.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know what she has.
[SPEAKER_23]: I bet you anything it's MC Groove's dance craze.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's probably what you're going to get in return.
[SPEAKER_23]: Either way, we'll have a review of whatever the hell it is that she has.
[SPEAKER_23]: Some subpar game.
[SPEAKER_23]: What am I...
[SPEAKER_23]: What am I looking for in this room?
[SPEAKER_10]: The girl's butt thing just totally inspired me to open a restaurant.
[SPEAKER_23]: Called what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you know, this objectifying women thing is pretty stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that men should be objectified.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm opening a restaurant called Heckers.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey, there's no problem with that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Or Bananas.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was in a commercial a while ago, I think.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's a chicken restaurant like Hooters, so it's going to be Heckers.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right.
[SPEAKER_23]: I thought about a cool pool hall called Great Wreck.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, Jailbait
[SPEAKER_23]: All right.
[SPEAKER_23]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think we're going to go to that break now.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: And we're going to start this break off.
[SPEAKER_23]: I said we'd do some in the groove music.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're going to start it off with a little trancy song called Walking on Fire because we haven't played this one yet on the show and it's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_23]: So enjoy this and we'll be back with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: The whisper in the breakdown Is the part of everything behind me Unexplained nature of the heaven Crushing every feeling that sends me
[SPEAKER_13]: Touch me, I wanna know if you know that I need you And you need me too Ah yeah, ah yeah
I want you to touch me Hold me
[SPEAKER_13]: I want you to touch me I want you to touch me I am a robot, a fucking robot Walking on the spaceship every night and day
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm Romeo, I'm Juliet
Thank you for watching!
The first time that I walked in my life, I felt a strange attraction.
Felt a strange
Gaming Radio, so uncensored that even Tom Brokaw could get a job with us.
Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: Some music there from Integroove.
[SPEAKER_23]: Coming to a console near you eventually.
[SPEAKER_23]: Romeo and Juliet.
[SPEAKER_23]: Before that, Touch Me.
[SPEAKER_23]: Bubble Dancer!
[SPEAKER_23]: Walking on fire starting that set off.
[SPEAKER_23]: A little diverse stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_23]: I like Bubble Dancer because it sounds like Aqua, but like a real cheap Aqua knockoff.
[SPEAKER_23]: Which makes it even worse, but at the same time, the only reason you liked Aqua is because it was one of those, it's so bad, it's good.
[SPEAKER_23]: So when it gets badder, it gets gooder.
[SPEAKER_23]: Nevermind.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're going to take your calls right now on the Skype line, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_23]: Click on Interact With Us and you can call into the show.
[SPEAKER_23]: Although I don't know if we have a lot of people that want to talk to us tonight because we don't have a lot of folks that are actually logged into Skype right now.
[SPEAKER_23]: So we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, on Fridays over at DDR Freak, if you want.
[SPEAKER_23]: And you know, if no one calls us, we have to get into Paris Hilton chat.
[SPEAKER_23]: And I don't think you want that tonight.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_23]: Even I'm sick of Paris Hilton chat.
[SPEAKER_23]: Nicole Ritchie chat, though.
[SPEAKER_23]: I've got a whole lot I could say about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: She sucks.
[SPEAKER_23]: She's Paris Hilton's partner.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, we're getting... Oh, on that stupid show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I watched the sausage episode.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not anymore.
[SPEAKER_23]: Saved by the call.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey, Scott.
[SPEAKER_23]: Siggy here.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hello, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_23]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_23]: What's on your mind, sir?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, last Friday I was able to attend the World Series of Poker.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, yes, I remember you talking about that on last week's show, and you were going to win us millions of dollars, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, I lost on the second level.
[SPEAKER_23]: Damn it!
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, at least you got to the second level.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is going to be one of my FUs of the week tonight.
[SPEAKER_23]: How bad did you lose?
[SPEAKER_23]: How exactly, I mean, I don't know how tournament poker works, but I guess, how many people do you play against at a time in tournament poker?
[SPEAKER_03]: There were 240 tables, and there were nine players, and I just multiplied it by nine.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_23]: You won out of nine people in the first round, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I already won over two tables.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, eh.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: But unfortunately, I lost to a professional poker player.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, well, that always kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_23]: So you got up there a little bit then.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's still pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_23]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_23]: Maybe next year.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, maybe next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: There goes my $1,000 buy-in.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh my god, it was $1,000 to buy in?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh my god, you didn't get any of it back.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, no.
$1,000?
[SPEAKER_03]: For a freaking poker?
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the thing, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: The top prize is $725,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there's going to be another No Limit tournament this Friday, which is going to be a $2,000 buy-in, and it's going to be twice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Twice than that for the top prize.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's pretty hardcore.
[SPEAKER_23]: Can you imagine a DDR tournament with $1,000 buy-ins?
[SPEAKER_23]: At least you could have a DDR tournament that has more than that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's like just under half of my monthly salary.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, what do you expect?
[SPEAKER_23]: It's Vegas, right?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right.
[SPEAKER_23]: What do you have to say to the people that are criticizing you for putting up $1,000 of your money?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's just, you know, I've already planned this for months now.
[SPEAKER_23]: Everybody has their thing, right?
[SPEAKER_23]: You're allowed to spend money on poker.
[SPEAKER_23]: Some people invest their money in their video game collections or their anime collections, so you have the right to spend your money on a poker tournament if you want, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'm doing it just for the fun of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to experience what poker players do.
[SPEAKER_23]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_23]: What's a really good poker game for the... I'm sorry, finish your thought?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, you finish it up.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: What's a really good poker game for, like, home, consoles, video games?
[SPEAKER_23]: Because there's a whole lot of them out there.
[SPEAKER_23]: What do you think is a really good poker game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I say you should start with, you know, like, a low-limit Hold'em or, you know, low-limit Omaha.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's more complicated.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm talking about, like, a video game out there.
[SPEAKER_23]: Because the E3, it looked like there were a lot of poker video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: The World Poker Championship for the PlayStation 2 and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_23]: I hear that one's really good.
[SPEAKER_23]: What's the one that, does anybody remember there was one that Iguana Girl beat some guy at?
[SPEAKER_23]: What was the game they were playing?
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't remember his name.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me ask her real quick.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chatting with her right now.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know what it comes down to?
[SPEAKER_23]: You need to play more strip poker games.
[SPEAKER_23]: Why?
[SPEAKER_23]: Because they make you fucking work to get those women naked.
[SPEAKER_23]: And goddammit, it's not like any ordinary strip poker game, you know,
[SPEAKER_23]: Phil Hellmuth, Howard Lederer, Greg Raymer
[SPEAKER_03]: ummmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
[SPEAKER_03]: I was tired.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, before I headed to Rio, I went to Circus Circus for some 2GX Red action.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just to calm my nerves down.
[SPEAKER_23]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, let's go ahead and take another call.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hey, what's up, Mr. One and Only Ranma?
[SPEAKER_23]: Hello, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_23]: How are you, buddy?
[SPEAKER_25]: Hi, Uke-chan.
[SPEAKER_23]: Warning, cute factor approaching.
[SPEAKER_23]: What's on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_25]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_25]: I just had a real twisted weekend.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was forced to quit my job.
[SPEAKER_23]: You were forced to quit your job?
[SPEAKER_23]: Did somebody catch you in the storeroom with the lady, you know, something like that going on, or what?
[SPEAKER_25]: No, I actually caught somebody else violating corporate policy.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, how's that work?
[SPEAKER_23]: You've got to explain this one to me.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, on Geek Squad, you've got to sell services.
[SPEAKER_25]: One of the technicians was selling services, but he was pocketing the money.
[SPEAKER_23]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_23]: So how does that mean you lose your job?
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm still trying... More or less, I found that they were like...
[SPEAKER_25]: Tracking me and following me around.
[SPEAKER_25]: It seems that before I went to Anamaze, I told my general manager what was going on.
[SPEAKER_25]: Got a customer to make a statement about what happened.
[SPEAKER_25]: I made my statement.
[SPEAKER_25]: Go away.
[SPEAKER_25]: I come back.
[SPEAKER_25]: I come to find out that one of the managers wants to talk to me.
[SPEAKER_25]: It seems that I'm being accused of losing money in the department and I have an issue with not coming to work.
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkSakura is a great... She can give you some good advice on where to go if you want to kick some butt.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, I plan on it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_23]: Keep us posted on how that goes.
[SPEAKER_23]: How's your gaming week been?
[SPEAKER_25]: Pretty good, pretty good.
[SPEAKER_25]: I got a controller, so now I've been playing PSO a little bit more than I should be.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, Blue Burst?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_23]: Now, DarkSakura, you had a fun time in Blue Burst tonight, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, you need to play with me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm actually going to be starting an Orange Lounge radio team.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you playing tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, I can.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, only listeners are allowed to come into this room.
[SPEAKER_10]: I always play on Hyperion 7, and the room is Murdoch is question mark, and the password is God, with a capital G. Since I have the memory retention of a goldfish, I will be asking this a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll try and post a reminder in the chat room towards the end of the show on PSO.
[SPEAKER_23]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, have fun with that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anything else you want to share with us?
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, and remember I called a few weeks back and I told you about the slash pizza icon I saw at AMA Boston?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_25]: I sent DarkSakura the picture so you could take a look at it.
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkSakura, do you have those pictures?
[SPEAKER_23]: You emailed those, right?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I can hop onto my email momentarily.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll take a look at them during the cage match.
[SPEAKER_23]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_23]: Thank you for giving us a call, and we'll talk to you next time, all righty?
[SPEAKER_23]: You got it.
[SPEAKER_23]: And good luck with that.
[SPEAKER_23]: East Coast is waiting for you, Sky.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm going to be there with bells on.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you need me to look up anything legal for you to help out, let me know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll be asking.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_23]: Thanks a lot.
[SPEAKER_23]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_23]: Ranma calling in.
[SPEAKER_23]: A little bit of work drama going on.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, what we're going to do now is we're going to go ahead and take a quick break away from the Skype line because we're actually going to go into tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_23]: So what you have to do is if you want to call into the show, we will open it up.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, there's one more call coming up.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll make this a quick one.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm going to be nice.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm in a nice mood today.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll take one more call.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: This is Reznor.
[SPEAKER_23]: Like Trant Reznor?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I actually got the nickname from a mistake on somebody's part.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_23]: I bet you get that a lot, though, don't you?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: Everybody keeps saying, is it like the game?
[SPEAKER_23]: I guess I'm the only ass out there that wants to do, alright, whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, then I follow up with, yeah, I've got the vibration paddle with me in my pocket, too.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, because of Rez, okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: It took me a minute, it took me a minute, and then I'm like, then when he starts talking about vibrating controller, I'm like, oh shit, yeah, I know that one.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm an expert on vibrating games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: What's on your mind, Reznor?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, drinking, games, stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: You were talking about Neon FM.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually know the guy, DJ Potato, one of the creators of it, I know him really well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Get him on my show.
[SPEAKER_00]: I should.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's actually staffing for us at MAGFest.
[SPEAKER_23]: What's MAGFest?
[SPEAKER_00]: MAGFest is a non-E3 commercial video game convention in Virginia.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_23]: When's that happening?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's actually coming up.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're skipping this year.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to be in January.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's the weekend right before OhioCon, I think.
[SPEAKER_23]: So do you get distributors to come out there and show off the games and everything?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, this will actually be our fourth year that we've been doing the convention.
[SPEAKER_00]: First year was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_00]: We had an anime premiere of Ys.
[SPEAKER_00]: We had the first TurboGrafx-16 ever made on display.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_00]: It actually had serial number 00001.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want mine, please.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_23]: I love the PC Engine.
[SPEAKER_23]: I thought seeing the last Dreamcast ever made was pretty hot, but the first TurboGrafx, that's pretty hot as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, they had it in a little glass case and everything.
[SPEAKER_00]: The con chairman said, yeah, you'll find me curled up in a ditch in Mexico with this.
[SPEAKER_23]: It kind of sounds like what you've got going on is similar to Classic Gaming Expo.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kind of, yeah, but more emphasis put on the fandom, kind of like anime conventions are.
[SPEAKER_00]: This one's for video games only.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh god, do you have cosplayers?
[SPEAKER_00]: Last convention we had three, and they got really pissy because we had to cosplay at two in the morning.
[SPEAKER_00]: There was a really good Cosmos, but obviously for an anime convention...
[SPEAKER_00]: Her mentality was definitely not the right one for this convention.
[SPEAKER_23]: You can't have a convention, you can't have a geek convention happen without some rejected Ricky Lake guest doing Sailor Moon cosplay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thankfully, we didn't have any Sailor Moons or anything.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was all video game characters.
[SPEAKER_00]: We had, like, a Cid from Final Fantasy IV, and that was really cool when Tenebra Project played live.
[SPEAKER_00]: He almost climbed up on stage when they were doing Final Fantasy IV boss.
[SPEAKER_00]: For those that don't know, Jenova Project is the band that was before Mini Bosses.
[SPEAKER_00]: We actually had them play live, too.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wow, sounds like you guys have a good time out there.
[SPEAKER_23]: I wish we were on the East Coast so we could check it out.
[SPEAKER_23]: But maybe in January we'll have money in the travel budget.
[SPEAKER_23]: So keep looking at the change that falls on the sofa because that's the travel budget.
[SPEAKER_00]: We wouldn't be the only ones that would be coming from California.
[SPEAKER_00]: We had about 50 people come from California.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's nice.
[SPEAKER_24]: Good deal.
[SPEAKER_24]: Dude, if I was to go there, I would cosplay as King Hippo from Mike Tyson's Punk Out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, one of the most underrated 8-bit characters.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, Eggplant Wizard.
[SPEAKER_00]: We need Eggplant Wizard cosplay.
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually want to cosplay as one of the guys from Russian Attack.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, Akarnov, dude.
[SPEAKER_21]: Are you a bad enough dude to save the president?
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's get a cheeseburger.
[SPEAKER_10]: We need a bunch of people to do Super Dodgeball cosplay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I've seen people do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or the Kunio-kun hot-blooded downtown story, also known as River City Ransom.
[SPEAKER_00]: In EchoCon, there was actually a group of five people that cosplayed as the frat guys from RCR.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_23]: Did they say barf when they hit the floor and everything?
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, they did.
[SPEAKER_00]: They did.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was really cool.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: They only did it because X-Strike Studios was showing RCR at River City Rumble at NekoCon, which is really cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_24]: Actually, I have one more idea, and that's to dress up as Leisure Suit Larry, the original OG.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, give Spanish Fly to the secretary.
[SPEAKER_23]: So how much floor space does this con take up?
[SPEAKER_00]: We take up the entire hotel.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, that's nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: That sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: 24-hour game room.
[SPEAKER_00]: Land room is actually going to be split into four rooms because last year I actually got it up to about 68 people.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, you know, if our podcast takes off and we're able to sell out to the man and we get a travel budget, we are so there.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Travel budget.
[SPEAKER_00]: Rock on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, right now it's about five cents.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you can get down the block, basically.
[SPEAKER_23]: Actually, my other idea is to establish a swear jar, because that shit would fill up fast.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'd be dropping 20s every night.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'd be going to Hawaii every month.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anything else you want to share with us?
[SPEAKER_00]: Probably just pimping for X-Strike.
[SPEAKER_00]: X-Strike Studios is going to be at AMA coming up in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're going to be premiering Silent Horror, a video game movie that doesn't suck based on Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wait a minute, so it's like an actual movie that's going to be released in the studios?
[SPEAKER_23]: I kind of saw this already.
[SPEAKER_23]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_23]: The trailer for it.
[SPEAKER_00]: The trailer actually does no justice.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, because the trailer kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_00]: The trailer does suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, wow, this makes Uevo look good.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's actually like, it's both funny as hell, because they make fun of every, like,
[SPEAKER_00]: Any movie that has a line saying, it's like,
[SPEAKER_00]: What are you doing with all that crap?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you never know when you're going to need an empty lighter fluid can to fill up a lighter or a freakishly large statue to depress the switch.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's good to have a well-stocked inventory.
[SPEAKER_23]: Do they have a distributor for it, or are they still trying to find something?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's actually, they're sending it off to the DVD pressers.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're going with a different DVD...
[SPEAKER_00]: Press and Company that they did for River City Rumble.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it should be for sale at AMA.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's actually going to kind of premiere at AMA.
[SPEAKER_21]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Two commentaries, an outtake track, deleted scenes, director's commentary.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a fully loaded DVD.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, good luck to those guys.
[SPEAKER_23]: I love B-movies with inside jokes, so that sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_23]: So it's a bunch of gamer nerds.
[SPEAKER_00]: Make sure to watch the Transformer reference.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's a bunch of gamer nerds that did this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, that'll be great.
[SPEAKER_00]: It'll be great.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's x-strikestudios.com.
[SPEAKER_23]: x-strikestudios.com.
[SPEAKER_23]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, thank you for calling us, and I hope you have a good one.
[SPEAKER_23]: Have fun at your con.
[SPEAKER_00]: I need more beer.
[SPEAKER_23]: Seven months.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey, have another bud for us, all right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, it's Killian's tonight.
[SPEAKER_23]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_23]: Actually, have a Guinness.
[SPEAKER_23]: Have a Guinness for us, because the Guinness isn't really there.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, bye.
[SPEAKER_23]: Later.
[SPEAKER_23]: Getting his name from the Rez Trans Vibrator.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: That tiramisu's got, what is it, the liqueur in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It has booze, I must have some.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, we're going to get some tiramisu as we get into Cage Match here because I don't really like tiramisu usually though, but is it Olive Garden tiramisu?
[SPEAKER_23]: No, it's tiramisu from Rayleigh's.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will have a small corner because I've eaten mostly meat all day.
[SPEAKER_23]: I will give it a try.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've eaten mostly meat today.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, if I take this piece home and spread it out over the week, I can get away with it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, let's get into tonight's cage match, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_23]: Last week in the Orange Lounge cage match, the Gorillas were entered in, and they won in a narrow victory with their song, Dare, which is kind of a dance-y song, which you don't hear from Gorillas very often, but... Sounds like a happy Monday song.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's very happy, but Mondays aren't happy, so I don't know what that's all about.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyway, the way the cage match works, you must be in our chat room, www.orangeloungeradio.com We will play three songs for you, last week's winner, just a clip, because you already heard it last week, and two new songs in their entirety, and the winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio's video game music program, which plays 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, on this station when we aren't live!
[SPEAKER_23]: And what is the criteria for these songs to be in the cage match?
[SPEAKER_23]: They have to kick ass.
[SPEAKER_23]: We just have to like them.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's the only criteria.
[SPEAKER_23]: They don't have to be related to games at all.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's just cool stuff we think you should hear.
[SPEAKER_23]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_23]: A clip of last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_23]: Song number one.
[SPEAKER_23]: Is it worthy of a two-week victory?
[SPEAKER_23]: You be the judge.
[SPEAKER_23]: Gorillas dare.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, that was a clip of song number one, Dare, by the Gorillaz.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, let's get into a new song, which we'll play in its entirety.
[SPEAKER_23]: This one's six minutes.
[SPEAKER_23]: This better be good, Loki.
[SPEAKER_23]: What do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, it's not a Girls remix, sorry.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_23]: But see, now Girls Butts is okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: Girls by Prodigy, not okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, this is something I didn't really have much to bring this week, so I was going through some of my old CDs that have been ripping into my hard drive, and I found one on the Verse 1 and 2, which hit for me.
[SPEAKER_23]: And this is a remix, and I don't even remember the title of it, because it's really strange.
[SPEAKER_23]: And it's a remix of basically TAC stuff, and you've got... It's mainly DXY, but there's Thruanholic stuff in there as well.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think I've heard this before.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's Drexy, D-R-E-X-I-Y, I'm calling it Drexy.
[SPEAKER_23]: Which sounds like an eating disorder to me, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's pretty cool, I mean, I was trying to find a short song...
[SPEAKER_23]: Is the artist's name really VA on this?
[SPEAKER_23]: No, that's just various artists because it's on Diverse Systems.
[SPEAKER_23]: I can look it up, but I mean, it'd take me a sec.
[SPEAKER_23]: But, yeah, basically, I mean, it should be enjoyable.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll just say it's by Diverse Systems.
[SPEAKER_23]: So this is Diverse Systems.
[SPEAKER_23]: If you like Taku, you should like this.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_23]: Song number two in tonight's cage match, Drexy.
[SPEAKER_23]: Enjoy.
Thanks for watching!
Thanks For Watching
[SPEAKER_23]: Right, that was song number two tonight, Direxy.
[SPEAKER_23]: Is that Direxy good or Direxy bad?
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's find out.
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: I liked lots of parts of it, and you know me, I love Taku, but there were parts that just sort of kind of dragged on like that part at the end.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seven.
[SPEAKER_10]: Solid, but kind of drug a bit.
[SPEAKER_23]: Uh, my vote.
[SPEAKER_23]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: I give it a six for the number of minutes.
[SPEAKER_23]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_23]: Next time I'm picking a ten minute song.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, but I give the tiramisu a ten, by the way, because it tasted like liquor, and that makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_23]: I thought it was a good song, just because it reminded me a lot of the Legend of Attack song they did a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_23]: But, um, which I gotta do something else, because originally that Legend of Attack song was supposed to be every single Attack song in one mix.
[SPEAKER_23]: But, uh, I stopped before I finished.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyway, um, no, I give it, like, an 8, because it's good.
[SPEAKER_23]: Islander.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'd probably give it about a 6-2, but then, because my reasoning is, it was, it...
[SPEAKER_24]: I too feel this is a little too long.
[SPEAKER_24]: We've done without a few things.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's go on to song number three.
[SPEAKER_23]: Song number three, somebody sent me the music video for this during the week, and it reminded me about how funny this song is.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, and I love the video, it's so funny.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, um, and it's actually a pretty decent dance song.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, I chose this song, it's kind of like, I wouldn't say it's a remake of an 80s classic, but it invokes an 80s classic.
[SPEAKER_23]: So this is Eric Pryde's, and the song is called Call On Me.
[SPEAKER_23]: Enjoy!
[SPEAKER_23]: Song number three, Eric Pryde's Call On Me.
[SPEAKER_23]: Will you guys be calling that song back, or will you conveniently lose its number?
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love the original, but that one was also really repetitive.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would be good for DDR, I think, if it were cut down to a minute and a half, but it was just too repetitive.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's a six and a half.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's a club song, supposed to be repetitive.
[SPEAKER_23]: Actually, for me, it has the same elements of a Daft Punk song, where it's simple, it can be repetitive, but it's still catchy, and it doesn't get really annoying.
[SPEAKER_23]: And that's what's cool about Daft Punk, and I think there may be even some Fatboy Slim songs like that and stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: But it's just, it's one of those songs that lends itself to a club scene very well, so it gets a 9.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_23]: Sometimes I wish we were a TV show, because honestly, that song isn't done justice without the video.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, isn't the video is all these, it's women working out and like they're wearing like Jane Fonda style attire.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's like full on 80s.
[SPEAKER_23]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_23]: Consistent tits and ass shots consistently through the video.
[SPEAKER_23]: I remember the video for this, and that was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_23]: And then there's just some random guy there, too, that's just working out.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: I laughed.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, I'm gay, and I thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_23]: But maybe it's the whole boobies thing.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know, because they say gay men are infatuated with boobies.
[SPEAKER_23]: Islander, who is not a gay man, but is still infatuated with boobies.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_24]: But no, I sort of agree there with Loki's comments, how it's...
[SPEAKER_24]: It does lend itself to the club scene.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's in that mold of Daft Punk and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_24]: And if you don't mind hearing that type of music, I for one don't, I would bump that in my car.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, I'd give that probably an 8.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, and eight for 80s.
[SPEAKER_23]: How's that?
[SPEAKER_23]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, so pretty diverse selection here tonight in the cage match.
[SPEAKER_23]: Remember, our votes don't count for shit.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's all up to you guys in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_23]: So here it is, the three songs you can vote for tonight, starting it off with song number one, last week's winner, going for win number two, Gorilla's Dare.
[SPEAKER_23]: And song number two you can vote for tonight, Diverse System with Direxy.
[SPEAKER_23]: And song number three you can vote for tonight, Eric Pride's Call On Me.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, place vote now.
[SPEAKER_23]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_23]: And if you don't know how to do that, hold on.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'll tell you guys in our chat room how to momentarily.
[SPEAKER_23]: You guys have about three minutes.
[SPEAKER_23]: Loki, this is the part of the show where I let you explain what's going on in the sim world.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, I explained a little bit of what's going on in the sim world.
[SPEAKER_23]: Like, for example, there's a sim file for my song, Legend of Trance 2005, which you can find on Bamayu's cell.
[SPEAKER_23]: There's a few other things that happened as far as releases go.
[SPEAKER_23]: There was, what was it, DDRXX Mix, and I know that's a,
[SPEAKER_23]: Weird name, but it's Japanese, so what can we say?
[SPEAKER_23]: They released version 2.5, which has some more songs in it.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's actually a good 80 meg download, so you can go check that out as well.
[SPEAKER_23]: Then there's also... There's another one.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's actually kind of an older one that came out around the time Food Mix 1 came out.
[SPEAKER_23]: And it's... Oh, what's it called?
[SPEAKER_23]: It's...
[SPEAKER_23]: Party Night, Dance Dance Revolution, I guess Party Night Edition or something like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: They're calling it DDR Party Night Mix Appendix Series Number 1.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's kind of a tongue twister, but basically what that is, is a good download for you that's about, oh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's pretty big.
[SPEAKER_23]: 216 megs.
[SPEAKER_23]: So that's quite the download there.
[SPEAKER_23]: So go check that out.
[SPEAKER_23]: Now, granted, the first Party Night mix was not very good.
[SPEAKER_23]: DDR-D3 Mix 2.5
[SPEAKER_23]: Manhole Manhole
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, that's right, we do have the maturity level of preschool.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyways, yeah, that's pretty much what's going on in the sim scene right now, so check those out, and watch BomaniStyle's sim file database, because every now and then there will be a good one.
[SPEAKER_23]: But in the meantime, you'll have to deal with ParanoiaTwist, Omega, and MaxEvo.
[SPEAKER_23]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_23]: Goody, goody.
[SPEAKER_23]: Just a reminder, you boys and girls out there, we have a podcast where we talk about other games.
[SPEAKER_23]: We talk about games that don't suck and the news you really want to know about.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's available on our website, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_23]: Just click on the Orange Lounge Radio to Go edition, which is over on the left-hand side, and you can download that.
[SPEAKER_23]: And actually, that show's been very successful for us, so we're pretty happy about that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Also, if you have a chance, give us a vote over on Podcast Alley because, you know, we like attention.
[SPEAKER_23]: Even though that site is turning into one big popularity contest, hey, you know... We like popularity.
[SPEAKER_23]: We like being popular.
[SPEAKER_23]: Doesn't everyone?
[SPEAKER_23]: So, give us a vote over there.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'll paste a link in the chat room for you guys if you want to do that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, I completely forgot to mention earlier during my, you know, week stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: There was actually something... I mean, it's not, like, huge, but it was rather significant to happen this week.
[SPEAKER_23]: Um...
[SPEAKER_23]: Now, I may have made fun of this song earlier this week, or not earlier this week, but when we were talking about Karaoke Revolution 4, but Patrick Swayze came to my work.
[SPEAKER_23]: How many people can say that?
[SPEAKER_23]: Patrick Swayze came to my work as well as his wife.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was on Channel 3 News local here in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_23]: And he was basically promoting his new movie that's going to be coming out called Last Dance, which is about his, I guess, you know, he started off classically trained as ballet.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was a Donna Summer song.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyways, The Last Dance, it's going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_23]: Last Dance.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyways, so yeah, I got an autograph and it's the same from his wife who actually directed and wrote the movie.
[SPEAKER_23]: And he actually flew in on his plane into the Caron Park Airport nearby here.
[SPEAKER_23]: So he's a pilot and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, I realize they did a sequel to Dirty Dancing, but overlooking that piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_23]: They should do a new sequel to Dirty Dancing with Patrick Swayze and Jennifer Grey.
[SPEAKER_10]: They need to give her back her old nose.
[SPEAKER_23]: He's doing a movie right now, because this whole movie is supposed to be about going inside the mind of a dancer, what they're experiencing, so it's kind of a surreal movie in a sense.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dirty Dancing Sequel with the DDR Freak Movie
[SPEAKER_23]: Because you know how that always comes up.
[SPEAKER_23]: OMG to DDR Freak Movie.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's what it could be.
[SPEAKER_23]: It could be Patrick Swayze and Jennifer Grey reunited to win to dinner competition.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_23]: And then they can get to the competition.
[SPEAKER_23]: And now for the final challenge where you will have to face...
[SPEAKER_23]: Dark, Patrick Swayze.
[SPEAKER_09]: DOTH Swayze!
[SPEAKER_22]: Use the force.
[SPEAKER_01]: Use the bar, Luke.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't do this!
[SPEAKER_23]: Direxy
[SPEAKER_23]: All six minutes of it.
[SPEAKER_23]: And song number two that tied in tonight's cage match was... Gorillas with Dare.
[SPEAKER_23]: Now, the rules of a tie say that the host who put in the song that did not end up in the tie gets to break the tie.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's me!
[SPEAKER_23]: So I get to break the tie tonight because you bastards didn't vote for call on me.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, who loves me more?
[SPEAKER_10]: I buy you food sometimes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I brought you cake.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's true, you did bring me tiramisu.
[SPEAKER_10]: I brought you liquor.
[SPEAKER_23]: Uh, that's true, but, um, you know, Direxy just went on for way too long, so I have to give it to Dare tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_23]: But Dare's gone on for two weeks already.
[SPEAKER_23]: Too late, I've made up my mind.
[SPEAKER_10]: It has the mighty power of Sean Ryder and Damon.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, we got a weird buzzy sound.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, um, so there it is.
[SPEAKER_23]: Win number two for Dare, so we'll be back next week to see if it can go through.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dare to stay off drugs.
[SPEAKER_23]: Didn't they have a report?
[SPEAKER_10]: There are a lot of people singing that song to be saying that about.
[SPEAKER_23]: You want to know what a geek I was in elementary school.
[SPEAKER_23]: Think back to what year would this have been, like 89?
[SPEAKER_23]: We had the D.A.R.E.
[SPEAKER_23]: program in schools.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know if this is a nationwide thing or just California, but D.A.R.E.
[SPEAKER_23]: was the Drug Abuse Resistance Education.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think that's what it stood for.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was an anti-drug program.
[SPEAKER_23]: But they say that it was an utter failure because what it ended up doing is it actually taught kids about all the drugs that was out there.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's the ones that need to be funny.
[SPEAKER_23]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, methamphetamine.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, exactly.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think it's a nationwide thing.
[SPEAKER_24]: One of my ex-fianc in Colorado, she was a DARE graduate twice.
[SPEAKER_24]: Still ended up smoking, shooting up anything she can get her hands on.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to go get me some drugs now.
[SPEAKER_23]: Everybody in the chat room knows what I'm talking about, so they're all saying yes is nationwide, so cool.
[SPEAKER_23]: For our international audience, sorry, you're just screwed.
[SPEAKER_23]: Here's the thing, I don't know why I remember this, but I remember they had a little workbook that had all these exercises on it.
[SPEAKER_23]: You're supposed to identify different drugs.
[SPEAKER_23]: One of them was create your own license plate.
[SPEAKER_23]: What that has to do with drugs, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think it was like, if you go to jail, then you'll be making license plates.
[SPEAKER_23]: You'll be making license plates.
[SPEAKER_23]: So they had like a make your own license plate.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if they wanted to be really realistic, you know, they'd have to have, you know, the rubber glove up the ass.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, yeah, seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: Cavity surge, bend over and spread them.
[SPEAKER_23]: They'd have all us fifth graders take our clothes off and go shower publicly and have Bubba fuck us.
[SPEAKER_10]: Teach you how to make hooch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here is a can of juicy juice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here is yeast that we use to make the hard tack you have to eat.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, wait, I'm not done with my thought yet.
[SPEAKER_23]: So we had to make a license plate, and the deal was, you know, you have to have it be eight letters.
[SPEAKER_23]: So it was like, what would your license plate say, right?
[SPEAKER_23]: My license plate was N-I-N-1-0-D-O.
[SPEAKER_23]: N-I-N-1-0-D-O.
[SPEAKER_23]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_10]: You are such a nerd and I like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: I wonder if anyone actually has that license plate.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dude, I should get it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, if nobody has it in California yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember, Genesis does what Nintendon't.
[SPEAKER_10]: Suck.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sonic the Hedgehog, bitch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bad knuckles.
[SPEAKER_10]: And by the way, Shadow the Hedgehog sucks ass, but he has a gun.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm just reading some comments in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_23]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Ron Chan says, super sloppy OLR double dare.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's what dare makes you think of that show, Double Dare.
[SPEAKER_23]: And then I still have my dare shirt.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_23]: I didn't think they were still doing dare.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I expect to see something like that at Hot Topic soon, because they're doing like all the... Yes!
[SPEAKER_10]: They do have them!
[SPEAKER_10]: They do have them at Hot Topic!
[SPEAKER_10]: Do they?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_22]: You know what would be awesome?
[SPEAKER_10]: I love Hot Topic.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then they also have the drug testing, and it has like a bunch of drugs sitting in a classroom.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know what I want just for the hell of it?
[SPEAKER_23]: I want those prop sandwiches that they had on Double there.
[SPEAKER_23]: I just want two of those giant pieces of bread to put on my floor.
[SPEAKER_23]: The foam bread.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know why that would be so cool, though.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dude, F that.
[SPEAKER_23]: I want the giant hamster wheel.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hamster wheel?
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh my god, that would be cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's very funny, though, because what was his name?
[SPEAKER_10]: Mark Summers?
[SPEAKER_10]: He is supposedly such a neat freak.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, he's obsessive-compulsive.
[SPEAKER_23]: I saw a story on some network somewhere.
[SPEAKER_23]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_23]: I want the big-ass nose that you would have to pick.
[SPEAKER_09]: To pick this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that was awesome.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dude...
[SPEAKER_23]: Every obstacle course had that damn hamster wheel in it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, I forgot to mention, a couple weeks ago on Family Guy, they actually referenced You Can't Do That Television.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, I actually saw that episode, but we don't encourage people to watch Family Guy.
[SPEAKER_23]: That was a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, it's on the same time as us, so we don't encourage people to go watch that.
[SPEAKER_23]: TiVo it!
[SPEAKER_23]: It's a good show, TiVo or BitTorrent.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_23]: We encourage you to pirate Family Guy because it's our competition.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey, BitTorrent is mainly just free TiVo.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's all it is to me.
[SPEAKER_23]: Don't worry, I delete the episodes after 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, 24 hours so that you're not pirating it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_23]: Featuring some music this break from Dance Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_23]: What about the Hannah Wavy game?
[SPEAKER_23]: What, what, what?
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh yeah, you wanted to do the clips, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll do the clips when we come back.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll do the FUs of the week when we come back as well.
[SPEAKER_23]: And hopefully list lists, but we're still trying to think of a topic, so...
[SPEAKER_23]: You guys start thinking about that topic.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_23]: We will come back after this break.
[SPEAKER_23]: In this break, Dance Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, enjoy.
... ... ...
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: All you need is, Mr. Leather said it, all you need is Love, my love, my love, my love, my love My love, my love, my love, my love, my love Come on, come on, do the locomotion with me Locomotion, you got the notion Locomotion, do it that way Everybody do it
[SPEAKER_15]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft,
S, Actdeft,
[SPEAKER_15]: Loco-motion, come on, come on, come on Loco-motion
I'm gonna be, I'm gonna be, I'm gonna be the best
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_23]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_23]: Whoops.
[SPEAKER_23]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're still here.
[SPEAKER_23]: We forgot to queue up a promo.
[SPEAKER_14]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here's your promo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
[SPEAKER_15]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_23]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was too busy brainstorming for Listless.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're actually going to allow a guest person to come on Listless tonight.
[SPEAKER_23]: First person to call in Skype who wants to participate with this topic.
[SPEAKER_23]: Nickelodeon show you want brought back tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, so we'll take whoever calls in first, wanting to play that.
[SPEAKER_23]: The way listless works, everybody presents their top three, so when you call in, please have three shows that you want to do, ready to go.
[SPEAKER_23]: And then we'll come up with our list, and then we each take one off the list.
[SPEAKER_23]: You vote one off, and then the chat room ultimately gets the final vote when we have a list of eight that would be remaining.
[SPEAKER_23]: If that makes no sense to you, don't worry.
[SPEAKER_23]: It'll make sense to you as we start to go through it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's see if we get anybody in on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_23]: Boy, our Skype line's lighting up now all of a sudden.
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's take the first call.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_23]: Can you hear me, caller?
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, sucks to be that person.
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's go ahead and take the next call that came in here.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey, it's Dubz.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey, Dubz, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_10]: Woo, it's Dubz!
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, you wanna play listless with us tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hot, alright.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright guys, stop hammering the Skype line, we got ourselves another player here.
[SPEAKER_23]: But don't worry, all you guys in chat get to vote once we have a list here.
[SPEAKER_23]: So have you heard listless before, Dubz?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Then you know how it works, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, are you thinking of your list here?
[SPEAKER_23]: Nickelodeon show you want them to bring back.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, um... Wait, wait, wait, don't give it away yet.
[SPEAKER_23]: Think of your top three, and then we'll ask you for it.
[SPEAKER_23]: But you have to justify your choices, alright?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I do?
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, yes you do.
[SPEAKER_23]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, let's get ourselves some theme music, shall we?
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's get further down in the theme music here.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's right everybody, it's time for tonight's listless!
[SPEAKER_21]: Playing in tonight's listless is Sky, Loki, DarkSakura, and Doobs.
[SPEAKER_23]: Islander didn't want to participate tonight because he didn't have Nickelodeon as a child, you poor bastard.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_23]: I want to play Flinko!
[SPEAKER_23]: Wrong show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I found the tape, by the way, Rob.
[SPEAKER_23]: What tape?
[SPEAKER_23]: The tape of you on The Price is Right.
[SPEAKER_23]: I wasn't actually on The Price is Right.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I saw you.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, I was in the audience at The Price is Right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had the tape with you on it.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, we'll talk about that later.
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's get to Listless.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, who's starting us off tonight?
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkSakura always starts us off.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, DarkSakura, what is your number three pick?
[SPEAKER_10]: Start this party up right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Salute your shorts.
[SPEAKER_23]: Brief description of the show, Salute Your Shorts, and why they should bring it back.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has that redhead kid.
[SPEAKER_23]: I wanna say the original Rugrats, like the actual one with their babies.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, that one.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, Rugrats.
[SPEAKER_23]: That was the cartoon with the babies.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, yeah, I should bring that back.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not still on?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're all like teenagers and shit.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, that's bullshit.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's bullshit.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki, your number three pick.
[SPEAKER_22]: My number three pick is going to be... Oh man, this is tough.
[SPEAKER_23]: How about...
[SPEAKER_23]: Pete and Pete.
[SPEAKER_23]: Because it was a strange show, but it actually worked.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the mom had a metal plate in her head.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_23]: It reminds me of Malcolm in the Middle.
[SPEAKER_23]: It is basically, I think, is what became Malcolm in the Middle.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, brief description of Pete and Pete.
[SPEAKER_23]: Pete and Pete was just a story about two brothers that, you know, had the same name.
[SPEAKER_23]: They're both kind of nerdy.
[SPEAKER_23]: The one brother had a tattoo that he used to make dance.
[SPEAKER_23]: The mother had a metal plate in her head.
[SPEAKER_10]: She could receive radio signals.
[SPEAKER_23]: She could receive radio signals.
[SPEAKER_23]: And it was just such a weird...
[SPEAKER_23]: Weird Show, but it worked.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was just one of those shows that actually had a pretty good storyline to it, so it worked.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, Pete and Pete, you're number three.
[SPEAKER_23]: Goddammit, I was going to say that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, you've got time to think of another one, dudes.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, my number three I'm going to pick is Hey Dude.
[SPEAKER_23]: Because Hey Dude had the chick who married Ben Stiller, like, years later.
[SPEAKER_23]: Christine Taylor, remember?
[SPEAKER_23]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_23]: She was hot.
[SPEAKER_23]: And Hey Dude was about a dude ranch.
[SPEAKER_10]: She was also in, um, what was that, uh,
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: My number two one is Out of Control.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just an interesting Canadian show.
[SPEAKER_10]: It had a guy who looked a lot like Mark Summers in it and had, what was her name, Driz?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, oh man, when I was a kid I could do it.
[SPEAKER_23]: I can't do it anymore.
[SPEAKER_23]: And she used to tell the super fast jacked up fairy tales.
[SPEAKER_10]: I went through puberty.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was the sound she used to make.
[SPEAKER_10]: And she used to do the really funny jacked up fairy tales.
[SPEAKER_10]: You remember that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that show was just, it was, you know, it always came on right after You Can't Do That on television.
[SPEAKER_23]: And Dave Coulier cut it out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I always was like, okay, this show is awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so, yeah, that gets my number two.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it had the Python-esque animation in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, figure it out.
[SPEAKER_23]: That show was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was that game show where these kids would come up and they'd have talents and people had to figure out what their talent was by asking them questions and stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, her, yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dude, she went to my high school.
[SPEAKER_23]: She graduated the year before I was a freshman.
[SPEAKER_23]: She came back and spoke, like, years later, and so I always find that funny.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_09]: Follow your dreams.
[SPEAKER_23]: You can't reach your goals.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm living proof.
[SPEAKER_23]: Her dad's a dentist somewhere near here.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: And then she did VO5 commercials.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, figure it out.
[SPEAKER_23]: Um, Lokes, oh wait, is it my turn?
[SPEAKER_23]: No, it's Loki's turn.
[SPEAKER_23]: Loki, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_23]: I thought it was Doob's turn.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, he just went, okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: Um, sorry, I had a big mouthful of breadstick at the moment.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyways,
[SPEAKER_23]: My next pick would be... Oh, man, I just had it, too.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, I remember now.
[SPEAKER_23]: Since Eerie Indiana wasn't on Nickelodeon, as far as I'm aware, it might have been at one time, but I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, Are You Afraid of the Dark?
[SPEAKER_23]: But, like, the first season of Are You Afraid of the Dark before got really crappy.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, that's what... And this show is basically, they told, you know, kind of like ghost stories.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's almost like the stupid, um...
[SPEAKER_23]: Goosebumps book thing, you know, but it's better.
[SPEAKER_23]: I hate that show.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, dupes, you might know which one you want to bump off then because you get to take one off the list.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, well, hold on.
[SPEAKER_23]: There could be worse ones.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_23]: My number two pick.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hello, Nick Arcade.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Mine is Danger Mouse.
[SPEAKER_10]: I fucking love Danger Mouse.
[SPEAKER_23]: Danger Mouse is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because it's all about Penfold.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was just watching a tape of Danger Mouse episodes I have at my house, and it was the one where Penfold gets into the giant chicken feed and turns into a giant Penfold.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_23]: I have something just for you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, damn it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Way to go, Rob.
[SPEAKER_23]: Have the volume down when you play this.
[SPEAKER_23]: Penfold.
[SPEAKER_23]: Shush.
[SPEAKER_23]: Just for you.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Doobs, your number one pick.
[SPEAKER_02]: All that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_23]: Brief description and why it should be there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was like a... I say mad TV for kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was like one of those variety hour type shits.
[SPEAKER_02]: It still is.
[SPEAKER_02]: DOOBS HELP!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm saying... Okay, no, no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Han, let me say this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want all that to come back before it had all those preppy white people on it.
[SPEAKER_23]: He's got a point.
[SPEAKER_23]: He does have a point.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Islander, he said he wants it before the preppy white people ruined it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_23]: Pretty white, damn those pretty white people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty white people with phones.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I mean, I mean, like, um, like, I know they have, uh, Britney Spears' sister on it now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, whoa.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I remember the first couple episodes, it was all like, I remember they had, um,
[SPEAKER_02]: That girl from TLC sang for the intro.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, ooh, this is, like, hip-hop type.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I hear, like, you know.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's like, you know what it reminds me of?
[SPEAKER_23]: What he's talking about reminds me of Club MMC.
[SPEAKER_23]: Never mind, forget it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Click, click, click, ding.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, but then remember when it was MMC and it was all like, you know, like, we're hip and we're white and dance hip-hop.
[SPEAKER_10]: My friend's mom was a Mouseketeer for a day.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Roundhouse
[SPEAKER_23]: Roundhouse.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, we saw a guy from Roundhouse at E3.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, the guy from Roundhouse.
[SPEAKER_23]: At least those guys have friggin' talent versus, you know, all that where, we're trying to be like Sarah not live, but for kids.
[SPEAKER_23]: And who can forget the guy from Roundhouse at E3?
[SPEAKER_23]: Konami, Konami-yo.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was him?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, he was one of the pretty white kids on Roundhouse.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was him.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right.
[SPEAKER_23]: And Shane loved him.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, Shane has a crush on him, but that's another story.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, time for my number one pick, and there's so many good ones you could choose from.
[SPEAKER_23]: But, man, screw you all for not naming this show sooner, because this is the king of Nickelodeon shows.
[SPEAKER_23]: There is no doubt about it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Without it, you would not have Green Slime, ever.
[SPEAKER_23]: You can't do that on television, is my number one pick.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was saving it for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I knew you were picking it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't name it because I knew someone else would.
[SPEAKER_10]: And besides that, who else but me is going to say Danger Mouse?
[SPEAKER_23]: All right.
[SPEAKER_23]: If you can't do that on television and had been taken by somebody else, I would have said Count Duckula.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll have to do that on our show.
[SPEAKER_10]: You would have no Count Duckula without Danger Mouse.
[SPEAKER_23]: I know.
[SPEAKER_23]: If our show is ever live, we are going to do the green slime if you say I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you ever see the computer one?
[SPEAKER_10]: It said, aha, I have a way around.
[SPEAKER_10]: That does not compute.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gray slime.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, alright, let's... I remember the red slime and blue slime, and I remember the episode where you could vote by touching your TV.
[SPEAKER_23]: Never mind, anyway.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm showing my age here, people.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, here's the vote-off round.
[SPEAKER_23]: This is going to be a hard one tonight, you guys.
[SPEAKER_23]: You have to take one of these off the list.
[SPEAKER_23]: Salute your shorts, Rugrats, Pete and Pete.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey dude, out of control, figure it out, are you afraid of the dark, Nick Arcade, Danger Mouse, all that, Roundhouse, and you can't do that on television.
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkSakura, what's gotta go?
[SPEAKER_23]: Move your big head out of the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you afraid of the dark?
[SPEAKER_23]: Are you afraid of the dark gets taken off the list by DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_23]: And you knew the dupes was gonna take it off, so you just gave them a free pick.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: He can pick his nose, too.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, dudes, which one's going to come off?
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey, dude.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, you bastard.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, hey, dude comes off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because I'm too young to remember anything that happened on that show.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was going to say, how old are you?
[SPEAKER_23]: Because your picks are more new school Nickelodeon in my eyes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm actually 14, but I didn't watch Nickelodeon much.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: F you, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: F you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob, actually, it was pointed out to me that not a one of us mentioned Invader Zim.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ah, dammit!
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: I say we have a unanimous vote to put Invader Zim on the list.
[SPEAKER_10]: All of us vote?
[SPEAKER_23]: Fine, fine.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll put Invader Zim on the list.
[SPEAKER_10]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_23]: God, I'm so bad.
[SPEAKER_23]: Now that's new school, Nicola.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, Loki, take one of these off the list.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dammit, you know, these took off my Hey Dude Because I Was Gonna Say That Show bit compared to, you know, like, say, Sleezy Shorts.
[SPEAKER_23]: But I'm gonna take off Rugrats because...
[SPEAKER_23]: I mean, that used to be on, was it, you know, Nick Jr.
[SPEAKER_23]: And that's where it needs to stay, is Nick Jr.
[SPEAKER_10]: It needs to be back there by pinwheel.
[SPEAKER_23]: Spinning around.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pinwheel, pinwheel, spinning around.
[SPEAKER_23]: My turn, huh?
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm gonna have to take off, um... I'm gonna take off Roundhouse.
[SPEAKER_23]: I just...
[SPEAKER_23]: There's too many sketch comedy shows on Nickelodeon.
[SPEAKER_23]: Nah, I do.
[SPEAKER_23]: I have excellent taste.
[SPEAKER_23]: You can't do that on television better.
[SPEAKER_23]: What would you do on that stupid... Nobody said Double Dare, but I guess they have a new version of Double Dare.
[SPEAKER_23]: Lots of shows not named.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_23]: Here it is, the list that you guys can vote on.
[SPEAKER_23]: Salute your shorts.
[SPEAKER_23]: Pete and Pete.
[SPEAKER_23]: Doobs, what the hell are you doing over there?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, my thing's just messing up.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_23]: Salute your shorts, Pete and Pete, Out of Control, Figure It Out, Nick Arcade, Danger Mouse, all that.
[SPEAKER_23]: You can't do that on television and Invader Zim.
[SPEAKER_23]: You guys can send a vote.
[SPEAKER_23]: You get to vote for one.
[SPEAKER_23]: Send a private message to Sky in the chatroom with your vote.
[SPEAKER_23]: Some of the ones we missed, you guys, according to the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_23]: Count Duckula, Ren and Stimpy,
[SPEAKER_23]: Um, that's a big one.
[SPEAKER_23]: Actually, I think Vader Zim should come off the list because while it's still, um, it is a cancelled show, they still rerun it.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm saying no, we already put him there.
[SPEAKER_23]: Um, Amanda's show?
[SPEAKER_23]: No.
[SPEAKER_23]: Clarissa Explains It All.
[SPEAKER_23]: Clarissa Explains It All, thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I liked Clarissa Explains It All because the guy who came in through the window.
[SPEAKER_23]: She never taught me about sexuality, she didn't explain it all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would also say Turkey Television.
[SPEAKER_23]: But nobody remembers that show, not a damn person.
[SPEAKER_23]: Today's special.
[SPEAKER_23]: I remember today's special.
[SPEAKER_23]: Doug, Pinwheels.
[SPEAKER_23]: Doug is now on Disney.
[SPEAKER_23]: I mentioned Pinwheels.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's actually on Disney in the morning now.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dang, that show's been going forever then.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, well, dudes, thanks for playing.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll let you know how it turns out, alright?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, thanks for playing and have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Later.
[SPEAKER_23]: You just wanted to say boobs on our show.
[SPEAKER_23]: Rocko's Modern Life.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's okay, we say boobs all the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Boobs, boobs, boobs, boobs, boobs, boobs.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, Rocko's Modern Life, the characters from Rocko is supposed to have like a cameo in the, or not the Rugrats movie, the Spongebob movie, but I don't remember seeing them.
[SPEAKER_23]: Fucking Spongebob Squarepants, but again, that's all.
[SPEAKER_23]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's all Nickelodeon is now.
[SPEAKER_23]: I hate Spongebob.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dude, Spongebob is not that bad.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, technically all that is still on there too.
[SPEAKER_22]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, it's still on there.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: Because now that one of the guys from it actually is on Saturday Night Live, they're like, oh, we're famous now.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: Legend of the Hidden Temple was freaking awesome and Guts was on my list.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I took it off in favor of whatever the first one was.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Guts was a good idea.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'll just remember the referee that they had on the show.
[SPEAKER_23]: We have all these veggie cords.
[SPEAKER_23]: What are we going to do with them?
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's play every game with them.
[SPEAKER_23]: The aggro crag.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's climb up the big glowing purple hunk of plastic.
[SPEAKER_23]: Uh-oh, I got aggroed by the crag.
[SPEAKER_10]: You lost ten minutes because you didn't hit the little charger thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_10]: Time to go back to kindergarten.
[SPEAKER_23]: And the NFM?
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, the Neon FM.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll get to that, too.
[SPEAKER_23]: I promise we will.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll get to that.
[SPEAKER_23]: So let's get those votes in real quick because we're going to get to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_23]: Don't send your FUs just yet, though, because we've got to get the votes for listless out of the way first.
[SPEAKER_23]: So we'll be back after this quick break with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Go on the mic, word up, this groove is set to soon Move you, fuck people now, it's time to
and many more.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, technically this next song is from second mix, but Jamie begged.
[SPEAKER_09]: I cried.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now I realize, it's all the love I'm bringing
[SPEAKER_12]: We're back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: Love by Sonic Dream from Second Mix.
[SPEAKER_23]: Before that, Bakwa.
[SPEAKER_23]: And starting us off, Extreme Wonderland.
[SPEAKER_23]: I heard Miracle last night when I was at Red Lobster.
[SPEAKER_14]: Miracles.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, from Max too.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, Max.
[SPEAKER_23]: Max.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, you want to find out tonight's listless winners?
[SPEAKER_23]: We did the votes.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, Kay, thanks.
[SPEAKER_23]: This was a toughie.
[SPEAKER_23]: We had a lot of votes kind of spread out tonight.
[SPEAKER_23]: Everybody loves Nickelodeon, so I'm glad we could talk about it here.
[SPEAKER_23]: Nobody loves MTV, though.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, nobody.
[SPEAKER_23]: Seriously, I actually watched a little bit of MTV for the first time in a long time yesterday.
[SPEAKER_23]: There was a marathon of Next, which is some type of speed dating show.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's awful.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, I remember.
[SPEAKER_23]: I've seen that show.
[SPEAKER_23]: What about, they also had a marathon yesterday, I thought, of True Life.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't watch TV, so I have no idea what the fuck either of you are talking about.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, no, I'd have to see that, because that would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_23]: True, they honestly had that, it was great.
[SPEAKER_23]: True Life is actually one of the few decent series they have now, I think.
[SPEAKER_23]: But, like, all these, like, you know what my friends are into, and I don't get this at all.
[SPEAKER_23]: They don't watch the real world, they don't watch Road Rules, but what they do watch is that fucking, like, Inferno show, where it's like real world meets Road Rules on, I don't know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: Isn't, like, MTV All Reality shows nowadays now?
[SPEAKER_23]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's MTV.
[SPEAKER_24]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_24]: Liquid Television.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I remember Pauly Shore.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know that Aeon Flux movie is coming out next year?
[SPEAKER_23]: Or is it this year?
[SPEAKER_23]: I think I'm going to see that.
[SPEAKER_23]: It looks kind of, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: However, there's one show that I do watch sort of.
[SPEAKER_24]: My guilty pleasure on TV is Pimp My Ride.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because I want to take my mom's ice cream truck and see what they can do with that.
[SPEAKER_23]: They love crap like that, you know, where it's just like something weird.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know what my guilty... I'm actually going to go see Aeon Flux, you know, but my guilty pleasure movie of this year, which is an MTV movie actually, is going to be Roll Bounce.
[SPEAKER_23]: The hell's that?
[SPEAKER_23]: Roll Bounce is a movie set in the 70s during the roller disco era, and it's actually... I remember roller disco!
[SPEAKER_23]: Basically, it is...
[SPEAKER_23]: It is, um, You Got Served on Roller Skates.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, look.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need to see that!
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, no, my fucking... It's looking awesome, okay?
[SPEAKER_23]: Look, people, we'll do the MTV show they need to bring back at a later date, but we gotta get rid of tonight's list list first.
[SPEAKER_23]: Check out the trailer, though.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's online on Apple.
[SPEAKER_22]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, let's do this.
[SPEAKER_23]: Uh, top three list list tonight.
[SPEAKER_23]: Nickelodeon show they should bring back.
[SPEAKER_23]: Number third, number three.
[SPEAKER_23]: Number third.
[SPEAKER_23]: Uh, You Can't Do That on Television in third place tonight.
[SPEAKER_23]: In second place tonight, Invader Zim.
[SPEAKER_23]: Rightfully so.
[SPEAKER_23]: In first place, what are the gamers going to say?
[SPEAKER_23]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nick Arcade.
[SPEAKER_23]: Nick Arcade in first place, you guys.
[SPEAKER_23]: Good job, tonight's list list.
[SPEAKER_23]: I would watch it if they brought any of those shows back.
[SPEAKER_23]: They need to have Nick Classic.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, they have gas.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, I have gas too, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm not going to be watching it.
[SPEAKER_23]: They need Nick Classic.
[SPEAKER_23]: Honestly, the old school shows need to just run the reruns.
[SPEAKER_23]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, let's get on to tonight's FUs or we're going to run out of time here.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, Jamie, why do we do the FUs of the week every single week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I hate everybody and everything and I just need to slip my wrist.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want my god damn car you bitches!
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I have been, oh hi ferret.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have been without a car, okay get this, I've been without a car now for a month!
[SPEAKER_10]: A month!
[SPEAKER_10]: A month with no ride!
[SPEAKER_10]: I need a car this week and I need my god damn three thousand dollars check to be here now
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I don't care when the fuck you mailed it, you should have sent that shit Federal Express to my door, hand-delivered by, you know, young boys dressed in, you know, old pageboy livery or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It should have been at my door.
[SPEAKER_10]: It should have been in my hand a week ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: It should have been in my hand three weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need a car.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_23]: I only have two.
[SPEAKER_23]: The first one is this fucking headache that's been on my head for two days.
[SPEAKER_23]: I say on my head because it switched from the right side to the left side last night.
[SPEAKER_23]: So now whatever parasite it is in my head is on my left side, and it still hurts, and it's the Sunday headache.
[SPEAKER_23]: And I don't know why I can't get rid of it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyways, and the second thing goes to, well I actually have three.
[SPEAKER_23]: So the second thing goes to the servers on Final Fantasy because they're still crashing.
[SPEAKER_23]: And they should have fixed this months ago, and I don't know why they can't seem to fend off a stupid DNS attack.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's just a DNS attack, come on, people, you know, fix it.
[SPEAKER_23]: and the third goes to the phone company for some reason charging me $80 when they should be charging me $40 for the first time thing and they're saying that I'm like there's some non uh some sort of charges that are non you know standard charges or whatever like 32 bucks I'm like what the hell is this I don't have any extra services so I have to call them and find out what that is tomorrow so that's it my turn
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm going to give an F you to missing deadlines at work, because that really sucks.
[SPEAKER_23]: I want to give an F you to earwax, because apparently I had a really bad buildup of earwax in one of my ears.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, look, this is a totally normal thing, okay?
[SPEAKER_23]: Y'all get it.
[SPEAKER_23]: I had a really bad buildup, and I actually lost hearing in my right ear a couple days ago.
[SPEAKER_23]: And I was totally freaked out.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was like, oh my god, I'm going to be deaf, and I do radio as a hobby, I'm going to be screwed for the rest of my life, I'll never be able to play DDR again.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's why I have one of those cool
[SPEAKER_23]: I was trying to clean my ear with a Q-tip, like a normal sanitary person would do.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's actually very bad for you, because what I did is I actually pushed the wax in further with a Q-tip and made myself lose hearing.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, don't push it in, you gotta go around.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, that's what I was trying to do, but somehow I pushed it in.
[SPEAKER_23]: So anyway, kids, if you have your wax filled up, go to the store and get the liquid that you put in your ear, because that's the only way you're gonna do it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Don't use a Q-tip, I went down the highway.
[SPEAKER_23]: Go swim in a pool.
[SPEAKER_23]: Swim in a pool, folks.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_23]: And I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, an FU to $15 copays to get your earwax removed, that's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, let's go to Islander.
[SPEAKER_23]: FU to airborne viruses.
[SPEAKER_24]: Why can't more diseases be like, I don't know, HIV?
[SPEAKER_24]: It's like, you know, you know what you have to do to get it, so if you just avoid that, you won't get it?
[SPEAKER_24]: No.
[SPEAKER_24]: The flu has to be something you can just give to someone by talking to them.
[SPEAKER_24]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_23]: Thank God you can't catch ugly.
[SPEAKER_23]: OMG, it's OMG Tits Boobs.
[SPEAKER_23]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: He took my suggestion.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that doobs?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, it's doobs.
[SPEAKER_23]: OMG Tits Boobs says, F you to my girlfriend being able to beat me on Paranoia Survivor Max Oni Shuffle.
[SPEAKER_23]: F you to Brazilian people on MMOs again because they suck at English.
[SPEAKER_23]: What a great generalization.
[SPEAKER_23]: And F you to my 13-year-old cousin for living in New York so long.
[SPEAKER_23]: He's like a big drug dealer now and he's 13.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, and F you for living in Florida because my house is infested with bugs.
[SPEAKER_23]: LemonLimeJump sent in a late vote for, um... Sorry, I thought that was an FU.
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkTetsuya says, F you to hire next morning.
[SPEAKER_23]: I guess he's going for the AAAs or something.
[SPEAKER_23]: Ron Chan says, F you to my old job for fucking me over, as he said earlier.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's okay, because I'm going to CompUSA, your competition.
[SPEAKER_23]: Who's getting pwned now, bitches?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're fucking you over, fuck them back.
[SPEAKER_23]: I love it when I get to say pwned.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dark Knight says, my FU goes to work being a bitch and not feeling appreciated when I bust my ass going out of my way to satisfy customers, even though I'm just a cashier.
[SPEAKER_23]: Illusion says, FU to my uncle's wife's gay brother that is covering it up by marrying a woman that is so into herself that she won't need any love for herself's wife's.
[SPEAKER_23]: I need a map to figure that one out.
[SPEAKER_23]: 30th birthday party that was full of boring rich people that only played corny songs like, This song is for all the girls, or whatever it was.
[SPEAKER_23]: F you to not being able to go to karaoke because of this party, and F you to the weekend being boring because of nothing to do this weekend, but I did finally get to watch Rocky Horror Picture Show.
[SPEAKER_23]: That coming from Illusion.
[SPEAKER_10]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_23]: Ninst says, F you to my computer for acting up lately.
[SPEAKER_23]: Reznor says, a big fuck you to customers that can't keep their kids from putting used condoms in their computer's floppy drive.
[SPEAKER_23]: You've got to be kidding.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_23]: I didn't know you could fit that in there.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wowie, wowie, wow.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, they're kids.
[SPEAKER_23]: What the hell would you think?
[SPEAKER_23]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_23]: Used condom receptacle.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dude, there's people that think the CD-ROM is a coffee tray, so, or a coffee cup tray thing.
[SPEAKER_23]: I can at least see that.
[SPEAKER_24]: My question is, where do these kids get the used condoms?
[SPEAKER_24]: From their parents?
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you should, like, hide that shit, or, like, better, or something.
[SPEAKER_23]: Here, leave me alone, go play this.
[SPEAKER_23]: Go blow up these balloons.
[SPEAKER_23]: Sugaru-chan says, F you to Ultramix and Ultramix 2 for having such horrible music.
[SPEAKER_23]: I disagree, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, actually, some girl got AIDS from that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_23]: And for their not having more Konami-Bomani games in the US.
[SPEAKER_23]: Sugaru-chan says, last F you for my boyfriend using me and cosplay.
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkLionXVI says, F you to David Williams for calling my pocket aces with his 6-7 of clubs on the World Series of Poker.
[SPEAKER_23]: No limit tourney.
[SPEAKER_23]: The flop came 8-5-9 of clubs for the straight flush, eliminating me in the process.
[SPEAKER_23]: F you to myself for playing one more lovely another, forgetting to turn off hard mode.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_23]: And lastly, Iguana Girl says, F you to bad car batteries and corrosion that causes Jessica to be stuck out in the heat and wind for seven and a half hours.
[SPEAKER_23]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_23]: They have had commercials!
[SPEAKER_23]: I have seen commercials on VH1!
[SPEAKER_23]: Advertising!
[SPEAKER_23]: Become a Hooter Girl!
[SPEAKER_23]: I was like, it's coming!
[SPEAKER_23]: It's coming!
[SPEAKER_23]: Soon!
[SPEAKER_23]: We are like, what, the last city in the nation to get a Hooters.
[SPEAKER_23]: Seriously, LA has 5 billion.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think Sacramento is the last city in the nation, big city, to get a Hooters.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're finally getting one.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're also getting Logan's Roadhouse, which also makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_23]: Somebody in the chat room is yelling at me because they already signed to our website.
[SPEAKER_24]: I got busted.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know, there's actually someone down the street from where I live who does this for a living.
[SPEAKER_24]: Straight up.
[SPEAKER_24]: Dancing Dan.
[SPEAKER_24]: If he doesn't have a gig going, his sign says, hire me.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_23]: And this guy, this dude says, $11.50 an hour is what he makes doing that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Holy.
[SPEAKER_23]: I know.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, well, I mean, like, for just doing that?
[SPEAKER_23]: Now I understand.
[SPEAKER_23]: Try to put Nelly on the corner, man, because she's not making that kind of money.
[SPEAKER_23]: You are going to put your fianc on the corner, have her work the corner.
[SPEAKER_23]: Seriously, that's some good money there.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_23]: Plus, she's bitching about not having a tan.
[SPEAKER_23]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's a twofer.
[SPEAKER_23]: You're a bastard.
[SPEAKER_23]: Who would want to marry you?
[SPEAKER_23]: Neon FM
[SPEAKER_23]: Sounds like a lot of Naoki songs I've heard before, but that's kind of cute that they invoke that.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, what do you guys think, real quickly?
[SPEAKER_10]: Naoki.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know what the point of 1981 is.
[SPEAKER_23]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: Bride and Dream.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dude, it's like an Ayumi Tamasaki techno song.
[SPEAKER_10]: Time to drop some E and go to a rave.
[SPEAKER_23]: I have heard that whole song before, I remember, somewhere, and it's really good.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's kind of hot, I like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Bring the beat back.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wow, that bitch is off-key.
[SPEAKER_24]: Is it just me?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, well, once she's off-key, and I think for me, for that song to be cool, they need to lose that techno-ish aspect.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm actually liking this so far, though.
[SPEAKER_23]: This isn't bad.
[SPEAKER_23]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_23]: Can you feel the music?
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, that's Can You Feel the Music.
[SPEAKER_23]: I kind of like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Do you have an artist list up so we can tell you who the artists of these songs are?
[SPEAKER_23]: I have to look.
[SPEAKER_23]: Go to the site so we can get some of that, because I only have the song titles here.
[SPEAKER_23]: You like that one, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I do like that one a whole bunch.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, Complete Shot.
[SPEAKER_23]: Here's the earlier...
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh yeah, we heard this one earlier.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_23]: Wait, what was that song again?
[SPEAKER_23]: Complete Shot.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, the one before that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Can You Feel the Music.
[SPEAKER_23]: There's a song list on there.
[SPEAKER_23]: Why are you going to that page?
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, I'm going to... This is the same page.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm just looking to see... Whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: We've got to get through this.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're running out of show.
[SPEAKER_23]: Control...
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait, this song's familiar.
[SPEAKER_23]: I like that one.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's a different drum song, I think.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think it is.
[SPEAKER_23]: Is that the Alien 6?
[SPEAKER_23]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's... Damn, because I've heard of that.
[SPEAKER_23]: The Nine.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's from... It's a free... Or not a... A different drum song.
[SPEAKER_23]: You can actually get the whole song on Amazon for free.
[SPEAKER_23]: Because I know I've listened to that.
[SPEAKER_23]: The Nine.
[SPEAKER_23]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Enough of you.
[SPEAKER_23]: Thomas Howard.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yay, a ballad.
[SPEAKER_23]: OLR staff favorite.
[SPEAKER_17]: I can't wait to play this.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, let's run through this here.
[SPEAKER_17]: Gotta Kick My Love.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sounds like Togo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Haruharu
[SPEAKER_23]: Hi-G doing that one.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hiro is the guy that does Gotta Kick My Love right now, and you can go to his website, www.hiro777.com.
[SPEAKER_23]: Nation's World.
[SPEAKER_23]: I hate this song.
[SPEAKER_23]: This song came out a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_23]: Again, we're playing clips from new songs on Neon FM, which are available on Neon FM's website, yes?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_23]: DJ Potato featuring THL, this is Putter in Reverse
[SPEAKER_24]: What?
[SPEAKER_24]: I feel like I should be waving my hands in a per-per-motion.
[SPEAKER_24]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sexy, sexy, sexy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Rhinestone Cowboy.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's Ricky and Daz.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's actually kind of a commercially known song.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, Ricky and Daz, the Space Cats.
[SPEAKER_23]: You can go to SpaceCats.com Oh, so that's why it sounds like Bus Stop, because those are the singers from Bus Stop.
[SPEAKER_23]: Aha!
[SPEAKER_15]: Gotcha!
[SPEAKER_15]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_23]: You guys know this one if you've ever played Frequency.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dude, Freeze Pop rocks.
[SPEAKER_23]: You shut up.
[SPEAKER_23]: That was Science Genius.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like some Freeze Pop, I just didn't care for that Freeze Pop song.
[SPEAKER_23]: DJ Siamie, I don't know, DJ Siamie, Siamie, I think so, with Skyward.
[SPEAKER_23]: Not bad, not bad.
[SPEAKER_23]: Freeze Pop, again, Stakeout.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's the song that almost got retired in the cage match, but Jamie decided in a tie vote its fourth week to go for the other song.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, that much freeze pop every so often makes my head want to go floaty.
[SPEAKER_23]: You'll love this.
[SPEAKER_23]: Super Sprode is another song.
[SPEAKER_10]: I should like Super Sprode.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's in a minor key.
[SPEAKER_23]: DJ Potato with Tune In.
[SPEAKER_23]: This is a theme song also.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know for a theme song.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's a little weird.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, they had a different version of that, or cut of that, but actually it was really good when I saw the preview video.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alien number 613, You Got the City.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm digging this one.
[SPEAKER_10]: It makes me think of Chemical Love from Bust a Move.
[SPEAKER_24]: I am really digging that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_23]: And lastly, Zap Remix.
[SPEAKER_24]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_23]: Final Thought Time Islander, thanks for being here tonight, appreciate it Final Thought
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, final thought, uh, um, why am I blanking out?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: I, final thought, um, drink more orange juice.
[SPEAKER_23]: Loki, your final thought for tonight.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, I had something, and I can't remember what it was, but, uh, all I'm gonna say is two things.
[SPEAKER_23]: One, go vote for our podcast on Podcast Alley.
[SPEAKER_23]: Go do it now, because honestly, you want to.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know you want to.
[SPEAKER_23]: and also go check out my MySpace page, myspace.com slash LokiFusion and that's where you're going to find when I unveil brand new songs or even upload works in progress.
[SPEAKER_23]: So check out that page, it's got a spiffy little thing you can download.
[SPEAKER_23]: A couple songs, including the Ecstasy remix and the Radical Faith remix, which you might not have heard.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's on there, and also there's a cool little banner that I made, and it's pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_23]: So anyways, check it out.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's myspace.com slash LokiFusion.
[SPEAKER_23]: LokiFusion, all one word.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right, I'll put that in the chat room as well.
[SPEAKER_23]: My final thought is, because I promised somebody I would say it again, Hyperion 7, Murdoch is password God, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, that's where I play.
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: Reject false spirits.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, and final word of the show.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know I gotta give it to the guests when we have one.
[SPEAKER_23]: Islander, one word that sums it all up.
[SPEAKER_23]: See you guys next week.
[SPEAKER_23]: We appreciate you tuning in tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know, one word isn't gonna do it.
[SPEAKER_24]: It has to be two.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ghostbots.
[SPEAKER_12]: And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Approach, students.
[SPEAKER_07]: Close the circle at the feet of the Master.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have come to me asking that I be your guide along the path of Tai Kwan Leap.
[SPEAKER_07]: But be warned, to learn its ways, you must learn the ways of your own soul.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let us meditate upon this wisdom now.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, Aum.
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh, sir?
[SPEAKER_18]: Sir?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, oh, sir?
[SPEAKER_07]: Who disturbs our meditation as a pebble disturbs the stillness of the pond?
[SPEAKER_18]: Me.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ed Gruberman?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ed Gruberman.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, uh, no disrespect or nothing, but like, how long is this gonna take?
[SPEAKER_07]: Taekwon Leap is not a path to a door, but a road leading forever towards the horizon.
[SPEAKER_18]: So like, what, an hour or so?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, we have not even begun upon the path.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ed Gruberman, you must learn patience.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, yeah, yeah, patience.
[SPEAKER_18]: How long will that take?
[SPEAKER_07]: Time has no meaning.
[SPEAKER_07]: To a true student, a year is as a day.
[SPEAKER_07]: A year?! !
[SPEAKER_18]: I want to beat people up right now.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got the pajamas.
[SPEAKER_07]: Beat people up?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, just show me all those nifty moves so I can start trashing bozos.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's all I came here for.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only use of Taekwondo is self-defense.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you know who said that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ki Lo Ni, the great teacher.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, the best defense is a good offense.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know who said that?
[SPEAKER_18]: Mel, the cook on Alice.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, um... Taekwon Lip is the wine of purity, not the vinegar of hostility.
[SPEAKER_07]: Meditate upon this truth with us.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh...
[SPEAKER_07]: Listen, shrimp.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now, are you going to show me some fancy moves, or am I going to start wiping the walls with you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ed Gruberman, you failed to grasp Taekwon Leap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Approach me that you might see.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right, finally some action.
[SPEAKER_07]: Observe closely, class.
[SPEAKER_07]: Boot to the head.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ow, you're pulling me in the head!
[SPEAKER_07]: You are lucky, Ed Gruberman.
[SPEAKER_07]: Few novices experience so much of Taekwon Leap so soon.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ow!
[SPEAKER_07]: Now we continue.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, hey, I wasn't ready.
[SPEAKER_18]: Come and get me now, shorty, huh?
[SPEAKER_18]: Come on, are you chicken?
[SPEAKER_05]: Boot to the head.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, okay, now I'm ready.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, now, come on, try it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boot to the head.
[SPEAKER_18]: Mind if I just lie down here for a minute?
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, class, we shall return to our... Master, it is wrong to tip the vessel of knowledge, student.
[SPEAKER_07]: Many apologies, master, but I feel Ed Gruberman is not wholly wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to boot some head, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you learned nothing from the lesson of Ed Gruberman?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, master.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have learned two things.
[SPEAKER_07]: First, that anger is a weapon only to one's opponent.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_07]: And secondly, get in the first shot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Boot to the head.
[SPEAKER_07]: You missed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: You two shall be honored to learn a lesson about us.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't have to, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Boot to the head.
[SPEAKER_15]: I gotta be going.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can anyone tell us what lesson has been learned here?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, yes, master.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a single one of us could defeat you.
[SPEAKER_07]: You gain wisdom, child.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll have to gang up on you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get him down!
[SPEAKER_04]: Boot to the head.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_06]: And now, class, let us rejoin the mind to the body and gaze into the heart of the candle in meditation.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aum.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very good, class.
[SPEAKER_04]: People talking in movie shows, people smoking in bed People voting Republican, give them a boot to the head
[SPEAKER_04]: Botanics who can't fix a car Politicians who can't think The salesman who won't leave me alone The waiter who forgot my drink
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you very much for listening and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_23]: God damn, that was a long fortune cookie message.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought I was just putting the song up, but I forgot that I had that as the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_23]: Our chatroom got a kick out of that, so we appreciate anything that can get the chatroom all happy and stuff, because the chatroom is really what keeps us going with this show.
[SPEAKER_10]: The chatroom needs happy pants.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kisses!
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, thanks you guys so much for tuning in and supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_23]: I just broke my damn headphones.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's really great.
[SPEAKER_25]: Son of a bitch.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right.
[SPEAKER_23]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in and listening tonight to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: We hope to see you again next week and the week after and the week after that.
[SPEAKER_23]: You're now going to get dumped from our stream, but please retune back into the station in about 15 seconds to resume.
[SPEAKER_22]: What?
[SPEAKER_22]: Continue.
[SPEAKER_23]: Reconnect to the stream in about 15 seconds for Orange Lounge Radio's video game music program.
[SPEAKER_23]: Good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_23]: Have a good one.