[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of June 6th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, everybody out there on the interweb, and welcome to the latest edition of Orange Lounge Radio To Go, your home...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Jamie Summers DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
[SPEAKER_04]: The Day of Evil because it is the man's birthday.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll talk about music some other time because tonight we've got to talk about games.
[SPEAKER_05]: First off, though, I want to give a big thank you to one of the podcast directories out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's PodcastShuffle.com because they made us their podcast of the day, week, moment.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's one of his favorite podcasts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: That makes me all go squeak.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So check those guys out, PodcastShuffle.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we really appreciate all your guys' support.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Ferret is so happy that he had a seizure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Great, good to know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's start off with a little bit of how was your gaming week, the type of stuff you've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll start off with Loki tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what kind of games have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I played not too much in the realm of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played a little bit of Rengoku, just, you know, killing more stuff on the same level, getting more experience.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't beat this stupid game because it's just boring.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's one of those ones where you're so far into it now you just have to beat the damn thing, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not really, but it's just not that great.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just doesn't get much harder.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, the first generation of PSP games just kind of blew.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why, but... Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Luminous, hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most of the first generation PSP games blew, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Granted, there are some good ones, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: There's really not too much out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Smart Bomb, for example, sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, my boss gave me a clean copy of it, so I was able to take it back for free, and I still have Smart Bomb.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I got all my money back, and I got the game for free, basically.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it's nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now I have $90 in credit to GameStop, and I have nothing to buy there.
$90?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, um, also, I played a little bit of the Simpsons arcade game on my meme cabinet, because I had to fire that up to show Nelly's parents what that was.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, um,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakra, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I played lots and lots of PSO
[SPEAKER_02]: Blue Burst, correct?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, Blue Burst.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played some Silent Hill 3 and then turned it off because I was kind of bored.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I watched Dan beat Fire Emblem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which Fire Emblem?
[SPEAKER_05]: The new game?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Sacred Stones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the one that just came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: The GameCube one that's not out yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, I got to see the end of Fire Emblem.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's like all he plays now is, well, let's put in the Game Boy Advance player and play Fire Emblem.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, Fire Emblem was one of those games that was popular in Japan for a long time, but it took a long time to come over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know what they're playing today?
[SPEAKER_02]: Busted out the Super Nintendo and popped in the Super Famicom card of Fire Emblem 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw that when I went over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw that one of your friends was playing like a Japanese game on the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the kind of stuff I only see happen at your house.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: But I watched Sega Fantasy 5, which was frustrating because the text would move just fast enough that I would catch words and bits and pieces of Kana and not be able to read the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was like... That's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't know that existed.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sega fanboys and fangirls are pretty rabid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll see about posting a link on the OrangeLoungeRadio.com live journal forum.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice plug.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, my gaming week, you know, there's not a whole lot of new stuff out there that I really wanted to check out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wanted to buy a new DS game this week, but really, all that's out right now, I think the only game that came out was Madagascar, which is a game I might be excited about if I was seven years old, but I'm not, so I could care less.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't Polarium... I played another game, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, what's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots and lots of the Pac-Pix demo at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Medios is coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Medios is out June 27th.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the day after my birthday and I couldn't be more happier that the DS is getting that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sigma Star Saga is coming out, Game Boy Advance, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, yeah, I think that's Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_04]: That one's actually supposed to be pretty interesting because it's, imagine, you know, your typical RPG, but instead of the random battles, it's random side-scroller shooters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, so since I didn't really get anything new, I went back to my collection and I said, well, what are some games I really didn't play enough of?
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm checking out Mario DS, Mario 64 DS, because I really didn't get that far into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I got about 30 stars, and then I said, eh, screw it, I got more games to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I really want more minigames right now, because surprisingly enough, the minigames to me were the best part of Mario DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, and also, I don't know if it's just me, but Mario 64, and I'm going to get a lot of crap and hate letters for this, I think Mario 64 is one of the most overrated games ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I see a lot of lists out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know how every website out there has got to have a top 100 list.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Super Mario 64 is always in the top three of the greatest platformers or the greatest games even.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I have to disagree with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I have special memories of Mario 64.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Dan and I would play Mario 64 together and bond over it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, see, you got special stuff there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, add one single word in there, then it makes all the sense in the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario Kart 64.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game rocked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mario 64 for me was nothing but a bunch of frustrating cameras.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it was darn innovative at the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I got to give it that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't know if I would place it so near the top in the great...
[SPEAKER_05]: Mario Sunshine was cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shine get!
[SPEAKER_05]: Mario Sunshine to me was not that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was... It was like Mario 64 with water.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate to say it was better than Mario 64, but I was entertained longer by Mario Sunshine than I was in Mario 64 initially.
[SPEAKER_05]: And honestly, folks, if you have a GameCube,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: August is going to be the release date for Geist.
[SPEAKER_04]: I keep up on that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I know you got it for your work stuff, but you have to make it sound exciting for our podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is exciting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you do that for me?
[SPEAKER_05]: It is exciting because there's not that many good GameCube games coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: A little bit of PSP news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, you'll love this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: PSP is getting some bonafide actual porn.
[SPEAKER_05]: I read about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not somebody putting the porn on their memory sticks, as most PSP users probably did the first day they got it.
[SPEAKER_05]: UMD porn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actual UMD porn coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the company that's putting this out is Glaze, G-L-A-Y apostrophe Z, starting off July 8th.
[SPEAKER_05]: The titles will be anywhere between ¥1,995 and just under ¥4,000.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's about $18 to $37 US.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I will horribly butcher some of these names if I try to pronounce them.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, I like some of this.
[SPEAKER_05]: On July 22nd, Bybody Aeroterrorist Noah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aeroterrorist, what is that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: And let's see, HMP Countdown 2005.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, humping?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, HMP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hump Countdown!
[SPEAKER_05]: July 8th, Kanishiro Ana, Koiku Soap Jewel.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just like that because it has the word soap in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it's like Bubble Bath Babes, the porn.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this something we're going to see in the U.S.?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, honestly, probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know who I'd actually see probably putting stuff out for it would be like Playboy, something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: We did have a story a couple months ago about Playboy.com doing something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, their iPod crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I mean, honestly, you might see some of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it'd be better as downloadable content because, honestly, I couldn't see buying.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, really, I just can't see a situation where this would come in handy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean,
[SPEAKER_04]: Come in handy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't see it being something I'd spend money on.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then again, I don't see myself spending money on UMDs.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here's a kind of story that ties in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure if you can cover it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, we're talking about the first two UMDs actually hit 100,000 in sales.
[SPEAKER_04]: 100,000 units sold.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the first two would be...
[SPEAKER_04]: Air Force One took nine months.
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what it reminds me of?
[SPEAKER_05]: When did DVD players really take off?
[SPEAKER_05]: When PlayStation 2 came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: So maybe it's kind of similar, where people don't want to buy portable DVD players, but they'll buy a PSP, which is like a portable DVD player.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't explain it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever makes you happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, you had a comment?
[SPEAKER_05]: Porn on the PSP?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it's going to be really big in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here, it's not going to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't think so, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I don't think they're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Age demographic, it's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, PSP news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, going along with PSP news in Japan, they're saying it's slumping over in Tokyo, actually, in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: A new story coming out of Tokyo saying that the sales of the PSP are slumping.
[SPEAKER_05]: from the week of May 23rd to 29th only four PSP games were in the complete top 50 none of them cracking the top 20 whereas you look on the other half of it six Nintendo DS titles in the top 20 Nintendogs
[SPEAKER_05]: I love the puppies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played Frisbee with the puppies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this a sign of things to come?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is the DS going to...
[SPEAKER_02]: Outdo the PSP here in America?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, it's America.
[SPEAKER_02]: We want it bigger, faster.
[SPEAKER_02]: It needs to do more shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: It needs to do more Sony because the world sucks the cock of Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was honestly a big launch of games from the beginning.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had about 20 or so games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now it's dead as far as what's coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's what's happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like there's only a couple games.
[SPEAKER_04]: People are tired of the old games, and now they're waiting for more stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's in DS syndrome now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_05]: PSP is now suffering the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: DS is, I would say to most extent, still suffering through.
[SPEAKER_05]: Both systems, to me, are at a dead still.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't have any really great games out on the horizon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe Meteos on the DS, of course, coming later this month.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's by the Res guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looking at the PSP calendar, Batman Begins is coming out in June.
[SPEAKER_05]: Midnight Club 3 Dub Edition, now that could be very cool, also coming out in June.
[SPEAKER_05]: Currently the only game slated for July, according to the calendar I have here, is Star Wars Episode 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's really not a whole lot of stuff coming out this summer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_04]: Armored Core is going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Armored Core Formula.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pop Oculus.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Dead to Rights will be coming out for the PSP as well in July or June, I believe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I haven't heard anything about Star Wars yet, The Revenge of the Sith.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that got pushed back.
[SPEAKER_04]: And same with...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Midnight Club 3, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: DS, on the other hand, DS is starting to pick up a little steam here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, they've been slumping through the past few months, so they're starting to pick up a little steam.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got GoldenEye, Kirby, Canvas Curse, Bomberman, Meteos, Tom Clancy, Splinter Cell all this month.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nanostray.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Nanostray in July, along with Spyro Shadow Legacy also coming out in July.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can kind of see that it's starting to pick up a little bit of steam, whereas the PSP is in that...
[SPEAKER_05]: At least in my opinion, now everybody's got a different opinion, but for me and the games I'm into, PSP's slumping right now, whereas DS is finally starting to pick up steam.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but the PSP is going to be getting a lot of play in my house from me when Popokoros comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aren't you getting sick of this crap, though, where the launches put all their games out for the launch titles and then it's dead for like four months?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm honestly kind of looking forward to seeing Sony get screwed over for their arrogance.
[SPEAKER_04]: That right there, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: See that right there?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what's going to make the revolution rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, if the next-gen systems pull this same crap, it's going to be over for one of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not usually one for resting on your laurels, but Nintendo has always had, even though they haven't been at the top of everything, they've had the staying power.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are stable.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, again, this backs up what I said last week when I said I don't think that it's such a bad thing that revolution wasn't shown at E3 because I think they're taking their sweet-ass time so that they can.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they can.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're doing it because they can, because they know.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have been a trusted name for how long?
[SPEAKER_02]: Was Sony there in the beginning?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Sony was the bitch of Nintendo for a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did the sound processor for the Super Nintendo, and we're working on the TV system.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to get angry emails on that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine with me here, just for a second.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's where Nintendo's going to be revolutionized.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura's not finished.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still had a rant to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Nintendo has been there since the late 80s.
[SPEAKER_02]: There has always been a Nintendo system since, I would say, right after the... I think the Master System was out first.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just about to ask you, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Couldn't you say the same thing about Sega?
[SPEAKER_05]: They were there in the beginning, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look what happened to them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but Sega actually started off doing third-party publishing because I've got some Sega games on my Clicovision.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they went, and they were pretty strong, but I think that they sort of shot themselves in the foot with the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was there early, it was out, but they needed to market it a little differently, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they actually really got fucked over by the fact that Sony said, hey, we're going to jump in the market too.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is what screwed over the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a matter of timing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, I was going to say, imagine if you will, because this is why the revolution is going to rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to build Delim to your DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put it in sleep mode and take it with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on, though, anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got a lot of news to get through tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dirge of Cerebrus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cerebrus?
[SPEAKER_05]: Cerebus.
[SPEAKER_05]: My horrible pronunciation skills coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or as we call it, Vincent May Cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Final Fantasy VII sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Import Website is up and you get new downloads and you get more information on the story and everything going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can check that out at square-enix.co.jp slash games slash ps2 slash dcff7 Now obviously you probably weren't writing that down so just type in square-enix.co.jp You have no idea how big my Vincent fangirlism has been.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a directory of something like 3,000 doujinshi official art, fan art, pictures of Vincent.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I lost them when my hard drive crashed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was a scary fangirl.
[SPEAKER_05]: When I played through Final Fantasy VII the first time, I never got Vincent.
[SPEAKER_02]: GameStop is already taking pre-orders for Halo 3
[SPEAKER_05]: which kind of doesn't surprise me considering every time I buy something at GameStop or really any store these days, they always want me to pre-order something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Would you like to pre-order?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's smart.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand, but it's just... You know, the thing is, though, is by getting your pre-order in early, you're guaranteed for shipment?
[SPEAKER_05]: I personally don't do it because I'm a very spontaneous person and I like to buy games, just walk in, and I feel like buying this day.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not a big pre-order person.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really not.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I have never been denied a game I want.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: So what do you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is there any merit to this?
[SPEAKER_05]: I go, no, this is BS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's just a mistake, just like, what was it, they had marijuana.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was exactly what I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Target.com was selling marijuana at one point, which was some web kid's joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think you can really trust Walmart.com as your source for gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, I would have heard about it already because it would have been announced.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would have had to put it on my list.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways, the thing is for, what was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo 3 is coming out when the PS3 is put out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will buy the Xbox 360 when Halo 3 is out because there's a better chance that the Xbox 360 might get its first price cut before then in order to entice sales of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not going to matter at my house.
[SPEAKER_02]: We get them all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of which, since we're talking about stuff in vendors and all that wonderful stuff, PSP, there's rumors about it actually getting a price cut to $200.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the reason why they are saying that this is going to happen and...
[SPEAKER_04]: Best Buy and EB Games are now stocking the official stuff like the Sony headphones, the little soft case.
[SPEAKER_04]: The 32 meg memory stick card and the battery chargers, they're all sale individually, which this stuff's usually bundled with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if there's going to be a non-bundle, then it's going to drop in price.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, logically, but okay, that's...
[SPEAKER_05]: All good, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then at the same time, it doesn't make much sense because you have to have a memory stick with a PSP, so you're going to end up buying that separately.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to have some type of charger, so you're going to end up buying that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, if I think what's going to happen, though, the charger, I could see maybe a replacement memory stick as a replacement.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think if they were going to do one, it would be just system, memory stick, charger.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Sakura, what do you have to tell the kids about tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Today's bit of advice is how to jump from a bridge or cliff into a river.
[SPEAKER_02]: so that when people tell you to take a flying leap, you'll know what to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, kids, don't really try this at home.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't want to get sued.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, besides, if you have a cliff or bridge at home, that's just weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_02]: My advice column, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number one, jump feet first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Two, keep your body entirely vertical.
[SPEAKER_02]: Three, squeeze your feet together.
[SPEAKER_02]: Belly flop!
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Four,
[SPEAKER_02]: Enter the water feet first, but cleanse your buttocks together.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you do not, water may rush in and cause severe internal damage.
[SPEAKER_04]: My ass exploded.
[SPEAKER_02]: Five.
[SPEAKER_02]: Protect your crotch area by covering it with your hands.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, can you imagine?
Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Six.
[SPEAKER_02]: Immediately after you hit the water, spread your arms and legs wide.
[SPEAKER_02]: Move them back and forth to generate resistance, which will slow your plunge to the bottom.
[SPEAKER_02]: But my, uh...
[SPEAKER_02]: Honest final piece of advice on this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drown.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, avoid rocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like the major one right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you see rocks poking out of the water, it might not be a good idea to jump towards it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please don't do that at home.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not Vin Diesel.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't need to be jumping off of bridges.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cliff diving?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll jump off the rainbow bridge.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wowie wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did he remember to tighten his buttocks when he jumped?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll have to ask him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, please ask him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gaming companies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know that most of you guys are located in Silicon Valley, although the rest of you guys are... Some are located elsewhere in the nation, New York, wherever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Louisiana.
[SPEAKER_05]: is trying to get you to move your company over there recently passed Louisiana bill 341 it grants game developers generous tax credits if they relocate to Louisiana it was unanimously passed by the Senate it gives a 10% state tax income credit to studios that spend anywhere between $300,000 and $8 million by setting up shop in Louisiana and then remaining there for one year
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you see game companies rushing to Louisiana?
[SPEAKER_05]: It could happen if they can live through the freaking humidity.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the first thing I was going to comment on, too, is that, you know... I have been there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's one thing that Louisiana, and with all due respect to our listeners in Louisiana, I love you guys for tuning in, but let's think about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They probably don't have to blow on Nintendo cartridges down there to get them to work anymore because it's so damn humid.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you just have to deal with them resting.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, you laugh.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I laugh because it's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd have to clean your contacts with alcohol.
[SPEAKER_05]: For our buddies over in the UK, DarkSakura's got your back.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's going on for the British folk?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is about the Gizmondo.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Gizmondo is put out by a UK company.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually looking over their stats, it's a pretty, pretty impressive little system.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to play Johnny Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sort of like a game where you wail hard on your guitar and then you have like a little karaoke mode that plays sort of like
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Guitar Freaks meets Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: But basically it's going to be powered by Windows CE.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has a 2.8 inch TFT color screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually supports MPEG-4 movie, multimedia messaging, digital camera, GPRS network.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, it's looking like it's trying to really compete with the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a run over of some of the features.
[SPEAKER_02]: 400 MHz, ARM9 processor, 64-bit graphics processor, 8-way D-pad, left and right triggers, all these bajillion buttons on it, integrated digital camera, 3D game engine.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, DarkSakura, can you play pornography on it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Eventually.
[SPEAKER_05]: MPEG-4 video, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has Windows Media Player 9 on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Polyphonic ringtones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently it's also going to try to kick Nokia back under the grave.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even if they aren't already there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, but I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, this is like the nail in the coffin.
[SPEAKER_02]: Games coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Conflict Vietnam.
[SPEAKER_02]: Carmageddon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Battle Stations Midway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Total Overdose.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSX 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: FIFA Soccer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sticky Balls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Meh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rayman.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if they relocate to, you know, Louisiana, then that won't be a problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, that game Johnny Whatever, which we have pictures of on orangeelgeradio.com on my E3 gallery.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any idea for a release date for our British friends?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be good.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it's a portable system, they don't exactly have to redo the specs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that's usually why games take so long.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they have to go from NTSC to PAL and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's usually why games get delayed.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they won't have to worry about that with Gizmodo.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, and the thing is, it's like the same reason you can play PAL discs on an NTSC on your computer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's the same difference.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it really is looking like it's trying to go head-to-head with the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: And on top of that, it actually takes flash drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually see it as more, not so much PSP, but more N-Gage, what N-Gage really should have been.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like it's trying to bridge the fence.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to have to compare the N-Gage to anything, because nobody is deserving of that kind of punishment.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know... But apparently it's being put out by Tiger.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tiger used to put out all those little LCD games back in the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Tiger's been around for a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: And honestly, I honestly, honestly really think that I'm going to get a Gizmondo.
[SPEAKER_02]: After playing it at E3, and also with just the excellent show they put on, it's looking like it's going to be big.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not going to get it just because you have every other console system known to man?
[SPEAKER_05]: I am a completion whore.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will just borrow yours when you let me.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, and honestly though, it actually was pretty comfortable to play You know how some systems just feel kind of out of whack in your hand?
[SPEAKER_02]: I felt pretty comfortable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you mean the taco?
[SPEAKER_05]: Gizmondo's going to have to wait in line because I still have to pick up a PSP, but I'm interested in Gizmondo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why don't they just call it the Magic Taco Gaming System?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it would sell better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Video taco!
[SPEAKER_02]: We love the taco!
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, tell us about some hacking and cracking.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some cool stuff coming out, actually, for the PSP that you can get.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of them is actually this...
[SPEAKER_04]: Group, that's a Spanish electronica group called the Overkillers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they actually have a download, their whole music album is available now for a free PSP download.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can get that at, I would say it's probably better to go to PSPHackers.com and then find the link because the website's too long.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways, you can get it, it's like a good 63.6 meg download, so check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some, obviously, they're going emulator crazy on...
[SPEAKER_04]: The PSP, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I've noticed lately, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen a lot of gaming blogs over on 1up.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: People are posting pictures of their PSP emulated stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm almost tempted to go get a 1.0 version PSP, one of the Japanese first ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, soon enough, once that 1.5, you know, once they crack that, it's going to be heaven, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to have all the Game Boy Advance games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They actually have Neo Geo emulated on that, and that's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, definitely, if you've got a
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're lucky enough to have one, the brand new version 1.01, definitely check all this stuff out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tons of fun stuff for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, if you like more gadgety junk, they've got the PSP Shuffle, where this program you can download, and it'll actually put random content on your PSP, basically.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds kind of freaky.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Life is random.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why would you have to buy this program?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways, you can buy it if you want to, but honestly, save your time.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are consumer whores out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if you want to be random, I'm never having a problem figuring out what I can put on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to be random, put a dollar in an envelope and send it to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, that would be pretty random.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I would have money.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, that's some cool stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I know that there's been some more stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was watching the whole
[SPEAKER_04]: DS Linux, the whole thing going on with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they actually have some progress on that, and it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got on themodgods.com, and it's a site that carries a bunch of information about, you know, just, you know, DS hacking.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they actually have DS, or DS... DS!
[SPEAKER_04]: DS!
[SPEAKER_04]: Gotcha!
[SPEAKER_04]: No, dshacker.com they actually released.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they've got a whole thing...
[SPEAKER_04]: They're showing pictures of, I believe it was actually on dshacker.com, pictures of the new version of Linux that's running on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it actually has a picture of the Linux penguin with the Mario hat on it, which I thought was pretty cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's coming along pretty soon, and you'll be able to actually, you can actually download a copy of it, the Duelist 9 DS emulator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's an emulator for DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, check that out too.
[SPEAKER_04]: A bunch of cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for my final thing to leave you guys with, actually two things.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple other things.
[SPEAKER_04]: The DS, more colors, pink and red.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now you've got red that's going to be coming out for Jump Superstars, which, I don't know, is another game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not here in America?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I need to import the graphite one, because the graphite one is all shiny black.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, those are going to be coming out, and definitely check out the brand new screens for the Linux, because it'll be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And yes, DarkSakura, I did say CGA.
[SPEAKER_05]: All its cyan...
[SPEAKER_05]: Magenta, Black, and what's the other one I'm missing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yellow?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not Yellow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, Cyan, Magenta, Black, and... No, Cyan, Magenta, Black, because C is Black.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's four colors.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cyan, Magenta, and Yellow.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was White, Black, Cyan, and Magenta.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, that's awful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember Monochrome Green?
[SPEAKER_04]: How did we live?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oregon Trail, that's how we made it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, a couple more stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's talk about what's going on in some MMOs worlds right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not technically an MMO, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Warcraft 3, more of a head-to-head game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blizzard...
[SPEAKER_05]: closed over 53,000 Battle.net accounts on Warcraft 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, they were closed because they were hacking or cheating during a multiplayer session.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of them were just banned for ladder play from a month.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some were permanently removed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, man, don't mess with those Battle.net.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't mess with your games because they'll get you.
[SPEAKER_05]: and one of the granddad, now this is as old school as MMOs get here, Ultima Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do we know anybody that still plays Ultima Online?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, I don't know anybody that still plays this, but that's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ultima Online is getting another expansion.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called Mondaine's Legacy.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know that game's been out for eight years now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mondaine or Mundane?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mondaine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: You would think after eight years.
[SPEAKER_05]: August 30th is the release of this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want a free trial of Ultima Online, see what you might be missing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't make fun until you've played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have played it.
[SPEAKER_05]: UO.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still know people who are freaking playing Asheron's Call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not so surprising.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Ultima Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing I remember from Ultima Online is just because you can buy your own house.
[SPEAKER_04]: People put their horses in the house so it wouldn't get stolen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Meimoto made a very interesting comment this week in an article on CNN Money.
[SPEAKER_05]: There need to be more quick play fun games.
[SPEAKER_04]: but see the thing is with Grand Theft Auto though that is a quick play fun game same with Halo 2 actually because you can go and play multiplayer games it's fun Grand Theft Auto you don't even have to play the game you can just run around and exist in the world and it's fun and that's the whole point that's why I love that game that's why I can take Grand Theft Auto not play it for like a year and come back to it and still have fun in it and just be able to pick it right up again or even just be able to play it for weeks at a time because you can find little fun things to do in it
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo has always had, though, a family-oriented point of view.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, we have had the fair share of violent games, but for the most part, Nintendo has been, you know, they have brought out things that are kid-friendly, family-safe, you know, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendo only started getting a little more violent with that stuff, though, after they were publicly embarrassed with Mortal Kombat's sweat thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that was the laughing stock at the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you put in the blood code on Mortal Kombat 2, it would change some of the fatalities.
[SPEAKER_05]: on CNET, that the next generation consoles will kill off PC gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: The bottom line is that console manufacturers often heavily subsidize their new machines, swallowing huge losses up front in hopes that they'll make it all back selling games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is to say that once the 18-34 demographic starts buying $400 PS3s instead of $400 video cards, developers may have no choice but to follow suit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Agree?
[SPEAKER_05]: Disagree?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nah, the PC market is still going to go... And honestly, I really think that the whole PC gaming market is going to be dominated by the MMO.
[SPEAKER_02]: The more of them that come out, the more addicts there are going to be, and the more people who are going to upgrade their machine... Even I bought a new graphics card so I could play Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now it makes PSO look so beautiful.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, still...
[SPEAKER_05]: You can already play Final Fantasy XI on a console, and then Xbox 360 is going to get it too.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it looks like shit on the console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the Xbox 360 is going to be nice, you've got to give it that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but you can still always build a PC that's going to kick its ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just think that as the consoles evolve, the PCs evolve too, so I think they'll always be a place for PC games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: you pull your console out of the box six weeks later your computer technology is going to make it obsolete it's already obsolete you can build computers that use the cell structure processors they have them they've been having them they've been out for what a year now the cell processors
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they've been marketing them for all kinds of science research.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think what the article tries to say is that this kind of stuff is too expensive for most of us, but the game consoles make them affordable, I think, in a weird way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, you buy the package deal, but there are still going to be the hardcore PC people who are going to keep it alive, and the fact that the pieces are so expensive, it's just more fuel.
[SPEAKER_05]: and just right now, you can't play Xbox Live and be on IRC at the same time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_02]: I cannot do my homework playing PSO on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, who's to say that that won't change in the future with what all these next-gen systems want to do, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, you have another thought on this?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's never going to kill it off, because if you're spending $400 on a graphics card, you're a special kind of crazy anyway, so it's not going to matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, honestly, who spends $400 on a graphics card?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean... You know, if you're gonna spend that kind of money buying Alienware... Ooh, ooh, ooh, big man, buy a high-end graphics card.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Next week it's obsolete!
[SPEAKER_04]: And my $20, you know, graphics card's still, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the whole thing is, is you really don't need to spend all this money on console games.
[SPEAKER_04]: People that are playing console games are gonna still be playing console games, and people that are playing the
[SPEAKER_04]: PC games.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, because the PCs now, they're still going to get better, the graphics are going to get better, and it's still going to be one step ahead of the console systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: The console systems will get closer, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd play all of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I play them.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you're also a special kind of crazy, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why we love you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, emulators are one thing, but I have to have the stupid half-broken joystick in my hand so I can play kicks on my Atari 5200 and play it right, goddammit.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's definitely very first-person shooter-y, but they got them looking right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know, though, a bit of trivia.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know Richard Dean Anderson was MacGyver.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But dude was also in a few episodes of MacGyver, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: July is the release date for that game, so you kids look for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to bring another edition of Orange Lounge Radio to go to a close.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final thoughts, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have my headache still.
[SPEAKER_04]: It needs to go away.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I loaned out Grand Theft Auto San Andreas.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was I thinking?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reject false icons and happy birthday to the old man.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my final thought is my birthday is coming up very soon and I hope you're all going to get me something lovely.
[SPEAKER_04]: My second final thought is
[SPEAKER_04]: Vote for us on Podcast Alley.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go there now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't hesitate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because if you vote us, we get better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you feel like it's running for student council, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need to vote for us so that my ego can inflate to astronomical proportions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Need to go now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Podcast Alley.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, go vote for us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And vote every month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't just vote once.
[SPEAKER_04]: Vote every month.
[SPEAKER_02]: I, your favorite internet celebrity, beseeches you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Vote!
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Vote or die.
[SPEAKER_05]: Vote or die!
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just going to say, as P. Diddy says, vote or die.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one, you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see you next time on the Orange Lounge Radio Deco Edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio To Go edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next update.