[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of June 13th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, everybody out there on the internet who has subscribed to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition.
[SPEAKER_03]: We appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks a bunch for tuning in.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a new car!
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm moving out of my hellhole apartment.
[SPEAKER_03]: In a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Before the end of the month.
[SPEAKER_03]: My birthday's coming up, what are you getting me?
[SPEAKER_00]: and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they must be ranked in the top ten over on the alley, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, my name is Rob Roberts, of course, also known as Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're here to talk about games, and we're going to start off tonight's edition as we always do, talking about the games that we've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, how about you?
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, Phantasy Star Online, Blue Burst.
[SPEAKER_00]: The beta's over, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, actually, the beta will be over as of tomorrow, so it goes pay-to-play, and I will be...
[SPEAKER_00]: Registrating my account and canceling my Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will probably be canceling the Xbox One, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm considering starting it on the PC, but I'm kind of on the fence.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had a lot of fun with the beta, but I just feel like, do I really want to commit to this MMO?
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of do.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of us!
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish more folks would be taking that Guild Wars model, where just gouge me for 50 bucks when I buy the game, then don't charge me to pay per month anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I guess...
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Guild Wars has been doing very successful for that reason, but I guess other companies don't want to follow suit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've also been watching Dan play a lot of Fire Emblem.
[SPEAKER_00]: Lots of Fire Emblem.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's hard for me to think of the second release in the States as the second one because it's technically the third one on the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_00]: The first one was the one that Marth and Roy were from, even if you ever played Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, I know Marth and Roy.
[SPEAKER_00]: But we never got that game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, Dan found a ROM of it, and I found him an English patch for it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So he's been quite happy playing through that and getting his Fire Emblem on, and I like seeing how the games all connect.
[SPEAKER_00]: And honestly, I'm thinking about starting to play it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I hate turn-based strategy, but I would play this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fire Emblem is a game I never really got into.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just need to give it a second look, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_00]: One of the rarest games I own is the Macross strategy game on the TurboGrafx, the PC Engine Duo.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I hate that game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just have it because it's hard to get.
[SPEAKER_00]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you have Night Trap, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: And that game sucks.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, yeah, but Night Trap you can find anywhere.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I thought that was a rare one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, you find it.
[SPEAKER_00]: They say it's rare and blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not much of a collector.
[SPEAKER_00]: It has what's-her-face from different strokes.
[SPEAKER_00]: She died.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: She killed herself, did she?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, she OD'd.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know, it was years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: After being in Night Trap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_00]: Be nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: Remember, down the block, not across the street.
[SPEAKER_00]: If I were in Night Trap, I would do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: If I were desperate enough to be in Night Trap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, not really.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'd be like, okay, I have money.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's better than porn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Y'all are stupid for the stupid game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Could be worse.
[SPEAKER_03]: Could be boring.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anything else you've been playing?
[SPEAKER_00]: Only the games on the Gorillas webpage.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been playing with the darts at the toilet.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll come back to web games in a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, what have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I played a little bit, very briefly, of Tetris Worlds for the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's Tetris in eight different forms, or seven different forms, all of which are just too damn similar.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Tetris is Tetris.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I played WarioWare Twisted.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I played WarioWare Twisted about five minutes ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's fun, and it has a bunch of weird, stupid minigames in it that are just fun and just strange.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you can grade cake.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you think of this game compared to WarioWare Touched?
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't played WarioWare Touched.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I thought you had.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to pick it up, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought about picking it up, and I need to go do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, most people I've talked to that have played all the games say that Twisted is the best, Touched is the worst, with the
[SPEAKER_03]: WarioWare Twisted is a very short game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I can keep playing the same stage over and over, and I can just get unlocks that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, yeah, the thing is, though, is because Nellie was playing some of the older stages, so she was unlocking games that I didn't have before, so I go and play my game, all of a sudden there's these games, and I'm like, what the hell do I have to do here?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of fun, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XI, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to play that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still wish they'd fixed their server problem, whatever it is, because it, like...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and it couldn't load anything, so I just backed out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know what the problem is, and I know that it stopped me from playing a few times, and it's always around the same time, usually around 11pm-ish around there is when it stops.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is great, because right before that happened, Nelly was bitching at me about... Nelly, my fiancé, was bitching at me how I was playing... Not the rapper.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not the rapper.
[SPEAKER_02]: She was saying how...
[SPEAKER_02]: I was playing this stupid game and stuff and how I should, you know, come pay attention to her or something and then the game, you know, started crashing on me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, are you sure she just didn't pull the plug?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm positive because my cable modem, my cable modem is right on my desk.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a DOF attack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Denial of fiance.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, this, the game, she didn't, she was just being cranky.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, she's just like, typical, never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, seriously, typical.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a spirit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Typical woman, she's like, I didn't say it, I didn't say it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, this shit doesn't happen in my house.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to go outside, but I don't want to stay inside.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there's no in between.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't not go outside, not stay inside.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell her to go sit in the doorway.
[SPEAKER_00]: Patio.
[SPEAKER_00]: This shit does not happen in my house.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like, get your ass off the PS2, because I want to play fucking Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's never that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's just like, that'd be stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell her to take up smoking.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's been doing cross stitch, so, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: More power to her.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: My Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also checked out WarioWare Twisted for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just because I had to play the Kid Icarus stage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, damn, that's a game they need to bring back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been how many years?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why have they not brought that game back?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so upset.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they tease us in WarioWare Twisted with a level inspired by Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have the boss battle.
[SPEAKER_02]: The boss battle for the retro games is you're playing Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's like...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: None of the unlocks were really that great, but I'm kind of impressed with some of the things I'm seeing in Twisted so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that they have a lot more of the minigames.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played the Apple Shooter or whatever that thing was.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also, like, they have the Sheep County one that's pretty hard, because they... Oh, man, it pissed me off yesterday.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was, like, getting really far in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All of a sudden, the sheep stop, and then they run really fast, and they run into the wall, and then you're fucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know... And then they have, like, another one that's ski jumping that's pretty fun, and then...
[SPEAKER_02]: Space Boomerang, which is just strange.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have to play this if you get to murder sheep.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like in Lemmings, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you don't get to murder sheep.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not trying to murder sheep.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just that they smash into the wall and then you get a sheep pile.
[SPEAKER_00]: That just reminds me of a commercial.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you get to great cakes, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_00]: And carrots.
[SPEAKER_00]: This reminds me of a commercial that I saw today.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dan went on the classic video game commercial website, and they had one for a football game, as in soccer, of this old man lecturing his dog on, you know, don't let the sheep make fun of you, go out and get them, and so the dog's herding him in here, crowd cheering like it's playing with a goal and everything, and he's herding the sheep.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is coming from a woman!
[SPEAKER_00]: Smile and nod.
[SPEAKER_00]: Learn the fine art of filtering.
[SPEAKER_00]: When you start to hear the pitch rise just a little bit, say, you know, why don't we just take a moment and sit down and talk about this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Can we get away from the women are from Venus and men are Mars chat for a minute?
[SPEAKER_00]: Because I will totally admit that we're from the moon.
[SPEAKER_02]: If by Venus you mean Crazy Town, then yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, stop, enough.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, as a woman, I can vouch for this, we're nuts.
[SPEAKER_00]: But so are men, because men are stupid.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm willing to live with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can say without a doubt that I've never played any PopCap games ever.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, maybe you should.
[SPEAKER_00]: I had Neopets.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well, that's laughable, so I feel better, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I was very, very good at that bullshit game they had on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why, but I've just been all about playing Zuma and all the games that are on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And San Aquarium.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel like I'm letting everybody down by admitting that I play PopCap games because they're the same games that the 50-something-year-old women I work with play on their breaks.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're playing Bookworm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that like Apple saying, you know, we're going to put Intel processors in our PCs now?
[SPEAKER_02]: We're letting you down.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh well, alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, let's move on to some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: We want to do a follow-up to a gaming story we were talking about a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: The gaming actors, you might remember, they were threatening to go on strike.
[SPEAKER_03]: This would have to do with the voice actors.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did vote, and actually a majority voted to strike, but they needed to have a super majority in order to strike, two-thirds, and they did not achieve that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just no ordinary majority will do.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need super majority.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically right now... Is that even a real concept or is that just saying, we don't really care what you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, this is the contract.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's now going to be good through the end of 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will grant the voice actors an increase in pay up to 36% through the duration of the contract.
[SPEAKER_03]: The first raise, which will be a 25% hike...
[SPEAKER_03]: goes into effect July 1st.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're curious how much they make right now, the minimum rate for a four-hour voice acting session, $556.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's going up by 25%.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to be a voice actor now.
[SPEAKER_03]: One thing that the voice actors didn't get was the residuals.
[SPEAKER_03]: You might remember that this was a big thing they were pushing for was they want to get... If the game's successful, they want a chunk of the profits because the actors feel that they contribute to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they wanted that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did not get that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They only got the pay raise.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, well, at least it's something, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: Voices of Famous People in Your Games
[SPEAKER_03]: and so therefore when they say all in favor of you know striking's AI you are a dumbass alright moving on to a follow up from another story we did a couple weeks ago actually it was a couple months ago at this point can you believe we've been doing this crap that long GameStop and EB you might remember it was announced they're gonna merge into this powerhouse gaming store but remember as we said to sum it up GameStop and EB were not each other's competition the real competition Walmart, Target
[SPEAKER_03]: So now they're joining forces.
[SPEAKER_03]: The merger was okayed by the federal government.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's a done deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: So those of you guys that maybe work for one or the other that were a little bit nervous about teaming up with the enemy,
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, it's a done deal now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, they're the same store already.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's just like, you can literally put like a GameStop sign out from EB and it would look just like a GameStop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, one thing that you may not realize is that, and this is something I learned today, is that they advertise match.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if EB's running an ad, GameStop will match that ad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, granted, this would be, you know, some stores may not go for this, but most stores are going to do this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any, you know, store that wants to stay in business will do the ad matching.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can even take in an ad from EB Games to a GameStop and...
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember when they used to use...
[SPEAKER_02]: Engage Games going in the discount bin.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Engage is gone from Dan's store.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually overheard a guy in one of the stores.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was at one of the other stores today, and I actually overheard a guy asking for help on the Engage tech support, and I just felt like walking by going, dude, just throw it away.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop wasting your time.
[SPEAKER_00]: The taco of doom.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was just sad walking through E3 and seeing what a big, beautiful setup they had, and all of five people there, including us as we were passing through it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was trying not to make any sudden movements in case any of the Engage Arena staff might see me.
[SPEAKER_02]: You go...
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone's interested!
[SPEAKER_02]: Get him!
[SPEAKER_00]: I thought someone was heading to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like... Dude, it only took me... I swear to you, 30 seconds of playing Civilization on the N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I just had... Civilization is one of my... Probably... No, I... And keep in mind, I was addicted to Final Fantasy XI for two and a half years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Civilization, I was addicted to for a longer period.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I absolutely love that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's my favorite PC game of all time.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I had to see what happened to it on the N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_03]: 30 seconds or less, there was a guy over.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you have any questions?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: How do I do anything on this game?
[SPEAKER_03]: I cannot figure anything out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why does it suck so bad?
[SPEAKER_03]: I laughed.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what's weird, though?
[SPEAKER_00]: This game is making my stomach lighting bleed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Love Civilization 1, never got into Civ 2 or 3, even though most people consider Civ 2 as the peak of the series.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never got into Civ 2 or 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't know why.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm still curious about Civ 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Another follow-up story.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots and lots of follow-up stories tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo, you might remember that there was this rumor going around about the revolution, where they're going to be doing the downloadable games.
[SPEAKER_03]: That hasn't changed.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're still going to be offering the retro games for download in the library.
[SPEAKER_03]: No real specifics.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what did happen is that in an interview in Famitsu Magazine, Nintendo president Satoru Iwata says, you guys are making up rumors out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We never said this was going to be free.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some Might Be Free
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, obviously it's not going to all be free because, you know, let's just not make any money from re-releasing our games 50 times like we do all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I kind of found it hard to believe, too, that when you are releasing these classic Nintendo games such as, you know, Metroid, even though you can unlock Metroid through two other Metroid games, either Metroid Zero Mission or the Metroid Prime Fusion link-up, they were charging $20 for this separately.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of found it hard to believe that suddenly this game would be free on the Revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Very interesting story out of China going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: You might have heard about this online, but there was actually a fight that broke out between two individuals in China over a virtual sword.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this one Chinese guy...
[SPEAKER_03]: and I will horribly pronounce this, I apologize.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kui Chengwei was the guy that attacked Zhu Kaoyan and murdered him, basically, over a dispute over an online sword.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the parents are upset.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kui received a suspended death sentence for this attack.
[SPEAKER_03]: The virtual sword
[SPEAKER_03]: was sold to another gamer for 7,200 yuan, and that's $600 United States money.
[SPEAKER_03]: So a $600 sword got murdered over.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds like a cracking club.
[SPEAKER_02]: in Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_03]: Would you murder someone over a Kraken Club, though?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's insane.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: You gotta draw the line somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kraken Club, that's just like, you know, knees broken, I mean, because that's not even worth that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, granted, this is a story out of China, but the sad thing is, I could see this happening here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does anyone want to doubt me?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't doubt it at all because people are stupid.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, people... Life... Allow me to get a little philosophical here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Please.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, we live in a world where things are not the bright, beautiful sunshine that, you know, MTV and Teletubbies wants us to think it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, I love you!
[SPEAKER_00]: But seriously, it's not all about pop star drama and reality TV.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's an illusion.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the thing is that people are looking, you know, people understand that
[SPEAKER_00]: That we're really living in a pretty dark time right now with all the crap that's going on in the world.
[SPEAKER_00]: And even their own lives are so mundane and maybe so unhappy that people are always looking for a form of escape.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's why we watch TV.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's why we listen to music.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's why we're here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Honestly, we're here to offer that to our listeners.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it's the point where you start...
[SPEAKER_00]: Wanting to escape it to the point where you are totally immersing yourself in fantasy.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the point that it's gone on too far.
[SPEAKER_00]: When you start losing touch like that, that's when you start losing it in your head.
[SPEAKER_00]: at least there is poetic justice in this world because Britney Spears Chaotic is one of the lowest rated shows on television so at least there is poetic justice in the world I didn't mean to be down on it but that's my whole theory on this whole epidemic of people immersing themselves in all these MMOs is the fact that basically life sucks
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's have some fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you see MMOs as an escape?
[SPEAKER_00]: I see it as any form of entertainment.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll admit it.
[SPEAKER_03]: To me, Final Fantasy XI, when I was so into it, was a bit of an escape.
[SPEAKER_03]: But games in general are kind of an escape.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't let it blur the line with the real world.
[SPEAKER_03]: I realize it's fictional.
[SPEAKER_03]: But unfortunately, not everybody has that brain capacity.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Vanadil doesn't exist.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shush.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I think, though, that it's these people that get too far into it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or even, you know, get too far... I have to admit, I'm a pretty rabid, you know, Gorillaz fan, but not to the point where I can't distinguish between reality and not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where you think you're going to marry Murdoch, considering he's a cartoon character.
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I'm saying...
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a limit to that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Remember in the 80s, the screaming Michael Jackson fans and the woman who thought that she was his wife and had his baby.
[SPEAKER_00]: And to this day, she still claims to be his wife.
[SPEAKER_00]: That is losing yourself.
[SPEAKER_00]: That is going to the point of going nutso.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that's like the guy in China.
[SPEAKER_00]: They were too far into their game to be able to distinguish it from reality.
[SPEAKER_00]: And when you go that far, that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you have any feedback, comments, want to give a shout out to Jamie, or you want to maybe give her a question or whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: I look forward to seeing a counterpoint.
[SPEAKER_03]: 2go at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: We actually added a new section of our website even over at orangeloungeradio.com that says contact staff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you want to contact any of us, our emails are all right there, as well as the general address.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would like to give a shout to the people I heard from last week.
[SPEAKER_00]: To Jimmy, who...
[SPEAKER_00]: Likes our podcast and Misty's back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_00]: And to Robin from PodNova.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, hi to all you guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for writing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'd like to give a shout out to the people that have contacted me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you to VidRx for the wonderful blue pill ads.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love those.
[SPEAKER_02]: And thank you to...
[SPEAKER_02]: HotSluts.com for sending me ads.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also, I have enough free PSP offers, so no thanks for those.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, the game in question, because I'm sure you guys are curious, what game was this?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the actual game called Legend of Myr 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: So not something I've heard of here, but it must be more popular overseas.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think I have heard of that one, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not me.
[SPEAKER_03]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think a good follow-up piece would be DarkSakura is on a roll here, so I think she needs to start dishing out her advice column here because, you know, we here at Orange Lounge Radio, we're not just here to talk about games all the time because if we talked about games all the time, we'd have no time to go sit in the doorway.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we are here to better your life with the advice column because you need to go outside once in a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: And who better than our one and only DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, what are you going to give the kids some advice about tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: Today's piece of advice is how to survive when lost in the jungle.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is helpful.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Number one, find water.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you do not have the means to purify water, cut sections from large water vines or cut banana trees to capture the water welling out from the stalks.
[SPEAKER_00]: Only drink water from streams and rivers as a last resort as this water will most likely give you diarrhea.
[SPEAKER_00]: Number two, eat only foods that you can peel or cook.
[SPEAKER_00]: Avoid brightly colored plants or plants with a milky sap.
[SPEAKER_00]: Many of these are poisonous.
[SPEAKER_00]: Insects, grubs, and raw fish, except those with bristles or spines rather than scales, are safe to eat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Peel fruits before eating.
[SPEAKER_00]: Peels may harbor diarrhea-causing bacteria.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, my final piece of advice?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Stay out of Brazil.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless... We might have listeners there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Be nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless, of course, you can't go... I mean, in the jungle.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't go to the jungle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't go to the jungle unless you can't, you know, go.
[SPEAKER_00]: And watch out for dinosaurs.
[SPEAKER_00]: And bring toilet paper because you might breathe and catch diarrhea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Be sure not to slip on the diarrhea in the jungle.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's more usages of the word diarrhea than we have allotted for this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, did you have some stories you wanted to share with us tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know you're excited about this PSP hacking thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: As it's been rumored all week, PSP, everyone's looking for a way to run homebrew applications on version 1.5 PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: For those not in the know,
[SPEAKER_02]: The version 1.0 PSPs were the very first ones launched in Japan and all the US ones were version 1.5.
[SPEAKER_02]: So all of us over here, unless you actually import a 1.0 version PSP, you can't run those cool emulators and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, now there's this one website stating, yes, they found a way and they're going to launch it on...
[SPEAKER_02]: June 15th on the 15th hour.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I get it.
1.5.
[SPEAKER_02]: The website, only4.info, they have a video on there that's showing a version 1.5 PSP running.
[SPEAKER_03]: The number 4, only 4, or only F-O-R?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's only and then the number 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: All one word, .info.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they have a video, people are of course saying, oh it's fakes, and people are saying, oh it's real.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess you'll find out on Wednesday when this is actually launched.
[SPEAKER_02]: And supposedly they have a tutorial on how to make programs to run in version 1.5.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it only works in version 1.5 because whatever the hole is was fixed in version 1.51.
[SPEAKER_02]: So hopefully you haven't upgraded your PSP to anything above 1.5 because otherwise you're screwed.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this makes a lot of sense since also they have some brand new stuff for the PSP homebrew stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like for example...
[SPEAKER_02]: X-MAME was released for the PSP, and that's MAME for your PSP, so you can play all your favorite arcade emulators.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then also there's emulators now out for the Game Boy Color, for the Mega Drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: for Neo Geo Pocket.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just tons of stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And hopefully this will happen and we'll see this being able to play these homebrew applications.
[SPEAKER_03]: So when you go to this website on the 15th, either you're going to find the holy grail here of emulation on the PSP, or you're going to find your computer filled with spyware.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because this would be a practical joke.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it sounds pretty legit.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be, it'll be everywhere on the net if this is the case because it's going to just
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a big thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure you will bring us a full report.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also, on the other portable end, we have DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Space Invaders for the DS, and they're actually playing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I believe they're running on Linux, because they have Linux running for the DS right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: When's it going to be installed on a toaster?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you hear this story from earlier this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't have the article up in front of me.
[SPEAKER_03]: For some reason, I forgot to pull it up for tonight's stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But PlayStation 3, they're saying, will have Linux installed on it by default.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 3, their hard drives will come with Linux installed on them because they're not being included.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they said that you would be able to install other operating systems such as Windows and Tiger, which would be the Mac OS X.
[SPEAKER_02]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see here, we've got also details that the Nintendo DS outsells the Sony PSP and PlayStation 2 combined in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's actually sold that well, and you can probably thank that to Nintendogs, because Nintendogs rocks.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I think it's going to be a big thing here too.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nintendogs actually has a little epidemic attached to it, sort of catching on the way Pokemon, you know, the little shaky ones...
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, um, they're, you know, it's like I was talking to the guy at E3.
[SPEAKER_00]: They'll be, the boys start playing Nintendogs to pick up girls.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because the girls were all playing it and their little puppies would bark at them.
[SPEAKER_00]: So the boys' doggies would bark back.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, what's going on in the UK?
[SPEAKER_00]: National University of Singapore by a mixed reality lab.
[SPEAKER_00]: And what they were doing, they're having it, they're using GPS, Bluetooth, virtual reality, Wi-Fi, infrared, and sensing mechanisms trying to create a virtual world.
[SPEAKER_00]: So these people are wearing these hats, these goggles, and it's actually putting the dots in front of them and they're running the maze.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, it's pretty cool, you know, there's pictures in the
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: That was just kids running in the street pretending to be ghosts and stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think I think that to you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: The virtual dots that project in front of you, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the new part of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen the GPS-based Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, this one, yeah, they were using more of a radio sensor, and there were people actually dressed up as Pac-Man, and people dressed up as the ghosts.
[SPEAKER_00]: being directed by people basically functioning as the AI.
[SPEAKER_00]: And this was done in New York because they actually had it sectioned out around Central Park where it all mapped out to exactly the Pac-Man grid.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I thought this was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: And what they're doing is also an experiment on the whole GPS system, but also on integrated gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, thanks for that report.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on, you might have heard about the Halo movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Microsoft's been shipping out the Halo movie like mad this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: They sent folks dressed up in Master Chief outfits to deliver the scripts to the studios.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_03]: They wanted $10 million plus 15% of the box office revenue, and they wanted a heck of a lot of control over the film as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: They wanted all these seats for the premiere.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, granted, some of this could be rumor, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: But the internet's saying they wanted seats for the premiere and they wanted control over the actors that were going to be in it and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they got some of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Two studios actually teamed up, Universal Pictures and 20th Century Fox.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to offer $5 million and 10% of the initial box office revenue.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll be looking at more formal details announced a little later on when all the T's are crossed and I's are dotted.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you can look for a joint studio, Halo the Movie Productions.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure it'll be decent since it's got a pre-generic storyline.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need a decent video game movie, but this could be a good trend because Silent Hill's looking good, Halo has a lot of potential, Spy Hunter... Two words when it comes to a Halo movie.
[SPEAKER_00]: Starship Troopers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Starship Troopers wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'd be fun to... What was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Spy Hunter.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's being worked on Universal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Granted, The Rock's getting it, but The Rock's now becoming a more legitimate actor, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: It could be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't think there's a lot to work with with Spy Hunter, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you have a lot of room to... With Spy Hunter, there's not a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got the car.
[SPEAKER_03]: With Halo, you've got a very intricate story between Halo, Halo 2, and Microsoft, in fact, wants to make sure that their story does not get screwed up by the movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was very important to them because they are going to do a Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a big duh.
[SPEAKER_03]: They want to make sure this movie isn't going to F that up.
[SPEAKER_00]: We don't want to run into Resident Evil syndrome.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I'd love to see, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Red vs. Blue, the movie.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a chupa thingy!
[SPEAKER_02]: They should totally, and I would, because Red vs. Blue has kind of become the spokesperson for Halo, sort of.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what they should do is have, you know how they have cartoon movies, you know how they have the little mini-cartoon?
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a Red vs. Blue little intro movie or something, that'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: I wonder if there's actually been any updates to Red vs. Blue, because I haven't watched it since the second season.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have new seasons, but yeah, anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm surprised a lot of these things like Red vs. Blue, Homestar Runner, Strangerhood, I love the Strangerhood.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm surprised they just don't all team up and start their own dang network, honestly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would watch it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would... Okay, honestly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Red vs. Blue.
[SPEAKER_00]: Internet TV Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Red vs. Blue, The Stranger Hood, all these.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do a damn show on G4.
[SPEAKER_02]: G4 has some really weird stuff that doesn't really fit with that gaming network.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like their whole import car thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's something that should be on MTV.
[SPEAKER_02]: Put this stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's done for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just publish it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The end.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess it just doesn't sell.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, you got a really quick update for us on Liberty City?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yes, Liberty City stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: Grand Theft Auto, there's a story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because basically, another magazine has leaked information.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the magazine in question this time was the official PlayStation Magazine UK edition.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, there's some more UK news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, and if you...
[SPEAKER_02]: And for our wonderful podcast listeners, if you mosey on down to OrangeLaunchRadio.com, you can see that in our little read more section, I have included six packages for your enjoyment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those packages being scans of the actual magazine so you can see the wonderful in-game shots.
[SPEAKER_02]: Start moseying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, it's going to be just like Grand Theft Auto 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be in Liberty City.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, you play as Tony Kipriani.
[SPEAKER_02]: and a 1998 Liberty City.
[SPEAKER_02]: So some of the stuff is going to be a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have the same targeting system, motorbikes, as in the later games.
[SPEAKER_02]: The missions are going to be a little bit shorter, but there's going to be more than there were in Grand Theft Auto 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And basically, one of the theories is you might be able to play your own MP3s off the memory stick on your own radio station, just kind of like the PC version.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Different packages and different secret stuff, but definitely worth picking up, and that's going to be coming out, I think, in September.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Going into a very, very different type of game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dig Dug is coming back and it's going to be on the DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called Dig Dug Digging Strike.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_03]: DS, Digging Strike.
[SPEAKER_03]: Going to be coming out in Japan on September 8th.
[SPEAKER_03]: The very interesting thing about Dig Dug Digging Strike is that they are taking elements of the original Dig Dug
[SPEAKER_03]: and mixing it with Dig Dug 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did any of you guys ever play Dig Dug 2?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure y'all played Dig Dug 1.
[SPEAKER_00]: Briefly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Barely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you ever play Dig Dug 2 with like the island and you were kind of axing off parts of the island?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a very different style of gameplay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what they're doing now, and this was actually announced in the latest issue again of Famitsu Magazine, has kind of the...
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's kind of neat, just the idea of combining two games in a new way for the DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is kind of a cool thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it doesn't look like it's whoring on the touch thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like it's using the dual screen aspect of it more than just the touch, which I think is good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of interesting, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: The DS doesn't have to be all about touching.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure they will use the touchscreen in one way or another, but I think it's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, moving on, Sega.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sega's launched a brand new community site.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called Sega Link, and what it does is allows users to create their own blogs and photo albums, and you chat with other users and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sega Link also has a huge library with online games and board games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Simple Games, Sega Classic, and Link Collection is what they call it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Sega Classic section features Windows ports of Genesis titles like Golden Axe, Phantasy Star, and it would cost you about $1.12 to play for 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not too shabby, but here's the bad news.
[SPEAKER_03]: SegaLink.jp.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a Japanese-only site right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Credit card dork in Japan.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can get a Japanese address.
[SPEAKER_03]: segalink.jp if you're thinking about going around the back door to get on that site.
[SPEAKER_03]: Might be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: What I think is interesting about this article is it's talking about the Nintendo Revolution, and of course we don't know a lot about...
[SPEAKER_03]: What the Nintendo Revolution is going to offer, but we do know now one thing that they will not offer.
[SPEAKER_03]: They are saying, and this is GameCube Advanced that is reporting this, the Revolution will not support high definition signals.
[SPEAKER_03]: From the article, quote, Nintendo doesn't plan for the system to be HD compatible as with that comes a higher price for both the consumer and also the developer creating the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want more information on that, gc.advancedmn.com I'm not sure that's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I heard that a lot of the TVs, the analog signals are going to be cut off pretty soon here where they're going to be mandating where they have to make more HD TVs versus analog TVs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me read the second part of the quote though.
[SPEAKER_03]: With the technology being built into the revolution, we believe the games will look brilliant and play brilliantly.
[SPEAKER_03]: This can all be done without HD.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think that their intentions are good as far as making it a more affordable system.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because there are people who will just go out and buy the cheaper one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, and that will definitely help sales for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: However, with the way that the market's behaving, isn't that sort of the same nail that the Dreamcast put it in their coffin?
[SPEAKER_00]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't know, don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Microsoft, it's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Microsoft and Sony are really whoring the HD thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Microsoft is saying you must make your games HD compatible.
[SPEAKER_00]: Microsoft has not made a profit on the Xbox yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm smelling some tricks up Nintendo's sleeve, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just blew it right wide open there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take it as you will.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: More to come, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: One last story tonight for you guys here.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it has to do with Final Fantasy XI because I know Loki is a big Final Fantasy XI whore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, another one from Famitsu Magazine who is feeding us with all these articles tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Final Fantasy XI producer Hiromichi Takahashi.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Tanaka disclosed that his team is currently working on a new MMO specifically for next generation consoles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Will it be a sequel to Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's unknown at this time, but it will be specifically next generation consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: And finally, I have a brief, really quick, we're going to sum it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: A few things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Television coming to DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: That looks cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that legit or is that a hack?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's legit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Two more games also coming from Capcom to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those would be Mega Man Legends and... God, I can't remember the other one.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyways, Mega Man Legends is coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the one I was happy about.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think some role-playing game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fire Emblem or something.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, the new Fire Emblem on GameCube is supposed to be really tremendous, really good.
[SPEAKER_00]: And there's been just a jump up for it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Lots of people.
[SPEAKER_02]: To be continued on a later podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: And anybody out there listening that's in the PlayStation Portable or DS, you know, home development community, please, please, please port
[SPEAKER_02]: ZZT or Megazooks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_03]: ZZT would be needed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, that's going to do it for another podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope I can beat WarioWare Twisted and I hope I can get my Grand Theft Auto San Andreas back because I need to play it and I hope the PC version is done being purchased onto my computer.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_01]: as always, reject false icons and my brand new 2002 Lancer OZ Rally completely kicks your ass and my final thought is beware, I hunger goodnight everybody, thank you for tuning in and we'll see you next time on the Orange Lounge Radio to go edition that's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio to go edition this podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com see you next update