[SPEAKER_05]: Tonight, August 10th, 2008, Ozzy Osbourne gets ready to rock Guitar Hero, Sega admits to Sonic errors, and Grand Theft Auto 4 PC is announced to no one's surprise.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello everybody out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are that video game independent podcast on the internet dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_09]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm one of the three hosts here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: The other co-hosts with me as always say hello to the one, the only, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_09]: How you doing, Jamie Summers?
[SPEAKER_03]: A little warm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it is a little warm in the studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not terrible, thank God, compared to weeks past, but just a little... I'm having geek issues.
[SPEAKER_09]: Geek issues?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or geek drama?
[SPEAKER_09]: What type of geek drama?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no, I'm just trying to figure out, essentially, how to move over my ringtones and stuff from my laptop, iTunes, to my PC, so that I can start syncing my iPhone from my PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I thought, before the show, you were talking this whole thing about Linux.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought your geek issues had to do with Linux, not the phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it does.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does, because I've decided that instead of using my PC, putting another drive on my PC, I'm going to reformat my laptop to Linux Mint.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that I can play with it and not have to worry about the Frank and Vio going... Is it Minty Fresh?
[SPEAKER_02]: You saw it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks fresh.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty and useful.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember when fresh was a word used to describe cool things?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fresh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Crescent fresh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: How are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you feeling fresh?
[SPEAKER_10]: I was fresh until this fucking pizza dripped on me.
[SPEAKER_10]: So now you're not so fresh?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: See, I think it's the curse for having white shorts.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah, it's inevitable.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a magnet for shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everything's fine, all of a sudden a rogue drop of something will hit the shorts and...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Also present, our always present fourth guest on the show, you in our chat room when you join us live on AllGamesRadio at AllGames.com when we tape Sunday nights right after the Bobby Blackwolf show at 6 o'clock Pacific.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although as of late, Bobby's been running over, eating up our time slot a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, we forgive him because he always has us on at the end of the show anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you can always check that out on AllGamesRadio live on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_09]: and SSJ100 Matt is quoting from Cifaloli.
[SPEAKER_09]: Calls, calls, calls, calls from the public.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, we always love having our chatroom on board and the regulars and always some new faces so please feel free to stop by our chatroom chat.orangeloungeradio.com while we are taking live calls and during chat hours when we're taping live on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_09]: No Phoenix Wright for reals.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really wanted to get on a trial.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is fascinating stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody should do it at least once in their life.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to be civic-dutied.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, however, I do actually, I did sit down and start playing Oendon a little bit more, and I'm still playing Aurora Faint on my iPhone, which is crack-tastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game is fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Sudoku and Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ragnarok Ragnarok Ragnarok
[SPEAKER_09]: So is that so you can run your storefront in one window and so you can quest in the other?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no, because I play on private servers.
[SPEAKER_02]: All I have to do is auto trade.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it'll vend while I am gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, it's just so that I really want something that runs a lot more efficiently.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just need to make sure that my system is going to be okay with it for me to make the switch.
[SPEAKER_02]: and right now I have to figure out because I've tried doing this before trying to get my iTunes my ringtones and contacts and everything to sync on my newer computer and so far iTunes said ah fuck it so as soon as I get that to work I can reinstall on my laptop and see how that goes
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I am considering upgrading the computer here in studio, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to talk more about next week's plan in just a minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: But since it's likely we're not going to be here with a show next week, I'm thinking about taking the time to upgrade the computer here in studio because I have my eyes on some quad-core systems and some fancy stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you can tell it's old because it's that off-white color.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because all the computers nowadays are black.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, they're black now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Black is the new off-white.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything else for you?
[SPEAKER_10]: And it also doesn't have a window and excessive lights in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything else you want to share about your gaming week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: My annoyments with my husband because he still hasn't got me The World Ends With You and he was supposed to and he didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Liar.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have it with me if you wish to play it during the break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and also there was a whole lot of GTA-ing going on in the house.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you still won all to yourself.
[SPEAKER_09]: The world ends with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: For me.
[SPEAKER_09]: For you.
[SPEAKER_09]: To have.
[SPEAKER_09]: Comments in chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dreadlock Lord says, Sky, get an Alienware.
[SPEAKER_09]: And SSJ100 Matt says, Alienware is overpriced.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just build one from scratch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm thinking of doing the scratch thing, but damn, there are some good deals in those package systems.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's so tempting.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Newegg.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to get so many nerdy emails from nerds everywhere that say I'm stupid, but I have my eye on a gateway.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's really cheap, and it's really good.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know this is radio, but I just got the look of shame twice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Listen, I have a gateway laptop.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's because you can't build a laptop from scratch.
[SPEAKER_10]: And trust me, I looked.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was going to build one from scratch, even if it's the ugliest piece of shit thing ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: As long as I built it from scratch.
[SPEAKER_10]: But no, I got this because it was an open box and it was just, price was right at the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I have a... One of my friends does a little bit of laptop tweaking and can build a Mac as long as it has the right hardware in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got my iBook.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's enough Mac for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: For the house.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually, as soon as I get money set aside for it, I'm having him...
[SPEAKER_02]: Help me with building a Mac from scratch.
[SPEAKER_10]: What kind of hardware is required?
[SPEAKER_10]: A Heen element for toast?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I want a Mac because I deal with artsy stuff all the time and I need it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, shut up.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_09]: Having edited movies on PC and Mac now, it's so much easier on the Mac.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is so much easier to edit movies on the Mac.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, look.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not every computer is meant for games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Back to games for a minute.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_10]: My gaming week was alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't play too much.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was trying to catch up with stuff that I meant to play.
[SPEAKER_10]: This week I did check out Braid because I was like, hmm, I haven't made a random purchase online yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Random!
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Buy that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I bought it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think...
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, because the big thing right now is that $15 is worth it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think everyone's kind of not really concerned whether this game's worth $15, but when these games that are $15 start selling, Microsoft goes, oh, so they'll pay $15.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, we're going to make all of them $15, and now $20.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, they'll pay $20.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll make them all $20, and now $25.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like the price of gasoline.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was just saying something about this the other day.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know how gas prices have been coming down lately, and it's about, like, what, $3.90 a gallon locally now?
[SPEAKER_09]: And everybody's going,
[SPEAKER_09]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_09]: Gas is under $4 a gallon, hooray!
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm like, that's what they want you to think.
[SPEAKER_09]: They want you to think you're getting a good deal, but you've got to remember, a year ago, it was $2.90.
[SPEAKER_09]: And even that was high.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, don't buy into that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly, and that's what's going on with this, is I think the gamers are trying to tell Microsoft, hey, listen, we're going to buy this game, but we don't expect all these games to be $15, and we're not going to fucking buy all of them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, all that being said, I think Braid is worth $15.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say it's worth $10.
[SPEAKER_10]: but that's about it and the only reason because it it's quick I mean I know you said you had a little bit of problems with it because I'm stupid and it takes me a long time to figure out these puzzles I'm almost all the way through the game and it's only been about two hours and it's just I mean there's some of the puzzles later on are a little bit tricky but the first few ones I kind of figured out what they want me to do really quick and I kind of look back at this and like okay there's going to be speed runs you can do throughout the game um
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's really the only replayability.
[SPEAKER_09]: Quickly though, because I knew nothing about Braid.
[SPEAKER_09]: Absolutely zilch about this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I might have heard it mentioned out of a game developers conference once or twice.
[SPEAKER_09]: But about the game itself, I knew nothing about it except that it was supposedly this really critically acclaimed game until I got my hands on it this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: So for those of our listeners who have no Xbox 360, what is this game all about?
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to hear the Loki version of this.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's about this dude who's going around and...
[SPEAKER_10]: Being all emo about the fact that you lost somebody and you're searching for something.
[SPEAKER_10]: And to be honest, it's like, text, text, text, I'm walking past it all.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, yeah, thank God you can bypass the story.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, but I read it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did.
[SPEAKER_10]: I read it, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: But I was just like, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: My whole thing is, like, there's one of them that sounds like, you know, he had a wife or something, but now he's going after some other chick and
[SPEAKER_10]: He left her to go find this old flame or princess or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm thinking, you're just going to realize that you lost your wife because you're an idiot.
[SPEAKER_10]: But at the same time, this guy is some crazy dude that's got a tie and walking through this world that's a ripoff of Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the game is nothing like Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: But at the same time, it is...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's got really cool, unique gameplay elements to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Portal could take notice of this, and maybe this would be perfect for Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: There are some things, though, that I did read that, you know, there's eight hidden stars in the game, which may unlock some more stuff later, which would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: But there's just... Once you're done with the game, I don't see it really going... I guess it's like Portal a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, you don't really go back.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they built the speedrun thing into it, the speedrun contest, which I thought was kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, once you beat it once, you can go through and do the speedruns.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm too stupid to beat it even once.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, this game makes you feel like a dummy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know You're smart, you got more pieces than I do
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm also trying to be a completist, so I won't continue on until... Unless that last level, because I got pissed off with it, so I just ran all the way through.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I just ran all the way through all the levels once, and then I went back and tried to beat them.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, you know, um...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would be cooler if it was longer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully they'll have some download stuff later because that would be pretty cool for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, enough with Braid.
[SPEAKER_10]: I also played this week the demo for Battle Fantasia which is like this weird medieval anime fighting game type thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've heard about that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think of it?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's pretty.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's all 3D and stuff but...
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_10]: I also got my 360 back from Microsoft being repaired.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was actually really quick, which I was surprised.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that went pretty well.
[SPEAKER_10]: I kept the old box just in case another one dies because so far a track record's been like 5 out of 6.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or 7 if you include the new one I bought.
[SPEAKER_10]: So... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm looking... Definitely looking forward this week for...
[SPEAKER_10]: by Commando.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or is that this week?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that should be fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Xbox did a good thing with this whole Xbox Live Arcade for August.
[SPEAKER_09]: Between Geometry Wars 2 last week, which I'm still playing, and Braid this week, I'm busy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've barely been touching Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the only time I played Soul Calibur at all this week was when one of the listeners wanted to do some fightin'.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which I did.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I didn't get to play a lot this week because I was actually... I'm sorry, I felt bad because another listener wanted to battle me and I was too into Braid.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just ignored all the messages that were popping up and I'm like, oh, I should go look at them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, the poor guy wants to play, he's so clever, and here I am all sucked into Braid.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, it was just this week I didn't get to play a lot because I was doing some video editing for something I'm making for work.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I also didn't get to work on the PSP website at all, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Dark Knight, Dark Knight, Dark Knight
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not bashing the Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Great movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: But why is it okay to spend $30 there, but yet $15 feels like such a ripoff?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's apples and oranges.
[SPEAKER_09]: I get what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: I completely understand what you're saying about the whole you don't want to set a precedent for Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because especially the fact that, okay, then there's games like Fusion Frenzy 2 that cost, what, $50?
[SPEAKER_09]: That entertain me for 30 seconds.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're out of time for the logo to get on and off the screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a retarded argument.
[SPEAKER_10]: I understand what Penny Arcade was trying to say, but it's fucking a retarded argument.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, well, let's go to Disneyland, because you can spend a day there.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's about eight hours, and you spend $100.
[SPEAKER_10]: So let's charge $100 for every fucking online game, because it's over eight hours of entertainment.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, however, however, I can absolutely disprove that there's any validity to that argument, because going to Disneyland is like paying for 30 MMOs.
[SPEAKER_09]: And going to Disneyland has Space Mountain.
[SPEAKER_09]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_09]: End of argument.
[SPEAKER_02]: California Screamin'.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: You pay $50 for console games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why can't you pay $50 for this online game?
[SPEAKER_10]: I know it's only 6 hours long or 8 hours long, but some console games, because they suck, are only 8 hours long as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Has anybody, a quick, quick poll in chat, folks, chat.orange.radio.com, did anyone drop $10 on that crossword game?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you really need the achievement points that bad?
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't be shy, this is a real needy survey, because I want to know if anyone dropped $10 on that game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now... Because it wasn't worth it and it sends a message.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I do give them props for having demos for this stuff, which is nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what they really need to do because there's some companies, Nintendo, that don't put demos for their games up there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so you buy it and you're like, wow, this sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I get my money back?
[SPEAKER_10]: No?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, well, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not buying it anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately, there's nothing we can do about it because games like this are going to sell well and they're going to say, hey, people are going to be willing to pay this kind of money, so let's raise the price.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, well, we'll just use the excuse that my game's small and I'm an independent publisher and if you don't buy my game at $15, I don't make any money.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or, you know, oh, development costs are going up more and we need more money for this stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dude, I mean...
[SPEAKER_10]: Development costs for a game?
[SPEAKER_10]: No offense.
[SPEAKER_10]: The art style is awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: The engine is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure that took some time.
[SPEAKER_10]: But seriously, they're Goombas.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're piranha plants.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's so much more to it than that.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're just going to have to disagree.
[SPEAKER_09]: That happens sometimes when you have three people on a show.
[SPEAKER_09]: I say it's worth it and go spend the money right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nintendo will sue.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's...
[SPEAKER_09]: Nintendo has nothing to sue over.
[SPEAKER_09]: The game is an homage to Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: and Donkey Kong and other games.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, did you notice that the Donkey Kong level was called Jumpman?
[SPEAKER_09]: Which is Mario's name in Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_09]: What about stories, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, you really need to check out Braid.
[SPEAKER_09]: You really do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I planned on it and actually I added Major Nelson to my Twitter and so he put up a download code up for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you get it?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was at work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, then somebody else did.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm just saying, you know, if anyone wants to check out some of these games, you know, for free as they come up, he's doing crap like this all the time on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just pray you're first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Results of our quick poll in chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did anyone buy the crosswords game?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no, nope.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't even know there was a crossword game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Flash games, anyone?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so on.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I didn't see anyone say yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, just kind of throwing that out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, the rest of my gaming week, Geometry Wars 2, WoW, Soul Calibur, pretty much nothing else new besides Braid.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's okay, because Braid was a worthwhile expenditure this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, that's it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's get into tonight's housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_09]: My Vegas trip I talked about last week got canceled due to personal reasons.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just didn't end up being able to do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we're still, because some of us kind of banked on there not being a show next week, we may still not be here, especially because...
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: The other housekeeping thing I wanted to say, iTunes reviews.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please be so kind to leave us a five-star review on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just search for Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Leave us a nice review.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll be posting the link in chat shortly if you guys would be so kind to post some reviews.
[SPEAKER_09]: We would heart that very muchly.
[SPEAKER_09]: It helps because the more positive reviews, it helps the ranking.
[SPEAKER_09]: The higher the ranking, the more likely people are to find us.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know, nothing against the shows that are all top-rated, but 80% of them are commercial, like G4, 1UP, GameSpot-style casts that don't need that attention.
[SPEAKER_09]: What did Quiltipo say?
[SPEAKER_09]: Waterboarding.
[SPEAKER_09]: What the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no idea, but I'm just saying... It sounds deadly.
[SPEAKER_02]: We endorse thinking for yourself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Waterboarding is where you pour water over someone's face when you're interrogating them and it gives them the sensation of drowning.
[SPEAKER_10]: And apparently there's some big controversy going on in the government because they do that too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do remember reading a politically oriented story on that now.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, what we endorse is thinking for yourself and acting responsibly within the confines of your own concept of morality.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does that work?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on, we have to pause the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: We hear an ice cream truck.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: The ice cream man does not have that kind of base.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the gangsta.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ice cream man.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I had an ice cream truck, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, gaming news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you are an attractive person looking for a cool game, well...
[SPEAKER_10]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Mace Suma says, so in other words, OLR supports torture?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: We just support people thinking for themselves and doing whatever they feel is morally and ethically correct.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, some of these past episodes that we've done, well... Anyhow, Strong Bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you excited about the Strong Bad game?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I never was one into Homestar Runner.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, then screw you.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, I know you like Homestar Runner.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you going to check out the game?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hell yeah!
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm a cool and attractive person.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you going to download it on PC, Rob?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I will check it out on PC since I'm having issues.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which is a bummer because somebody I know is... I don't know how much I should say.
[SPEAKER_09]: I should be getting the Wii one, but I'm not.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to get the PC one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm still supporting it one way or the other.
[SPEAKER_09]: I get to revisit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't even watched Homestar Runner in like two years.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of one of those, oh, it's revisiting an old friend.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's my plan.
[SPEAKER_09]: I demand an Ask a Ninja game.
[SPEAKER_09]: You'll never... We'll see, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Someday.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Check that out next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meanwhile, or Monday even, you don't even have to wait a week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meanwhile, also on the Wii, Rock Band 2, and apparently they are saying that Rock Band 2 is not going to hold back on any of the features that you know from the other Rock Band games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meaning, like, download content.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, that's something the first Rock Band was sorely missing.
[SPEAKER_09]: They had to put the bonus songs on the disc and call it like a bonus exclusive.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently...
[SPEAKER_09]: uh you're going to be able to download songs do the whole online thing make your own rocker drummer whatever uh apparently this is coming from Wired Magazine Wired is saying that the Wii version of Rock Band 2 is going to be and this is right out of Harmonix's mouth fully featured DLC online play it's going to be a much more competitive product
[SPEAKER_10]: Do they know something we don't?
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm kind of curious to see what magical little thing is going to be implemented between now and whenever this game comes out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: But good news for Wii owners, especially those that want to have Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you didn't pony up the money for an Xbox or PlayStation 3 and this is all you got in your house and you want to experience Rock Band, I'm glad to hear finally you won't be...
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Games!
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura games!
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, Mega Man 9, as we know, is going to be nestastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, you've got an option to make it even more nestastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can make it flicker!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Real flicker.
[SPEAKER_02]: As a built-in bug in the game, if you so choose to activate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, for anyone who is so young that they don't know what flicker is, this is a good way to discover what we grew up with.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is awesome too because companies like EA and Ubisoft and stuff like that tend to release games that have a few glitches in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, don't worry!
[SPEAKER_10]: It was intentional for your save to get deleted.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's retro.
[SPEAKER_10]: You like retro.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, in this case, you can select if you want it on or off.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's also saying that there's going to be other types of glitches that you would commonly find.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know, I found the glitch in Mega Man 3 by myself where you can kill yourself.
[SPEAKER_02]: You jump down a hole and then you hold the left and right button so that you do the super jump and you lose all of your life and you can't shoot anything but you can still use your weapons.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you're invincible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you're dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're undead Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to say this from chat because this kind of goes along with the story.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft says Mega Man 9 will have flickers and bugs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay for NES.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why is this exciting news that we're going to have bugs in the game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, granted they're optional but why is this exciting?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's something that you can pick because the whole purpose of the game is to have the experience of playing one of the old 8-bit versions of a Mega Man game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which technically that's what it is, and if you want to have it the way the other ones were, you can have it the way the other ones were if you want to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why complain about something that you can turn on or off?
[SPEAKER_02]: That earns you the STFU award.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drive-thru, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not really so much that, but the fact that it's like, OMG, news!
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it is newsworthy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll give it that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that it's basically everyone's excited about the attention to details like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I could see that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I could give it that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still say... Fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I say.
[SPEAKER_09]: So noted.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, put that on the OLR wiki, please, that DarkSakura's official statement on this episode is...
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, one series that's been known for a few glitches at least, in fact a glitch-themed musical number that was released on the internet, Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Saints Row 2 will not be coming to the Wii, which is not surprising.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, the concerns are over controversy that a game like that may cause, and also the fact that the graphics on the Wii aren't exactly what they are on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: They basically are worried that because if you had weak controls for like chainsaws and satchel charges and stuff like that in the game that you may risk running into an adults only raiding kind of like Manhunt 2 did.
[SPEAKER_10]: but I think that's stupid that they think that scene is there's been games out there that have had similar things already and been released mature and have done pretty well like Scarface or The Godfather or I don't know No More Heroes or Mad World that's coming out so I guess we'll just leave it to graphics I was going to say isn't this game just I mean controversy aside isn't this game just kind of too much graphically for the Wii?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it then, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Why play the controversy card?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wouldn't people just accept the fact that the Wii can't handle it, period?
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, what they need to do is have... It's going to take people releasing a big-name game, like another Grand Theft Auto that's on the Wii, before companies decide, hey, the Wii's viable for that kind of game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because right now...
[SPEAKER_10]: Even though there has been some mature games on there and they're starting to get a little bit more adult content, it's still perceived as a kid's system, just like the GameCube was.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're really having trouble getting past that stigmata.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo isn't helping.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're definitely not helping with Wii music and shit like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's really going to take a big game like Grand Theft Auto coming out on it before people go, hey, we can release our game on there and actually make it for the Wii only.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, look, one thing that is certainly exclusive to the Wii that we haven't seen on other systems yet is waggling and motion.
[SPEAKER_09]: And motion's about to get even better when Wii Sports Resort comes out and the Motion Plus accessory comes out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, the Motion Plus was developed by a company called InvenSense, actually made this accessory.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, news came out this week that this Motion Plus technology exists.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is no exclusive deal with Nintendo, meaning that if InvenSense wanted to, they could take this technology to other companies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you listening, Sony or Microsoft?
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't get into details about other folks that are interested in this technology but as you might imagine of course there's more interest out there so you know rumors have been abounding for a long time that Microsoft is going to get into the whole motion game although they didn't at E3 which was the expected time personally I don't see the other consoles getting into this whole motion thing in the motion plus you know where I bet this accessory ends up turning up again PC I bet you we see some type of small scale release of this accessory on a PC
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's my thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you're Nintendo and you're concerned about having all your proprietary stuff...
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do you put out this peripheral that's supposed to make things better and supposed to make things extremely lifelike or very sensitive to your movements and then you don't make it exclusive to yourself?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's kind of retarded.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like, I made this really awesome invention that'll make our game system awesome and no one else can have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh wait, no they can.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now GameGuru in chat has a comment that's kind of along those lines.
[SPEAKER_09]: He says, but Nintendo owns the patent on the pointer and that's the big plus for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: Granted, if
[SPEAKER_09]: This MotionPlus technology were to be adapted by the other companies, they wouldn't be able to do it in that same style that the Wii does.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really, I mean, I think this is going to be like Rock Band and Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe PlayStation will adopt this technology and they'll have 12 axes.
[SPEAKER_10]: They'll just, what they'll do is they'll make something that will work exactly the same.
[SPEAKER_10]: It'll be just different enough so that they can't get sued.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Over Rondo of Blood
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to have a fight at PAX.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I said that I would win because girls play dirty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which, by the way, all three of us are going to be at PAX in like three weeks.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Three weeks from today.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are going to be flying home, but we will have just spent the weekend at PAX.
[SPEAKER_02]: He can't use the elect beam posture trick on me because the blaster master grenade trick is stronger.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gaming news?
[SPEAKER_02]: I counter with my Konami code.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ha!
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to LARP to the death.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can I?
[SPEAKER_09]: LARP to the death.
[SPEAKER_09]: 8 now and whatever the hell 9 on DS soon
[SPEAKER_02]: I know!
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is the DS one.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're talking about Dragon Quest, the Chapters of the Chosen, which is in the trilogy of The Hand of the Heavenly Bride and the Realms of Reverie coming next.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's supposed to be released in... Okay, here's what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dragon Quest IV was released on the NES in...
[SPEAKER_02]: February 1990 it was Dragon Warrior 4 over here so this is a DS remake is what they're getting and they said that they're supposed to get it on September 12th over in Europe so hey cool and you get that you know fantastic Toriyama artwork so go for it cool the end oh not just the end there's more but wait even more more money more prizes I love it anyway
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone gets a dollar if they guess what game that's from.
[SPEAKER_09]: Smash TV.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where's my dollar?
[SPEAKER_02]: I gave you a dollar before.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get a retro dollar, so I've already given it to you.
[SPEAKER_09]: What can I buy with a retro dollar?
[SPEAKER_02]: iTunes song.
[SPEAKER_10]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_10]: You can buy flashing graphics.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah, I can buy flashing retro graphics.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember things the way they used to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chrono Trigger!
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, that gets Rob's attention.
[SPEAKER_02]: There has been a kind of...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the PlayStation one came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought the Super Nintendo one never did, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think you're right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought that your update disappeared.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that was for... No, I think that's something else.
[SPEAKER_09]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_09]: What else was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was there more?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob Hart.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, but really the DS version, the things it's going to have is a touchscreen control.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can use both the dual screens, a new dungeon, wireless play of some unnamed variety.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's actually...
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's also, just if anyone is curious, there is a gallery up on Eurogamer that has screenshots.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll link that in the chat room if anyone wants to check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, chat.orangeandre.com if you want to join our chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: I knew what it was I wanted to ask you about because we were talking about old video games and collecting and all that stuff.
42.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I went to a local record store the other day that was having a big video game sale, used video game sale.
[SPEAKER_09]: I found Zelda II The Adventures of Link in a gold cartridge for $5.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that a good deal?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'd say so.
[SPEAKER_09]: I should have picked that up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I was looking at it going, wasn't that the first Zelda they remade in the gray carts?
[SPEAKER_09]: So the gold carts are really valuable?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or am I crazy?
[SPEAKER_02]: But they're neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially if you've got the box.
[SPEAKER_09]: It would be worth $5 just to have the old school cart.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can put it up on the wall in the big blank spot we have on JustinTV.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm pointing at the blank spot.
[SPEAKER_02]: The thing to watch out for those is the battery.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I wouldn't play the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have an old school Nintendo to play it on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I told you I was going to lend you one if I can find one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can't you replace the battery?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can replace the battery.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I'm right, I think it just uses a standard small lithium battery.
[SPEAKER_02]: We replace the batteries in our Saturn all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I mean all the damn time.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, all right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry to derail the current gaming news, but I just had to know good deals or not.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're doing a public service.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good deal, bad deal.
[SPEAKER_12]: Your batteries can be saved.
[SPEAKER_09]: The store was advertising a huge video game blowout.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was like five games for $13.
[SPEAKER_12]: Old NES Games
[SPEAKER_09]: They had some in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's where I saw Zelda.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, originally, before I bought you Blastworks, my intention was to go there and find an original copy of The Guardian Legend, which obviously wouldn't be there because it's too valuable, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pala Abdul Spellbound
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh god, that was the one with Rush Rush on it, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes it was, and it also had such awesome songs as The Promise of a New Day, which I was trying to play a clip of here on air, but my computer's freezing up on me, which probably is a good thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it has a taste screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Two dollars for this!
[SPEAKER_09]: Diet Coke, yo!
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, please.
[SPEAKER_10]: Promise of a new game, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: Please stop that.
[SPEAKER_10]: There is a pretty cool hack that got released this week on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it will allow you to actually play region-free Wii games with no mod chips whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_10]: This will require, though, that you have the Homebrew channel installed.
[SPEAKER_10]: And...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: and you can also remove the health warning screen that pops up in the beginning of when you turn the Wii on well thank god because that thing annoys me more than anything I believe you have to have Wii system version 3.2 I want to say so which unfortunately if you have it all the way updated now you can't use this I'm sorry I can't stop laughing
[SPEAKER_09]: at the fact that somebody actually sat there and said, you know what I'm going to do to my Wii?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what project I'm going to take on?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to get rid of that health warning screen because damn it, that thing's annoying.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meanwhile, people are starving in other countries and war breaks out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you got rid of the health warning.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: The process to patch it is safe so you won't brick your console.
[SPEAKER_10]: The only thing that will happen is if you update your console again, it will erase all these updates that you've just made to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the only problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they are working on ways to prevent that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like I said, I think it's only compatible right now with...
[SPEAKER_10]: Version 3.2 firmware.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft is saying in chat that patch is only for Europe, Loki, with patching quotes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought it was for more than just Europe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Does anyone really need to remove the health warning screen that bad?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, really?
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it that intrusive?
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe you should be reading it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else in the Wii hacking world going on that we should be aware of?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that would be it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: and what apparently Game Daily, in this interview, he says that he kind of admits in a way that Sonic has not been quite as good as it could have been.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, he didn't come out and say Sonic sucks, but there was this interesting quote.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some of that criticism is probably warranted.
[SPEAKER_09]: We definitely recognize that a franchise that has been going as long as Sonic, you have to put a huge amount of effort in to make sure that you maintain that quality.
[SPEAKER_09]: which is why you're seeing us this year take the first steps in making sure the quality is right and we're constantly looking at innovation blending classic 2D gameplay with 3D beautiful landscape rich environments and then it continues on for fans of Sonic that have been looking for the next gen experience this is the game they've been waiting for so I guess all those other games were just I like the way he does that with words kind of sweeps the other games under the table oh no no this is the game you've been waiting for right here this is the good stuff
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mean it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all I say and mean it because you only got so many chances left before people just, you know, aren't buying this anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: But then again, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: You could make 20 crappy Sonic games and if one comes out and it's really good, word will get around.
[SPEAKER_09]: People will buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just about time they say, yeah, we fucked up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to ask you, as a Sonic fangirl, I mean, general Sega fangirl in general, look at your Classic Games of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: The last Sonic game that they did right was the first Sonic Adventure, I thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I did like, what was the racing game that they had on PSP?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sonic Rush, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: That one was pretty fun, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: And here's the comment you always see anytime Sega gets brought up by SSJ100, Matt in our chatroom, chat.orangelongeradio.com Dear Sega, Shenmue 3 I liked the Shenmue series, so whatever Shenmue was one of those things that was hokey when it came out, but it aged like a fine wine It was great, and Seaman Let's play Lucky Hit Well, how about something else?
[SPEAKER_09]: How about something else?
[SPEAKER_02]: EA, I know people like to groan and everything, but here's something new to groan about.
[SPEAKER_02]: EA is going to be doing a series of games for PC and DS that is going to be off of the For Dummies series of books.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can actually, for now, download Poker for Dummies on PC off the Pogo download area.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, in theory, you're supposed to be able to.
[SPEAKER_02]: That means if it's up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's also going to be Texas Hold'em, Omaha, Seven Car Stud.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there's going to be Solitaire for Dummies, Brain Training for Dummies.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's in October.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Solitaire one's in September.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sudoku for Dummies in November.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a whole bunch more.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about Braid for dummies?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I need.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want games for smart people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want Mensa Solitaire.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then you need to go play those cruel games like I Want to Be the Guy or La Mulana or those types of games that are cruel and unusual.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I mean like poker and puzzle and stuff games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want Mensa Solitaire.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fair enough, but here's the problem I have with this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although it's cute that they have the licensing for dummies, look at the games they're putting out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sudoku, Solitaire, Texas Hold'em.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, we've got like 50,000 versions of those games across all the consoles already.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's going to make these so special besides the four dummies tagline and the little cartoon guy pointing?
[SPEAKER_02]: The fact that people are admitting to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: GameGuru suggests Sonic for dummies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Frisbee says dummies for dummies.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have for dummies everything now.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have childbirth for dummies.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have podcasting for dummies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: We didn't need that book.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're living examples of the fact that any dummy can podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: For real.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought it took a special kind of dummy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It does.
[SPEAKER_02]: It takes a special sort of self-depreciating dummy to do it every week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It takes a special kind of dummy or dare I say it, idiot to do it for over six years.
[SPEAKER_02]: And who's coming up on 300?
[SPEAKER_09]: Practically every Sunday straight.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, granted, we miss some here and there, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought we were a little crooked.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're all a little bent here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, how about release dates for Dummies?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, this week, I hope you like Madden because that's coming out on everything, including God knows why, the original Xbox.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sinkin' Island Sinkin' Island
[SPEAKER_02]: The island sinks!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, spoiler alert!
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the ship crashes into an iceberg.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Jack dies, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm glad you asked.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sinking Island is about Walter Jones, a billionaire, who is found dead at the bottom of a huge art building.
[SPEAKER_10]: A billionaire and his wife.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, this sounds a lot like Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_10]: Found dead at the bottom of a huge Art Deco tower that he had built as a magnificent getaway on a tropical island.
[SPEAKER_10]: There are ten suspects who all have a motive for Mr. Jones' untimely death, as Inspector Jack Norm
[SPEAKER_10]: 3 days before the island disappears and sinks into the ocean to find the truth behind this mysterious death and catch the killer
[SPEAKER_09]: And I hope the island does sink and you're on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: If that's not amazing enough for you, then maybe the Cheetah Girls Passport to Stardom on the DS would be your type of game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Best week ever!
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, here's actually a game that might not be so bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Space Siege is coming out on the PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, Space Age?
[SPEAKER_09]: Space Siege, like Dungeon Siege.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was thinking Space Ace in my mind for some reason.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully there will not be a movie being made for this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also this week, Imagine Teacher
[SPEAKER_10]: for you to teach your Imagine Babies.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, Imagine Teacher.
[SPEAKER_10]: Imagine Teacher.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am a teacher, kind of.
[SPEAKER_09]: I teach adults.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's my day job.
[SPEAKER_10]: This game, you actually have to create lesson plans and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm kind of curious about this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Silent Hunter 4, the Gold Edition is coming out on PC as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ford Racing Off-Road, also for the PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: And... Oh, did I forget to mention?
[SPEAKER_10]: Madden the 20th Anniversary Collector's Edition.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's a whole bunch of Madden and a whole bunch of...
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I'm sorry, and I think I didn't see it on the list, but I think I thought Line Rider 2 was supposed to be coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although, judging that I don't see it on this list anymore, it might have been delayed.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you want to check out Madden, but you don't feel like shelling out that kind of money, you could probably find Madden 05 or Madden 04 for about $2 this week at certain closeout sales.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, we've got, I want to say, 900 copies of Madden 05.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll sell them cheap.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you melt them down in a landfill or something like that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I've told them to throw them away.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, let's travel over to Japan and Asia in general.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sometimes we cover the Asian release dates as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Madden NFL 09 will come out in Asia as well the same day it comes out here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meanwhile, Tales of Vesperia, the Japanese version, also makes its way to other Asian regions this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Otherwise, in Japan itself, nothing on the Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about on the PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_09]: Same story.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's really nothing new.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're going to have to wait until the 21st when Vampire Reign comes out for something new.
[SPEAKER_09]: Moving on to the Wii, nothing there either.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a very slow week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess just not a lot of demand.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you think they're all importing Madden, or what the hell's going on?
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: This could be DarkSakura if she had blonde hair and disproportionate sized boobies and one eye strangely larger than the other.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sometimes I wish you sat on cam because that was really funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've had blonde hair before.
[SPEAKER_09]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd like to see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've seen me with blonde bangs.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have seen you in blonde hair.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did not look good at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: Coming out on the Nintendo DS, a game called I'm sorry, it's not a game, it's an accessory.
[SPEAKER_09]: Accessories for your DS to make it look like Stitch from Leo and Stitch or Jack Skellington.
[SPEAKER_09]: That looks kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or Poo from Winnie the Pooh.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can check those out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Otherwise on the DS, there's no games coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can make it look like poo.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a really slow week.
[SPEAKER_09]: On the PSP, Crazy Taxi Double Punch, which I thought we talked about last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It must have gotten delayed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, Memories of Sword of Kata is coming out on the PSP from Cyberfront.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it looks to be another game starring Anime Girls.
[SPEAKER_09]: StrongBad's Cool Game for Attractive People Episode 1, Homestar Ruiner on PC and Wii
[SPEAKER_02]: Fable 2 Pub Games on Xbox 360, Ferrari Challenge on Wii, Madden NFL 2009 on Xbox 360 and Wii, Puzzler Collection on Wii, and Table Football on Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's a Wii-tastic week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Madden.
[SPEAKER_02]: All I've been hearing about that is Madden since my husband has to work the launch.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: You know my calendar, I have the Freakonomics calendar.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually stated why they wanted it specifically to be August 8th, 2008 to have the Olympics open is because eight's a lucky number in China.
[SPEAKER_09]: For both And that and women swimming
[SPEAKER_09]: Is women's volleyball still got the same outfits they had four years ago?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: All those women are kind of like female gym teachers anyways, and no thanks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, though, I actually have to crack up because I want to see if anyone makes the same mistake that the target shoot guy did last year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And to hit the target beyond his target, that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, he did not hit his target.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is Geena Davis going to be doing archery this year?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thelma is an archer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was going to say my favorite events are the ninjutsu events.
[SPEAKER_10]: The what?
[SPEAKER_10]: The ninjutsu events.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have ninja events?
[SPEAKER_09]: I like fencing.
[SPEAKER_09]: You never see them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: He likes curling.
[SPEAKER_09]: Curling is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the best part of DECA sports.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the best part of the summer event.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gaming news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've made the announcement that it's coming out October 21st in the US.
[SPEAKER_10]: October 24th in Europe.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, of course, along with that, you're going to be getting the Fable 2 Collector's Edition, which includes some, I guess they're like tarot cards, a bonus DVD with some behind-the-scenes stuff, also a little figurine,
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you pre-order your games now, as Jamie mentioned, the Xbox Live Arcade Pub Games will be available starting August 13th.
[SPEAKER_10]: One other cool thing, though, that you get with the limited edition is Master Chief, created in Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: As opposed to Master Chef.
[SPEAKER_10]: Using the character creator.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I suppose.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although he looked a little weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's kind of like taking a character that looks kind of like him and calling him Master Chief.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, they had something like this that they did during a demonstration at E3 where they created a character like this and I guess they kind of tweaked it a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: He has a lot of belts.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of belts.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I'm getting the limited edition because I like crap like that
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I apologize in advance if I'm horribly mispronouncing the name of this thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Onichambara?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that what that's called?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's correct.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: My Japanese is getting better.
[SPEAKER_09]: But just disregard that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You might want to know this game as Bikini Samurai Squad.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's still Onichambara.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's just a subtitle.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever, but look, it's chicks, and speaking of women's volleyball outfits, it's chicks in bikinis wielding swords.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, hello, do you need anything more in a video game?
[SPEAKER_09]: The only thing this game is missing is zombies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh wait, I think they have those too.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're battling a zombie horde.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, do games get any better?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think not.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a chick wearing lingerie with a cowboy hat.
[SPEAKER_10]: You forgot the cowboy hat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: And she has a samurai sword killing zombies.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank God it's finally here.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is coming out over here.
[SPEAKER_09]: D3 Publisher is going to port the game to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: in hopes that people everywhere will bow down to women with swords and bikinis slashing zombies.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, sound like your kind of game?
[SPEAKER_03]: That sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, it does sound like fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you don't want it on 360, remember they do have the Wii version coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wii!
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I almost brought my Wii today to view that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next week, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or whenever.
[SPEAKER_10]: I must see this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, we should just have a special playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And make that our pre-recording.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, that might work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get that game imported or whatever you gotta do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: I already have it, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_02]: Other news!
[SPEAKER_02]: We've been sitting around speculating about why Final Fantasy XIII is going to be coming out on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Microsoft has said something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, one of their marketers, Albert Penelo, said that it was actually the Xbox 360 sales.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had speculated before.
[SPEAKER_02]: were what would bring Final Fantasy XIII to the system.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said that they didn't really make any sort of behind-doors deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't offer a lot of money for Squeenix to break their exclusive...
[SPEAKER_02]: Exclusivity contract.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't speak today.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've had a crap week.
[SPEAKER_09]: They offered the market share.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what they offered them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox 360 does have the superior market in the United States.
[SPEAKER_02]: So far, they've had more term on it, more sales overall.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're actually stating right now that that was the specific reason that Square said, you know what, let's just do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's put it out on the 360 in the US.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they also are committed to a simultaneous launch for both of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: But their speculation is that it's going to hold up our PS3 release date in the US.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, depending on how long they've had this idea forming, they may have already started work on the port.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can hope so.
[SPEAKER_09]: They swear they haven't, and they're not going to, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw the note on there that says they haven't begun work on the 360 version yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it could be a lie.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: It could be a lie.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't have to tell us the truth.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think that they... What they do when they start programming these games is just... You're not going to have, oh, we are going to do everything on this dev kit.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you're going to start your textures in whatever your 3D program is.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to start laying out your scripts and other programs.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got to come together on a PC or Mac or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe they do it in Linux, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, whatever way, they have to come through it on some sort of computer to get everything together, and then it's made compatible with the hardware given.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think it's not going to be that difficult, especially since we've seen plenty of ports from one system to the other that didn't lose all that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let's get some comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: JV Mon says, I don't mind Final Fantasy XIII being delayed if it means I get it on the 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kel Tipo says, Final Fantasy XIII seems so far off at this point, another delay doesn't seem so bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of how I feel.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's that little spark way off in the distance that, you know, I'm kind of not expecting to see this game before Christmas next year anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com if you want to join us on this Sunday night as we tape on AllGames.com as we always do.
[SPEAKER_09]: 6 o'clock Pacific time on Sunday nights, except for next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got the classic game of the week coming up in just a couple more stories in our break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then part B, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Besides, I have one question for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is better than Final Fantasy XIII?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'll answer that with another question.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you smarter than a fifth grader?
[SPEAKER_10]: Damn straight, that's coming to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_10]: Game of the year right there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Will it have Death Foxworthy?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, it will have CG Death Foxworthy.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks like a zombie, by the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can a fifth grader beat Braid?
[SPEAKER_09]: If so, I'm in trouble.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this going to be one of their massively online games they were teasing at E3, like 1 versus 100?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm going to guess this is going to be a crappy port of the Wii game that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it is being put out by THQ, which I do think they are putting out the crappy game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yeah, it should be coming out sometime after all the cool games come out on Xbox Live Arcade this month.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, wait, it's Xbox Live Arcade?
[SPEAKER_09]: Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's kind of interesting, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I can embarrass myself and my friends online with what I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although usually I seem to watch the show and I seem to do okay on the show, but sometimes there's like a world history question that I just don't get because history was never my strong subject.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, he's just creepy looking, man.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously, it's like, if you get this question wrong, I'm gonna jump through the TV and eat your brain.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look how small his head is!
[SPEAKER_02]: His head's shaped like a cantaloupe.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna show the chatroom what his head looks like, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at his head!
[SPEAKER_09]: Dark Tetsuya says, bye, give me the mole on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: Reality games on Xbox Live Arcade, I don't think that could happen, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're too psychological intensive.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, speaking of Xbox Live Arcade games, we've been talking a lot, a lot, a lot about Braid tonight, as a lot of people have been talking about Braid.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's very interesting, though, have you checked out the official walkthrough for Braid?
[SPEAKER_09]: The creator, Jonathan Blow, actually put up an official walkthrough for Braid.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's available at braid-game.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: solve the puzzles yourself and stop using a walkthrough you stupid dork all the puzzles in Braid are reasonable if you're having problems solving a puzzle don't give up please do not use a walkthrough don't give up thank you for your time
[SPEAKER_09]: and yet might I point out the irony that currently this game is sitting at number 3 on the most requested FAQs on GameFAQs probably from people feeling as dumb as me however I will say though there are rewards to be got from this game like any game from not using a walkthrough that's not going to stop some people that want to know the story and there is going to come a point where I'm just not going to be able to freaking resist but I do like the little trick played on us by the official developers I thought it was cute if nothing else
[SPEAKER_09]: And that was something I found, by the way, on Major Nelson's Twitter, which you were saying earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been putting that to major use.
[SPEAKER_02]: That and there's some pretty funny stuff that he posts every so often.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should also add on the Xbox staff, Trixie's there.
[SPEAKER_09]: She posts a lot more random stuff, but she's a good read, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a lot of great gaming people on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's like the place where everybody's at right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have Twitterific on my iPhone.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's so many other indie game podcasters I'm following on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Godfrey, GamerEaty, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_09]: Off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, on top of that, there's other famous individuals on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Will Wheaton has a Twitter.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I've been reading that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, Obama is following me.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's how I found his Twitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was like, dude, I'm not even anything on there that says anything about being Democrat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a libertarian.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I'm voting for him.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Danger, danger, political discussion, danger.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know it's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can say who I'm voting for.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's fine, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's get into other topics, though, like your vote for the classic game of the week that all the kids should be playing this week because every week you like to pick a game from the archives.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this week, as I understand it, we have a nice change of pace.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not Sega-related this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just messing with you.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, here it is, folks, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: What should the kiddies be dusting off and playing this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this also wins the About Damn Time award, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because the game that I picked is Tempest 2000.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tempest 2000 is one of the only good games on the Atari Jaguar.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is the only Atari Jaguar game that I have ever used in this segment.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm actually referring to the Sega Saturn version, which is the one that I have.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, screw a bunch of the Atari Jaguar.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have played this on the Jaguar, believe it or not, and I endorse it on the Jaguar.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a good time.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just have to play the music.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's take a listen to some of the hot techno music in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Super Zapper Recharge.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, tell us a little more about Tempest 2000.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if anyone's ever played the original Tempest, it was a vector game that was put out by Atari.
[SPEAKER_02]: where you go on a series of different shaped fields and you can only move left or right for yourself but you'll have like ones that look like a V or some that look like a giant octagon or the first stage is basically a straight plane but this one other than just shooting the little ships as they approach your ship on this plane you have other little goodies added
[SPEAKER_02]: You also have spikes that come up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the spikes were in the original, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to shoot the spikes all the way back down to the bottom.
[SPEAKER_02]: If the enemy ship gets up to the top of the plane, they can catch you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, what they've added to this one is you get a particle laser so that you can shoot faster and more energy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can gain points.
[SPEAKER_02]: for bonus ships and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can get a jump power-up, so you can jump over the enemies when they're on the top line.
[SPEAKER_02]: An AI droid, which is just this little vector cube that follows you around and shoots.
[SPEAKER_09]: A warp token, so you can... Wait, wait, wait, we have to listen to this part.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, this version does have the voice, did it?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it says it really quietly.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Super Zapper recharges it on the...
[SPEAKER_09]: Super Zapper Recharge is the best part.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do we get to see the bonus stage in this clip?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that part of the game always tripped me out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: It had the weird ambient music too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me turn it down a little bit because those gunshots are getting a little annoying.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you also, as you go through, you can get warp tokens to travel to different stages.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can also get a power-up to destroy all of the enemies that are on the screen and move you to the next level.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called Outta Here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get one that, well, the female voice in there goes, yes, yes, yes, when you get this power-up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you get it when you're warping off a completed one.
[SPEAKER_02]: So when you start your next level, the first power-up that you get is an AI droid.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it says, yes, yes, yes, but in that really high-pitched sort of, oh, baby way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Eat electric death.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you use your giant zapper thing, it says, eat electric death.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just happened in the clip here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Eat electric death.
[SPEAKER_02]: Caught you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guy died.
[SPEAKER_02]: and when it says catchy, it goes, whoa!
[SPEAKER_02]: So we've also got other versions, like this particular music that we're playing here is like I said, the Sega Saturn version.
[SPEAKER_02]: It did first come out on Atari Jaguar.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a PlayStation version that's called Tempest X3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's supposed to be updated graphics and music, but it's, I don't, actually I don't think it's as much fun
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, however, if you are, if you put, in all caps, Y-I-F-F exclamation point on the high score table, you get to play the original Tempest 2000.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it doesn't save any of your high scores, so that's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: They also have this on PC, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, there's a PC version, which I've got it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, there's also, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Space Giraffe Space Giraffe
[SPEAKER_09]: It was kind of funny, like it had its moments, it was really funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the problem I had with it is that graphically the game was ruined.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, how graphics can single-handedly ruin a game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the same problem I had with Tempest on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: They remade the original Tempest, did this whole remake of the original Tempest.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was missing that... There's a Tempest 3000.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's that X factor I can't put my finger on that Tempest 2000 had that the Tempest on Xbox Live Arcade most definitely doesn't have.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do have to tell you one thing, though, that I do really like about the PlayStation version, Tempest X3, is it used the NegCon.
[SPEAKER_02]: The NegCon for the uninitiated is, it's a Namco controller that you, it's separate in the center so it twists.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was made for Wipeout and other racing games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have four of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: It took me forever to find them, but I have two Japanese ones and two American ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, but, um, the other thing, um, that I think is interesting is that anyone likes the music in this one, um, it was actually done by Imagine Design, which is now Brilliant Development, and they did the music for Jaguar games Alien vs. Predator and Battlemorph.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um, and I do recall Alien vs. Predator actually having some pretty sweet music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, you can also use the Jaguar's rotary controller on this, too, so you can get your sort of unschooled.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do we say about the Jaguar?
[SPEAKER_02]: It sucked!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know what, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there were other, there were, there was another couple of good games, but I think they were also remade, original games too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, anything that was on the Jaguar, it was good, it was probably remade.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at any rate, there have been people who actually went out and made a rotary controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can find them online somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: And people have modified old 2600 controllers and they're doing them too.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, it was designed by Jeff Minter.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I say go check out some of his other contributions too, even though he did give us Space Giraffe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so that's it then.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tempest 2000, Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was really just trying to talk a whole lot so you could keep your music playing because I like your music.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the clip's about up, so there you have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your Classic Game of the Week, Tempest 2000.
[SPEAKER_09]: Favorite thing about the game in a nutshell?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's not a favorite thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the entire package.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the whole thing is one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will accept that answer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, that's going to do it for our Classic Game of the Week and for Part A here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stay tuned, guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be right back after a quick free break with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: There are a couple of other things I just tell you when I remember.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you could not see the similarities in the personalities within the first couple of episodes, you need brain surgery.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Slappy.
[SPEAKER_11]: How?
[SPEAKER_11]: You didn't have to hit me so hard.
[SPEAKER_11]: It wasn't that hard.
[SPEAKER_11]: Find out on Anime Jam Sessions with your hosts DJ Ranma S and Kuro Usagi.
[SPEAKER_11]: Log on to DJRanmaS.net slash Anime Jam or look up Anime Jam Sessions on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_09]: How should people celebrate Pyramid Head of Rape Appreciation Day?
[SPEAKER_09]: We should have a rape carnival.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell them to rape things because rape is funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Walk around the neighborhood and rape cats in your neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold a plastic knife.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to have a plastic knife.
[SPEAKER_09]: And take pictures.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ladies and gentlemen, rape isn't funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unless if it's clown rape.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rape of people is not funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rape of monsters is funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because monsters are bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: And when bad people... What?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just not going to keep going down this line.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm digging myself a hole.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: The video game podcast where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because the army was using Halo on a sniper base to do one thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: To get the snipers prepared psychologically to be willing to kill as snipers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, except that asshole.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a direct causal link between interactive gameplay of violent games and real world increased aggression and violence in adolescents and teenagers.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't even fucking make sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: Welcome back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: August the 10th, 2008 is the night we are taping live.
[SPEAKER_09]: Myself, Rob Roberts, joining me as always, DarkSakura, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_09]: Back for more gaming news after feeling a little full.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had some pretzels to snack on during the break there and some vitamin water to refresh me now, even though they say this stuff is really not as good for you as you'd think.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm full of energy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's better than soda.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good!
[SPEAKER_09]: Lots of energy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lots of energy to get through gaming news?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_09]: How about you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you energetic?
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Will you mind doing some gaming news for us anyway?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, it's already been rumored that it's coming out at some point, but Guitar Hero Metallica was pretty much confirmed by Metallica themselves during an interview with Lars Orch.
[SPEAKER_10]: And basically, the quote is, if somebody's going to follow up Guitar Hero Aerosmith, we're talking...
[SPEAKER_10]: We're talking and it's exciting and the people at Guitar Hero and Activision are rapidly becoming our best new friends in the world.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can put the rest of it together yourself.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Guitar Hero, Metallica, once again, horning up the franchise next year.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there's going to be a lot of people that are going to buy this game, even more so than Aerosmith, I predict.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, probably.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, Aerosmith's a pretty rockin' band, don't get me wrong, but Metallica's even, like, more so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Metallica is godly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even after the backlash of Napster and all that, you know, we've kind of forgotten about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's such a really good light-satinger.
[SPEAKER_09]: Am I one of the few people on the planet that actually liked Reload and Load, those albums?
[SPEAKER_09]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought those albums were pretty good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, the best part of those albums was the fact that Marianne Faithfull was on a song.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was so rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: But nothing ever tops the awesome that was the S&M concert.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, was that the orchestra?
[SPEAKER_02]: The one with Cayman and the, what was it, Berklee, I think?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it was local, from where they're from.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just thought it was funny that people who bought season passes for theater and opera had to listen to Metallica.
[SPEAKER_09]: Comments from our chatroom, chat.orangelonceradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft says, Lars is a big sellout, according to Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there are still some people that are Metallica-hating.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jvmon says, my store still has dozens and dozens of Guitar Hero Aerosmith still in my store.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I've noticed the same thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, any idea?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if you know anything from the inside, but any idea on how Aerosmith Guitar Hero has been selling?
[SPEAKER_10]: We sold a lot of it, and then...
[SPEAKER_10]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, not a lot of reorders.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, okay, isn't that bad, though, when there's not a lot of reorders?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because that means the ones that were bought for the shelves aren't leaving.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't that bad?
[SPEAKER_09]: Could be.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I'm not trying to distort the facts or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe they are selling really good.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll have to look at the MPD numbers at the end of July to see how it did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, though, it'll probably still be doing pretty well through July.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe the MPD number is in September for August to see how well it's doing.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, you know, it sold a lot, but a lot of people were just picking it up
[SPEAKER_09]: JV Mon continues, Guitar Hero Aerosmith sold really well the first week, then people stopped caring.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do intend on picking it up, but again, I'm holding out for a price drop.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if they're not leaving shelves, maybe that'll happen sooner than people were telling me it was going to.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other thing, too, you have to look at is a lot of people may have already had the guitar bundles for it already.
[SPEAKER_10]: So maybe people just bought way too many bundles.
[SPEAKER_10]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: Say you're in the Guitar Hero and you've had one through three already.
[SPEAKER_10]: You probably already own a second guitar.
[SPEAKER_10]: You probably don't need a third guitar, so maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: And DarkTetsuya says the mandatory in Sky.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about Guitar Hero Journey?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know I'm down with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob's not going to stop believing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you hear?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not stopping believing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you hear the Journey is going to be in town?
[SPEAKER_09]: Where are they?
[SPEAKER_09]: With heart.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: And cheap trick.
[SPEAKER_09]: When?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It might be the same weekend as PAX.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to look it up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll find out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll look it up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll look it up while we read a story.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, if there's one thing better than journey, it's heart and journey.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's heart.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: As long as I get my power ballads, I'm happy.
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100Matt says Guitar Hero ABBA.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that's for my dream pop and music game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be like Keyboard Mania.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, sorry, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, shall we?
[SPEAKER_09]: Rock Revolution set list was released this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: Queen was Stone Cold Crazy.
[SPEAKER_12]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're Not Gonna Take It by Twisted Sister, which, you know, that's the Twisted Sister song.
[SPEAKER_09]: So this is Butt Rock's version.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kinda, in a way.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it has Blitzkrieg Bop by the Ramones.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the one they failed famously on stage at E3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Am I Evil?
[SPEAKER_09]: Bad Reputation by Joan Jett.
[SPEAKER_09]: And just to top it off for fun, Sk8er Boi by Avril Lavigne.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Linkin Park.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's not totally butt rock.
[SPEAKER_09]: All the small things.
[SPEAKER_10]: To go back to the non-gaming related stuff we were talking about just earlier.
[SPEAKER_10]: Journey with Heart and Cheap Trick.
[SPEAKER_10]: You were close.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is the 27th of September.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going.
[SPEAKER_10]: We can go.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are down.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's at the Shoreline Amphitheater in Mountain View, California.
[SPEAKER_12]: Guess what else is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mountain View?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, there's one in SAC too, whatever they call it, Sleep Train or SAC Valley, they change the name of it every year.
[SPEAKER_02]: But next month also is Weird Al.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: At the fair.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I've never seen Weird Al live before.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're coming with us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe we should do OLR live at the Journey concert.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's do that!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, that would be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if it's possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll find a way.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll go record in the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_09]: Concord Pavilion, the 24th.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know they're coming to Sleep Train Amphitheater.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look it up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look up the Sac Valley thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll look it up later.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, can I do my story?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, Jamie, just do your story and I will look up Journey and Heart.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're not as, you know, didn't go through their massive 80s-tastic mode because Ozzy always rocks.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there is going to be Ozzy and Guitar Hero World Tour.
[SPEAKER_02]: We actually have some tracks released today.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the two Ozzy songs are going to be Crazy Train and Mr. Crowley.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other tracks announced is Airborne, Too Much, Too Young, At the Drive-In, One-Armed Sister, Scissor, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Black Rebel Motorcycle Club, Weapon of Choice, Bob Seger, Hollywood Knights, Dinosaur Jr., Field of Pain, I love Dinosaur Jr., I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: We also have Silver Sun Pickups, Lazy Eye, System of a Down, BYOB, Survivor, Eye of the Tiger, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I'm sitting here squeeing.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's September 26th.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going!
[SPEAKER_09]: Friday.
[SPEAKER_09]: Friday night!
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going!
[SPEAKER_09]: We're there!
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the one in Wheatland, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zach Wild, Stillborn, and other tracks that were previously announced, just to repeat those for the listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: Billy Idol, Rebel Yell, which I'm like, hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blink-182, Damn It, Foo Fighters, Everlong, which, you know, that's going to make Drew all...
[SPEAKER_09]: It makes me all pee myself.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_09]: Foo Fighters are pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some Jimi Hendrix songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: That makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Purple Haze, the live version, Wind Cries Mary, Linkin Park, What Have I Done, Paramore Misery Business, Sublime Santeria.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to yawn so bad for that one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm so over Sublime.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's really overplayed.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Doors, Love Me Two Times.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Eagles, Hotel California, and Van Halen, Hot for Teacher.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, I'm not the biggest fan of the David Lee Roth era, but I love Hot for Teacher.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a fun one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love When I Kissed a Teacher by ABBA.
[SPEAKER_09]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, you know I've got a present for you from Ranma at my house.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have an ABBA album.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Album.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like old art and everything?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe we can put that in the blank space on Justin.tv.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he got you a Bette Midler album.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not as big on Bette Miller, but my mother is, so I'll take that to her.
[SPEAKER_02]: He got you Super Trooper.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge, Abba O It's Abba Lounge Radio Loki, save the show, please Anyways, since we were talking about Rock Band earlier And I mentioned that we were going to be talking about street dates Well, the street dates apparently were leaked out of some database somewhere The dates that they have It wasn't you, was it?
[SPEAKER_10]: It wasn't me I don't do that sort of thing Anymore
[SPEAKER_10]: and he doesn't do it any less so according to this database which I think I want to say that it was like Fred Meyer or something like that maybe it was Blockbuster probably Blockbuster the 360 version they have coming out September 24th the PS3 October 19th and the Wii November 18th that is about half true
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not entirely correct.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is there a certain element of that that might be incorrect?
[SPEAKER_10]: The dates for those systems are correct.
[SPEAKER_10]: They just don't mention one thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: In September, the game-only version for Xbox 360 is coming out and the accessories are coming out by themselves.
[SPEAKER_10]: The bundle's not coming out until the PS3 date, which is the same time the PS3 will be getting the standalone and the bundle.
[SPEAKER_10]: That actually makes sense if they're rushing the game out.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then the Wii version is coming out November 18th along with the PlayStation 2 version.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: And now you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were close, but not close enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're probably going to give them the game only version.
[SPEAKER_10]: What about the achievements and trophies in the game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, the achievements and trophies are going to be very similar to the last game.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have trophies for...
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: and then of course they have some drum challenge achievements and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks very similar to the first game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hopefully, now that Band Tour is supposed to be online playable, so I can play it with friends of mine and not have to have everybody over, I'll actually be able to unlock some of those achievements.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I don't have the full thing, so I've never got those achievements, which is sad.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm counting on my friend who plays Rock Band a lot more than I do to play my copy and get me the achievements.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll play it with you.
[SPEAKER_10]: You should come over one day and we'll get all those achievements.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need to get that kick-ass drum set.
[SPEAKER_09]: You just have to learn how to drum.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, onto a completely different note.
[SPEAKER_09]: This has nothing to do with music games whatsoever, although you might say these two are making music together.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is from a post on these forums, MMORPG.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're talking about the game Age of Conan, and this user, I don't know if the user themselves did it, I don't think they did, but they're posting screenshots from the Age of Conan game, where apparently, one of these players, who plays a male character in the game, uh...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, unfortunately if we did that, who knows what PSA we would receive next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, okay, they posted these screenshots here, and apparently they were cybering a little bit with the GM.
[SPEAKER_09]: And look, here's some of the quotes from here.
[SPEAKER_09]: The player, with dual-wheeled barbarians though, I mean, two, that's a bit difficult for me to handle.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd rather stick with one big sword.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the GM says, you like it rough, I take it.
[SPEAKER_09]: The player says, be gentle.
[SPEAKER_09]: The GM says, are you a real woman?
[SPEAKER_09]: LOL, not crazy question.
[SPEAKER_09]: You would be surprised.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the player says, yep, I just play a male character so guys don't flirt with me in game like on WoW.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the GM says, I'm wearing panties.
[SPEAKER_09]: Joke.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: The GM ends up saying, hmm, you are bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: What if I rip your panties off and fuck you hard until I'm satisfied?
[SPEAKER_09]: Want to feel you get really... Wait, want to feel... This is, of course, cyber chat, so the grammar is all horrible.
[SPEAKER_09]: Want to feel you get really wee so I can put it just the head of my you-know-what inside you and use my hand to slowly move it around before plunging it fully into you and making you take it all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow!
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, that's a GM in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: As you can probably imagine, this guy got canned.
[SPEAKER_09]: But here's the part that's kind of irritating.
[SPEAKER_09]: So the whole thing was a big joke.
[SPEAKER_09]: The player then suddenly yells, this is Sparta.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're so kinky, you just cybered with a dude.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then the GM says, LOL, why did you want this then?
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you gay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you serious?
[SPEAKER_09]: And then the player says, serious about what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was joking about the fapping, but then I am indeed the dude.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the GM says, LOL, okay, glad I put my clothes back on.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then the player says, yeah, probably a good idea, I have AIDS.
[SPEAKER_09]: You had me going here at the lulzy factor, but then this is the equivalent of me getting up on stage and telling this hilarious joke.
[SPEAKER_09]: Imagine I'm Ellen DeGeneres, and I come out on stage, and I'm really funny, and everybody's laughing, and I'm making jokes at people's expenses.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then at the very end of my show, I take my pants off, and I poop live on stage.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of what happened here.
[SPEAKER_09]: LOL, you had to end it with the ha-ha gay AIDS joke.
[SPEAKER_09]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's not funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this poor guy probably got fired over what you did and posting all these things on the internet.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you wanted to be funny, that wasn't the way to go about doing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you can suck it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you make me very angry.
[SPEAKER_09]: And therefore, we're going to do the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you have a comment, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do have a comment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: First of all, though, that's a big pile of mutual stupidity, so I don't feel sorry for either of them.
[SPEAKER_09]: The GM's no dumber than you are, my friend.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know I'm looking at you, but I mean the user.
[SPEAKER_02]: the user first of all is an asshole and also pretty much dumb fuck for the little comment at the end but the GM should have been a GM in the first place if you know they were going to basically act inappropriately especially if it's like a private server that's one thing but if this is a public server where someone is technically as an employee for said company they are a representative of the company they should know better
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Amaze Satsuma in chat says, Pooping on stage is still better than Carrot Top.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look, you get my analogy, alright?
[SPEAKER_09]: Even if you have to be a smartass about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, now, I'm still angsty.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still have enough residual angst.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hopefully DarkSakura does too to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: My FU of the week goes towards a hormone.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Damn those hormones.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: My FU of the week goes to my high school reunion.
[SPEAKER_10]: The 10 year high school reunion.
[SPEAKER_10]: What a complete fucking waste of time and money.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just a note for all you people maybe still in high school and thinking, hey, 10 years from now I can go see all my friends again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't do it, seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, about 30 or 40 people will show up and they're probably the people that you weren't friends with anyways.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just keep in touch with your friends.
[SPEAKER_09]: Me, myself, I don't really have a whole lot of FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had a fairly decent week.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I kick you, will you have an FU?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I will.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will have an FU.
[SPEAKER_09]: FU to the ferret.
[SPEAKER_09]: It stings.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I know I had a bad... FU to drama.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because there has been drama recently and it's no fun at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drama is poopy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Drama is poopy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Drama is no fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Save the drama for your llama.
[SPEAKER_09]: A gun is no fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a character on WoW called Drama Llama.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guns are lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guns are fun unless you're shooting people with guns.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then they're not fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: But shooting cats with guns is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe that everyone should have a gun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm completely in the opposite.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here we go in the political stuff again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to say one thing about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Promise me we can get back to gaming after that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think that most people are good?
[SPEAKER_09]: Most people.
[SPEAKER_02]: If everybody had a gun, a concealed weapon, whether they carried it or not, do you think that someone would be more likely to do a violent crime on someone who may or may not be armed?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want the responsibility that comes with a gun.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't have to have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't trust the 1% of people who shouldn't have guns.
[SPEAKER_02]: But do you think that 1% of the population is going to be stupid enough to attack the rest of the population who might be armed?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It shouldn't have to come to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all I ever have to tell anyone to think about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, don't hurt yourself.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's other people to hurt you for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, well, you know one of my favorite games ever is a Hudson game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Star Parodia
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we didn't get East Book 1 and 2 when it was supposed to be out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Star Parodia and Break-In are going to be on Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know I've mentioned this plenty of times before, Star Parodia is a parody of Star Soldier.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's a game where you basically, you can play as the Twinbee, you can play as Bomberman, or you can play as a flying PC engine and shoot things with hue cards and CDs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guns That Shoot Hue Cards I approve of.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, but I'm done.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, hopefully those games actually come out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I've never played this Star Parodia game, and I always hear DarkSakura rave about it, so I'm kind of curious to check it out someday.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's now called Mushroom Kingdom Fusion And it's got 12 playable characters now You can actually play as Arthur from Ghouls N' Ghosts You can play as Sonic, Tails, Luigi, Wario, Kirby, Zelda Or I should say Link, Samus, etc.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tingle?
[SPEAKER_10]: No Tingle Fail
[SPEAKER_10]: But they have all sorts of game references in this.
[SPEAKER_10]: A bunch of different custom levels.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's all fan-made.
[SPEAKER_10]: A bunch of different power-ups.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's fan-gasmed the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can actually download the beta of this, which I have still yet to get to run on my PC because it's very un... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Power-ups you can get, including for example, if you get the Mega Man power-up, if you're playing Mario, Mario becomes Mega Mario, Luigi becomes Proto Luigi, Sonic becomes Quick Man, and Tails becomes Gyro Man Tails.
[SPEAKER_10]: MKFusion.ipbfree
[SPEAKER_10]: IPFreely.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: IPFreely.com?
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: IPB.
[SPEAKER_09]: IPB Free.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Huh, I'll have to check this game out when they fix some of their memory problems.
[SPEAKER_09]: It sounds interesting, but it sounds like what would happen if the fans made Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what would happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, talk about legitimate games though.
[SPEAKER_09]: This one's legitimate and something the fanboys definitely want.
[SPEAKER_09]: Raiden 4 is going to be coming out for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: That has been announced by Moss, who is the developer of Raiden 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: They are porting the old arcade shoot-em-up to the Xbox 360 and apparently they're actually going to put new aircrafts in the game through download content.
[SPEAKER_09]: The game comes out September 11th in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: The game's soundtrack is supposed to be included with the game as well, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura will read those few emails we did get this week right now
[SPEAKER_02]: First email is from GS68.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, OLR crew, about the issue of Wii storage space, I'm not sure if this has been brought up yet, but can't you put VC games on an SD card and then put them back on your Wii when you want to play them again?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is there something wrong with that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not saying you're dumbasses or anything, just wondering why you can't transfer your VC games onto an SD card.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does that take too long or is it too inconvenient?
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: This email was brought to you by JustinTV, home of the never-ending spammers and assholes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, on the it's too inconvenient part.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a little silly that your Wii can read from it, but yet it can't read data from it and access games.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like not being able to run a picture.
[SPEAKER_09]: Imagine this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Every time you wanted to look at pictures on a USB card, you had to copy them to your computer to view them.
[SPEAKER_09]: You couldn't view them right off your USB card.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of annoying.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: If I wanted to play them, you know, later on, like, you know, like, for example, if I was playing, like, a lot of Alien Crush, I wouldn't move Alien Crush off there, but if, say, I played through, you know, what's another one on there, Blaster Master, and was kind of tired of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not yet, but someday.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just picking, I think, arbitrary title.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, so that would be the case that I think that that could be okay, but if it's, if you're, but not in a,
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to, you know, do this every time with every game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alpha Cananagram has a good point.
[SPEAKER_09]: He says it just takes too long to copy back on the Wii, especially Nintendo 64 games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's a good point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, I wonder how those TurboGrafx CD games would be.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just a little silly it's not supported yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if the slot access is too slow, but it's just, it's the principle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is from Saltech.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted to point out one thing the R4 has done for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Out of the five people I know who own DSs, four of them bought it only because of the R4, myself included.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo is going to make money because the R4 since they make money on every DS sold.
[SPEAKER_02]: where it is really bad for the third party developers because people will not be purchasing those games which is unfortunate but happens when devices like this are released.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep up the great work and I apologize if my grammar sucks but I'm very bad at writing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Saltech.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's okay, I forgive you.
[SPEAKER_02]: This time.
[SPEAKER_09]: To be honest, I think you're kind of in the minority, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: You and your friends are probably kind of a group of hackers, in the sense that you enjoy these types of things in the systems.
[SPEAKER_09]: You probably also bought a PSP so you could play NES games on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: But do realize you and your friends are not the mass gamer, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not saying I disagree with you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just saying you can't say that four out of all five gamers only bought a DS for the R4.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the only point I'm trying to make.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I don't think the R4 is a bad device when used appropriately.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am all for breaking region locks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am all for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the next and last email I should say, I'm actually going to be kind and check and see if there's one more email because I am kind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, we did get one.
[SPEAKER_02]: OLR, I was checking to see if OLR has any events or special guests for the 300th show and if there's any room in the studio slash garage I would like to attend pending travel arrangements slash work here is some of the reasons which can earn me a spot in the studio as an attendee slash guest this person is very fond of slashes
[SPEAKER_02]: having met DarkSakura must meet Sky and Loki to complete meeting the trifecta of OLR hosts gave DMN a ride home 35 miles from the arcade somehow triggering the random chain of events which would include DarkSakura paying for one of my games of DDR the following month
[SPEAKER_02]: I play DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am probably one of the oldest skilled DDR players.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've just turned 31 and I can keep up with people nearly half my age.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one, great scene, close pick, On My Summer Love is an indication I might have to see OLR Live in order to AAA that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have DDR Player as my license plate on my car.
[SPEAKER_02]: I must pay tribute to the fairy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those are just a few reasons to be there during the 300th show in some form or another, LOL.
[SPEAKER_02]: This email was brought to you by Olive Garden, home of the never-ending Olive Garden insert contextual question mark pound 78 dot track dot google dot com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Peace out and triple A, Jammer J.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to be honest, I haven't even thought about the 300th episode yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's still two months off.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's packs kind of in the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be a little while.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I saw the pictures.
[SPEAKER_09]: You, my friend, are a DDR fan if I've ever seen one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a big question mark right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: More to come.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you guys want to see for the 300th episode?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, what a nice perfect attack on my summer love.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you guys want to see us do for our 300th episode?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want pizza and beer and ice cream.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to go back real quick because I'm an idiot and I got called out on it in chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: GameGuru says the DS has no region lock and I should know that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've seen the import games for sale right on the store shelves next to the American games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what the hell I was smoking.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll be honest, I don't use the DS a lot for region locks.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's more for the PlayStation games where I'd like to get around it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm thinking, I've played Owen Don on my DS, I should know better.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have Owen Don on my DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought puppies from him.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, sorry, anyway, as far as the 300th episode, to be determined, don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're always welcoming of other people in the studio, but, you know, just try to give us a little advance warning.
[SPEAKER_09]: Plus, I would, honestly, you really want to come out here just for the show?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, if you're going to go to San Francisco and do some tourism around there, cool, but it ain't worth it to fly out here just for our little thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can call in on Skype.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I'm not trying to, you know, just being honest, we're not that exciting people.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're simple people.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're like Amish people, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura with video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are we video game-ish?
[SPEAKER_02]: Video game Amish?
[SPEAKER_09]: Video game Amish?
[SPEAKER_02]: One more email!
[SPEAKER_09]: Because someone snuck in.
[SPEAKER_09]: Comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft says episode 300 should be on Mexico, tequila, tacos, and more.
[SPEAKER_09]: JVMons, and he is from Mexico, so he can try to lobby us to get there just like JVMons is doing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Episode 300 should be in New York City.
[SPEAKER_09]: Frisbee says, Episode 300 should be in space.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look, I said things we can realistically do.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think OLR in space is not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like the ring of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: OLR in space.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, one more email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, last one says, Hi folks, since I just got an Xbox 360 Elite on August 2nd, I have some questions for you, mainly directed at Rob, since I know he has a 360, but Loki and DarkSakura can feel free to chime in too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, well, thank you so much for your permission.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, it's nice that the listeners give you permission.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1.
[SPEAKER_02]: For those in my situation where we both have the PS3 and a 360, is it worth getting the same multi-platform games over again if we already have the given game on one of the consoles?
[SPEAKER_02]: For example, Call of Duty 4, Rock Band, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nah.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you must, sell your other one back.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least get some credit for it before you buy the other one.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you feel you must.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is how some games try to milk money out of you, though, is by trying to entice you to buy it again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like Soul Calibur 4, the whole Vader-Yoda thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, I liked your theory about buying that other game to get both unlocked.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's very likely.
[SPEAKER_09]: My simple answer is no.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll ask him.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rarely is that type of thing worth it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sometimes the game might really have a lot extra when it comes out on the other console.
[SPEAKER_09]: It sounds like Bioshock might have, but even then I would want to sell my Bioshock on 360 back if I'm going to get it on PlayStation 3, which is actually not something I would do in the real world, but at least do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, moving right along to the next question.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you could come up with a top five list of games for a 360 owner should have, what games would those be?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you like, you can have separate lists for disc-based games and Xbox Live arcade games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to go ahead and tell you a few that I have.
[SPEAKER_02]: First of all, get Marvel Ultimate Alliance.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the hell out of that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the second one's coming out, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dead Rising, you can kill zombies with a lawnmower.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fun for five seconds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Symphony of the Night on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: What else was it that we were playing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Rez
[SPEAKER_09]: Symphony of the Night if you don't already have access to it on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you do, go Luminous if you've never played it before and you haven't gotten it on any other console like the PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I would say something like Uno or go try something a little different like Catan or Carcassonne or Ticket to Ride.
[SPEAKER_09]: Try one of those games on for size.
[SPEAKER_02]: But don't get Yaris.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, don't be enticed by it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_09]: Same with Totem Ball.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any contribution, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm being distracted by people saying that I need to be in a Tingle suit for the 300th show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Silly chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: That ain't happening.
[SPEAKER_09]: Recommend five Xbox 360 games our new listeners should pick up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_10]: When are they picking up their 360?
[SPEAKER_10]: They already have it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would do Earth Defense Force 2017.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, it's dirt cheap now, seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like five bucks or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Crackdown, if you want, I mean, because that's dirt cheap right now, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: The jumping game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would say the original Saints Row, if you want.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, if you... I guess that's also dirt cheap.
[SPEAKER_09]: I agree with JV Mon, who's flooding Lost Odyssey, if you're remotely interested in RPGs.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a lot of RPGs coming out, though, pretty soon, so... Lost Odyssey, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: Bioshock's good and probably OMG Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would not recommend Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Call of Duty 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: More.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving forward, have you had any issues with any other players in Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_02]: People essentially being annoying or all around a-holes.
[SPEAKER_02]: If so, what's the best way to deal with that issue?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't play with strangers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't play with strangers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Build up a friends list of good people.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I urge you to start on OrangeLoungeRadio.com slash forums.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if that's not enough for you, go visit other forums that you like and get other Xbox Live gamer tags.
[SPEAKER_09]: And don't play with strangers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Play with friends.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the only way you're going to avoid idiocy.
[SPEAKER_02]: or make sure that you can play in a game where you make sure you start the game and you can boot the players.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's another good tip.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to meet people.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's actually a very good tip.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, play games that idiots don't understand.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's one reason I recommended Catan and Carcassonne.
[SPEAKER_09]: Play games that idiots don't understand.
[SPEAKER_10]: Learn to laugh at the idiots instead of being offended by them.
[SPEAKER_10]: We did that one time when we played a bunch of people in the UK at Grand Theft Auto 4 and we kicked crap out of them.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were like
[SPEAKER_10]: It was about all these obscenities, and it was funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: We were just like, ah, they're angry.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're swearing with an accent.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ha, ha, ha.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're using words like, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just have to say, chat room reminded, orange box.
[SPEAKER_09]: None of us said orange box, and we really should have.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you need portal.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, sorry, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I was also going to say, it just goes back to what was it I was saying a few weeks ago, learn to be offended?
[SPEAKER_09]: I agree to an extent.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's so much idiocy on Xbox Live though.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's so, so much.
[SPEAKER_09]: It gets old.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's funny the first few times, it gets so old.
[SPEAKER_09]: I report every single one because I'm that guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last question on here.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you don't mind, would you please send me a friends list invite on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_02]: My gamertag is Spazinator on PSN.
[SPEAKER_02]: Minus the quotes, obviously.
[SPEAKER_09]: What about Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, if anyone has, Dan's, isn't his Gunstar underscore hero?
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, I don't remember, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Dan's his Gunstar hero, and he, um, boots people that he doesn't recognize, and so he's booted some people that I added on there, so if you add him and he boots you, don't be offended, it's not me, it's my husband.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, are you full yet?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I have like 70-something.
[SPEAKER_10]: So LokiOLR, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki space OLR, all caps.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for taking the time to answer my questions as it's highly appreciated.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a really nice letter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I add everybody, but don't expect me to play with you during the middle of the day when I'm at work doing our two 15-minute multiplayer games.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll ignore your invites.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, don't... Just because... Yeah, that's another thing, because that's kind of happened lately, is that I'm... Without fail, I always get invited to games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please don't be offended if I turn them down, but keep in mind, sometimes when I turn on the Xbox, I have a game in mind I want to play.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to go back... Like, I don't even know where my copy of Halo 3 is, and I can't... Like, from several people, I get Halo 3 invites.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please don't be offended when I decline them.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just don't... That's not the game I feel like playing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, same.
[SPEAKER_10]: I get granted a lot of horror invites when I'm not playing it, and Nelly's playing, like, Zuma or Bejeweled, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: but I do certain random things will happen like I got into a random Uno game the other night with some all games people and we had a good time not that I don't join random games every now and then I just haven't lately like right now it's all about Braid and Geometry Wars which sadly are not multiplayer so if you catch me in a good mood I can do Soul Calibur 4 if you catch me in a Soul Calibur mood anyhow, sorry was that it for Mailbag?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it was yeah
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, so send us more.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mailbag at orangelaunceradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100Matt in chat says, Dear Microsoft, expand the friends list count.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, thanks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, next story.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I don't know if this is, like, you know, important or anything, but G4 has announced the winners of the G4IA 2008 Awards, which were voted on by the fans.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_10]: And here are the winners.
[SPEAKER_10]: Game of the Year, Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why no love for Grand Theft Auto 4?
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: Favorite system, Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Best graphics, Metal Gear Solid 4.
[SPEAKER_10]: Best new character, Nico Bellic from Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_10]: Best party game, Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_10]: Best strategy game, Sid Meier's Civilization Revolution.
[SPEAKER_10]: Best sports game, Skate.
[SPEAKER_10]: Best Action Game, Grand Theft Auto 4, Best Shooter, Call of Duty 4, Best Racing Game, Mario Kart Wii, Best Role Playing Game, Mass Effect, Most Original, Portal, Best Online Multiplayer Game, Call of Duty 4, Best Downloaded Content, Rock Band, Best Handheld Game, God of War, Chains of Olympus, Best Voice Acting, Metal Gear Solid 4, Best Soundtrack, Rock Band, Most Deserving of an Ue Bowl Movie, Turok, and Longest Lasting Game Presented by Stride, Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then the awards were over!
[SPEAKER_10]: I just saved you about three hours, or two hours, or however long this damn ceremony goes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jvmon says, Grand Theft Auto 4 kind of sucked.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's in the minority, but Niko is the best video game character in a long time.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not that Grand Theft Auto was super duper awesome, because it was pretty awesome, but Halo 3 wasn't that awesome, let me put it that way.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, it wasn't...
[SPEAKER_10]: Halo 3, New Paintjob
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's officially happening on the PlayStation Network on August 14th.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can actually duel the creator of Eye of Judgment from Japan Studio if you are so lucky to in this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if they're actually doing a tournament-style thing or if this is one of those, hey, why doesn't everybody play this game online at the same time so there's lots of people playing?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know exactly what it is, but it sounds like it could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Play some Eye of Judgment on August 14th if you actually have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, even so, you've got more incentive to be able to play Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is great news for Loki, although it's probably not going to help at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Circuit City has Eye of Judgment and the PlayStation Eye for $40.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's on sale!
[SPEAKER_02]: And Walmart has it for $30.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well...
[SPEAKER_09]: Time to go buy those things off the shelves.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's start moving them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I might actually go pick up one.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's one in a million.
[SPEAKER_09]: Only $999,999 more to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it's at Walmart for $30, hell yeah, I'll get it just to have the webcam.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a good price for the PlayStation Eye because I think the PlayStation Eye by itself is like $39.99.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even I would pick it up just because someday I'll probably get a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd pick it up to burn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'd pick it up to have the webcam because you can use the webcam on your PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's better than the webcam I have now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't use my webcam for anything other than taking random pictures, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: The webcam we use for OLRs, Justin TV, is an actual video camera at this point.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we used to use an iRite.
[SPEAKER_09]: We used to use an iSight.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what we used to use.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then it broke because I dropped it on the ground.
[SPEAKER_09]: Before that, we used to use an iToy.
[SPEAKER_09]: We did, for a little while, use an iToy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was back in the day.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, lots of Eye of Judgment news around.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aren't you excited, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was the one that posted this story, so... I think they're desperate.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm well aware of what's going on in the Eye of Judgment world.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or the lack thereof of what's going on in the Eye of Judgment world.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, something that's about as ridiculous as playing a card game over your PS3.
[SPEAKER_10]: How about installing Windows Vista on your PS3?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, well, you can do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It doesn't really mean it's going to work well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, the guy installed a version of Linux on his other partition of his hard drive, and in Linux, emulated Windows Vista.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, well, it takes 25 minutes to boot, and 5 minutes to access the start menu, and about 12 minutes to open Notepad.
[SPEAKER_10]: 12 minutes to open Notepad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Power the cell processor.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, but seriously, though, I mean, you're emulating an operating system within an operating system, within an operating system, basically.
[SPEAKER_09]: Misty says my thoughts exactly in chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: She says, ew, it's bad enough on PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: And to be honest, you know, to be honest, Windows Vista just runs like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, you know, really, stick with Linux.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or Minty.
[SPEAKER_09]: I almost said Misty Linux.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bet you'd be excited.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or Minty Linux.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I don't know if you can install Minty Linux on a PS3.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it only takes Yellow Dog or something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about Misty Linux?
[SPEAKER_09]: Would that be like an OLR-based Linux system?
[SPEAKER_09]: Misty Linux?
[SPEAKER_09]: Misty Linux.
[SPEAKER_09]: Instead of Minty Linux.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'd be like Emo Linux.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, my eyes are misty.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like our listener Misty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not like...
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I will like you a whole lot, Loki, if you get this for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, you'd have to buy me a PS3 as well, so get working on that, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: LittleBigPlanet, if you actually pre-order this game, it was revealed by the official US PlayStation blog that apparently there are five separate pre-order bonuses that you can get in North America.
[SPEAKER_09]: It all depends on where you're going to reserve the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: They haven't said where you reserve it will get you what prize just yet, but one of them is a
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to pre-order a game and get a burlap sack.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's rad.
[SPEAKER_09]: A little big sticker book, which is a sticker book.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the official LittleBigPlanet Creator guide by Brady Games, but only the mini guide.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the little guide for the little game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's kind of cute.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is ugly.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bet the Naughty Girl one's better.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like a poop.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your butt looks like a poop.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not really too excited about the God of War.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was looking at the one for the Heavenly Sword one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, the burlap sack is like a zipper pouch.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would get the little big pouch or the Nariko if it doesn't look as hideous as the Kratos one.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Heavenly Sword one is really cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: She looks like a Fraggle.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, Fraggles are rad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do they have a Fraggle Rock video game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, they should.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, do they have a Fraggle Rock video game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe on the ColecoVision or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, they need a new Fraggle Rock game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you can wait for the remake of the Fraggle Rock movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to do a remake, I guess, of it or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then there'll be a video game coming out for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, this is something that no one will ever be able to forget once they've heard of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a shooter series that stars heavily muscled men wearing Speedos.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the Cho Aineke games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there is going to be a new Cho Aineke game on PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, but it's like, Uber Muscles and he's got like a little thingy over his, you know, pee-pee.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did they wuss out on the, you know, subtle gay porn hints, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Amen!
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know what, I told my husband in no uncertain terms that I'm importing Zero Cho Aniki.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you should also tell him that you're gonna make him buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I told him.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, my friend who introduced me to Linux Mint says no Mint on PS3 as of yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Darn.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had to spread that on air.
[SPEAKER_02]: Heart, heart, heart, heart, heart.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: GameGuru says, also, why?
[SPEAKER_09]: Why, Choaniki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Cho Aoniki is cool!
[SPEAKER_09]: And GameGuru would like to also point out that the Fraggle Rock redo is coming from Jim Henson and Disney.
[SPEAKER_09]: So hopefully that's a good sign.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's coming from beyond the grave.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there's a couple neat, I guess, mods that have come out for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: The first is actually someone that has basically put a cell phone inside of a PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: Where the UMD drive goes, and so now it's a PSP phone.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: It kind of looks retarded, but hey, it's a phone and it's a PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: Something a little bit more functional, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there anything this device can't do?
[SPEAKER_10]: Another modder has incorporated a touchscreen to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a little bit better, I would say.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that project now is called...
[SPEAKER_10]: The Touchscreen Project for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's on a website called PSPZ Project.
[SPEAKER_10]: And .dcemu.co.uk And... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, DCEMU.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember that site.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was... My Dreamcast got more action from that website than any game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember... Was it Feet of Fury?
[SPEAKER_10]: Heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, he's allowed it to, I guess, have better battery life somehow.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've redesigned the control pad and some other crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he's working on a keyboard application for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would be kind of cool to have a touchscreen on the PSP because, for the love of God, typing on that thing sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so wow, we've had Wii hacks and now PSP hacks.
[SPEAKER_09]: The hackers sure are busy.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to end tonight before we go to the Skype line with a story that I know is going to surprise you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to knock the socks off of you.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're never going to believe it, but brace yourselves.
[SPEAKER_09]: Grand Theft Auto 4 is coming to the PC, y'all.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?!
[SPEAKER_09]: Shock, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: I never would have guessed.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is unheard of.
[SPEAKER_09]: I never would have guessed, based on the 50 leaks that came out earlier.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Rockstar finally admitting it, saying, quote, We are very excited to be releasing the PC version of Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: The whole team is dedicated to bringing an amazing gaming experience to the PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: The game looks and plays beautifully on PC, and we can't wait for people to play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is coming out November 18th in North America November 21st in Europe There is a reason why this is following a story about hacking
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, that is all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just in time for Christmas for the hacking community.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, it's going to be so awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other thing too that's kind of cool about it though is they do have some expanded multiplayer options in there as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: No word on what that is exactly, but there are going to be some new multiplayer features.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not that it would matter anyways because people would add it anyways and recreate all new cities and all sorts of mods.
[SPEAKER_10]: I cannot wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to open up the Skype line now for your calls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio is our username on Skype or if you're feeling so inclined, you can pick up the phone 1-877-GAME-OLR is the toll-free number in the US and Canada.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unfortunately, if you're overseas, you're going to want to stick to Skype.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're not going to pay your phone bill, kids.
[SPEAKER_09]: 1-877-GAME-OLR
[SPEAKER_06]: I got sold.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: It didn't implode or go under like it closed completely.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's being sold as a property out of Turner.
[SPEAKER_09]: So sorry if I misrepresented that, which is good that apparently the stream went down right at that moment that I said that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's back up now, but we had a weird hiccup in the connection.
[SPEAKER_03]: How was it?
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyway, yeah, because the chat room is going crazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyway, oh shoot, Justin TV caught me saying it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, no, Turner sold it off.
[SPEAKER_09]: He was looking to sell it off, apparently.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Any other last minute stories while we wait for some calls?
[SPEAKER_09]: Again, since the stream went dead, 1-877-GAME-OLR, the skype line is open.
[SPEAKER_10]: You want to hear something funny?
[SPEAKER_10]: What, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: I was reading up a little bit more on that Mushroom Kingdom fusion.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've got a bunch of different levels.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have the Mushroom Kingdom, Alternate Earth, Mega Man's Realm, the Demon Realm, which is based on Doom games, Genena, Shoot'em Up's domain, Realm of Nintendo, Sonic Universe, Halo Ring World, Twisted Reality, and Minus World.
[SPEAKER_10]: But
[SPEAKER_10]: In the demon world, the boss is Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: How appropriate.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_09]: Long time no talk.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you want to talk to us about tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just random things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, I'm just trying to find some stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that whole Madden hype, which apparently is affecting me and others.
[SPEAKER_06]: How exactly do you make money off of Madden?
[SPEAKER_06]: Through league play.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you talking online currency or are you talking about some type of shady... No, real money.
[SPEAKER_09]: Real money through Madden.
[SPEAKER_06]: He did that through NBA Live recently.
[SPEAKER_06]: He and a bunch of other players basically did it through MLG or something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I never realized there was this whole underground betting activity going on on Madden and video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: How much money is your brother making off this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, actually, it's the team that he's in.
[SPEAKER_06]: He hasn't told me any specifics, but he did make a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: But most of the money is going to the team.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, what does the team buy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Shirts or a whole lot of pot?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, just to pay off their players, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So then your brother is making money if he's paying off the players?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, he's actually in the league, so he's actually making money.
[SPEAKER_06]: The earnings are split pretty much amongst all the other players in his team.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if I get good at Madden, which will never happen, if I get good at Madden, I could make money off of it on this whole underground gambling circuit?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, you could.
[SPEAKER_06]: They do hold those things from what I hear.
[SPEAKER_06]: They pretty much hold the underground Madden sessions where they have...
[SPEAKER_09]: They bet big dollars for each game No, it's just at the private meetups Just like, you know, at people's houses where they just like, you know, they play Madden for money
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I can't imagine any other game, maybe DDR, unless you put money on... Well, I don't see an underground DDR betting circle starting anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it could happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could basically put money on the number of greats you get per song.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like the less number of greats, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, besides Digital Life being held next month, coinciding with an anime convention also being held in the same place, that's pretty much it, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Next month, Digital Life, $3,000.
[SPEAKER_09]: What are you most looking forward to about Digital Life?
[SPEAKER_09]: I know there was a little bit of disappointment all around last year.
[SPEAKER_09]: What are you looking for them to most improve, or what are you looking forward to this year?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just want to, I don't know if there's, they have more, you know, they have more like game, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: Game developers showing up instead of all this other marketing crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, besides all the swag that you get for free, you could use a few more games like in 06, which was really good.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had the Wii and everything before it came out.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Zaku, we've got to let you go so we can get some more calls, but thanks for calling in, and good luck to your brother.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope he can make your family a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I hope so, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe you can ask for a loan.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get a loan out to get some of that DDR crack or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe if he wins enough money, he can get a 2DX machine for the house.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sounds good, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Would you ever bet on a video game real money?
[SPEAKER_09]: I love gambling, but it ends at slot machines nickel size.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, I don't play the lottery.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only closest I've ever done to it is a lottery pool at work where I was only out $2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't that fascinating though that there's this whole betting on Madden circuit?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's freaking sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is in a way, but it's... I don't think gambling is fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: For me, I'm willing to raise the stakes a little bit, like 20.
[SPEAKER_09]: Most, I think I've ever gambled at night, it's like 60 bucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I go, well, 60 bucks is what I might spend on a video game or spend, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I always set a limit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't take my ATM card into those places because it's dangerous.
[SPEAKER_09]: You go in with a set amount of money and you don't expect to walk out with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then you're okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, not that I should be endorsing gambling.
[SPEAKER_09]: But once in a while, it's not gonna... It's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, you...
[SPEAKER_09]: People know their tolerance is the best for themselves.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Skype lines are open.
[SPEAKER_09]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Use name on Skype as Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: While we wait to see if we get any more calls, Loki, do you have any last minute stories for us otherwise?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm still reading more of that wiki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, there's one thing here that's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: On Machima.com, they have a video for... You know how they have all those meet the classes of characters in Team Fortress 2?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, they have Meet the Cow.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess it's some cardboard cow or some wood cutout cow that's in Team Fortress 2 and it's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, we have another call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the one from Sweden.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our Swedish friend.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was hoping you'd call tonight with all the ABBA references we were making earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I'm just... What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: It wasn't about that, though, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: That's alright, I'm just messing with you.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the system specs for Age of Reckoning Warhammer has finally been released.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if you actually did mention it, but it has been released.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell us a little bit about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: The system specs for Warhammer Online has been released, which is a basic single-core...
[SPEAKER_07]: Pentium 4, 2.4, and mostly like a gig of RAM if you run AXP or Vista.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you're running Vista, you need two.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other than that, you need an average modern video card, and you're ready to go.
[SPEAKER_10]: That sounds like most anyone can run this if you have a modern PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: since they're aiming for basically the WoW scale of players.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even though I'm quite a bit surprised since, at least in my case, I'm running really on a, as current state, unfortunately a big low generation 7 GeForce card.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that one isn't supported.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the funny thing is that mostly low ATI cards are supported, but the NVIDIA ones are not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not quitting Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_09]: All the cool kids are quitting their games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not, pardon me, but I'm not that big a fan of a Star Trek geek, so I can't really say anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only space science fiction MMO I played for a while was EVE Online, which, well, is sort of fun, even though if you're really out of breaking down on EVE, just on the EVE front, it's basically a big Excel spreadsheet, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bobby Blackwolf says in chat right now, I want to join Rob's fleet in Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, I'm going to have a fleet.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, I want to be Captain Sassy Pants.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Captain Sassy Pants of the USS OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're getting off track.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know you didn't want to talk about Star Trek because you're not that big a geek.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go ahead, finish your thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other than that, I've had the opportunity to try out Age of Conan.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, well, I'm not that impressed, really.
[SPEAKER_09]: You didn't cyber with anyone in the game, did you?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: It sounds like you didn't think it was too high.
[SPEAKER_09]: What did you not enjoy about it?
[SPEAKER_09]: What turned you off?
[SPEAKER_07]: It really is the combat system that it's, well, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or maybe just I need to learn to play, really.
[SPEAKER_09]: The combat system wasn't saved by the fact that you could lob people's heads off?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I didn't lob any heads off, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it might be also due to the following fact that I'm
[SPEAKER_07]: My computer that I'm running Ejikonan on is really a lowest
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you get a lot of the high end stuff as we get it here?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or do you find that you guys lag behind a little bit?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, we don't like behind at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just me that don't have the possibility to dish out.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're poor here, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm poor.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I am going to probably dish out the money because I did a second job recently.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if you have the opportunity, you can...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really easy to dish out a few bucks, so you can get a respectable gaming system, so it's no problem at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, hey, we've got to let you go, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're running out of time, but thanks so much for your call, as always, and letting us know how the weather is on the other side of the pond.
[SPEAKER_09]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, we're going to go ahead and close up the Skype line and take any other last minute stories we have here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have something else we're trying to get to live tonight just for the live folks on allgames.com so anything else you guys have tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish I could read German.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_09]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_10]: It takes about 15 minutes to load, but it's supposedly worth it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to go around and give everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't wait to play this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, we are so going to see Journey, Heart, and Cheap Trick.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's freaking awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: And my final thought is I want to quote a Journey song, but not Don't Stop Believin'.
[SPEAKER_02]: When the lights go down in the city.
[SPEAKER_09]: When the lights go down.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, that'll work.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, have a good one, you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks so much for tuning in to us and supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: We wouldn't be here without your guys' support.
[SPEAKER_09]: Again, all we ask, if you like our show, tell a couple friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Leave us some positive reviews out there on the internet on your favorite podcasting website like iTunes or Dig or what have you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Help us spread the word because we're pretty stretched for resources here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sadly, there will be no live show next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're hoping to have something taped for you guys
[SPEAKER_09]: stay tuned to OrangeLaunchRadio.com for the details and don't worry if you're saddened by the lack of shows here in August PAX is going to more than make up for it because we will be bringing you something not only every day ourselves but we'll be bringing you something with AllGames.com it is going to be just information freaking overload that's later this month Labor Day weekend here on Orange Launch Radio Yay!
[SPEAKER_09]: Have a good one everybody.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see you next time here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: or allgames.com but we're probably right anyway see you next week