[SPEAKER_00]: Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, July 28th, 2013, self-publishing will soon be a reality on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_00]: A report is in on Ouya game sales, which might surprise you.
[SPEAKER_00]: And we get more insight as to why one fan-anticipated game was cancelled.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is Orange Lounge Radio for this July the 28th of 2013, episode number 514 of our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're here to talk to you guys about the latest and greatest in video gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts and joining me as always, say hello to Dark Sakura or Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: TechMasterLoki
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing Techmaster Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm getting full though.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're getting full?
[SPEAKER_04]: I still have another burger.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another burger to down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, that's right, you've ditched your fries in favor of two burgers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, not today.
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually wanted to get fries today just because I was a little hungry.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're being a little bit of a piggy today.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they're good fries.
[SPEAKER_11]: Usually they're not good fries.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of the Russian roulette of drive-thru fast food, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: McDonald's fries.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, and of course we do tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific and 9 o'clock Eastern at the Voice of Geeks Network, VOGnetwork.com right after the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when you do listen to our show live, you can check in and show that you're participating with the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did just turn those on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I'm lagging a little bit tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys might have to carry the show a little bit tonight I am pooped I had a super long weekend this weekend We don't want to know about your poop I may not have gone poop all weekend I've been that busy Are you that uptight?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, but okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sounds like a personal problem, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: As Jamie referenced a minute ago, last night was the big clue show, and I'm sure those of you that do listen to Understation Live here at the Voice Geeks Network, you've probably heard Jessica talking about it, and I've referenced it too.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the big show last night, which, you know, not only was the show, but all day leading up to that show, and then all week leading up to the show, and the Saturdays before that.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: um so there was that and then this morning um my buddies uh Captain Spike and First Mate Slidekick and and Tim from Crystal D were all here and they um graciously let me guest on a Game Buoy podcast we used the studio here to do that so I've already done one three-hour podcast today so now there's this there was Clue yesterday there was it's like I had Friday off of work and it still wasn't enough because I kind of want to call in tomorrow um
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aren't you starting your job tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, so I took a Tylenol PM last night, which I don't usually do.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so I'm feeling really groggy today.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like I can't kick this grog thing I've got going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I've just decided during tonight's show, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said, Alan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alan, do we have any wine?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's like, yes, we have like four bottles.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you want?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want wine.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what it is, but serve it to me in a Coke bottle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the wonderful Alan is over there right now cracking open a bottle of wine for me so I can have a little bit of a celebratory drink because it was a really kick-ass weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will say that.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and so it actually kind of made me go like, wow, why don't I do this more often?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm like, oh yeah, I have a three hour radio show every week where I get to kind of practice the speaking skills a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Alan, you rule.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to say hi to listeners?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: This first sip of wine's for all you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it sweet and fruity?
[SPEAKER_04]: It is extremely sweet and extremely fruity.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want a sip?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to... Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Entire... What?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's actually really good.
[SPEAKER_09]: It tastes like candy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: It actually tastes like sweet tarts.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's from a local winery.
[SPEAKER_04]: We actually drive out there to the winery.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's only about a 30-minute drive.
[SPEAKER_09]: Next time you go, grab me a bottle.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, seriously, I'll pay you for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tiger Claw in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com His legs are smooth.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm beardless for the first time in a couple years, I think, at this point.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I mean, I used to, like, for most of my 20s, I didn't have a beard.
[SPEAKER_09]: The last time you did it was for Rocky, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or for Repo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Rocky or Repo, one of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: But again, last night, Colonel Mustard, who I was playing in the movie, only has a mustache.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I took it down to my porn stash yesterday, which the minute I walk out of the bathroom, Alan goes, Oh, Freddie Mercury, I love your work.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm like, fuck off.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I shaved off the mustache last night, so now I'm clean shaven again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did the show must go on?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to break free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was your makeup flaking, but still?
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, so I'm trying to grow back at least some scruff for GamerX Because I'm going from one busy weekend to another GamerX is next weekend in San Francisco We will not be here live because of it I'm sorry, sorry about it But I won't be back on Sunday night for the show So unfortunately, Studio OLR will be closed on Sunday So Loki, you get a week off to do whatever And DarkSakura, you can come feed Sanrio
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Gamer X would probably just be like the ultimate dream of any convention because I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just would be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: You love gay men and women.
[SPEAKER_04]: You love video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm expecting that there will also be more bathed people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I'm hoping for that too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it's going to be a good time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fabulous people, fabulous games, and no con funk.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what they need to do.
[SPEAKER_11]: And this goes for pretty much any con.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I know it might annoy some people and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they need to have... What was it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, what the fuck is that place now?
[SPEAKER_11]: The place with all the stinky fucking shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: I keep wanting to say Bed Bath & Beyond but it's not Bed Bath & Beyond it's uh Perfumania god damn I don't remember the place now Bath & Body Works there you go they need to have a booth there because their stores fucking reek but they reek of like flowery stuff not con funk so you get them you put them in the middle of the con and then it just kind of averages itself out I was there at the AX that people were passing out um hygiene bags it was the last AX I went to by the way
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, this is important to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: GamerX is not just for gay people.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's for everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an all-inclusive event.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think it's going to be a good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am co-hosting, co-being on a panel on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's 6.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's 5 or 6.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't even remember at this point because I'm so exhausted.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're co-paneling.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm co-paneling Podcast Cross Zone with two guys from Game Buoy, two guys from Koopa Club, and one guy from Game Bar.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're going to just be talking about podcasting, and it'll be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says, I wonder, is there going to be any live stream happening at GamerX?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably, but not by us.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have no plans to do any live streaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: and you know whatever else comes from stay tuned on Twitter you can follow me on Twitter twitter.com slash SKIE Sky and I'll be posting lots of tweets from the weekend so I'm looking forward to it and hopefully no time on all PMs next weekend so it'll be good oh all right I don't know what else to talk about here at the top of the show does anybody else have a kickoff topic according to Loki I'm crocheting a rainbow penis cozy
[SPEAKER_11]: She showed me something that looked like, you know, a little, almost like a mitt for a finger or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm like, oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Middle finger cozy.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a picture on my Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, there you are.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Where's your Tumblr again, for those who don't know?
[SPEAKER_09]: Kuro Tsubasa.
[SPEAKER_09]: K-U-R-O-U-T-S-U-B-A-S-A.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's recognized by FemShep?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that's mass affecting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's all fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, my blogs are cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: No, but I'm going to be going back to, I'm going to be changing my live stream night once I'm out of training because I will be working on Thursdays.
[SPEAKER_09]: So my streaming will probably be earlier in the day.
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably, I have to find, make sure it's pre some show or something like that, but.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of live streaming, Bobby wanted me to throw a plug out here and this will be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: He will be live streaming Saints Row 4 on August 14th is the day he's going to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll be exciting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm probably going to finish my Mass Effect 3 stream just because I've beaten that game 27,000 times.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, no, I think I'm on my 20th playthrough.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, so yeah, I will be finishing up that, that if I can keep it from lagging from the high res graphics that I plugged in, I don't know why it's doing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: My computer is more than capable of handling it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, um, and then, um, I'll be, I'll be announcing that when that starts back up on mass affecting.tumblr.com plug, plug.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, um, in the interim, I am actually making stuff for video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am going to be making little slip pockets for 3DS I will be making them in XL size and as soon as I have everything set up I will be doing I think my first batch is going to be in Tetris fabric so anyone's interested talk to me fun yeah but yeah Animal Crossing and pinball what kind of pinball what games the stuff in my house you need some pinball games for your 3DS
[SPEAKER_09]: I need some other games for my 3DS well we borrowed Fire Emblem from George but Dan wanted to play the previous Fire Emblem first so he went and bought that there is another game going on in my house and that is Phantasy Star Generation 1 the Sega Ages one
[SPEAKER_09]: So basically I've been replacing all of the music in Animal Crossing for the updated Phantasy Star So everything sounds like combat from Phantasy Star in Animal Crossing It's been very, very weird
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_11]: Didn't play a whole ton this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just a little bit of Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was a few hours.
[SPEAKER_11]: I got all my cards in one sitting.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I played...
[SPEAKER_11]: Up through level 9, and I'm at, I just got the Sanctuary, so that's, you know, my, like, fourth time playing through this game, I swear, because I played through it on console.
[SPEAKER_11]: I played through it on the Xbox, like, three times, so it's like, ooh, I've already done this before.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, so, yeah, I'll do that, and...
[SPEAKER_11]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: I do it all the time.
[SPEAKER_11]: What else?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think I did play Super Meat Boy a little bit this week as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that's it though.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have Shadowrun Returns because they finally sent me the code from kickstarting that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did get to download that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although it looks fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Video Game High School Season 2 Episode 1 came out this week and it was fantastic and long because now they're all 30 minute long episodes instead of like 5 minute episodes.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was like between 6 and 15 minute episodes last season.
[SPEAKER_11]: It looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't get a chance to download their high frame rate version yet but the trailer was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: How they have 48 frames per second for the video game stuff and then 24 for everything else.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, but it's entertaining and they've had a lot of cameos in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's already been a Stan Lee cameo and, um, a Cliffy B cameo already in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, so that's what that guy's been up to.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: He, he was like, he was a judge for some, something, you know?
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, uh, it was, it was cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and then I played it again later in the week and it's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of like one of those like Metroidvania type of games but the castle each time you play is randomly generated.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when I say each time you play I mean each time you die and you come back as somebody else because that's the whole trick in Rogue Legacy is that you revive as the descendant of the last hero that you played as who will have some very different and unique traits.
[SPEAKER_04]: Such as they might be more of a paladin who, you know, has a shield Or they might be somebody who's a giant Or they might be somebody who has Tourette's So they just randomly have a little Q-Bert swear cloud that comes up Or somebody who has, they start to do some interesting and a little bit controversial ones They have one with dyslexia where all the letters when people talk will get switched around Like randomly And the vertigo one was a pain in the ass That's where the entire thing is flipped
[SPEAKER_04]: so like you're walking on the ceiling and all that oh my gosh that thing ticked me off uh but yeah that you a lot of fun because you collect as much gold as you can when you go to the castle and you can buy power-ups that all the future people will get to use but in order to go back in the castle you have to give up all your gold on hand
[SPEAKER_04]: so it really is about get as much gold as you can make the next hero a little stronger so he can get further he or she make get as much as you can make the next hero stronger and so on and so on and each time it's random although at one point you can hire somebody like I think it's an architect they call it and the architect will allow you to keep the same castle as the last generation but you'll only get 40% of the gold
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really a brilliant little trick in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really liked it a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to say, you'd be a lot better at the vertigo levels if you played more Strider.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or if I turned my monitor upside down when those came up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or played a lot more VVVVV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or just don't pick those guys moving forward, which is my plan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you get to pick from which one of three descendants do you want to play as.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did the Vertigo one for the LOL on the feed when I was broadcasting, but no more of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of one of those you do it once for the laughs and then that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that was Rogue Legacy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby and I finally had our much advertised and talked about Borderlands Noob Night on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I missed that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I didn't read my tweets and I...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we tagged you in it just to see if you were going to drop in.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we actually played from the start of the game to about level 7-ish.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think we were in like chapter 3 or something by the time we stopped.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you know, we played a pretty good chunk of the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: So did you finish Captain Flint or did you... Yes, I think that was the last guy we killed.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we got on a boat and we were taken somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, so you're in chapter 4 then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, was it really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: The first few chapters are fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: But it was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we had a good time, and I think we entertained the folks that were watching us broadcasting on Twitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, I'm really bad at first-person shooters.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the cool thing about Borderlands 2 is that, like, the character I was playing had a little, like... Once you got to level 5, you got a little gun turret that you can place on the ground.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll automatically shoot people.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that was cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Bobby was playing the Mechromancer, who is the...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: now when Borderlands 2 was on sale on Steam I was gifted a copy of Borderlands 2 by a great listener and I picked up the season pass myself because I'm like alright well I know I'm going to want to do all the DLC and all the other stuff that's out right now so I'm just going to pick up the season pass and that way I'll have it when I want to play well when I go in to play the game again the second time later in the week I went back in the game I'm like I'm going to try this again but this time I'm going to do the Mechomancer she's locked
[SPEAKER_04]: and I'm like, wait a minute, I should have this because I bought the season pass.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I do some research and I'm like, wait a minute, the season pass is showing on my account, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_04]: The characters aren't included in the season pass.
[SPEAKER_04]: She was a pre-order bonus.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, and that's the line I've been getting from a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, okay, she was a pre-order bonus, but they're still selling her.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not everybody's going to agree with me, and that's fine, but we all get opinions, so take it or leave it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of think when they're selling this as a season pass and they're leaving parts out, that's a little bit disingenuous to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you may argue with me on that, and that's fine, but to me, it's like picking up, like...
[SPEAKER_04]: When you get a season pass, like when I pick up Lost Season 7 on DVD, Episode 4 is suddenly missing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well, Episode 4 was a pre-order bonus only.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not how it works, yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think it's more appropriately titled as a bundle.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what you're selling.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're selling a DLC bundle.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: We haven't gotten into it yet, but for Saints Row 4, it's like...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, but they didn't market it as something that like, you know, season pass I think implies a particular thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And maybe this is just a terminology thing in our industry.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we've been here before with the whole download content that's actually on a disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think we were all sitting here on the show saying that is not DLC.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is pay to unlock content.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what I'm saying is that the Borderlands 2 season pass is not a season pass.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a DLC bundle.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can disagree with me if you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: that's fine, that's my opinion it's not a season pass, it's missing some episodes sensible so, anyhow
[SPEAKER_04]: Overall, that doesn't reflect on my opinion of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still think it's a fine game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think even if you don't like first person shooters, I think it's just got a really, you know, it's got a neat story.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's got some cool mechanics that are reminiscent of like an MMO and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very Diablo-esque.
[SPEAKER_04]: And co-op mode is a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will say that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, that was just my one little thing that did irk me a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you find yourself comparing guns a lot?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, like going, ooh, ooh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you have the passive-aggressive gun?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not yet, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, if you had been a better shot, you wouldn't have been wasting bullets.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those cost money, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was tough in co-op because what I'm used to in Diablo is that everybody gets their own loot.
[SPEAKER_04]: That doesn't happen in Borderlands, so if Bobby picks up all the ammo, I'm stuck.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: It will pool ammo, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, will it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I knew it pooled money.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it will pool ammo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay, my bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's the question I have to ask about this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got Borderlands 2 now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually have the first one because I got it for free back in the day.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do I have any benefit to finishing the first one before starting the second?
[SPEAKER_11]: No benefit from finishing... Well, a story, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: You get to learn a little bit more of the backstory of different characters because they do end up in the game as NPCs, so you know who this person is when you go and see them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Aside from that, the only other bonus you get is you get some unlockable skins when you play the first game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you have to have a save file from the first game, so just play for five minutes to get a save file going and then play Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, I mean, I watched Dan play the first one, you know, and I got so motion sick.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm planning on playing through Borderlands 2 and calling it a barfest when I stream it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I'm planning on streaming it.
[SPEAKER_11]: They have a third-person mode that you can unlock via hack.
[SPEAKER_09]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm looking at our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com Dungeon Buster says, it would have been nice if the season pass weren't limited to only for the four DLC campaigns, but would allow you to pick which four DLC you would want for the entire season.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, again, I don't think season pass is the name for that, but I really like the idea of pick them and choose them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would have bought the Mechamancer separately in addition to the season pass if I'd known.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I will take some accountability for not reading thoroughly as I should have but it's just kind of like a certain thing is sort of implied by that.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I was with you because I was like looking at the Mechamencer thing and I saw that it was separate too.
[SPEAKER_11]: It wasn't actually that that I noticed.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was I was going through some skins because I
[SPEAKER_11]: I modded it to unlock all the skins.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so I was going through the skins.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm like, oh, I want to wear that one.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it popped me to the Steam store.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm like, why does it show me stuff that's in there that I don't have?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you want me to buy it?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm not going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dangling the carrot in front of you.
[SPEAKER_04]: But again, all that other...
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what STO does, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: All that other junk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, STO's a free-to-play game, too, so you cut at some different concessions.
[SPEAKER_09]: But for paid outfits, it gives you the option of setting up that outfit, and then when you load the outfit on your character when you're making them, it says, this is pay XX amount.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, gotcha.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, speaking of free-to-play, the other game I've been playing this week, and I really can't explain how this happened, but I've sunk in about five, six hours in Dota 2, Defense of the Ancients 2, which is a free game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, there's probably some people out there going, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: League of Legends League of Legends League of Legends
[SPEAKER_04]: have influence from the original mod called Defense of the Ancients that was in Warcraft 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was an insanely popular mod to the game, just like Team Fortress was a popular mod to Quake, and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes mods become their own little thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Defense of the Ancients became its own game, essentially.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Valve has the Dota 2, there's League of Legends, and there's all these other games that are inspired by it, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blizzard's going to have their own thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: All-Stars, I think is what it's called.
[SPEAKER_04]: Heroes of Newerth
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing with Dota 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think what happened is I was looking around the community marketplace, I was looking at the trading cards, the value of cards, and I was looking at some of the stuff that was in Dota 2, like that was up there on the marketplace, and I decided to just launch the game because I wanted to see, because apparently I had some stuff from Dota 2 for just being in the beta.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I just wanted to launch the game and see what it was all about.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I noticed right away when I launched the game, the launcher looked different than it did before.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, oh, this is laid out all differently.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it threw me right into this tutorial mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want to learn how to start playing the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: So I said, all right, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to sit here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't get it when I played League of Legends, but maybe I'll get it this time.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I started to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played the first tutorial.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played the second tutorial.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I kept playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here I was.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was actually learning how to play Dota 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: And all these things that I'm sure if you're a League of Legends player sitting out there listening, you're probably going, duh, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: And then it takes you from that to, okay, now you're going to play a map and all you're going to do, you're going to take out one tower.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then it says, okay, now this time you're going to do a middle lane fight.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only lane that's available is the middle lane and it's a 1v1 map.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you just kind of learn and learn and learn that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: And right now I'm on the part of it where I'm playing an entire match against bots, but with limited heroes selection.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm like, I've been learning how to play the game and it's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's still an RTS, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's what they call a MOBA.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of a new genre of game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a multiplayer online battle arena.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's different.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't really say it's like an RTS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because RTS games just make me hurt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, imagine an RTS mixed with World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's really a crude way of putting it, but it's the best I can do.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still don't know that I would like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been thinking about it and I've seen people play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I hate real-time strategies.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's not because I'm not good at them.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm really good at them.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just think that they're very boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I would honestly recommend Dota 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just get in there and play the tutorial mode because you don't really play against other people until towards the end of it if you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the nice thing about Dota 2 is if you want to play an all bot match you can but here's the interesting thing now that I've done this now I want to go back and play League of Legends again because I feel like okay now I get it and everybody tells me League of Legends is kind of easier to wrap your head around than Dota because I guess there is still a lot of stuff beyond the tutorials and Dota that I haven't really experienced yet but I want to go back and play League of Legends and you know you can do bot matches there and everything's
[SPEAKER_04]: So, the only negatives I ever hear about these games is the community.
[SPEAKER_04]: That the communities in these games are really awful.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, the makers of the games, to their credits, are taking strides to try and combat that.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a big old blog post on the Dota 2 forums and League of Legends, I know, has their whole community tribal councils.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we were calling it on Horde House and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, they're trying.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, yeah, so this week I want to go back and play League of Legends and see if I get it this time.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll give it a... Okay, how about this?
[SPEAKER_09]: How about at some point this week, if I'm not completely fried with my new job, I will give it a try.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I will report on it by the next show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Techness in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com says, if you really get into Dota 2 League of Legends, you would actually find that they do play differently.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I don't doubt that, Technus.
[SPEAKER_04]: I read some of the comparison articles online.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard a lot about the timing and things that they do play differently in that regard and just the way they're laid out and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Technus says, I felt that League of Legends had a better hand-holding tutorial, but I haven't touched Dota 2 past beta.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that tutorial went in when it launched.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, Kasson in our chatroom, I hope I said that right, says, Dota has tutorials now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you're curious about it, why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I guess that was really my gaming week in a nutshell.
[SPEAKER_04]: So some quick housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't forget to visit our website at OrangeLaunchRadio.com and our Twitter, Twitter.com slash OLR and Facebook, Facebook.com slash OrangeLaunchRadio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I apologize.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was no Fugle Question of the Week this week, so we won't be able to do that segment in Part B. That is my bad and just the insanity crazy weekend I had.
[SPEAKER_04]: I literally threw this show together about an hour before we went live tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, we cut some quarters.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just thought of a question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we can ask it in two weeks when we come back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it won't be relevant then, but it's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: What were you going to ask?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll bring it up with my story.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say ask the chatters.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can get some immediate feedback there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'll ask the chatters and then we'll, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe some emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com Alright, let's get into the news tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, as the next continuing chapter of the 180 saga, Microsoft has now confirmed that despite what they said earlier, they made a small error and yes, there will actually be self-publishing now for the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_11]: And...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, Loki,
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: We don't know all the details yet of what the self-publishing is going to require.
[SPEAKER_11]: What you can do.
[SPEAKER_11]: It sounds cool that we can use any of the retail consoles as a dev unit.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: But we don't know yet what the requirements are going to be as far as submitting something in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you going to have to go through a review process?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is it going to be like XNA was?
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you mean by cover ground, cover their ass?
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, yeah, to help make up ground for that they lost.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, and then also there's a rumor that this might not just pertain to the Xbox One, that, uh, apparently the, um, developer Farsight Studios, um, who's, you know, done some work on the Pinball Arcade, uh,
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: So, it sounds like that this may also apply to the Xbox 360 as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, technically you have to file that in the rumor bin, but when it's coming out like this, it's kind of like one of those things where it's like, oh, they probably got told something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that game was a pretty big deal, and it sucks that it disappeared.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it's no wonder.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet Microsoft themselves kind of wants to get that game back.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, this is interesting with how they're going to do this, but at the same time, I mean, I don't know, this is almost like...
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, now that this isn't really exclusive to the Xbox One, you're kind of competing with yourself again.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just like all these great games are coming out on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why do I need to spend $500 to get an Xbox One that has pretty much the same games?
[SPEAKER_11]: They look slightly better.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: they have a 4 gig system with Kinect a 250 gig system they got rid of the 250 gig system with Kinect because that was competing with the Xbox One they figured that the people that are going to be buying that are going to be buying the Xbox One so then you have the Xbox One and then whatever holiday bundle it is that's their strategy going in and I think that's going to be going forward is how they're going to do it they're going to have 4 or 5 SKUs depending on whether there's a holiday bundle available or a bundle of some sort
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100, Matt in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says, just seems very vague.
[SPEAKER_04]: I expect this won't be ready day one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think a lot of this they're just trying to save because they're talking at Gamescom.
[SPEAKER_11]: They don't want to just like, yeah, you guys already heard all this information.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's just repeat it again.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I think it's kind of lame that they're doing that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, because, you know, people want to know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Developers want to know what the details are so they can consider making their games for your platform.
[SPEAKER_11]: And yet you're just like,
[SPEAKER_11]: AkumaJP in our chatroom says, Sounds like Microsoft is suffering from multiple personality disorder.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, to be fair, they did take a beating at E3, and they went through a major management change just in the past month.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the fact that some of these things are starting to come out isn't that surprising.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like, how fast can it really happen?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's all good news.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it's good news at the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it'll be interesting to see how it's going to work as far as like, are we going to see the Xbox Live Arcade marketplace turn into kind of like what Xbox Indie Games is?
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope not, because that's going to be really difficult to find stuff with everybody publishing titles.
[SPEAKER_09]: Especially since one of the big words they used was deliverability.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, they have to make it easy to access to make it deliverable.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think a lot of it too is it would really help them out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would think it's going to look more like iTunes because iTunes is the self-publishing central.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll tell you what this really is.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not about publishing on the Xbox One stuff, although that's good and everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: What it is is it's...
[SPEAKER_11]: The way they have it, the way you develop games, it's not even really the Xbox marketplace or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the Windows Store is basically what it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: When you publish a game, it's available for Windows 8, Windows Phone, and now the Microsoft Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what it's going to be, is publishing on all three platforms.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're trying to get to a point where...
[SPEAKER_11]: You buy Angry Birds on Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now you have Angry Birds on your Xbox One and on your Windows phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's exactly where my mind's going.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is key because that's how iTunes works if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can buy from your mobile device or your iPad or you can buy on your desktop.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then through the cloud, it all shows up on all your devices automatically.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I really think that's how the game systems ought to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony included.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo too if they could ever get there.
[SPEAKER_11]: unless you buy the better version for your iPad that takes advantage of the iPad's resolution but from what I heard from them they're a long way away from that like they may be promising something like that right now but 2015 at the earliest this is going to happen wow so it's a long way off wow
[SPEAKER_11]: We had discussions with the Microsoft reps about this kind of stuff because that was my thought and they were like, yeah, you're right.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm kind of hesitant at the same time as like, okay, you can develop games for Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are they really going to be Xbox One games, or are they going to be these Windows games running on that Windows OS portion of the Xbox 360 that just happened to be part of the Xbox One?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not actually a true native Xbox One game, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's going to be interesting to see what develops and also kind of how the Microsoft Sony dance continues with this.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I mean, obviously Microsoft's doing this in some way to catch up to Sony and their reaction they got at E3, but it'll be interesting to see what Sony might do to kind of one-up that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, let's talk about a big budget game and a game that a lot of folks are excited about over on Nintendo's platform, Smash Bros., Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, a new story came out this week that Masahiro Sakurai said that in the story mode, there will not be a subspace emissary storyline that was in Brawl.
[SPEAKER_04]: There will be a single-player campaign, however.
[SPEAKER_04]: But in Famitsu Magazine, he actually said that the story mode won't happen because cutscenes get uploaded on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: really weird excuse but here's the quote for us to ponder quote unfortunately the movie scenes we worked hard to create were uploaded onto the internet you can only truly wow a player the first time he sees a cutscene I felt if players saw the cutscenes outside of the game they would no longer service rewards for playing the game so I've decided against having them
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a very strange quote.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's chew on that for a minute.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a quote from somebody who doesn't understand how the internet works.
[SPEAKER_11]: Right.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, it's basically... I understand his point of view where, you know, woo, that's a really cool video and stuff, but...
[SPEAKER_11]: That's like saying, if you see a movie trailer, you're not going to want to see the movie because you saw scenes from the movie in the movie trailer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but with all the Let's Play and all of that, you can see a heck of a lot more than a trailer of a game that's out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand that, but not... And Nintendo's also taken a stance against Let's Play in the past, even though they might have went back on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But people that are watching Let's Play videos aren't necessarily going to be the people that are going to be spoiled by, Oh, I can't play this game anymore because I watched it being played through already.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not gonna be like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: If anything, it's gonna get people excited because they see these awesome cutscenes.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're like, whoa, I wanna see more of this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: But just instead of making excuses about YouTube and saying that's why you did it, just be honest.
[SPEAKER_11]: We want to get this game out right away.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is a feature that not a lot of people utilize, so we're going to focus on the multiplayer and make that the best part of the game because that's what people want to play when they play Smash.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just come out and say that instead of being a dick about it and saying, hey...
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it's because those people upload our videos on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, it's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm with you there a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really with you there a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: This does seem like a convenient excuse to get the game moving right along, which is fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, exactly the way you said it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think if he came out and said it that way, a lot of people would be like, yay!
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, if something we tried...
[SPEAKER_11]: Brawl, some people liked it, not a lot of people really played it.
[SPEAKER_11]: So instead of splitting our team down the middle and focusing it all on half on the single player and half on the multiplayer, we're just going to focus on the multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hell, that's what they did for Titanfall.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I still don't buy that excuse, by the way, for Titanfall either, because honestly, I do care about a single player campaign for Titanfall.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope that the game really kicks butt, but if the fighting element of the game is really, really good, then I think people will forget about this in six months.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there could have been a better way to deliver this news.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speaking of other bad news, or don't care about this news, who knows.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I've heard from people that there's various minds going on about this.
[SPEAKER_09]: But Polytron put out an announcement that Fez 2 was cancelled, and Phil Fish says, yep, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is going after some internet dramas of various...
[SPEAKER_09]: Bitch Levels.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just gonna go out and say it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's people being bitchy on the internet and people out bitching the other and out trolling the other.
[SPEAKER_09]: And actually...
[SPEAKER_09]: Listen to Bobby's show.
[SPEAKER_09]: He went off on it in a way that I 100% agree with.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's something that he would do because one of the things he was arguing about with the Annoyed Gamer thing was, what kind of art have you put out?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's almost like your stupid show or whatever is nothing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've created art with Fez.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like, dude, you've put out one indie game.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're not fucking God, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just, it's a game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it was great.
[SPEAKER_11]: People liked it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you're not like, just get off your high horse.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's one damn game, man.
[SPEAKER_11]: One game.
[SPEAKER_09]: This to me looks like an internet meltdown.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a movie, and reality shows distort people all the time, you always take that stuff with a grain of salt But this really just seems like a big pomp and circumstance about something that doesn't, this whole thing is like a waste of time And in the end Oh sorry, my favorite comparison I heard out there on the internet was that Phil Fish is the Amanda Bynes of gaming Okay
[SPEAKER_09]: My whole thing with it is that if you find yourself close to a meltdown and this is what you need to do is take a step back, go someplace safe where you have nothing to trigger you, watch some cartoons, sit back and watch some Adventure Time, open a couple beers, and play on Tumblr for a while because Tumblr is sort of safe too.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it happens to the best of us.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a diva fit here on OLR one night.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was an infamous moment that happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like five years ago at this point.
[SPEAKER_09]: You scared the shit out of Shermie.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: That wasn't at your place.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was at the studio.
[SPEAKER_09]: You had one at my house.
[SPEAKER_04]: I might have had a little one, but I had a big one when something like the wrong thing was said in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: And remember, I left and I'm like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you don't like... I left.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just...
[SPEAKER_04]: Quit mid-show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't quit the show, but I just said, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go do something more fun than this right now because I'm not taking this right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: No way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not making Fez 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I kind of sit here and go, you're going to take what this guy who calls himself an annoyed gamer says to get under your skin?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, and again, I don't know this other guy either, this annoyed gamer or whatever, but I kind of look at that name going, wow, you sound like everything that I hate about the games industry, all in two little words right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Besides, I am the annoyed gamer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't you just call yourself cynical fuck?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I'm just kind of like...
[SPEAKER_04]: the angry video game nerd did it better and that was parody yeah and he's actually hilarious and I think this other guy is kind of trying to be legit but it does seem weird to me again if the whole thing boils down to that you know Phil Fish did not want to comment on this you know Xbox thing that's going on he should have just said no comment or no thank you as opposed to fuck you you fucking fuck which is you know not a direct quote but the sense of what I get happened in that particular case
[SPEAKER_04]: I paraphrasing a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, like I said, he needs to take a step back, go to a safe place, maybe put on some old school Duran Duran, bop out a little bit to Hungry Like the Wolf, and then maybe come back with a cooler head.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, and I'm checking the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: ZZZ in our chat room says, Was the episode where Rob Rage quitted the show ever uploaded?
[SPEAKER_04]: I only listened to the podcast at the time and didn't get to hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the whole thing happened over a video card error that happened because that's why the listeners pulled together and bought this new computer that we broadcast the show from.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that happened after the D.Va moment.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think...
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the video card like went out mid show and I actually lost the show up to that point and then when we recorded again it was that comment was said and I think the show got thrown out I don't think it was ever podcast to be honest I think it was captured on because at the time we were streaming on Justin TV this is before Twitch existed I think some of it lived on there but I think it's gone long gone as too old at this point so unless we had our bootlegger you really don't need to see it
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't try to capture one of my worst moments in radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the downside to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like to think I've done about... It says it was on the feed and actually it isn't.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't either.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: One bad moment out of 514 episodes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do you want to fixate on that one bad moment?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because that's what people do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, maybe Lindsay Lohan was once a great actress, but people remember all the bad shit she's done.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about all the good things Lindsay did?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just people are focusing... Like going to rehab.
[SPEAKER_11]: People are just focusing on everything because it's just a slow news week, honestly.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, I couldn't believe how many people were like running, how many different outlets were running that story.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was just like, are you kidding me?
[SPEAKER_11]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't the whole thing that Bill...
[SPEAKER_04]: Phil Fish blew up at... Didn't the whole thing boil down to the fact that this media guy felt like he deserved a comment on the situation, was calling out him and Jonathan Blow because they wouldn't comment on the Xbox situation?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't that what it boiled down to?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was like... They tried to provoke a reaction.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they got one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was at a three-year-old's birthday party, and I look on the internet, because I check Twitter just every now and then.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe I should make him a rainbow penis cozy.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, annoyed gamer or whatever, welcome to my world, where we just get ignored.
[SPEAKER_04]: How would you prefer that?
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, I mean, I get ignored by all the different media outlets.
[SPEAKER_11]: Exactly!
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm like... Except occasionally Namco.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should be lucky you get any comments at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who are you?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, I'm the annoyed gamer, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm annoyed and I'm a gamer.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are kind of the OG annoyed gamer guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we talk about Saints Row 4 or Grand Theft Auto, you suddenly become the he-he-he gamer.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're more the tickled gamer when it comes to those games.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about the bipolar gamer?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm a little annoyed that I'm not playing Saints Row 4 right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is a little annoying, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: What does that make me?
[SPEAKER_09]: The crafty gamer?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Penis cozy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you're the rainbow penis cozy gamer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe we should send him one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe that would make him feel better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's 100% cotton.
[SPEAKER_08]: Feel it.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's too hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can already tell.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's move on with more news.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so, you know, to kind of keep along the theme of Microsoft fixing some of their hiccups in their, I don't know, game development process.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're working World of Tanks.
[SPEAKER_11]: The developer is basically saying, you know, they're working with Microsoft to help streamline the process of certification.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because certification takes quite a long time with Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_11]: and because games like free to play World of Tanks need some frequent updates to be able to push that through Microsoft it's very difficult to get one of those games to work on the Xbox 360 so right now they're working out what they need to fix on Microsoft's end to help alleviate some of that problem with the certification process
[SPEAKER_11]: So hopefully it'll get better.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hopefully this, by the time we get to November or whatever, I'm assuming it's November when this console is going to launch, that all this stuff will be ironed out and everything with self-publishing and all that stuff, it'll be a lot easier to get your game on there and keep it updated.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like a lot of this crap that Microsoft's had to go through is really going to make them a better company when it comes to gaming with all these things that they've had to kind of change, one of them being the certification process.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I wonder, like, I mean, I don't know if it's just a coincidence in timing or whatever, but, you know, the departure, you know, Don Matrick there, if he was holding all this stuff back, I mean, it's like, hey, we're fixing a lot of problems, but I think it's just coincidence, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know the next thing they need to fix, and maybe this is a little bit pie-in-the-sky dreaming, but the whole, like, no cross-platform play issue.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, because they let it go by with Final Fantasy XI, but they won't do it with Final Fantasy XIV, and I'm sure there's a host of other games that would like to, maybe Defiance or things that would like to be cross-platform.
[SPEAKER_11]: Honestly, I would like the ability to be able to play my game system without Kinect being attached.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not to say that you can't have Kinect features in your game, because obviously you can still program your game with Kinect features being in there, because you know every system is going to have a Kinect.
[SPEAKER_11]: But say I don't want to play with a Kinect on there, it just disables those features instead of not working.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if it is a Kinect-required game, sorry, this game requires Kinect, please plug in Kinect to play this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why is that so hard?
[SPEAKER_11]: I told her she should watch that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Does she like it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, she likes it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: On season two, they actually had an episode where it was all of the same stuff that's going on right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: NSA had this device to be able to spy on everybody using webcams and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dude, this is like way before all this stuff happened.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's the whole arc of the second season.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so hilarious.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was ironic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Scandal's a hella good show, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's total trash, but it's like one of those shows where it's like... Sometimes you want to watch a good drama show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why people watch Game of Thrones or Orange is the New Black or something, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to watch Matlock for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But sometimes you want to just watch crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's that bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, it's not a terrible show, but yeah, it's a little ridiculous in their plot.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't watch a show I have to turn off my brain for.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's about, like, Loki, she's banging the President of the United States on the side.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, that's a little bit like trashy romance novel, you know?
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's not as... Okay, coming from the fact that this show was created by the people that did Grey's Anatomy, they've toned it way down.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, they've toned it way, way down.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll give them props for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That actress is so good, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: She just commands the screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kerry Washington?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: She just commands the screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's so fun to watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now they want to talk TV and chat because Actdeft says Orange is the New Black is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm about three episodes in.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what I'm disappointed they got rid of?
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because all these shows I'm catching on, you know, Netflix and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Better Off Ted was actually great.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just don't understand why that show got canceled.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, we watched it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just... That's sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shadownextchat in our chat says everyone at OLR should check out the show Suits on USA Network the show is really well written and the cast plays off each other really well I have not seen that but the show on USA that everybody tells me I need to watch is Psych because that's the one that does all the tribute shows like they did the Twin Peaks episode and the Clue episode and they do all yeah that's the one I need to see there's only one show going to be coming out that I care about I don't even know the name of it but Seth Green's in it
[SPEAKER_11]: I am going to bring this back to games real quick here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, probably a good idea.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did see an advertisement today on Nickelodeon because my son was watching Spongebob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Next Saturday, they're going to be launching the show for The Rabbids, the animated series.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, that'll be coming next Saturday.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, if you're interested, check out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you let your son watch Spongebob?
[SPEAKER_11]: Only at my mom's house.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of kids, let's talk Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, bad transition, bad transition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, look, I honestly file this a little more in fan wank and people dreaming of what could happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a huge leap of faith, but I will bring it up anyway since we're about discussing the news, not necessarily reporting it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But apparently we heard about the problems that Atlas' parent company was having, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's this rumor out there that because there's going to be some subsidiary auctions going on on July 28th, Atlas is one of those subsidiaries up for sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Nintendo could be a key player in that because apparently there's already some financial liability in that whole situation.
[SPEAKER_04]: So could Nintendo end up buying Atlas, which would mean that's a development company for them that could end up meaning Persona ends up being a Wii U exclusive, Shin Megami Tensei ends up being a Wii and 3DS, Wii U exclusive and 3DS and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is there a Romance of the Three Kingdoms?
[SPEAKER_11]: Romance of the Three Kingdoms cross Pokemon game or something like that I think that's what it was and so they have that come out last year so because yeah they're working with them on that I don't think that's necessarily a reason and just because they publish a lot of those games on 3DS and stuff I don't think that's necessarily a reason that they're gonna purchase that company
[SPEAKER_11]: Honestly, I think it's just going to get purchased by somebody else and it'll just continue kind of the way Atlas is going.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe Marvelous USA or something like that will purchase Index Media because that's kind of all the wheelhouse there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the weird thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Today is July 28th, so it should be July 29th over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: We haven't really heard what's come of this yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's also morning.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: But still, that was supposed to happen on July 28th, so I'm not sure why we haven't seen a five-minute look at the news to see if anything's come out of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't see Nintendo purchasing anybody, because...
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: but the vast majority is on the 3DS still for it to be exclusive especially Persona that's a huge one right there if that series takes a leap over to Nintendo exclusive that's a big thing I am kind of of the mindset that I think most people that play Persona and again I am totally generalizing here and might be wrong fine I think most people that play Persona are the type that probably collect a lot of video game systems anyway and already have a Wii U
[SPEAKER_04]: But I am kind of making a big assumption.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about the reverse?
[SPEAKER_09]: We collect a lot of systems and I haven't played a single Persona game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe now you'll have a reason to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, because I don't have a Wii U. Not yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably won't get one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not ever?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario Kart 8 won't sway you?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was never a big Mario Kart fan.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Mario game at the end of the year won't sway you?
[SPEAKER_04]: There'll be something.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I would not be surprised.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shin Megami Tensei characters in the next Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_11]: game would not be surprised.
[SPEAKER_09]: We just haven't been really excited.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, if something, like, I didn't get a 3DS until Animal Crossing came out.
[SPEAKER_09]: And what have I been playing a crap load of?
[SPEAKER_09]: Animal Crossing?
[SPEAKER_04]: There'll be that one game that gets you over it.
[SPEAKER_09]: There might be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Animal Crossing Wii U, it'll happen eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm having more fun playing it portable but I mean but I mean I'm honestly I'm not really too excited about anything Nintendo's doing yet so alright ZZZ in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com says if Nintendo bought Atlus I would put an evoker to my head IRL now now now no need for that no need for that let's not go to extremes here
[SPEAKER_04]: to register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Use the passphrase, city.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, DarkSakura, what do you have for us before we get to release dates?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, a whole crapload of indie developers are coming together to be a super group.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're making a game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's called Experiment 12.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so these are 12 different developers included.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's Terry Kavanaugh who did VVVVVV in Super Hexagon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ian Snyder, Jack Kingspooner, Zaratustra, Richard Perrin, Michael Brough.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, just a bunch of people on the list.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's supposed to be kind of an interesting game associated with mental illness.
[SPEAKER_09]: But who knows what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've only got a few screen caps out so far.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's so far only on PC, but they're considering a Mac version.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I think it's a super group along the lines of Damn Yankees.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, they're going to get Ted Nugent to come out and play guitar.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: That is the weirdest comparison you've ever made on this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I look forward to seeing what these guys come up with.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ted Nugent, man?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talk about crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's travel around the world and check out some release dates and games that will be coming a little bit sooner than this experiment.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's not a whole ton of stuff coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pretty much, we've got the collector's edition of Terraria coming out on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's kind of a big deal.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it's just the game with, like, they have a pick-shaped USB drive and there's some vellum stickers and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: The actual PlayStation 3 version is on, it's a card to download the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: The 361, though, they put on discs like Minecraft, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: Rise of the Triad this week on PC.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm actually looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that like the remake?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the remake, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's going to be coming out, so that'll be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_11]: On PlayStation 3, a game which I noticed you still haven't reviewed or probably played yet, Arcania.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Complete Tale is coming out this week on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I've got to get my review done this week, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: uh so that's coming out and then um I think honestly that's it and I will have you know I have opened that case all right I am just saying yeah all right no I look forward for that on vognetwork.com soon
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, let's travel over to Japan and check out the releases over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: August 1st on the PlayStation 3, we'll see the release of Killer is Dead, the Premium Edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Metro Last Like, it's a Japanese release, this week as well on August 1st.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Sangoku Hime 2, Oki Haukou Kakosei Meshidaiga in Limited and Regular Editions comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was just checking out what kind of game that is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like it's a strategy game featuring cute little anime girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: and moving on to the Xbox 360 to see if we have anything there in Japan this week we have Killer is Dead and Metro Last Light both over there as well checking out some of the other consoles like PlayStation Vita PlayStation Vita has Mind Zero out this week on the Vita
[SPEAKER_04]: Puppies!
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that was a game about puppies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I gotta say, the Wii U list looks really bare for August.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe some games aren't dated yet, but the only other game for August, Wonderful 101.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that does it for Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's check out the UK.
[SPEAKER_09]: Only a bare few.
[SPEAKER_09]: On... What's today again?
[SPEAKER_11]: 28th.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, on the 20... Actually, only on the 31st we have PixelJunk Monsters Ultimate HD and I didn't see anything for the beginning of August, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: I forgot to mention since it is kind of next Sunday on the 4th I believe Pikmin 3 is coming out so that will be something yes there's that whole early release though yeah keep in mind Shadow Next Gen those were Japanese releases and I didn't see that on the list maybe that was the game that was the 8th of August so and those of you in chat that are saying Pikmin 3 is in August again those were Japanese releases I was reading
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's go to a couple more stories in the classic game of the week, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so, I mean, even we've kind of seen this a little bit, or this isn't shocking news, but even with just like our small group of...
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_11]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_11]: and what are they doing to, I don't know, combat that?
[SPEAKER_08]: No one likes pandas.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Basically, so far they're not really saying anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: Their comment is, despite the shrinking subscriber base, Activision Blizzard notes that World of Warcraft remains the number one subscription-based MMORPG.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Warcraft is backed into a corner I think they're going to need to go free to play I don't know how long Final Fantasy 14 is going to be able to get away with a subscription model to be honest if World of Warcraft goes free to play Final Fantasy 14 Final Fantasy 14 is going to be backed into at least the buy to play like Guild Wars model it's going to have to
[SPEAKER_11]: That's acceptable.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd probably play it if that was the case.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: They really talk about a lot of content for Final Fantasy XIV Realm Reborn.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the problem with Warcraft is really just in this stagnant place right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, I don't know what to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like they do keep trying to put out these new patches and things.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you think they're going to do a new graphical overhaul of the whole game?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think one of the two big things is coming with the next expansion at BlizzCon, and it's either going to be giant graphical overhaul to modernize the game, although I don't know if they would want to cut out all these... Part of WoW's allure is that it runs on old systems, but they do bump up the specs little by little each time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, they could just have that as an option, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not necessarily... Perhaps, perhaps.
[SPEAKER_09]: so I believe that will either come out or it's going to be free to play but Warcraft's kind of backed into a corner at this point it's going to be one or the other I've already quit ages ago because I mean I played through the Panda stuff and then it wasn't fun it just was more it was the same reason I was quitting before because I just kept getting bored
[SPEAKER_04]: I also shouldn't say it's gonna go necessarily because like you know if World of Warcraft had a hundred thousand subscribers it's still making some pretty good money I mean it wouldn't be a very pleasant place but they'd still be making money but you know Blizzard is gonna get people in in other ways Hearthstone you know is a free-to-play game that's gonna bring in some cash for them the Blizzard All-Stars thing they're working on that's gonna be a free-to-play game and
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to bring in some cash for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know what the hell Titan's all about, but then again, that's not really going to be out at least until 2016 at this point.
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100Matt speculates that the graphic overhaul will be Titan.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, there is some buzz that Titan is World of Warcraft 2, but I don't know how much stock I put into that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so far away that it probably doesn't even matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I sort of think EverQuest 2 and EverQuest kind of showed you really shouldn't do that to your MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yet, we have Final Fantasy XI and Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Final Fantasy XI is pretty much... It has its fans that have stuck with it this long that'll keep with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, hey, now that I'm working, I'm going to be playing XIV.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I've pretty much decided on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_11]: XI needs to go free-to-play.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, one more story for you guys before the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's about the cancellation of Mega Man Legends 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was about two years ago that Mega Man Legends 3 was cancelled.
[SPEAKER_04]: We never really got the reasons why this game was cancelled.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there was an interesting kind of report that came out this week about Gregaman, who's with Capcom Unity, talking about a recap of things we've already expressed in one form or another.
[SPEAKER_04]: So sort of a, I don't know, maybe like a post-mortem now all this time later about why the game was cancelled.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quote,
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember that Legends 3 was essentially a 10-year late sequel to a sequel to a spinoff that had middling success even back when it was one of the only games of its kind before 3D action-adventure was an established genre, if you can even remember that far back.
[SPEAKER_04]: And consider its place within the greater Mega Man brand.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you thought DMC was a deviation from the Devil May Cry brand, remember that MML changed virtually everything you could possibly change about Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even I remember scoffing at the sight of it until I got my hands on it and realized it stood on its own merits.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then consider that the game was designed for a platform that didn't even exist yet in the wild.
[SPEAKER_04]: All that isn't to say that MML3 was a bad project, it was just weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: But MML has always been a passion project,
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a cash cow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hence the dev room angle.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there is a little YouTube that showed a little bit of play from the game that's out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: They go on to talk about involvement in the community and so forth.
[SPEAKER_11]: At the same time, though, they're taking risks.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're putting out risks for different things.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're rebooting Strider.
[SPEAKER_11]: They made the Bionic Commando game and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And
[SPEAKER_11]: and you know and saying that it's completely different than the other Mega Man games well every Mega Man series is different than the other Mega Man games okay so it wasn't a 2D platformer game so what Zelda Zelda you know the 3D Zeldas weren't 2D platformer games anymore is that you're saying that that wasn't worth you know the risk I mean or you know Wind Waker is completely different than all the other games you know yet we're getting the re-release of that because apparently it just sucked so bad that we're just gonna re-release it again right you know it's not because people liked it or anything
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't this whole trial version of Mega Man Legends 3 they were going to put on the eShop for like five bucks?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't this practically done before they pulled the rug on it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I thought the whole thing was just to gauge interest in that stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: So release it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It doesn't make sense.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Make it download.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just make it download only.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the plan for the prototype thing they were going to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were basically going to do a paid demo to see if people were interested in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Give it to some fanboys and let them finish the last steps.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what they do now for everything on their stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember all the Dead Rising Zero stuff where it's a prequel but it's really just a demo.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's disappointing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's travel back to a time when things were a little simpler and maybe because we didn't have the internet or anything like that, we didn't get disappointed when games suddenly got cancelled.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although they might show up in a Nintendo Power and then suddenly disappear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or in this case, a Genesis Power.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or who knows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or a Sega Master System Power.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week this week?
[SPEAKER_09]: Fantasy Star, Wii, which I can't believe I haven't done this one yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't believe you haven't done it either.
[SPEAKER_04]: You kind of brought this up earlier in the show, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_09]: I did, because Dan's playing the Sega Ages Generation 1, which is Fantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_09]: We bought these back when the Sega Ages ones came out, except it was all in Japanese, and our friend was trying to translate while we were playing, and she's like, oh, well, this part isn't important.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't need to know what they said.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we're like, okay, we'll stop playing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dan, actually, someone has done an English patch.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I linked from the Generations one because the music in it was so good.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the first fantasy star came out on the Master System.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it came out in Japan on December 20th, 1987.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then in North America and Europe in 1988.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is one of the I'd say granddaddies of the RPG genre and it's also one of the first games that had a female protagonist.
[SPEAKER_09]: There have been other versions of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty traditional for RPG format.
[SPEAKER_09]: You go over your overworld maps, you talk to people.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your dungeons, though, are done sort of a pseudo-3D, where you're walking through, kind of first-person perspective, like it's, you know, Doom or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then it flashes into an over-the-shoulder view when you're fighting critters and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: and they even have little animations which is a lot more than Final Fantasy had at that time.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you get different weapons and magic and you have really memorable characters.
[SPEAKER_09]: You had Alice, you had Meow who's like this kind of cat thing and Odin and Noah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically those are your main characters through the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: You've got your antagonists.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically, this is one of the... And especially for the Sega fans, this is the game to have.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thankfully, we've got all the Phantasy Star games complete in their boxes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And trust me, it's something that's just really fun to have.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, like I said, it did get a re-release through the Sega Ages branding.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I think that the Generations 1 is really good.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's basically just touched up.
[SPEAKER_09]: It maybe looks like an early PS1 RPG, a little bit cleaner maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, I mean, you're taking a game from the Master System and updating everything in it, so it's a very, very good translation.
[SPEAKER_09]: The music's great, the graphics are great, they're really fun to play, and there is an English patch out right now if you've got a PS2 emulator.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although, I can't, you know, say, go do it, go do it, go do it, because that would be wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, the game right now, as far as the Master System version, um...
[SPEAKER_09]: It can go for a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: When the game first came out, it retailed for $70 and some places sold it for $80.
[SPEAKER_09]: And keep in mind, this was an 8-bit game, so that was a lot of money for an early game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And other ones that sold more than that were like Time Zone, but Phantasy Star was the most expensive console game ever sold at its time.
[SPEAKER_09]: and it did get a price drop when the Master System 2 hardware came out it had sequels of course we had Phantasy Star 2, 3 and 4 if I'm right I think 3 is the one that's really hard to find of course the other ones came out on the Genesis slash Master System
[SPEAKER_09]: With the Japanese release, one really neat thing about the first one is that it did take advantage of the FM chip, the Yamaha YM-2413 chip.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it had some really good sound, but since the North American Impala systems didn't have that chip, it doesn't sound quite as good.
[SPEAKER_09]: But on Virtual Console, you get an option of playing it with the FM soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_09]: So this is probably one of the greatest video games of all time, especially in the RPG genre.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's actually, as far as its popularity when it came out, it actually went sort of outside video game publications and was even mentioned in, like, Boys Life.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, which I don't even know if that magazine's out anymore, but wasn't it like one of old camping...
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought, wasn't that the Boy Scouts magazine or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I think it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I used to get it when I was in Cub Scouts.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I mean, seriously, if none of you have, and I'll be honest, I didn't play it when it came out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't played it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I played it as an adult.
[SPEAKER_09]: But even me coming into it as an adult, I still enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's one that anyone can pick up if you love RPGs And I also, being a fan of Phantasy Star Online It's sort of neat seeing how some of the graphics in the updated version Actually correspond to some of the updates in the Phantasy Star Online series So it's pretty neat Kind of seeing where it all came from
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like they pulled the original concepts and then with what they're doing for Phantasy Star Online, they're sort of merging the two, sort of bringing one up to date.
[SPEAKER_09]: A little bit slightly different, but they have lots in common stylistically.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Phantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, there it is, your classic game of the week, Phantasy Star for the Sega Master System.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, certainly the Sega Ages series on PlayStation 2 is a big part of that as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and like I said, it has been translated however you want to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: or watch people play it on YouTube like we've been doing here in studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: How much Mercedes do you have on you, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, 50 bucks maybe?
[SPEAKER_09]: I had to laugh because Dan actually called me when I was in the back room last night saying, I finally got to the Rappies!
[SPEAKER_09]: Come look at them!
[SPEAKER_09]: I was like, I'm watching Dan kill Rappies because I hate Rappies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's interesting how much of that... Playing Phantasy Star Online as much as I did, it's interesting going back to the Phantasy Star games and seeing where the Monomates and the Telepipes and all that come from.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yes, the Rappies too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to tell you a story about Julie.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know which Julie I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_09]: Julie paid $120 to order a Rappie plushie.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's as big as my upper torso.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's dedication.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's probably almost as wide as your table.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a gigantic Pikachu.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, take your Pikachu and make the wrappy a little bit bigger than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And fully stuffed in, you know, with the bits and everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's because she was that much into PSO at the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds adorable.
[SPEAKER_09]: That sounds like a waste of money.
[SPEAKER_09]: Judge, judge, judge.
[SPEAKER_04]: We all do silly things.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would have just made one.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to take a break, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio, some rapid-fire news, of course, the mailbag, what little may be in there, and we'll talk a little bit at OUYA, and take your calls as well if we have some folks who want to call tonight at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: But all that when we come back after this break with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio, live on this Sunday evening, July the 28th, 2013, with the 514th episode of our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to get back into some news here in a moment.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wanted to make sure I got a clear plug out here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mentioned this in the beginning of the show, but I just wanted to make sure I got a plug out here to my buddies over at GameBooey Podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's GameBooey.org.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just think Game Boy, but B-U-O-Y.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gameboy.org.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to be on episode 33, part B of their show.
[SPEAKER_04]: The episode was so long, they split it up into two parts, but I'll be on the part B, which was like almost three hours in itself.
[SPEAKER_04]: We talked all about music games tonight was the topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, or I should say today, music games was the topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, just having done the early days of OLR, we were nothing but music game chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a lot to talk about hence why the show was so damn long but it was a really good time we had a lot of fun taping it so be sure to check that out over at Gameboy.org episode 33B I will be on First Mate Slidekick should have that posted on Monday it's not up there yet although it is a fantabulous show you can go check out their old episodes
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get back into some rapid fire news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so let's talk a little bit about old games.
[SPEAKER_11]: For example, Star Control.
[SPEAKER_11]: Star Control was one of the franchises that was being auctioned off as part of this whole Atari...
[SPEAKER_11]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: Wargaming Total Annihilation
[SPEAKER_11]: Master of Orion, Moonbase Commander, Epic Gear, Tomo, Humongous Franchise,
[SPEAKER_11]: Fatty Bear's Birthday Surprise and Math Grand Prix Fatty Bear's Birthday Surprise?
[SPEAKER_11]: Fatty Bear's Birthday Surprise.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm assuming these are all educational PC titles at some time.
[SPEAKER_04]: What exactly would Fatty Bear get as a birthday surprise?
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, a fatty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some honey.
[SPEAKER_09]: A rice cake.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fatty Bear.
[SPEAKER_04]: He gets cholesterol.
[SPEAKER_04]: He gets... Oh, Loki, you could appreciate this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tangent time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Choo-choo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Alan and I went to the State Fair on Friday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know they've got deep-fried food like crazy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Act surprise.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Deep Fried Red Velvet, but we settled on Deep Fried Oreos.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Alan, do you want to talk about how they tasted?
[SPEAKER_05]: They were really good, but at the same time, it's almost too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm at that age where I'm like, okay, it's not disgusting, but I only just wanted one or two, and you made me eat three of them out of the four.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so it was delicious.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have you had deep fried Oreos, Loki?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, but I'm very disappointed that you didn't talk about the booth dedicated to bacon.
[SPEAKER_11]: They had a whole bacon booth.
[SPEAKER_04]: We didn't find the bacon dedicated booth.
[SPEAKER_04]: We saw like the chocolate covered bacon and we saw the bacon maple something something.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, they had a whole booth that was dedicated to bacon there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, we missed that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't go.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't see how you could have missed that.
[SPEAKER_11]: There should have been mile-long lines going to that booth.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was empty.
[SPEAKER_04]: We went Friday morning.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had the day off work.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess Fatty Bear would want some deep-fried Oreos.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had deep-fried bacon there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So fried Coke is when they take funnel cake batter and they put Coke syrup in it until it turns brown inside of Coke flavored.
[SPEAKER_05]: They drizzle it into the hot grease so that it looks like a funnel cake.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all just, you know, the little ropes of dough.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they put that in a cup and they sprinkle powdered sugar on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they put more pure Coke syrup on top of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's fried Coke.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then fried Kool-Aid is pretty much the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: They put Kool-Aid in the dough or in the batter and then they put Tarani strawberry syrup on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you remember when we did fried Twinkies at... I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was like our sideshow at... It wasn't... It was... Shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sacramento hosts another fabulous tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what we publicly called it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were selling deep fried Twinkies for no reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, through half of one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're so... Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to go to our chat room at live.vognetwork.com because we have... Ionotropic says, Loki wants deep fried gummy bears, three pound bag version.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why would you want... By the way, that took me two days to get through that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw a tweet from you that was like, my stomach's so full.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I was like, why do I keep eating these things?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because they're delicious.
[SPEAKER_11]: Still eating them as I'm posting it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Delicious.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, so basically... Yeah, it took me two days to get through that three pound bag.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, actually, I wouldn't want deep fried.
[SPEAKER_11]: It would just dissolve into mush because it would, you know, liquefy.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had some weird stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like this one booth had like 20 different things.
[SPEAKER_05]: There were deep fried Pop-Tarts.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was like, that's already bready.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, why would you just want to put more dough on that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Deep fried.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did they have deep fried?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fruity Pebbles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Deep fried Fruity Pebbles.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I think deep fried Cocoa Puffs and Captain Crunch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, like different cereal.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fruity Pebbles might have been alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: See, that's something more of you bread it with that, you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just going to tell you right now that all of that sounds really disgusting.
[SPEAKER_11]: What gaming thing?
[SPEAKER_11]: Fatty Bear.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's the one that was disgusting.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't remember what they called it, but it was a deep fried Twinkie with some sort of cheese on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it was either Cheez Whiz or some sort of nacho cheese wrapped in bacon.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was a Twinkie wrapped in bacon with cheese and then deep fried.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm having a heart attack listening to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spray cheese is always automatically disgusting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry if that's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not anyone's lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Easy cheese is gross.
[SPEAKER_09]: When it says cheese food on the label, you know that's what cheese eats.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, back to video game news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Alan, for bringing a little fatty bear to our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't mean that in a negative way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where are you going?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: and last but not least they're already talking about the DLC plan for Saints Row 4 which doesn't sound like much as far as like content stuff the first piece of DLC is going to be the Enter the Dominatrix now you may be thinking hey wait a second didn't Enter the Dominatrix become Saints Row 4 I mean they kind of expanded upon it
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it's not necessarily gonna be... That's kind of all the stuff they cut out of the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stuff that they couldn't really work in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now there's gonna be some sort of mockumentary take on all the things that they couldn't do for the game, but...
[SPEAKER_11]: I did watch some interviews where they pulled a Bethesda where the Skyrim team had a week to develop whatever they wanted for the game
[SPEAKER_11]: and so Saints Row they did the same thing at Volition they had all sorts of things like a dragon that breathed fire that you would have been able to ride was one of the things that you know they were going to try to do but it just didn't work in the game um you know some of the limitations and stuff so I hope some of that stuff becomes DLC that would be pretty cool but um they do have a season pass that they announced that's only two pieces of DLC and it's ten dollars
[SPEAKER_11]: that once again as we were talking about before in part a that's a bundle that's not a season pass as a bundle of dlc because it's two the season pass is not two things
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess I'll have to buy it because it's only two.
[SPEAKER_09]: A season pass would be they give you these two things and then you've paid for the other stuff that comes out that season.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I have a feeling there's going to be a ton of customization DLC like they've had before.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's all paid unlock stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure they're going to have that available.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's how they did Saints Row the Third.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, moving on to some other stories in gaming real quick here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Connect Sports Rivals, that was one of those games that was announced for Xbox One at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has been confirmed that it will miss the launch window.
[SPEAKER_04]: Originally, this game was going to come out in November.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, Microsoft told Polygon that there is a delay and it is necessary in order to give Rare enough time to polish it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before launch So it just wasn't ready to go Spring of next year, the new time frame that's being given for that These things happen all of the time Launch games get pushed back Wasn't Pikmin 3 supposed to be a launch game for the Wii U?
[SPEAKER_04]: And now it's just now coming out?
[SPEAKER_04]: These things happen You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Take the time to get it right Even though this game doesn't really sound like one I'm really interested in anyway It still might be interesting for other people It's one of those family games Yeah, it's a family game, kiddie game Families aren't going to be picking up Dead Rising 3 for their little kids True, very true
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you kidding?
[SPEAKER_09]: I would totally play that when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully this delay won't cause people to go over to the Wii U. Or, well, depending on how you look at it, maybe this delay will, yay, make people go over to the Wii U. However you're looking at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the Wii U is looking at possibly a Legend of Zelda Wind Waker HD bundle.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a report from an inventory system at a major US retailer.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know which one, so take this with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_04]: These stories are often a little eh, unless Loki, of course, is the one reporting on it, because I trust him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo is looking at a Wii U bundle for Legend of Zelda Wind Waker HD, supposedly a 3DS handheld that comes with Pokemon X and Pokemon Y as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, aren't there those limited edition 3DSs with Pokemon with the art on them?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know those are coming out in Japan, so it would seem very logical those come out here, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Those might come out over here.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're supposed to be getting that 3DS, the black 3DS XL, next month.
[SPEAKER_11]: The one that was rumored to be coming out over here is actually coming over here next month.
[SPEAKER_11]: Surprisingly enough, actually, Zelda is coming out a lot earlier than I thought it would be, because I pegged that as a November title, but they said it was October, and it's actually the first week of October, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, I was going to say, October is when these games are launching, so you could bet that this bundle will come out at the same time.
[SPEAKER_11]: First week of October for that, and third or fourth for We Party You, which no one gives a shit about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, you never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: There might be that one fan.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then there's probably, I'm assuming then, you know, November is going to be the 3DSL, then, you know, Super Mario World 3D.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Disney is looking into a new technology called Aerial Aerial is a new invention that blows air
[SPEAKER_04]: That's supposed to simulate a tactile experience.
[SPEAKER_04]: So in other words, you're supposed to be able to feel objects where there might not necessarily be one because of the way the air goes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was created by PhD student Rajanidhar Sodhi and a Disney researcher, Ivan Popriev.
[SPEAKER_04]: It can be placed on a TV or even on an iPad.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it can actually simulate buttons to touching in midair to making you feel like water moving.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stone, Sand This could actually be something really cool My mind always goes to Disney theme parks and how could that make rides feel That might be really cool I just don't understand how that would work The tech is in a very early phase so no word on where this is going They have a YouTube up if you want to see more about it There you go You alright over there?
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate Destructoid for iPad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hate.
[SPEAKER_09]: It brings up an ad and then it shuts down my Safari.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm on spite.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't want to read that story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which one was it?
[SPEAKER_09]: The Zelda mod.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can mention it real quick here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Jamie out of spite will not be telling you about this Legend of Zelda mod.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got a great trailer, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's a fantastic trailer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently it's this mod for Zelda.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to figure out what Zelda game it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not for Zelda.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's almost like all the different Zelda worlds put together.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's the medieval Total War.
[SPEAKER_04]: Total War.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, so it's the other way around.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the Zelda hack for Medieval 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's really crazy.
[SPEAKER_11]: The trailer, they've got giant characters and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course there's an add-on.
[SPEAKER_09]: All I read was carrying around Link's dead corpse.
[SPEAKER_11]: but I and I do give the ad credit because I did see the same ad earlier today and I did not know Sigur Rs had a new album coming out so I yes that was it's out now actually yes that was they're going on tour again oh I really need to see them they're a great band just just but anyways yeah there's got they've got some really crazy stuff as you get into it um
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't know who some of the characters were.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, obviously I know who that is.
[SPEAKER_11]: But there was, like, they had some of the guy from Majora's Mask or whatever in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: This looks neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: It looks very, very epic.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some of it looks a little bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: A little derpy, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Her crying looks a little bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I think it's supposed to be, like, some sort of... But, yeah, like, that thing looks cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what that is, but... It kind of makes you want to check out Medieval 2 Total War, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but, like, let's see if this is the one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Towards the end there, they've got some really cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Jamie, there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you, because their page has never worked right on my iPad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop crashing people's iPads, fools.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your developers seriously need to have their hands slapped.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: Destructoid, hire better designers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gauntlet thrown.
[SPEAKER_09]: um anyway uh there is a report that a Gran Turismo movie is in development um it's uh supposed to be produced by let's see Michael DeLuca and Dana Brunetti and uh they're also the people though that are working on Fifty Shades of Shit I mean Grey so I don't know how I would think about that whatever
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, in other news, this is, well, you know, we rag on dating games every so often, but this one is just hilarious.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is an appearance in a dating game by Keiji Inafune.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, it's, uh, basically the game is called Sweet Fuse.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a dating game for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you can seduce one of seven steamy bachelors.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, uh, Inafune is, uh, in the game and you can, uh, court him.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_11]: They have that coming out on PSP over here.
[SPEAKER_11]: The end of August.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now that I know what that is, that's even creepier.
[SPEAKER_09]: His, uh, portrait here looks creepy.
[SPEAKER_09]: And he's listed as legendary creator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on to some more news in the meantime
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so sales haven't been that great.
[SPEAKER_11]: There was an article that was on Gamasutra, and they were talking, or I should say polling some of the developers that have games on there, and they were talking about some of the attach rates and stuff and how not good they are.
[SPEAKER_11]: For example, one of the games, I guess, Hidden in Plain Sight, it's brought in $4,381 on 1,900 purchases, and that was basically sold at a pay-what-you-want price, so
[SPEAKER_11]: Minimum $1
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, there was another game, Get On Top, that's earned $728 off of 9,700 downloads and 520 purchases off that.
[SPEAKER_11]: They were saying some of them, like Bomb Squad, which is one of the more popular games, peaked, I guess, 200 sales per day, and now it's sort of around 70 per day, which is a $5 game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a really indie guy who created a game called Bomb Ball who's made a little over $30 a day.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not terrible.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, for an indie, maybe that's not terrible.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then Tower Fall, which is probably one of the most notable games on the OUYA right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: He said they've reached about 2,000 sales so far at $15 each.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, $30,000?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: But basically, overall, the stats have shown that I want to say that only about 27% of people that have an Ouya have actually bought games for it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whereas everyone else is just playing kind of free stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to say it was 27%.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was some ridiculously high number of people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now are we talking like actual free stuff like, I don't know, the Amazing Frog and the Parking Valet or No Breaks Valet and the stuff that's actually free on there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or do you think emulators?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's just that they're playing a lot of the free stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think that it's necessarily... I think that a lot of the developers on there are... Yeah, 73% of owners haven't bought a thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I don't think right now that
[SPEAKER_11]: I think some of the developers that are on there probably have never published the game before.
[SPEAKER_11]: They may not know how much of the game to give away for free.
[SPEAKER_11]: There was something, I don't remember which game it was, where they were saying they had certain difficulty levels that were available and the higher difficulties were behind a paywall.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: so it's just I think it's a lot of it's just experiment a lot of new people putting stuff on there that you know they may not be they may not know all the tricks to being able to bring in revenue on that kind of pay model you know it leads us to this interesting comment in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com from our pal Bobby Blackwolf who says why buy games when you can pirate them so easily
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, that's the thing, though, is you can't really pirate Ouya games too easily on there, at least as far as I'm aware.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can pirate all other Android games on there quite easily, but you can't pirate Ouya games themselves very easily that I've seen.
[SPEAKER_11]: But yeah, because they don't have the Google Play Marketplace tied to this console, there's nothing to check for the authenticity of...
[SPEAKER_11]: Those purchases, so anything you sideload on there, if you happen to download a random API for anything, it will just run it, full version or whatever, and it'll just run it without having to purchase it.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, yeah, in that sense, it is really easy to pirate games on there, but for the actual Ouya games, it's not, because of the way they have it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, that could very well change if, you know...
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what they would have to do to do that or if they can even put the Google Play Store on there I know you can sideload that but yeah it's just
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: Why spend the money on an Ouya when you can just spend your money on something else that works a lot better?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just like a lot of people have taken the Ouya concept and made it better.
[SPEAKER_11]: Unfortunately, there's not really anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: They can't just put out another Ouya right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be very interesting to see where the Ouya ends up in about six months, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyhow, moving on to another news story about a game you're not going to be able to get on the OUYA, but probably about everywhere else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Disney Infinity.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, Disney Infinity, of course, has Toy Box, which is like the creation mode, which, you know, makes me kind of think at first about like LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't realize really how powerful this is until I saw this video.
[SPEAKER_04]: And in this video, somebody basically recreated Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-1.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what's weird to me about this video is that, like, isn't this, like, an official type of, like, trailer or whatever?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, well, what's interesting about this is that they actually show, like, there's the little staircase with Buzz Lightyear going to a flagpole, and it's like, wait a minute!
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
[SPEAKER_11]: Isn't level 1-1 kind of... It's not similar with LittleBigPlanet 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to be fair, it's just one small component that you see in the video here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But still, wow, it looks very powerful.
[SPEAKER_04]: And are you going to be able to share these across the internet and all that good stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure you will be able to.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, you will be able to.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is going to be an interesting game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting player.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've already seen some of the next characters coming out too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like they've got...
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not stuff that's new because they've shown them in the trailers already.
[SPEAKER_11]: Perfect example right here.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're going to have the stuff from Wreck-It Ralph.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're not going to have a Wreck-It Ralph play set, but they're going to have a Wreck-It Ralph... They're going to introduce a new thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Instead of the play sets, it's a...
[SPEAKER_11]: Toybox set basically it's the characters and you get pieces for the toy box instead of you know an actual play set they're gonna have a Toy Story one coming out Jack Skellington around the same time and then I think in the Toy Story one it's Buzz Lightyear and because I haven't watched Toy Story 2 it's the the female cowboy
[SPEAKER_09]: Jesse.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it's going to be Buzz and Jesse and then Woody sold separately.
[SPEAKER_08]: Buzz has Jesse and no Woody.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it's just they always put a female character in there because they want the appeal.
[SPEAKER_11]: Except for the starter pack, it's all males.
[SPEAKER_11]: But for cars and stuff, they try to put a female character in there so that girls will buy it too.
[SPEAKER_11]: So they can play as the girl characters and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: but yeah it looks fun I mean it's expensive I just don't want to buy all those characters any word about like exclusive figures only at parks or things like that I haven't heard of anything yet I mean they haven't really said that they're gonna do stuff like that it might come later on like next year I mean assuming this all takes off I know Skylanders does that they have exclusive characters for Toys R Us but usually they're just recolored characters and it's dumb
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I got tangled.
[SPEAKER_09]: And not in a fun way either.
[SPEAKER_09]: So anyway, we've talked a little bit about the Oculus Rift thing, about how kind of creepy it can be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Creepy awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there is a Japanese sex game that will be bringing out Oculus Rift support.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: The game is called Custom Made 3D, and it basically lets you create a maid that you can play with.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it comes with a controller called the Juicy Air Support.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like a move controller, but it is... It's a fleshlight controller.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: So thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: So now, even though the game's been out for a little bit, it's got Oculus Rift support.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you can get your action a little bit more up close and personal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cutting edge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever you're into, have fun with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever sinks your battleship.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, we've talked about this on the show before, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: TTP, which is for time to penis, which usually is about peripherals.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that is, how long will it take when they release this peripheral for someone to stick their dick in it?
[SPEAKER_11]: or how long will it take for someone to create a giant phallus in their toy box?
[SPEAKER_11]: 10 seconds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's another further proof of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this great new technology comes out how long before somebody figures out how to work in wieners and boobs?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure this isn't necessarily the first attempt either as those development kits have been out for a bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, just a few more stories for you guys in the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so Nintendo is now working to draw some indie support as well to the Wii U. Already, it's pretty easy to publish indie titles on the Wii U, and you do see a lot of indie games coming to the Wii U, especially a lot of Kickstarter-backed stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: You'll see, like, hey, we're making a Wii U version of it as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, there were some comments done by...
[SPEAKER_11]: some of these indie developers including I guess Daco Daco is one of the studios they have a game called Scram Kitty and his buddy on the rails or buddy on rails and that'll be coming to Wii U basically they don't shout very loud about it but they are working hard behind the scenes to make their platform as welcoming as possible I gotta see what the hell this game is
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's got a cat.
[SPEAKER_11]: It looks kind of evil.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a... Puzzle platformer?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then, of course, they're saying that... Former... I can't even pronounce this guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: This company, Niam Niam... Where...
[SPEAKER_11]: Niam Niam, I think that's Niam Niam.
[SPEAKER_11]: Niam Niam.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to say Nom Nom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nom Nom.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're saying they focus quality over quantity.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're actively seeking indies, but they're looking for quality, experienced developers that can maybe form a longer-term relationship.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess they're bringing Tengami is the game they're bringing there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dreamfall Chapters Dreamfall Chapters
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Lolo Ranger
[SPEAKER_04]: The Lone Ranger, the Ryan Reynolds and Jeff Bridges movie really tanked too that just came out like last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: R.I.P.D.?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, that one really tanked too.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know some of these companies are having to take big losses on these and that's why a lot of movie companies really prefer to find these low budget movies that don't cost a lot of money that make...
[SPEAKER_04]: Ryan Reynolds Deadpool
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's a good example.
[SPEAKER_11]: Clerks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty much any movie that guy makes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except for Jersey Girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Mallrats.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mallrats was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it was a good movie, but it didn't profit, really.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not all of his movies profit, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how we got on that tangent.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess because about indie games, there's a potential for better return on investment there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know exactly how it happened.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because the same thing also happens in the movie industry.
[SPEAKER_09]: For example...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I totally forgot this movie came out this weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tigerclaw said he saw The Wolverine.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Wolverine came out this week and did really well at the box office.
[SPEAKER_04]: It literally made back its budget.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wanna see it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I do, but... It looks so terrible, too, and that's kind of...
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, as an 80s Wolverine reader, we're forgiving.
[SPEAKER_04]: The weird thing to me is that I thought they already made a Wolverine movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I guess this is like a sequel or whatever, or a different direction.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is taking on the whole Wolverine in Japan arc.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's the same guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so weird to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hugh Jackman is a good actor, you know, just on the general.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to pet him.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know that his wife would like that, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course you do.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure some of you guys saw this crazy video that was out there on the internet this week where some folks were driving a car with a Nintendo controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, obviously, there are limits to this, but cables that connect the controller to the electronic unit inside the car, a 2010 Ford Escape and a Toyota Prius.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was a project funded by DARPA, and it's to raise awareness about over-reliance on computer systems and vehicles.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the researchers who goes by Charlie Miller said, quote, we would love for everyone to start having a discussion about this and for manufacturers to listen and improve the security of cars.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if that's how most people are taking this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think most people are looking at it going, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Mario Kart for real.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meanwhile, we have operatorless cars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Driver's School Driver's School
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: Echolocation sensors, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that brings us to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: And every week you guys can email us at mailbag at orange lounge radio dot com.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura will dive in the mailbag head first and hopefully she won't find the anthrax.
[SPEAKER_04]: But she will.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was talking about an 80s metal band, but she will find some excellent emails.
[SPEAKER_09]: If it's anthrax and a public enemy, sign me up.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: She will find some of your emails to read here live on air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, that's mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please feel free to email us unless you are a spammer, in which case you can fuck right off.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can fuck off and die.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We actually have had a last-minute, looks like, email that came after the show last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I emailed earlier but forgot to ask, is it possible that for the FUs of the week you could play the old Final Fantasy Advent Children's Life Raw theme?
[SPEAKER_09]: I miss it so bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: That should be badly, by the way, that's an adverb.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks again, Reesimo.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Should I try to dig that up and give this guy his wish?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'll dig that up while you replay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Only if you use adverbs correctly in the future.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not so bad, it's so badly.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a conditional granted request.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're having some faith in you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't say I want that so bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: We believe in you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want that so badly.
[SPEAKER_04]: We believe in you, but don't you dare let us down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awful.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please call me Surtr.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, Surtr.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know DarkSakura has been having house buying drama.
[SPEAKER_09]: God, no shit, especially today.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I thought I'd encourage her with my own success story.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or make me jealous, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a long-term renter and I've been saving for a home, but I needed that final push to start the arduous home buying process.
[SPEAKER_09]: The spring I was playing Animal Crossing Wild World on my 3DS XL and paying my loan to Nook and it hit me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I should be paying off a mortgage for reals.
[SPEAKER_09]: Long story short, I'm closing on house on August 19th.
[SPEAKER_09]: Next I plan on getting married after playing Harvest Moon.
[SPEAKER_09]: You gonna get a cow?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, is this for real or is this kind of troll?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I kind of, like, you seriously?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, sometimes people have aha moments.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry if I called you a troll, but it's just kind of amusing to me that you played Animal Crossing and you realized, wow, I should go get a house for real.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then the whole, I should go get a girlfriend for real, that's where I'm starting to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this such a troll?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was actually...
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey y'all Hey
[SPEAKER_09]: Ha!
[SPEAKER_09]: This is from Osfer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh god, this is long.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stop it!
[SPEAKER_09]: Stop!
[SPEAKER_09]: In the weeks following this year's E3 showing, I sought out other video game podcasts to listen to, in addition to yours, of course.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good.
[SPEAKER_09]: While I did enjoy some of the other shows I heard, I came to the realization that the host of OLR is what truly gives it a solid advantage over the rest of the competition.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, shucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have three hosts, each with very different backgrounds, and each of which cover a different social aspect and identity.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love what each personality brings to the table as well, and I love your grammar.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, while often funny, yet ranty voice of the show, plays an important role of speaking openly his thoughts on what a lot of gamers might have on their minds, but might not have the balls to speak it.
[SPEAKER_09]: His rants are welcome, at least by myself.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's got an amazing head on his shoulders and shows that he's very knowledgeable about the industry as a whole.
[SPEAKER_09]: These rants only happen because he's a guy that truly cares about the games and the gamers who play them.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, DarkSakura, long emails are okay when they exist to inflate our egos a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep going, sir.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep going.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, it's the part about me next.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura is a bitch.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura is a very admirable host due to her ways in which she approaches deep gaming discussions or discussions on any topic for that matter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you saying I get off topic?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: While sometimes she may be quiet for the initial talk between Rob and Loki, you can tell she has been gathering her thoughts to make some great points.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, she hasn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's been catching bugs.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_09]: I turned off Animal Crossing in the middle of Bobby's show just because I had a visitor.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been crocheting the whole time, but I've been listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Her penis cozy is now like a boa constrictor cozy.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're really going to have a limited target demographic with that one.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to say this.
[SPEAKER_09]: It helps me concentrate to have something to do with my hands.
[SPEAKER_09]: and as a corporate trainer during the day I can actually say that as like some people when they are actually like moving their hands it's very like they actually learn more that's why they encourage it's called kinesthetic learning oh I know I like at one meeting when I was working for the student loan place and they put out Legos to see if we retained more by playing with Legos I built a little tower but I remembered more anyway where was I more stuff about me okay
[SPEAKER_09]: just been gathering her thoughts to make some great points and also quick to point out something the other hosts may have missed she's an awesome listener and I really admire her desire to understand what others may have trouble communicating such as the incident of an angry email the show received that bashed another host close to the OLR family even through that she calmly read through and restated the point the email was trying to get across gaming wise and that's pretty freaking awesome that she even gave it the chance well thank you
[SPEAKER_04]: You were a saint for giving that email a chance, but yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then there's Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, then there's that guy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some may say he's the glue that holds the show together.
[SPEAKER_09]: Others may poke fun at him for making flappy hands while taking a single shot of some sort of outfit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob, as a gay gamer, you've certainly felt what it's like to be pressured by your family before coming out to them.
[SPEAKER_09]: You must know what it's like to have them wondering why you aren't trying to find a girlfriend or to feel that pressure that you have to please them by giving them grandchildren one day.
[SPEAKER_09]: at least you might have felt that until you came out to them how did you do it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I asked because very recently I was on a walk with my dad he's very conservative, often scoffing at any gay issue that he sees that comes up in the news yet when I showed him concerns about my uncle telling us that you choose to be gay and if you're gay you're going to hell obviously this isn't true and when I told him that I had sour feelings toward him because of it he said you shouldn't hate someone because of something they said they might just be uninformed
[SPEAKER_09]: After this you followed up with you can be with whoever you want with as long as it makes you happy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't care what you want to do with your life as long as it satisfies that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Should I just tell my parents that I'm gay?
[SPEAKER_09]: I know this is a tough question but I don't know anyone better to come out to about this except for yourself.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll make my decision based on what you tell me following this email.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sincerely, Osfer.
[SPEAKER_09]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really sorry this email is a bit long.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just need some thoughts out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can I say one thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Please.
[SPEAKER_09]: Usually your parents know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, this is what I was going to get to as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a very heavy email and not about games, but I'm all about there's more to gaming than the games themselves, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: because the first thing my grandma said when my mom said Rob's gay is my grandma said so what which is a great thing I realize though that I'm very fortunate in that regard where I have a very cool supportive environment and not everybody is so lucky like your uncle sounds like a bit of a knob you know unfortunately you may not get that same level of support from him and
[SPEAKER_04]: The point I wanted to get at, though, is that the reason why my mom escalated in asking me the question is that apparently, unbeknownst to me, I had a female friend stay the night at my place once while I was in college.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she called her parents to ask if it was okay to stay over.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she said, even though she was kind of whispering on the phone, she said, no, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: My mom overheard that conversation.
[SPEAKER_04]: So she already knew and she was waiting for me to tell her.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she said later on, she's like, you know, I've always suspected since you were younger.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not a big fan of that because I don't think that certain behaviors are indicative of certain sexuality.
[SPEAKER_04]: We could get into this whole larger discussion about gender norms and, you know, being effeminate and gay is not necessarily the same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: is it possible your parents have come across something that maybe they already have this indication and they're waiting for you to tell them now I think as far as you telling them that is really up to you you know best when the right time to tell them is I think sometimes there's a lot of pressure in the gay community to be like come out come out wherever you are come out get out of the closet da da da
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a little bit more of the mindset of that is a little bit more of a utopian view of where we should be but it is quite frankly dangerous in some areas to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So my advice to you is if you are out on your own and living on your own and doing your own thing and making your own choices then guess what you get to live your own life and I think yeah I think it might be a good time for you to tell your parents about this especially if you get this indication that they already know.
[SPEAKER_04]: but if you're still living at home and there's the chance there could be an ugly backlash you need to have a backup plan if you're going to tell them just in case and I pray to you that you don't have to use it and I really hope that you don't have to use that plan B but it is the smart thing to do just in case but if they did already know it might have already been ugly so I really have to say I can't sit here
[SPEAKER_04]: and say, yes, do it or no, don't do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know your parents.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know your life.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know the way you conduct yourself on a day-to-day basis.
[SPEAKER_04]: You really know the answer to this question.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you're in a place where your life where you can be your own person, then I say, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead and tell them.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, remember your friends, your real friends will always support you through this no matter what.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the most important thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I will say this, I don't want to get into this too much on a video game podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did, in my mind, I did lose a brother to this issue.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's still alive and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't speak.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't spoken to him for a very long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it is partially because of this issue and there will be some tough decisions you have to make along those lines but you know what I may have lost a brother there but I have made so many other close male friends that like honestly I would consider brothers that are more brothers to me than my my
[SPEAKER_04]: It's complicated.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's actually adopted.
[SPEAKER_04]: But my biological amusement.
[SPEAKER_09]: The one you grew up with.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not even that because he was 14 when I was born.
[SPEAKER_04]: My mother-brother.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll say that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel closely to these guys than I do my mother-brother.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, anyway, that's my very long-winded answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry for the folks that were here to listen for the games, but maybe you were curious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know, and it's... He might be the only person out there having that same sort of thought, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, if it benefits somebody, then by all means, ask the difficult questions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: and you know what if you're if you're straight out there listening to this and you know maybe you don't you know take this little feedback I'm giving to Osfer here as maybe like a little bit of perspective like maybe this is why we need an event like GamerX because a lot of people respond to something like GamerX going well when's the straight gaming convention or
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well when your parents kick you out of your house for being straight and you get persecuted by society for that and you are treated as a second class citizen and people pass laws against the way you are Look at Russia right now Then you can get your fucking con These are the same people who ask when we have White Pride Month Some people need a safe place Thank your white privilege that you have a safe place Yeah
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I'm gonna say and I'll get off my soapbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: I swear to God that shit pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_04]: When do I get my straight pride parade?
[SPEAKER_04]: You get it every single fucking day.
[SPEAKER_09]: So next email?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is Raginator.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, Loki, DarkSakura, and Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's your friendly neighborhood Raginator.
[SPEAKER_09]: Provided that there is enough time in tonight's show, I'd like to propose that you do something akin to combining listless and classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why not come up with a definitive top ten list of classic games that people should play?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: but I like your idea maybe for other topics like we need to do more like special shows and one-off things so it'll be fun yeah well um I think that's let me check and see if there's any more emails um in Korean no it's in Mandarin oh there's a thank you mail yay oh wow this is okay we got one more good thing I checked isn't it dear OLR I wanted to send you a quick email to thank you for putting on a great show for so many years
[SPEAKER_09]: We don't always agree, but I always enjoy listening to OLR and I look forward to the next-gen discussions that will take place once we get the PlayStation 4 and Xbox One in hand.
[SPEAKER_09]: I look forward to the day when we can separate fact from fiction and conversations will be steered toward how fun Knack is or how I lapped Black Wolf in Forza 5.
[SPEAKER_09]: I also look forward to adding everyone to my friends list on Xbox Live and PSN once the friends cap is raised with these new systems.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know everyone likes to think I'm an Xbox fanboy but I am truly looking forward to experiencing what Sony and Microsoft have to offer us over the next five years or so as well as what Nintendo will be bringing to the table as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hopefully I can accept Rob's invitation to visit OLR in person at some point since I only live a few hours away in Fresno.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep up the great work.
[SPEAKER_04]: When I ran into him at E3, I was like, you live in Fresno.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't you drive up sometime?
[SPEAKER_04]: We had a dude from Bakersfield come up and do the MS walk with us.
[SPEAKER_04]: If he can do that, you can do this.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yes, open invite, Shadow Next Gen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on over sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And thank you for the email.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm sorry for Fresno.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's halfway to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_04]: Think of it that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's near the Bravo Cheese Farms.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about the good things that Fresno did?
[SPEAKER_09]: I went to a Weird Al concert.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, thank you very much for the emails.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Shadow Next Gen, you shut up about your Forza lapping.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some really kind emails tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys rule.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though we got a little heavy with one of those emails, it was a good discussion.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you guys rule.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So speaking of emailers, we shall grant the wish of one of our emailers tonight and bring on the FUs of the week with an old school song from Orange Lounge Radio, what we used to use for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has my stabby part in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: With murder.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the FUs of the week time.
[SPEAKER_09]: My FU goes towards losing that house.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had been told we lost the house, but turns out that it had actually been an old message, so we thought we got it, and it turns out we didn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a very selfish, spiteful part of me that still hopes that there's one way we can get it, but it's back to looking.
[SPEAKER_09]: We may talk to a house flipper.
[SPEAKER_09]: So back to the hunt.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just ready to be done.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm ready to be in a new place.
[SPEAKER_09]: And F you to my nerves because I'm pretty sure that my job is going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody there was awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: All the stuff that goes with it is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just a little nervy because I don't want to fuck this up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, that's just F you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: F you the fact that all my co-workers are gone.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, all the co-workers that used to play games with us are gone.
[SPEAKER_11]: So now it's my boss and me.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I kick his ass every day.
[SPEAKER_11]: Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's just like...
[SPEAKER_11]: And half the time he doesn't even want to play because he's got errands to run.
[SPEAKER_11]: Our other co-worker has errands to run.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't even take breaks anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why bother walking over to the play game by myself?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's a law.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to take a break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you hourly or salary?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm hourly.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're supposed to take a break.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm supposed to.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're breaking the law.
[SPEAKER_09]: To quote the argument sketch from Money Python...
[SPEAKER_09]: I could be choosing to argue in my spare time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: So yeah, there's no point in me walking over to the game room to try to play an Xbox Live game because our live connection is absolute shit and we get disconnected all the time.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's because we're on 20 gigs.
[SPEAKER_04]: 20 gigs down for the whole company so it's like my internet running a hundred computers it's not gonna happen so that's it all right um let's see my fu of the week um one goes to stress and uh because stress will just drive people insane stressful
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck up your body.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stress sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm going to give an F you to stress.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's not necessarily me that's going through stress, but I just feel like the impact it has on other people, and it's never any fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I want to also say an F you to the fact that Video Games Live was in San Francisco on Thursday and Friday, and I didn't go because I was so busy with so much other stuff going on this weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm kind of irritated at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really wanted to go, and it just wasn't going to work out for me this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I do want to give a thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to give a thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Should I give some thank you music here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go back to the hippy-dippy classic Game of the Week music here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to give a thank you to Brad from PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not only is he pretty much just an awesome guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's helped out Horde House and so forth, and you all should be listening to PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_04]: But he said here in chat, you never have to apologize for the tangents, serious or funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are a part of you guys and thus a part of gaming and why we tune in.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, shucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just had a big smile.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys, many hearts.
[SPEAKER_04]: To all of you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you to all of you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not just Brad, but Brad needs to share his thanks with all you guys that tune in every week, be it live or podcast form.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aw, shucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: You made it this far in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gold star for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let us move on, shall we?
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so this is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of a culmination of a lawsuit that's been in the works for a while.
[SPEAKER_11]: You may remember the original creator of Madden was filing a lawsuit against EA for some royalties that were unpaid between 1990 and 1996.
[SPEAKER_09]: Didn't they find out there were more monies due too?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if this is the same situation, but apparently he got $11 million.
[SPEAKER_11]: Great for him, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Finally, the Madden games are good for something.
[SPEAKER_11]: The jury found that the games released during that time were virtually identical to the original version of Madden NFL Football developed by Antonik.
[SPEAKER_11]: and basically saying that they, you know, I guess the Antony and his attorneys will seek to appeal previous rulings that exclude the Super Nintendo games and fraud claims from the jury deliberations.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I think they are still going to try to seek some more money.
[SPEAKER_11]: But right now, $11 million isn't nothing to shy away from.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe he can buy himself a new game studio for that amount of money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Atlas is on the table.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might be able to pick up a Atari IP while you're at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is really sad news, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Meaning if you were looking forward to Darkstalkers 4, you'll be waiting a little bit longer.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's all because you didn't support Darkstalkers Resurrection.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is basically all your fault.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm okay with that, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but okay, let's look at all the games that they've decided to put out again or make new versions of or something versus Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've had the Dungeons & Dragons arcade games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Final Fight's good, but... DuckTales.
[SPEAKER_11]: Strider.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the problem is?
[SPEAKER_11]: The problem is, I mean, DuckTales is all good and everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why can't we get a new Mega Man?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I guess we got Mega Man 9 and 10, but we need more Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're still making Dead Rising games, and those aren't that great.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Strider trumps it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no interest in a Strider game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, going to the chatroom at live.vognetwork.com, Actdeft says, No, no, fuck Strider.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want new Darkstalkers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Blackwolf says, I want new games not based on old IP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, ShadowNextGen says, and before I open up the phones at 1-877-GAME-OLR or use your name on Skype, Orange Launch Radio, all one word.
[SPEAKER_04]: ShadowNextGen says, there was some fairly big Activision news that is happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm surprised no one has mentioned it, at least not yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it did mysteriously not make the show roll.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: It means that... 8 billion.
[SPEAKER_04]: They paid 8 billion for themselves.
[SPEAKER_11]: They bought out the shares that Vividi owned.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, Vividi still owns part of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's 12% of the company versus, I guess, a controlling share or something.
[SPEAKER_00]: Over 50%.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, so they basically bought that stuff back.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's also another...
[SPEAKER_11]: Some folks in the chat room are saying, Activision is now an independent company.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if I'd go that far
[SPEAKER_04]: but uh it it is it's it's more interesting to see what's going to develop from this i mean from a financial investing stock side it's it's fascinating but i'm waiting to see like what does change in policy come from this because the management's not going to change the ceo doesn't change this means they make more money at the end of the day because more that they don't have to answer to a greater board of directors that's the one thing that gets cut out we can raise the prices of the games like
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_04]: Or maybe make some big decisions to take World of Warcraft free to play or whatever they gotta do.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you want to call in and talk about this, the Activision split, or anything else we've talked about this week on the show, or this week, yeah, this week, tonight on the show, 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to open those phones right now for you to call in.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have anything you want to talk about at all, you can do that right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, I will look for some last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go to Twitter as well, see if there's anything on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Loki, DarkSakura, either of you have some last-minute stories you want to share?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I mean, no, my voice decided to die.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, no, I don't really have anything right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Holy moly.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a slow news week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a little bit of a slow news week when all that drama about the indie game and all that kind of takes center stage.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that kind of tells you what kind of week it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, uh, okay, there's a few things that the Twitter folks are sending us, so let me read some of these tweets real quick, and maybe some of you guys heard about these stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, SSGO100Matt says, uh, there was some Punch-Out related news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, Mike Tyson was caught by TMZ.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know TMZ is that really trashy tabloid site that, like, stalks celebrities at airports and asks them really stupid questions?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Mike, apparently one of those guys at TMZ asked Mike Tyson...
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, how far can you get in Mike Tyson's punch-out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you been able to beat yourself?
[SPEAKER_04]: And he said that he sucks at it, like he can't even get past the first guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, that's so stupid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, Mike Tyson, what's your favorite brand of chips?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, what kind of... It's like, what kind of ice cream are you like?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that really what they're approaching?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, Loki, I think I like the Ruffles chips, because I don't have ears.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that like what they really like?
[SPEAKER_11]: That was the worst impression by the way.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that like what they're really doing to celebrities nowadays?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like stalking them to ask them really fucking stupid questions?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you looked at TMZ?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's awful.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is the cesspool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is the cesspool of the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like if the Big Brother house is the cesspool of society, then TMZ is the pooper in that house.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yo, Mike, what do you think about the royal baby?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, look, we got a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Slimes Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: I just want you to know I had to bite my tongue during that whole segment so I wouldn't bust out in full laughter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you like my impression?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're just terrible, man.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_10]: First, I want to say the advice that you gave earlier in the podcast...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: It means a lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: It does because I'm dealing with some similar issues.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to tell you about that another time, but I truly understand somewhat where you're coming from with this and that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I actually called in to let you know that
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm actually getting my replacement headset from Astro Gaming.
[SPEAKER_10]: Long story short, I was having issues with the mixer and the headset and it took them maybe about several months through various emails to try to get it fixed.
[SPEAKER_10]: The mixer got replaced, the mic got replaced, but not the headset.
[SPEAKER_10]: The problem still persisted.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like the clouds in the sky parted and the sun shone through and all these customer service issues are getting fixed this week because Loki's finally getting his damn controller, too, for the OUYA.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, allegedly.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, until that thing shows up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except it's coming from DHL, so it'll be probably fired out of a cannon across the Pacific Ocean and hopefully land.
[SPEAKER_11]: I gotta get my OUYA back for me this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're delivering by carrier pigeon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_04]: that's because DHL packed it up and left they couldn't compete with FedEx and UPS they closed up several years ago it's just whatever's left well congratulations on getting what you needed from the company it's a good happy end to the story we hope
[SPEAKER_10]: It took two phone calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: The guy called me back.
[SPEAKER_10]: I explained everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they sent me a brand new 2013 kit and the appropriate cables for the new mixer.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkTetsuya in our chat room, sorry to go on a tangent here real quick, but says about the whole Mike Tyson impression I did earlier, Rob should really get into VA work after this OLR thing ends.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, why do I have to wait for OLR to end?
[SPEAKER_04]: You want OLR to end?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last show, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_10]: That means Ook-chan gets started on OLR, the Flash animated series.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why does that have to be something we wait on?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I did used to want to be a voice actor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the VA thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I would be so down with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Throw me a script, people!
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not very good at pursuing that stuff on my own because I do have a day job and all that, but it would be a dream to be a cartoon character or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Throw an idea my way and I'd be happy to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if it's just a little cameo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if I have to play derpy hooves or whatever, I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else is going on with you, Rama?
[SPEAKER_04]: What else in gaming?
[SPEAKER_04]: What have you been playing lately?
[SPEAKER_10]: You might get mad if I tell you the game I've been playing for the last several weeks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Try me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sailor Moon S Fighting Game.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been playing Candy Crush Saga.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: JudgingYou.com I'm judging you times two.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, is that a site?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's coming from people who play Warcraft and FFXI.
[SPEAKER_10]: For shame, good people.
[SPEAKER_10]: For shame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, look.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bobby told us to hang up on you.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're not gonna because we have some tolerance, but still.
[SPEAKER_09]: Judging.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, somebody has judgingyou.com and it says it's currently under construction.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like a webpage from 2005.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now we're judging you, judgingyou.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm totally judging you, judgingyou.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Candy Crush Saga, what stage are you on in Candy Crush?
315.
[SPEAKER_04]: Holy shit!
[SPEAKER_04]: How much have you spent?
[SPEAKER_04]: None.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, okay, I am kind of impressed.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I blocked that today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of those levels are pretty fucking impossible without buying power-ups, so applause to you, my friend.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no applause, because I'll be the first one to admit that I cheated on half those levels, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Even with all the extra power-ups...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: I play on my tablet.
[SPEAKER_10]: And believe it or not, even though it's an online game, there are ways to access the Facebook app through third-party applications.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gotcha, gotcha.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well thanks for the call, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to let you go and try to get some more calls, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay fabulous, darling.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will, always.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay black.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got it!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for anyone that's been a long-running inside joke on the show, just to be clear, it's something that Dan started, which was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because my husband's a douche.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, he didn't know what else to say in that moment, so it was just really funny when he said that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: BlackWolf in our chatroom says, I'm sad to report that Candy Crush Jam Session has been cancelled.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I didn't let poor Ranma plug Anime Jam Session.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you should listen on Tuesday nights.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's go back to the phones.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, I still have some more tweets for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100Matt did have a second Punch Out tweet for us, and that is, A gaming did you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: The title theme to Punch Out came from Gillette's Cavalcade of Sports 1950 intro.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Bobby Black will follow that up with, it actually was one of Gillette's theme songs, very famous back then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's Boston Pop's version, and a whole bunch of YouTubes were linked.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: I watched a video today of Left 4 Dead 2 mods that had Whitney Houston as a playable character.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my, that's terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, just putting a shout out there for some phone calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio, all one word on Skype or 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob, remember when we used to make the RIP names in WoW?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I still have R.I.P.
[SPEAKER_04]: Betty White, just for the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I, you know, again, guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had R.I.P.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whitney.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that woman, and I don't want that to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: But when it does, I'll be ready.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I still had?
[SPEAKER_09]: Rebecca Black.
[SPEAKER_04]: She was, like, max level at one point.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's 85 right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, no, she's 86.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, you can always start Final Fantasy XIV and have Rebecca Black mage.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's really funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe I'll do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rebecca Black Mage.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll make like a human character in 14 and do Rebecca Black Mage.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to name my Final Fantasy 14 character because originally my little Taro Taro was named Lil Poundcake.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which, if you watch RuPaul's Drag Race, you'll understand why.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now I think I'm going to have a character, a human, because Shane's convinced me I need to play a human.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I'm going to name her Lisa Turtle, after one of my favorite Saved by the Bell characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Lark Vujerys is a hot mess now.
[SPEAKER_09]: You want to know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that I've managed to get Homestuck names.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah?
[SPEAKER_09]: On the busiest server.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: and no one else had them.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I was like, heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So is Skype working, y'all?
[SPEAKER_04]: Poke, poke.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give it a few more minutes, but if nobody else calls in, I guess we'll call it a show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do have a few tweets from Tigerclaw, however.
[SPEAKER_04]: Disney registers some Star Wars Attack Squadron domains.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Possible announcement for later.
[SPEAKER_04]: And PlayStation 4 devs can only use 4.5 gigabytes of the system's 8 gigabyte RAM.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, the FCC report came out from PlayStation 4, I think even the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_11]: We now know what the operating temperature is going to be.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who the fuck cares what the goddamn operating temperature of a console is going to be?
[SPEAKER_11]: It makes no sense.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's nothing.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just another article they can get some fucking hits on their website for.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_11]: We don't know what the hell that means.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think it means anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: So what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I bet you anything with three fucking operating systems on the goddamn Xbox One, there's going to be a good chunk of that that's going to be dedicated to those.
[SPEAKER_11]: However, there was a rumor I saw that they're going to allow some of that for indie developers.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I think all that stuff is just being pulled out of someone's ass.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, no one knows what the hell is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it doesn't matter in the end of the day because there wasn't that much RAM on the Xbox 360 or PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, you know, there's some pretty good games on those consoles.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think it's a big deal.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll just play the games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who gives a shit about the specs?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just play the games.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: How the magic's done, no one cares.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we do have another call coming in, so let's go to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, this is Raging Eater.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Raging Eater.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I just thought I'd call in with two very quick topics just in case someone else wants to call in.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, although the first talk is probably more appropriate for an anime jam session kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have a series called Gunslinger Girl.
[SPEAKER_01]: For those that haven't heard of it, it's an anime series.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's two seasons long plus it has two OVAs.
[SPEAKER_01]: It basically centers around an agency in Italy that
[SPEAKER_01]: has like a social welfare front.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really like a spy and CIA type of agency in reality.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it involves cyborgs.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm probably not doing the series justice by describing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But needless to say, it's a very excellent series.
[SPEAKER_01]: For those that haven't seen it or haven't seen it in a while,
[SPEAKER_01]: and you like anime or at least someone interested in anime, I suggest watching.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, was there a question in there somewhere?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, is that...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not so much a question, but a recommendation.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, okay, it's all good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought you said it was a question.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I'll just watch Dollhouse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, no, it sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was poor crazy on my part.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't watch a lot of anime, but not that it's bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't dislike it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just hardly watch any TV at all because I'm always playing video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, but it sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll add that to my ever-growing list of shit to catch up on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's probably one of those series that is probably really great for those that don't watch a whole lot of anime.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, it's like an entry-level anime.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's one of the first series I watched, and I still love it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That makes me so incredibly sad to hear that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really, it does.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_09]: because I remember my introductions to anime were classics like Ranma and Devil Hunter Yoko and then watching Robotech when I was a little kid and Voltron and all that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Technically, I did see Robotech a few episodes of that when I was a kid but I really don't remember too much of it and I wasn't even sure if Voltron qualified as
[SPEAKER_01]: and me or not.
[SPEAKER_01]: As far as I know, there was American Beauty.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was Matt Cross.
[SPEAKER_09]: It definitely qualifies.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, then I stand corrected.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, well, anyway, just to switch gears so I can hurry this call up to keep someone on the calls in.
[SPEAKER_01]: As you may or may not be aware, in case you haven't seen me on scheme, I've finally gotten into the Civ games and both 4 and 5
[SPEAKER_01]: and thanks to BlackWolf and I'm loving them and um I was thinking you know uh although I kind of brought up briefly the other day when you were doing the noob nights on uh Borderlands 2 one of these days we all should have like a VOG community night on set five maybe again like a pretty decent game going I don't know what the
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's eight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't hold me on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Since I guess that's one of the games to play on Steam, from what I can tell, it's pretty popular.
[SPEAKER_01]: We should probably get like a
[SPEAKER_01]: Community Night going on, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if there's noobs, the problem is one person can really hold up those games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So everybody has to be well-versed enough in Civ to keep the game moving.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be one thing for just Shane and I to play, because he hasn't played at all, so he has to learn.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that could kind of move at one pace.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if eight of us are going to play, we all need to be relatively familiar enough with the game to keep it moving.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because otherwise, we're going to need 120 hours to play that fucking game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I'll be first to admit that, you know, I'm not on the same expert level as, say, like you or... Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put the car apart.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, put the car apart, because I am by no means an expert at Civ.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm actually quite bad at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have the strategical mind it takes to play a game like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm just saying, you don't have to necessarily be good, but you just have to be able to move relatively fast and not get yourself held up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, well, I was going to say, I'm not as good as some of the other people within the VOG community, but ever since playing the game for the first time during that free weekend, I've certainly gotten a whole lot better.
[SPEAKER_01]: But for those that don't already have the game, either Civ IV or Civ V on Steam already,
[SPEAKER_01]: I definitely recommend getting those games.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're really, really great.
[SPEAKER_04]: You missed the hell out during the Steam sale, to be honest, but hopefully it'll be on a Flash sale again in the coming weeks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I'll let you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sure you probably want to get more calls or wrap up the show, but it's been a blast talking to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, take care, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, nice talking to you, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: I always appreciate an endorsement for Civ.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or a username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll give it about one more minute, see if any other calls come in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did I do all the tweets?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I did the last one there, because that was from Tigerclaw, about the partial system RAM, and we were kind of talking about other systems and that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that was it for tweets.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you want to send us a tweet in a future week, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you want to send us an email for a future week, of course, that address is mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do not see the phone ringing here and we are out of last minute news, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think we got to close up shop.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go ahead and close.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're having big discussion on old school anime now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, are you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Ranma just brought up Devil Hunter Yoko, which is one of my favorite old series.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, actually, it was good through the first three OAVs.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we have talk about the most depressing stuff like Dog of Flanders and watching certain episodes of Galaxy Express 3-9.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we're going back to the 70s and the late 60s now for our references.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I have to say that one of my favorite of all time, 80s Dirty Pair.
[SPEAKER_09]: Heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I guess I'll close up the Skype line since nobody else was calling in.
[SPEAKER_04]: But thank you to those that did call in.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you do want to comment on the show, mailbag at orange lingerie dot com or, of course, tweets and Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: As a reminder, we will be off next week since I will be out of town.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, and plus we just we haven't had a week off in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes we want a frickin vacation.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I believe Bobby is still here live, though, at the Voice Geeks Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: So please still tune in to support him and all the other shows that air on the network throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before we wrap it up, I do want to say thank you as always for listening to our show and downloading the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do do this for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't ask for your money unless, you know, there's like a charity event going on or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we just say, hey, tell a friend or two about the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Help spread the word about our show and just help the family grow a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all we want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Help the Oil Army grow.
[SPEAKER_09]: um meanwhile let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts since we're closing up shop here um DarkSakura and your boa constrictor cozy what is your final thought today I'm almost done with this thing but we also have other good references to other stuff like Zenki Record of Lodoss War Record of Lodoss War by the way inspired one of my first D&D characters oh really yes
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought tonight is I had this Chex mix today that's called Honey Nut Sweet and Salty and it's delish.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like the Honey Nut Cheerios mix they used to sell.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's almost the exact same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool story, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, your last minute thought tonight or final thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: I see Bobby's going back to play Saints Row 4.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm just going to go make my own Saints Row 4 with hookers and blackjack.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or maybe no blackjack.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, I'm pretty sure Saints Row 4 probably has hookers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe that's so much blackjack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you still going to do your game programming thing on a smaller scale where you do a blackjack?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you could still make slutty blackjack or slutty breakout.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, because there wasn't that much.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would say there was not really very...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: You do you on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to play Borderlands the other day anyway, so, you know, to level up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes there's just more important things like Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I had to level up so I can, you know, I can play with you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, that's going to do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys very much for tuning in.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will be back in two weeks with episode number 515.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will see some of you next week at GamerX.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please, if you do see me around the convention, just come up and say hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't bite, I promise.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to meet many of you while I'm there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for those that are not going to be in the area, have a great week off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I'll see you online gaming and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't forget we have a Steam community and some other communities as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And maybe this epic Civ night will have to happen at some point too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a great two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next time here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_00]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_00]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next week!