[SPEAKER_00]: Sky, and Loki!
[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, July 14th, 2013, there will be no sequel to Zombie U and we get inside as to why.
[SPEAKER_00]: Exhibitors are announced for the Tokyo Game Show, and is League of Legends the next great American sport?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is Orange Lounge Radio for this episode 512, July the 14th of 2013.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you guys doing out there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Live at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do tape live every Sunday night at the Voice of Geeks Network right after the Bobby Blackwell Show, 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we always love it when you can come out and participate live with the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you're listening on the podcast feed, be it through iTunes, through Stitcher, through whatever it is you use to listen to podcasts,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also say hello to, and I don't know how firm his butt is, but let's say hi to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Doing fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably not that firm when you get two cheeseburgers at McDonald's, but today you have Subway.
[SPEAKER_04]: You going the Jared diet or what's up with this?
[SPEAKER_12]: No diet.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just got sick of eating cheeseburgers.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's fair.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've actually been trying to eat better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been doing more salads at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't go out and get fast food.
[SPEAKER_08]: How do you like in the candy bar?
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to get to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do have Friday as a cheat day.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was like, chicken McNuggets don't even sound good.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think that's a good thing, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: When the really bad food starts to sound bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: After a while, it stops tasting good to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then Dark Sakura, this bitch, shows up and brings candy bars to the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're not just any candy bars.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're crunch bars with Girl Scout cookie mix or something in them because basically she brought me Samoas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically candy bar form.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if you read the label, they are less bad for you than a serving of Samoas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: The entire package is 190 calories.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cool, can I have two?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, you can have two.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, bitch, if you want to eat it, then sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will just do some butt-firming Just Dance 4 after the show, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, I had the worst Mongolian barbecue last night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Never go to Sue's Mongolian barbecue in Santa Clara.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Girl, girl, first mistake.
[SPEAKER_04]: You went to Mongolian barbecue in the Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yet to find a good place over there.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, Dan said that they had a really good place that they went to last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so we thought we were going there, but they went to a different place, and it was nasty butt.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, I want to introduce a guest that doesn't drive us to drink out of anger, but we might have a drink with him because he's a good friend of the show and he's been here on and off for really the past 12 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully you recognize this name, even though he hasn't been here in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bradley is here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: How's it going?
[SPEAKER_04]: Arcadian42, if you rather.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that still your screen name all these years later?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Still going that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Howdy.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm doing okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's new with you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Catch us up on the past year, since you've been on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it was about six months ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, six months ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't done too much different.
[SPEAKER_10]: I went to California Extreme, and I saw Dan, but I didn't see Jamie at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was actually hanging out in the Bimani Corner for quite a while, and then I hung up playing Metallica for quite a while.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I played that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you get to play it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I played it a few times.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you get to play Wizard of Oz?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I saw it, but I didn't have time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you see the horde around Wizard of Oz?
[SPEAKER_08]: I got to touch it.
[SPEAKER_10]: California Xtreme
[SPEAKER_08]: California Extreme is basically a bunch of pinball tables and a bunch of classic arcade games and a couple of new ones here and there like I said there was a 2DX and a couple of DDRs and a Beatmania 3 and also it's where a lot of pinball vendors which the number is kind of dwindling now but parts vendors will come you know people sell like I almost bought a Bionic Woman lunchbox like from when I was an infant I was so close
[SPEAKER_08]: So anyway, it's just a big... Man, lunchbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, I ended up not.
[SPEAKER_08]: And people, there's documentaries they do there.
[SPEAKER_08]: They do panels.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like we went to this one that was called Galaxy Game where they were talking about the old Space Fight game and how they programmed it and how much a computer cost in 1971.
$13,000.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it was expensive.
[SPEAKER_08]: It talks about having 8K of RAM and how wonderful it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was just a really neat event.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I ran into tons of people I know that I never see.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's like a celebration of classic gaming with like a splash of modern gaming.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically if Bobby Blackwolf's show were an expo, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's also, you know, all these games are on free play on top of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Stern comes out every year and brings like their top new tables.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so there was like an Avengers there.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was an X-Men.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was ACDC.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was the new Metallica table with all the three different types of back glass on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: and
[SPEAKER_08]: It was just really a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course, man, I feel so bad because the guy who owns this Big Bang Bar, actually no, he I think sold it to the convention finally, a Big Bang Bar prototype, which was like one of Capcom's last tables they produced.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really beat.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's in rotten shape.
[SPEAKER_08]: It needs to be shopped.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the thing now is that you can get repro parts for it because they've actually, there's a person reproducing the Big Bang Bar table in Kingpin.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had a kingpin there too.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then there were like the Gottlieb tables that were all like Miami Heat instead of Miami Vice and Raven instead of Rambo.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, all these little knockoff titles because they couldn't get licensing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, Data East tables that are always kind of between cheeseball and awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a Super Mario Mushroom world there, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and it was broken when I tried to play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then all these other people who were taller than me were trying to play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like, dude, I'm actually the right size.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then there was this game that had like
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like called Alley Cat or something that had trash cans and they lift up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little kid's ball game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I've seen that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Melody and I were there, got on our knees and we're just throwing balls and balls and balls and balls at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you got on your knees and we're playing with balls.
[SPEAKER_08]: And cats.
[SPEAKER_08]: Balls and pussy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, just making sure we're clear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Balls and pussy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bradley, were you on your knees playing with balls at some point?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, not really your thing?
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't get on my knees, but I did play that little, the Super Mario one, the small table.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because Mario had a kid's table and an adult table, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, because they were right next to each other.
[SPEAKER_08]: They did have one that was on adult-sized legs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it was just to display the LEDs.
[SPEAKER_10]: That might have been something different, but there was two next to it, the little one and the other one.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know the complete name of it, but there was an arcade near my high school that had it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, Ice Rink had it, and I went there and played it every so often.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a good, fun one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just gonna say about California Extreme it's not really just the games either you because you run into a lot of people right which is what ticks me off why I couldn't go because you ran into like tons of people blast from the past from the DDR days right
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I ran into Richard.
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw Chris Tang, which you see Chris Tang at every event that has the money.
[SPEAKER_08]: I ran into Ali.
[SPEAKER_08]: I ran into Wendell, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Chris from DDR Freak back in the day, he actually arrived late at night.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm in the middle of playing the song, and then I end the song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next thing I know, I'm in this bear hug.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of like a little mini con of sorts.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then it's a lot of, you know, because a lot of us who, you know, started off back in the day, we're all grown up, so we were going out, you know, drinking in the, because there's like a little bar in the front of the Hyatt, and, you know, $15 lemon drop, but I also did want Grey Goose.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're all actually out there having our adult frou-frou drinks and talking about games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it more of an adult convention?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I'm not talking about... There were some kids there, but a lot of people...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: We actually ended up hanging out at a table just chatting about collections versus buying a house.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because that's what Dan and I were trying to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you get more listeners for VOG while you were there?
[SPEAKER_08]: I did pimp us out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's some people, I'm sorry I've forgotten to put you on my Facebook, but hi, it was great to meet you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I met a friend of Kyle Snyder.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkTetsuya put together had his premiere in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: I just thought it was pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Running into people who knew people that I knew.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I spent all day on my DS checking where I tagged people from.
[SPEAKER_08]: And running into people whose screen names I recognize.
[SPEAKER_08]: And going, I want to send them a message!
[SPEAKER_08]: Find me shit!
[SPEAKER_04]: You should be able to add friends from that.
[SPEAKER_08]: or at least send a message.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually did tag him twice and I could have sent him a message but it was toward the end of the night and he wouldn't have gotten my message.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're having fun with your 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is only the second week you've had it, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I swear everybody... Oh yeah, I've already got... Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've expanded my house.
[SPEAKER_08]: I bought my house, expanded it twice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bought my upstairs, expanded it once and I have my basement now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm paying for my dream suites.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm getting Club LOL and...
[SPEAKER_08]: Blathers wants to expand my museum.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're on it in Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's because I go to the island and pick fruit instead of doing the little games and then go sell my fruit and then I do it like five times in a day.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's how to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how to do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm making money.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's 80s style.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let me go back to Bradley, our guest.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bradley, you had fun at California Extreme.
[SPEAKER_04]: Were you there Friday and Saturday or just Saturday?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, just Saturday.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a Saturday-Sunday convention.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why did I think it was three days?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, just two.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_04]: What kinds of games have you been playing the past year or six months?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you beaten anything lately?
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: As you get more money, once you die after a while, because the enemies are kind of hard and it's easy to fall into spikes and all that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: So once you die, you basically build up your castle.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, as you upgrade, you get different options, and you get new options for what children can be, and runes and things like that to basically expand your gameplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Help you along, get you more HP, more MP, and other options like that And then you keep trying over and over again for hundreds of times Yeah, I saw this game on Steam and I wanted to get it But it is not part of the, and we'll obviously have to talk about this The Steam sale going on right now, which has many people's attentions But it's still worth it outside the lack of sale price, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, actually I did see it on sale for like $2 off or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not too big of a deal, but... Well, it's something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but I bought it at $15 and that's well worth the price.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's no like Tomb Raider for $12 or Borderlands 2 for $10, but that's still a pretty good deal.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and you can play this for hours and hours.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some people can beat it pretty fast.
[SPEAKER_10]: That took me like 22 hours just because I took a lot of time exploring the castle each time and didn't try to kill the bosses really early.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: So... Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then there's Nuclear Plus and you can just keep going and going as much as you want.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds like a fun time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Another big game was playing Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been playing that shitloads.
[SPEAKER_10]: Obviously, I'm already up to 85 hours in the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: and part of it too is that it's a slow process.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like if I could just open up my 3DS and be in my town, yay, I'd be there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's like you gotta open it up, load the game, wait for the game, wait for the thing to load your town, then you gotta make sure you save and quit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you gonna get Mr. Resetti?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just kinda like it takes too fucking long to get in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: True.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but it is a lot of time investment to do a bunch of things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and basically the masterboards I go at basically have loads of people that are messing with each other and getting swapping items and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically I've gotten a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Almost done with the house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you will get my small pitiful house in your plaza now since I see the green light on my 3DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: And other games, FTL was a big game that I played a lot of.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I played that this week for the Trading Garden thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you got sucked into that trading card thing too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know about the trading yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually doing the trading because that seems like a ton of annoyingness.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I did play that and a bit of Meat Boy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Super Meat Boy and haven't played too many other games that were...
[SPEAKER_10]: in that thing that's trading cards so far.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, they're adding new ones every day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I probably go play... I want to play Portal and Portal 2 again because I haven't played them on Steam yet so I could see them other than 720p and watch them in 1080 or however good they are for the Steam version.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I might do that pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: And another big thing right now is the new Meat Plaza games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, they just released those last week.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can basically get the bundle for $15 of all four of them.
[SPEAKER_10]: And basically, I think near the beginning of California Extreme yesterday,
[SPEAKER_10]: I almost spent an hour standing off right near the entrance doing the updates for those, or doing those games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, for each new game, you can take all the 10 tags that you have and take them through each game, so that takes a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's not for convention play.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just too many people.
[SPEAKER_04]: For when you occasionally street pass with people, I think that's a good thing to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to let you hold more than 10 people in the buffer, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be nice for conventions.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was annoying because then I think I'd be done.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then like, nope, more people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine when I was at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just waiting until my next Disneyland trip.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Disneyland's not as bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you will fill it up partway through the day, so you want to check a couple times a day.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's going to be harder with these four new games because now it's like, now I've got to play the Fantasy Zone game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I've got to play the Kingdom game and whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think I kind of have to pick my battles and which game do I really want to progress on the most?
[SPEAKER_04]: And for me, that's the puzzle trading to get the little 3D pictures.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did finish two puzzles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they just opened up two new ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right when I was like, I was within like 40 pieces of having everything and now two new puzzles.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's four new puzzles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bastard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jerks.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I guess I've been blurring the line here a little bit between trying to interview Bradley and getting to our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: But one thing I wanted to bring up was Steam Sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure you guys listening to this show can't avoid it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is it about the Steam Sale that gets everybody in the gaming community talking?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably them prices, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: The fact that, you know, what is it today, right now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Tomb Raider, as of the taping of the show, $12.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, that was yesterday's deal, but they last for 48 hours, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Borderlands 2 for $10.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the season pass, another $10.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really cheap stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, of course...
[SPEAKER_04]: or by spending money.
[SPEAKER_04]: or by crafting badges.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: He gave me the two cards I was missing in the Super Meat Boy set and I crafted my first badge before the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I got a summer sale card for crafting it now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I got my little emoticon that's deal with it with the Super Meat Boy shades.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I got the Dr. Fetus background with the big middle finger from my profile.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you visit my profile, well, I haven't changed it yet, but I will.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will be flipping you off on my Steam profile.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I wanted to say, if you are getting into the trading card whoring thing for no explainable reason like myself, visit vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check out the forums.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have posted an official Steam trading card forum there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not only did I trade with Loki, I traded with Rababa the other day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm starting to trade with other people, but I would like to help out VOG listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll go to the general Steam trade community if I must, but I'd rather help the VOG people get the cards they need first.
[SPEAKER_04]: I only have a couple extras right now, but if I have something you want, let's talk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because now, what do I need?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm two cards short on Really Big Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you have the cards for that, help me out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alan Alchemy in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says, The trading cards are neat, but I'm annoyed at their integration into the sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: They already had a great metagame for sales that worked and did more to enrich and create content for the community, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, write a recommendation for a game you own, post screenshots, and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you know, Steam did kind of generalize that into a community badge.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, I liked, I did like how you'd kind of get the perks every few months when they did these big sales, the summer sale and the winter sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I do kind of miss that a little bit because the kind of homogenizing it all into just the general community badge is going to make the sales lose that little special end of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the trading cards is something.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I draw the line at spending real money.
[SPEAKER_04]: I won't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I promise.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will probably end up with Borderlands 2 because Bobby got Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll play.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you've got Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do and I haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki has Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's four people to all play some co-op on live streaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get the thumbs up in the other room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get into our other gaming weeks and the other types of games that you've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I figured you probably got out what you were currently playing in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Jamie's back, so let me ask DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_08]: Busy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played a lot of Beatmania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got to try a lot of new songs, some of which I passed the first time through.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was playing on standard, so, you know, easy mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: I passed Starmine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ain't no shame in that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're in your mid-30s now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get to tone it down a bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't touched it since we last had one.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what did we have last?
[SPEAKER_08]: A red?
[SPEAKER_08]: So, and this is a, it actually had the DJ Troopers banner on it, but it was a Tricoro.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I got to play a lot of fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played some Beatmania 3, which going from 2DX to Beatmania 3, the timing is just freaking bizarre.
[SPEAKER_08]: So anyway, I played Quartet, which I was super disappointed that I couldn't hear the music.
[SPEAKER_08]: So our fortune cookie reflects the music because I want to freaking hear that song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, I also played, um, I didn't play Journey, but because there was someone on it every time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, I played a lot of Metallica pinball.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's super good.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's like funny with me and three other people behind me singing Master of Puppets while I'm playing the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: and he got it signed by uh the uh I think the artist's name was Dirty Donny I think he got it he just ran into him and got him to sign it so that was cool um I uh I know I played a bunch of other stuff well I you know I did play some uh
[SPEAKER_08]: Little Inferno, as far as not classic stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I pretty much played a ton of different games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played Timber with Melody.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we threw our balls at some pussies.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it was pretty fun too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I also played ACDC Pinball.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played...
[SPEAKER_08]: Big Bang Bar.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played the Wizard of Oz pinball and I've got some, like I said, some footage of it that I'm going to be putting on my Tumblr and reposting to the Orange Lounge Tumblr later tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Including the rainbow mode.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob, it's so cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like they've got multicolored LEDs underneath the in the playfield so that they'll cycle through different colors over each area instead of just having the standard incandescence of the older tables.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, I won't go too much into the classic stuff because, like I said, there's a bunch of it there and I played a bunch of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played a lot of Animal Crossing, like I said.
[SPEAKER_08]: Little Inferno, I finally put down the two bucks to get Little Inferno on Steam.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's freaking fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: and you just burn stuff and you can like earn money the more that you burn things and buy different things out of catalogs and as you get different combos of stuff you unlock more catalog and you have to use up your catalog before you can get a new catalog and just you have to make 99 different combos of stuff
[SPEAKER_08]: Put in Pluto and then put in the sun and then the moon and then it'll do everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: You get like ice cubes.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's one that's called the well-medicated combo that's like wine and happy pills and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: That one's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the wine is called the Midlife Crisis Mitigator.
[SPEAKER_03]: What game is this still?
[SPEAKER_03]: Little Inferno?
[SPEAKER_08]: And I actually have not played any Mass Effect for an entire week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_04]: What is the date?
[SPEAKER_04]: July 14th, episode 512.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one where she didn't play Mass Effect all week long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Holy shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob, in my defense, I've been looking for houses and I didn't play live on Thursday because of the stupid cough.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm allowed to take a vacation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Commander Shepard is shedding a single tear.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sometimes people in relationships need to take some time off from each other.
[SPEAKER_12]: Allowed to take a vacation.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is something a pod person would say.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, I did buy a few more games on Steam, but I forgot what they were because I'm probably going to buy more tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I was going to get FTL, but it just doesn't seem like my kind of game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I did get Hotline Miami and the download pack.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I haven't tried it yet, but it just looks like it's so much fun because I like going around in a virtual environment, a safe virtual environment where there's no risk that I'm actually going to do anything like this in real life and kill a bunch of people.
[SPEAKER_08]: And big bloody massacres with a neat soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not like I'm going to go plug in my iPhone and listen to some Deadmau5 and shoot up a mall.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, so I figured I needed a little bit more than just the really cheap blower fans that they had on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I crafted a thing using, uh, basically the parts I had from my, my PC and my laptop cooling tray.
[SPEAKER_12]: So after, you know, cutting some of the plastic around and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: I screwed in two 120mm fans in there that are from my Antec case so they have the three speed settings and of course you need a dedicated 12V power supply so I have a separate plug in the wall now and I had to manufacture a super long Molex cable to connect to it
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I'm not picking that up yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although tomorrow, that's another thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That gameplay trailer, which I haven't seen yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: How'd you feel about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: We talked about it on Horde House this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess there's a teaser at the end about a Grand Theft Auto Online?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, it's just what they're calling their online portion of the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because there's an online portion to Grand Theft Auto 4, but now they're calling it Grand Theft Auto Online.
[SPEAKER_12]: and it looks great.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it looks really good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Obviously, the screenshots that they've been putting out aren't as the same quality as the gameplay trailer, but that just leads to the rumors that, yeah, they're producing a higher quality asset version of the game so that it can be ported to the PC or next-gen consoles when the time comes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just so y'all know, Loki told me before the show tonight, you will get Grand Theft Auto V and you will play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it was not you need to, it was that you will.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, because you have Grand Theft Auto 4 and you still haven't played it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alan played it on PC.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's Alan playing it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not talking about Alan.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm talking about you playing it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Honestly, though, you probably should just skip 4 at this point and just go straight into 5 because it's going to be way better anyways.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know, everything looks great about it.
[SPEAKER_12]: The gameplay looks tighter, the combat looks better, the level of detail in the game is just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_12]: It just looks fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: It looks like a game that I can sink hundreds of hours into.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's not kid ourselves, you will.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game will cause disagreements between you and the wife.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, no, it won't because it's good because I will.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, the only problem is going to be getting this scream to play that on.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess I could play it in the other room, but yeah, I can because, you know, my Xbox 360 has Wi-Fi, so that'll be just fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can play in the other room.
[SPEAKER_12]: Problem solved.
[SPEAKER_12]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anything else for your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm just getting ready.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was installing Arma 2 in the expansion, Daisy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, because Gally had sent me a message on Twitter saying that he has a Daisy Breakpoint server.
[SPEAKER_12]: So maybe we could do that in a future VOG game night.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although, for now, I'm just suspending VOG game night because it's hard to get everybody together.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just to think of games to play.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: By some miracle, they fixed our Minecraft server long enough for me to download the backup of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I made a backup and downloaded the world.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we still have the world intact now.
[SPEAKER_12]: So my plan is when I do eventually get around to actually...
[SPEAKER_12]: Aw, that's just fantastic.
[SPEAKER_12]: Brad, you're awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, Brad from PodCulture sent me a copy of Fallout New Vegas Ultimate Edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brad, you are too good to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: That man sends us booze.
[SPEAKER_04]: He sends us games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brad, you're the man.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: And he sends me episodes of Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else does a nerd need besides games, Doctor Who, and booze?
[SPEAKER_06]: Coffee!
[SPEAKER_04]: Coffee.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brad, you rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody listen to PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_04]: 6 o'clock Pacific, Monday nights here at VOG.
[SPEAKER_12]: So anyway, the plan is, what I'm going to do with it once I get around to actually setting up that Minecraft server with mods and stuff, is I'm going to do a multi-world server where you can travel between the server that Gally has set up right now, which I think is a survival server, so I'm going to just leave that alone, and then ours, which is a...
[SPEAKER_12]: Creative servers, so you'll be able to go back and forth between that stuff, and I think it'll be the best of both worlds there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to ruin the mood, but don't download that while the show's going.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, of course not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, going to the chat room, it's almost like it's a list list going on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else does a nerd need besides Doctor Who, liquor, and games?
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100Matt says, boobs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a gay male and I'm not going to disagree with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need boobs too.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sometimes boobs get in the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will co-sign that to the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fifth dream says masturbation.
[SPEAKER_04]: No comment Misty says Mountain Dew I don't know Nasty shit Maybe beverage of some type Coffee So a caffeinated beverage of some sort I will let caffeinated beverages go Except Mountain Dew is nasty shit Which by the way Rob I have to say something Speaking of nerd drinks Do you remember a soda called Josta?
[SPEAKER_04]: God, yes, it sounds familiar for some reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: And somebody brought a 15-year-old can of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I do remember this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody brought a 15-year-old can of it to California Extreme and you drank it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I found a soda at the Russian market that tastes almost exactly like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a Brazilian Guarana soda.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is the most random thing you've ever said on this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Josta was made out of Guarana.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, y'all, remember Josta?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you can get it at the Russian grocery store.
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep in mind, I used to drink this stuff and watch Sailor Moon marathons.
[SPEAKER_04]: Josta is the official drink of my Sailor Moon marathons so you can stop laughing at me alright so let me just add that to the list Doctor Who, boobs, game, liquor apparently Josta and Sailor Moon are on the list too well I'm glad that the Josta clone or whatever was more important than playing Mass Effect this week
[SPEAKER_08]: Now looking for houses is more... Which, by the way, the other... And by the way, it wasn't Russian, it was Brazilian, but it was a Brazilian soda at a Russian market.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, the other comment we got in chat, this is a little bit delayed here, but that the Gaben.tv song, the G-A-B-E-N.tv song, is appropriate for when Dark Sakura announces that she hasn't played Mass Effect for an entire week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now this is supposed to be for the Steam sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is also for you not playing it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Are you ready for a miracle?
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, that song is going to play.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what's going to happen when they play that song on Steam.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's when Half-Life 3 gets announced.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's just going to all of a sudden be like, hey, wait a second, this is from the Steam sale.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, whoa, now hold on a second.
[SPEAKER_12]: Something's different.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's not dressed.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's dressed up like a... I want that song played at my 40th birthday.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know who you people are.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm leaving.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: and listen to VOG on the TuneIn app, which you can do.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you own an OUYA, I urge you, go get the TuneIn app and check out VOG because we are on TuneIn and you can listen to us through your OUYA.
[SPEAKER_04]: I also played that parking valet simulator, the No Brakes Valet, whatever that's called.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game cracked me up.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was playing around with the Twitch TV app, which runs, I gotta say, it runs, no surprise, it's the exact same setup as the mobile Twitch TV, but it runs very well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't getting any screens that were entirely black, which I get a lot on mobile.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was getting a lot of good-looking feeds on Twitch TV, so that was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, as far as other games go, thank you Steam Sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought Scribblenauts Unlimited for $5 and I've been having fun with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Scribblenauts, of course, is a puzzle game of sorts where you can type whatever object that comes to mind to help you solve the puzzle.
[SPEAKER_04]: for example I was in a museum level and I had to put things on the paintings that the people looking at them would appreciate so for example there might be a caveman so one thing that he might appreciate a campfire so you put in campfire and you put it in there
[SPEAKER_04]: Scribblenauts Unlimited allows you to use the descriptive text so like you get an adjective, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like a red balloon or a red whatever or like I think I had a mission where the guy was going to go pick a girl up on a date and needed a cool ride so I said pink SUV and I got credit for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should have done DeLorean.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now here's, yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the only, like, the only negative I can think of for Scribblenauts Unlimited is it's basically like a, it's more of a word puzzle than it is platformer puzzle, at least in the early levels.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now granted, I'm still early on, I probably have like 16 stars total, so I'm not like super far into the game, but I've played it for an hour or two, and I imagine the puzzles get more complicated later on, and maybe there's not so much maybe platforming
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkDeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what Cthulhu does.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's an Elder God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a cute game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's kind of an elaborate word puzzler.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first few levels you're going to be like kind of tapping your fingers on the desk like, okay, this is pretty easy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know what I'm going to do when I get to that level.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Little Red Corvette.
[SPEAKER_04]: and if it's driven by Prince it'll be even better I haven't really seen a sandbox stage I mean I guess you can always go back to the farm level and do whatever you want there but I was kind of surprised that like there isn't like well the first Scribblenauts game it was just a mode that you just go in the sandbox yeah I didn't I haven't really seen that in this so but anyway it was five bucks amazing
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft in chat says I summoned Cthulhu for a monster party you do see some funny stuff like in I think it was in the diner level in the basement there's some monsters that are dancing around and they want another person to dance with them so I summoned scary unicorn and it was a unicorn with a mask on that was scary it is really cool how the game really can translate like whatever you type into items and you can even build your own items which is pretty cool and edit stuff so yeah I was uh
[SPEAKER_04]: I was I there's there's still a lot of fun to be had in it even if the game itself is is pretty simple um otherwise other games I've been playing not a lot of new stuff uh still the Final Fantasy 14 beta which beta 3 finally ends this weekend okay here's how much I've played the Final Fantasy 14 beta you guys I actually got to the point where it said well that's all the story we have in the beta you have completed everything in the beta
[SPEAKER_04]: Go home!
[SPEAKER_04]: I got to that point in the story where it's like, look forward to the release of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You beat the beta.
[SPEAKER_04]: And even then, Shane's like, well, you could still go get your Chocobo.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not really done yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go get your Chocobo.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got more instances to run.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't play it all this weekend, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I was... I think a lot of people are just kind of waiting for the release now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had to save up the money so I can buy it.
[SPEAKER_12]: And also, they're going to nuke everybody pretty soon anyway, so it's like, eh, why am I going to waste that time?
[SPEAKER_04]: But beta 4 should be in about...
[SPEAKER_04]: 3 weeks or so and that supposedly is going to have the voice acting in the story quests and some other stuff too, it'll have more of the game oh there's voice acting in the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: for the main story quests there's going to be voice acting yeah I didn't know that until I read it I think on Reddit and it was out of a producer interview or something like that so I don't question its legitimacy
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm loving Realm Reborn.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's such good fan service.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just so well done.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first game, we don't acknowledge that anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is really what it should have been the whole time.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is what people want out of a Final Fantasy MMO, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some XI purists would probably argue with me on that, but I really think there's a lot of people that are going to be very happy with what Realm Reborn is doing.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want, out of an MMO, Final Fantasy XI to go free-to-play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: WhatUpG in chat asks, how many hours did you put in, Sky?
[SPEAKER_04]: I lost count.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there a slash played?
[SPEAKER_04]: Easily 20.
[SPEAKER_04]: Easily.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably more.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm not just talking this weekend, I'm talking kind of comprehensive across the beta, but it's probably more.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100Matt says, Final Fantasy XIV Realm Reborn on max graphics settings is amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Soundtrack is great too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, the soundtrack is phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, to be fair, the soundtrack was actually pretty good in 1.0, but a good soundtrack won't save a shitty game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's great that now there's this nice game that the soundtrack complements very well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: That was really it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the Mii Plaza games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played those quickly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll just say a couple of those I checked out.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a space shooter type game where your Miis that you collect by street passing, the color of their shirts determines the weapons that you can place on your ship.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can have a red shirt as a flamethrower, a blue shirt as a homing missile, and then it's a little space shooter game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's an awesome little addition to Mii Plaza.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bummer that they cost money, but they're decent games for, you know, what is it, $15 for the bundle?
[SPEAKER_04]: For four games?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a nice little expansion.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, great.
[SPEAKER_04]: To register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com, use the passphrase COLOR.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, that's it for our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we can get into gaming news, but quickly I'm just going to say housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't forget to add us on Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR, and follow us on Facebook as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Be our friend, facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're also on Google+.
[SPEAKER_04]: All the places you can connect with us are located at our website, orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_12]: The only way that I would get into that is if it was conveniently timed with a game that I'm playing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I'm not going to really play a game, although I did for Super Meat Boy.
[SPEAKER_12]: I did play the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you gave me your cards, so I'm more than happy with the way it turned out.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you know what, though?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm glad that I did, because Super Meat Boy was an excellent game, and I do like it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a great way to revisit games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't talk about it during my gaming week, but not only did I play Scribblenauts, I played Really Big Sky, I played Super Meat Boy, I played Magicka, I played... What else did I play to get cards out of?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's something else, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, there's all these games I'm collecting cards in, and it forces me to go back and play the games again.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, anyways.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um...
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, so how popular are these next-gen systems going to be?
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I think they're going to be very popular.
[SPEAKER_12]: And if anything, we should learn from these pre-orders that they are so popular that they're selling out of their allotments.
[SPEAKER_12]: So yes, like any other console launch, they're going to be hard to find at launch.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, for example...
[SPEAKER_12]: GameStop, they've stopped taking pre-orders for the PlayStation 4 and they are also running short, I guess, on Xbox One systems, the Day 1 edition.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um...
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess, well, right now they are still selling some of the Xbox One bundles, but a lot of them are gone.
[SPEAKER_12]: So they are almost out of those.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also, Amazon.
[SPEAKER_12]: They have stopped taking pre-orders for the Xbox One and the PlayStation 4 launch bundles as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: So...
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, probably the demand's been just very high for these things, so that's gotta be a good sign, unlike the Wii U.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_12]: I remember there's still that rumor that they were having some problems making the problems with the yields from the chips for the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that could possibly lead to some shortages there.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see if there's anything to that.
[SPEAKER_12]: But either way, it should be a very successful launch as far as console numbers go.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100 Matt says, of course there's going to be shortage.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to drive up demand as much as possible.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, yes, but I mean, honestly, I don't think they try to do it on purpose.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, granted, that's a wonderful side effect of, you know, the console being popular.
[SPEAKER_12]: Unlike, you know, I seriously think with the Wii and the Wii U or whatever, that they were shortening that stuff on purpose.
[SPEAKER_12]: At least the Wii U, because I remember they were saying, oh, it's so impossible to find, and yet it was just sitting on shelves, like all these different places.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I just kind of wonder about that stuff, but...
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Once again, they're going to have to sell a lot of units to get the third-party support because if it's just not there, if they're not selling any units, then they're not going to sell games and they're going to lose support.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're going to develop for systems that have the numbers.
[SPEAKER_04]: What systems would be left?
[SPEAKER_04]: The 360 and PS3?
[SPEAKER_12]: You'd be surprised, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: They would just develop for current-gen stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: WhatUpG says, I think they are putting out more PlayStation 4 than Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dungeon Buster says, in Microsoft's case, it could also be a continuing problem with silicon yields for their new CPU.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alan Alchemy says, it's only on purpose when Nintendo does it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Live.VogNetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's why, and this is kind of going back to, how long were there shortages on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, over a year.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, even with the Xbox 360 and the PlayStation 3, there were shortages for maybe six months when they were catching up on the demand and stuff, but then they were able to keep up with it.
[SPEAKER_12]: But the Wii, it was hard to find just forever.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_12]: And...
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, seeing the day to day operation of how Nintendo works.
[SPEAKER_12]: They do allocate a lot of stuff where they kind of hold back things that they could possibly sell and place them in certain places.
[SPEAKER_12]: For example, there may be shortages for some retailers, but other retailers are getting product because they're filling the demand there first and shorting everybody else.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or they're holding back because they don't want any extra units sitting on the shelves to make it seem like the system is selling out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, way too early to still call a victor this year though, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything can still happen.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I'm, all I'm gonna say is Nintendo has got their work cut out for them to really sell those consoles because they're, you know, betting that these first party titles are gonna sell consoles and, and,
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, Nintendo Mario games are great.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do remain the cheapest option on the table.
[SPEAKER_12]: They are the cheapest option.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, speaking of cheap options, actually, I was going to say there is a PlayStation 3 SKU coming out next month for $199.
What?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, PlayStation 3, wow.
[SPEAKER_12]: PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's still, wow, that's great.
[SPEAKER_12]: However, the hard drive is really small.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a 12-gig hard drive.
[SPEAKER_12]: They had it in Europe right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: They were selling it.
[SPEAKER_12]: But a 12-gig hard drive for $199, that's still pretty cheap.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, I mean, granted, those hard drives are replaceable, and you can get a cheap hard drive, so it might be an easy way to get in if you want a PlayStation 3 system.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, there's that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, that might go through the holidays as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: That'll help out.
[SPEAKER_12]: But yeah, I mean, seriously, I hope that that Mario game does really well for them.
[SPEAKER_12]: I hope that Mario game and Zelda and stuff really does sell systems for them.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because if it doesn't, I don't know what more they can do.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, Mario Kart will be good, but...
[SPEAKER_12]: They may be in the shitter for another year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't think they're just going to stop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo themselves will not stop supporting Wii U. No, I understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll still see games that people are going to want on that for the next couple years.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just, you know, it may not be the powerhouse that the Wii was without all the other third-party support, but, I mean, Nintendo will still make games for their own system while they work on the successor.
[SPEAKER_12]: And a lot of games are, you know, Nintendo...
[SPEAKER_12]: People that buy Nintendo systems a lot of times buy it for Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not a huge loss, but it does affect if you want to buy a system or if you're contemplating buying another system.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's consider it next-gen.
[SPEAKER_12]: I still don't consider the Wii U next-gen because of the hardware and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you're considering a next-gen system and you're looking at all the games that are coming out that I want to play and the Wii U is missing a lot of them,
[SPEAKER_04]: you just might not buy the system and by the way just because I say Nintendo working on a successor I don't mean like they're hurrying a successor but it's very common that the research and development of these systems is years in advance PlayStation 5 is probably already being worked on
[SPEAKER_04]: very, very, very slowly in its early planning stages.
[SPEAKER_12]: If the roadmaps are to be believed, the one that leaked out for the Xbox system and the Kinect and the VR stuff, Microsoft's working on some VR stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_12]: Next year is apparently when that's supposed to come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of Microsoft, apparently, as Bobby likes to call them, the Microsoft space bucks, the Microsoft points, they're being phased out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, we kind of knew that that was going to be happening at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe that came up during E3, but it is actually now kind of dated when that's all going to go down.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Xbox Live rewards will be doing away with these bonuses as of August 1st.
[SPEAKER_04]: XBOX Live Rewards Program
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently some problems right now in the new dashboard build that's being previewed that's going to roll out in the fall.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I guess some problems there about some negative exchange rates and some that are too favorable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Incorrect game title pricing in wrong regions and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, it is a beta, so you can't exactly sit there and go, Microsoft, you suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's what you get when you sign up for a beta is that things are going to...
[SPEAKER_07]: We can still say they suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: We just can't say that that sucks.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't understand how they can't, like,
[SPEAKER_12]: Are you telling me that Microsoft is confused on how their space bucks work?
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, granted, I know it's easy for the North American stuff where it's like 80 points equals a dollar.
[SPEAKER_12]: But in other regions, I'm sure it's X amount of points equals whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: With so much crap in the marketplace, though, I'm sure it's a database conversion issue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like it's one wrong little line of code that fucks everything up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure it's something that simple.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, uh, don't know yet exactly when the points will move into dollars, but it's gonna be before, probably this same September timeframe.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the 20 points thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before on your birthday?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even think I got that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who, who, who even cares?
[SPEAKER_12]: That is just so ridiculously stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: What can you buy with 20 points?
[SPEAKER_12]: There was, uh, someone, I think it was... I think it was, um, uh...
[SPEAKER_12]: and Flaco Jones who said, you know, hey, I got 20 points on my birthday.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm like, don't spend it all in one place.
[SPEAKER_04]: How can you not spend it all in one place?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's only 20 points.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know how we've talked about the poor sales of the Wii U are probably going to start affecting third-party markets as far as what gets developed for them?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it looks like Ubisoft has come out and said that they're not doing a sequel to Zombie U just for that reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: That basically the Wii U hasn't sold enough and the game itself, Zombie U, hasn't sold enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: So even though they have a prototype of a sequel, they are not going to pursue development.
[SPEAKER_08]: There will be no Zombie U 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: No Zombie The Edge, no Zombie Bono.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's probably going to be called something else, be my guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's going to be multi-platform because that's why they can't, they know.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's sad too because Zombie U is probably one of the most successful third-party games they had at launch.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was really surprised by this news.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was that bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zombi-me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zombi-us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zombie1!
[SPEAKER_04]: I was surprised to hear that it was that bad, but it also kind of shed some light on why they pulled the plug on the Rayman thing so fast.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's exactly the same reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, because we didn't know this then, and we were kind of like, Ubisoft's just being dicks.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, but I guess financially, that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, well.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the one time that Mr. Negative over there, Norman Negative, is right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else we got?
[SPEAKER_04]: Next up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ha ha ha ha, Beatrageinator.
[SPEAKER_08]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: To my really awful U2 joke.
[SPEAKER_08]: Beat him with your shoe?
[SPEAKER_08]: Zombie Bono.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, you know, one of the things that PlayStation 4 was going to allow developers to do is self-publish on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, you know, basically their thought is, you know,
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going to treat every single individual developer as a publisher as far as we're concerned.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we don't separate, we don't segregate indies from traditional publishers.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which I think is a fantastic thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it's awesome that you see these indie games next to big budget games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Honestly, it's kind of refreshing compared to the stuff that was happening with the Xbox indie games.
[SPEAKER_12]: Where it's just like...
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm hoping that that also carries on over to the Vita as well because the Vita could always use more games.
[SPEAKER_04]: XBOX ONE XBOX ONE
[SPEAKER_12]: I think Microsoft's strategy with the Xbox One, or not even really with the Xbox because now they're kind of treating all their platforms as one platform.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think the problem is they know that people want to develop games for the Xbox One, but they also know they have a lack of application support on Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, their end is going to be basically, hey, develop games for the Windows 8 platform, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because we have that kernel running on, you know, or that version of the firmware, whatever, however you're going to split it up.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have that running on the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_12]: Your games will be able to be ported over to the Xbox One very easily.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's how they're going to win on both platforms, because...
[SPEAKER_12]: They want to sell those operating systems because that's where they're probably going to make a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_12]: At the same time, they also want to have stuff on their console.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just think that's what they're going to try to do is try to get people almost like...
[SPEAKER_12]: Trick them into making games for the Microsoft platform, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: ShadowNextGen in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says, You have to worry about whether PlayStation Network on PS4 will turn into the App Store, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the App Store has a lot of crap on it, like a lot of crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, how many fart apps do we need, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Flashlight apps, really.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think it's going to happen that way, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because even right now with the way PlayStation Network's indie games are, it's easier for them to get on, but I don't think it's like they can just throw games up there like you can on the indie store and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: It'll be interesting to see how they do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All it was was pictures of Pokemon, but people legit thought it was like Nintendo's Pokemon on the App Store.
[SPEAKER_04]: And people were downloading it like crazy and losing money on it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that they'll probably have some sort of review process in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know...
[SPEAKER_12]: They'll probably just, they have just a fun and happy medium.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, you can't just make it super duper easy to put stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, look at, like, for example, the Ouya.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's a perfect example of how you can self-publish on there, but there's not a ton of stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: That store's a mess, too, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, well, that store has been a mess since launch, especially with their...
[SPEAKER_12]: Like fucked up like menus and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: The way to navigate that is it's not very well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And like, you know, you look at like all the different bars that feature things like every single one of them has got the same games in it, just in a different order.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like the Wii U store when it first launched or not too much different now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, so it's just kind of weird, but they do have it where you can easily publish stuff on there, but I think it's just some sort of quality sorting and stuff and just better ways to search for what you're actually looking for.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, you know, THQ had some problems last year and they went bankrupt and, you know, a lot of their properties went to all these different places.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hence why, you know, we have Deep Silver doing Saints Row now and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Sega, apparently not happy with the way things went down because they filed a claim against THQ and bankruptcy court, of course, because THQ is bankrupt.
[SPEAKER_04]: for almost a million dollars just shy of that about $941,000 that apparently is the amount that THQ received in pre-orders after Valve's cut for Company of Heroes 2 apparently Eurogamer had also reported that about a half million was made after THQ filed for bankruptcy so Sega wants to get that money back that came in from pre-orders for Company of Heroes 2
[SPEAKER_04]: Double Fine, Codemasters, and other former THQ executives also looking for the money that they're supposed to be getting this doesn't mean any of them will get anything I imagine this is part of the process filing the claim so you can ultimately later on claim it as a loss when it comes to tax season later on but it's interesting that this THQ drama still goes on
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, the reason why Sega wants the money is because they got Relic, the developer, and the Company of Heroes property.
[SPEAKER_04]: They bought that for $26.6 million at the THQ asset auction.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what's going down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sega wants their money.
[SPEAKER_04]: They want to buy their building back from Zynga.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, they say, if we had a million dollars, we could make Dreamcast 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I had a million dollars, maybe Sonic 4 wouldn't suck.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, it's funny the difference between what a million dollars is to you 10 years ago versus now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now I'm like, house!
[SPEAKER_08]: I can buy a house!
[SPEAKER_08]: League of Legends
[SPEAKER_08]: It is now been considered, and this is a quote coming from Riot Games esports manager Nick Allen, said the United States government recognizes League of Legends pro players as professional athletes and awards visas to essentially work in the United States under that title.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, it is officially an esports and the pro players are ethletes, as I'm calling them.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's my new word and you have to give credit to me, ethlete.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you suck at croquet?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, actually I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I cannot play croquet without singing Que Sera Sera to myself because of Heathers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm pretty good at miniature golf.
[SPEAKER_08]: So am I. My husband's really good at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that a sport?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is mini golf a sport?
[SPEAKER_08]: It is officially in my universe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well that's all I need.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I've been talking about forming the Island of Awesome, and I think the national sport of the Island of Awesome should be mini golf.
[SPEAKER_12]: I honestly think that they should make mini golf courses the size of actual golf courses and televise that shit because I want to see someone doing a drive off of a giant loop-de-loop and all sorts of crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be right there with Dodgeball and League of Legends on the Ocho.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been 8, the 8th
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to have Blizzard, All Stars, Valve has Dota 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't there another one?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's another one I'm not thinking of.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's another smaller one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, all those guys that contributed to the original Defense of the Ancients mod in Warcraft 3 all went their own separate ways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you got all these games because of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is Dota 2 going to be a sport?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or what happens next?
[SPEAKER_08]: How do you guys feel about... I still think we want Pro DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you guys feel about... But DDR's dead, yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haven't you got the memo?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR... It's like the disco boys in Mystery Men.
[SPEAKER_08]: Eddie Izzard.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR's life.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's death.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, after we're done playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can sweat playing chess.
[SPEAKER_12]: In a hot room.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: But those people are... You're not going to see it in the fucking Olympics, okay?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_12]: And don't even try to petition that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw says it's called eSports.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like new sports.
[SPEAKER_08]: Will we have the Olympics?
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be actually kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft in chat says, how about stuff like Evo?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's all going on right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, that's a huge Olympics type of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's only for fighting games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But still, I mean, getting quite a bit of viewership and controversy of its own online.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll get into later in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Infinal in our chatroom says, Next, Mario and Sonic at the Olympics will be an eSport.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's very meta.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to release dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to travel around the world and check out what games are coming out that could be a sport in a few years.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see, Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I don't know about any of the games you're going to support this week, but... Because, like, for example, there's Turbo Super Stunt Squad, which is a game based on the... Is it TurboTastic?
[SPEAKER_12]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's based on that DreamWorks movie about the snail that somehow ingests NOS and so becomes, like, a super fast snail.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because, you know, that's science right there.
[SPEAKER_12]: So they have that coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360...
[SPEAKER_12]: Wii, Wii U, 3DS, and DS.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also this week, your ever-yearly multi-release version of you versus a bunch of other feudal Japan warriors.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dynasty Warriors 8 coming out on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also this week, Time and Eternity on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's see, the Serious Sam Collection being released on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's a bunch of Xbox Live Arcade games that were on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want to say, I think that might be it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Am I missing something?
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me move to Japan then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye, I'm moving.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving to the Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XIII 2 gets a price reduction on the PlayStation 3 on July 18th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shin Sangoku Mosou Online Z in regular edition and Treasure Box edition comes out on the 18th as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Dynasty Warriors Online, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what that is.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XIII 2 gets its reduction there too.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's like a digital contents version and Platinum Collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I bet digital contents is just all the DLC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the Saw's side story and all the stuff that came out for XIII 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a lot of DLC for XIII 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't care about XIII 2?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I am incorporating them into my own virtual consciousness fair enough on the Wii U yes Sniper Elite V2 is out this week from Ubisoft in Japan Sniper Elite is that that's a game that's out here is that like one of the Tom Clancy games no it's not it's a World War 2 Sniper game ah
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo 3DS sees a little bit this week Mario & Luigi RPG 4 Dream Adventure comes out this week from Nintendo Danball Senkai W. Cho Custom comes out this week from Level 5 There is a special Luigi Nintendo 3DS XL this week I don't know if it's like green or what the... I gotta see what this is Is it a green... I mean it has to be, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S doesn't try and import one of these.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe he will.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also on the 3DS this week, Shin Sekaiju no Mikyu Design Skins.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those aren't even games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are just little skins for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Osahari Hamster 2 Korosau Isho ni Orokake comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do something together.
[SPEAKER_04]: Play with adorable hamsters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my gosh, it's hamster sim.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe it's let's play together.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, the box.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is adorable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do we get games like this here?
[SPEAKER_07]: They're on a sunflower.
[SPEAKER_04]: The hamsters are sitting on a sunflower.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wearing bows.
[SPEAKER_04]: One is wearing a tiara.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you look at the game shots.
[SPEAKER_04]: and like they're playing in this like cherry blossom field with a little hamster wheel and then there's one underwater here and then here's one with the hamsters they're just chilling at the beach this little chief hamster there sitting in a lounge chair just chilling at the beach
[SPEAKER_12]: That's not realistic at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, if they were in that field of flowers... Well, they're not going to have Richard Gere's asshole as a level, Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I understand that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not saying that they do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: They'd be like running from owls level.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm just saying that they would just need to be there, and they would just shove in their face full of food, because that's all hamsters do, is shove in their face full of food.
[SPEAKER_12]: They throw their poop, actually, because they like to keep their cage clean, so they huck it like footballs.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they pee on you when they're nervous.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ranma is pointing out that he's not interested in this 3DS XL because it's region locked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to find a way to un-region lock Osahara Hamster to Koraso Isho ni Odakake because, again, here's the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it says, like, let's play together.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's a game that we need in America.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't we have this game in America?
[SPEAKER_04]: And Nintendo's fascist state 3DS will not allow me to import this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is a challenge to all our listeners now.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you have a hamster, I want you to put a bow on it and send me a picture.
[SPEAKER_04]: But keep the hamster's... Oh my God, don't harm the hamster.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't glue it to the hamster's head, you know, like... Or what do they do?
[SPEAKER_08]: Staple it to the hamster's... Safety first.
[SPEAKER_07]: In Scrooged?
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be this great.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, like, I want to see... Or you can Photoshop a tiara onto your hamster.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to see your glammed-up hamsters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Photoshop DarkSakura's face.
[SPEAKER_08]: Glamsters, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the game that we need, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that a dream game?
[SPEAKER_08]: OLR dream game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Glamsters.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: There have been games...
[SPEAKER_12]: by Activision.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's actually, I believe, like a Pets Hamsters with a Z in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they have had games where it's Pets fashion where you actually do dress up.
[SPEAKER_12]: It is not that cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: I beg to differ, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's also a Hamtaro game.
[SPEAKER_08]: But not like little CG actual looking hamsters that are adorable that wear bows and tiaras and go to the beach.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want Photoshop of a hamster with a crown on a beach chair.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's my challenge.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I could do it myself, but I'm lazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just going to... No, this is a whole President Cat thing going on here because who made this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who made this?
[SPEAKER_08]: We need to start harassing them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nipong Columbia, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want their Twitter harassed.
[SPEAKER_04]: and we're going to call this game Glamsters is the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: localization title.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I want Glamsters.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know what it translates to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Glamsters.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I want Glamsters in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob, the name is essentially playing with hamsters or playing together with hamsters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Glamsters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who made this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nippon Columbia.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's their Twitter?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oil Army, get to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bring me a Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the 14th, which is what today?
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't it now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mega Man Unlimited for PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the 16th, Momotokun Curse on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the 18th, Plants vs. Zombies 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's about time.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that wasn't me saying that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's actually the title.
[SPEAKER_08]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm spent.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm surprised Mega Man Unlimited was listed on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that's a fan game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it's a fan game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm kind of surprised that's on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's on there, so good for them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_12]: As a precautionary measure, they basically said that credit card information was not stored on the server, and they weren't sure what was taken during the breach, or if anything.
[SPEAKER_12]: But basically, all the stored passwords were encrypted, and they're saying it's very unlikely anything can be done with the passwords.
[SPEAKER_12]: But they've reset them, so you've got to make a new one anyways.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Konami has also been hacked as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Konami's ID portal website had a large batch of unauthorized logins, I guess, during the month of June.
[SPEAKER_12]: And basically saying that it's exposed some customer information and they recommend changing your passports.
[SPEAKER_12]: So...
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, and apparently also the information that may have been exposed, customer names, addresses, dates of birth, telephone numbers, email addresses, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Change your passwords.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hackers gonna hack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope your password that you used on these websites was not the same that you used on your bank website because that would have been a really bad idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why these things get hacked for people that use the same password everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe you'll see Glamsters on the show floor at Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, you won't because it's already out in Japan, but we can still dream it will still show up at Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tokyo Game Show had its list of exhibitors announced this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: When is Tokyo Game Show?
[SPEAKER_04]: October-ish?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's usually September.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it is September.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Exhibitor list is out and Microsoft's on it, which is a bit of a surprise because the Xbox One...
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you laughing over there?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, we got all these cool things to show you that we're not releasing this year because the Xbox One's not coming to your region because you're second tier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox One coming to the second tier country of Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I don't say that to be offensive, but the reality is that since Japan didn't support the first Xbox... Do they have cosplay at Tokyo Game Show?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good, someone can cosplay at Tumbleweed and maybe roll through the booth.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're such an ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft also going to be going to Gamescom if anyone's keeping track of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, it'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, folks at Tokyo Game Show, Sony, Capcom, EA, Sega, Squeenix, Konami, Namco Bandai, Tecmo Koei, Bethesda.
[SPEAKER_04]: All those folks are going to be at Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess who's not there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they're never there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo will not be there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they never do Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_04]: They usually do their own thing that same week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they're Nintendo and that's what they do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brad from PodCulture in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com with a comment on the hacking article saying it is Konami's own fault they were hacked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their code was up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A, start.
[SPEAKER_12]: Shouldn't use the same code in every game that you make.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, it's different in Proteus.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was backwards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Respect this game or get out of my planet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Off my planet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get off my patalandia.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Pinbot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, good choice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's actually not the table.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the NES game that Rare developed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Excellent choice.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game came out in... Crap, I didn't link the YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, it'll take me a minute to get the audio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everybody, I'm sorry for Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry for your face.
[SPEAKER_04]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aw, epic rare soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_08]: God, I didn't know I didn't have such good music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we just listen to this for a minute?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to hear you talk.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just want to hear this.
[SPEAKER_08]: You what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Head face.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, sexy lady pinball.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like her electro moves.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I suppose you can talk now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, the game came out in North America in 1990, and it was a version of the same pinball machine that Williams did in 1986.
[SPEAKER_08]: The NES version actually has most of the stuff from the machine, and graphically is pretty darn accurate, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like how they even have the Williams logo at the bottom and how they did the scores where the normal price things are.
[SPEAKER_08]: So the point really is just to get points.
[SPEAKER_08]: You start off with your marker set on Pluto.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to go through the solar system by hitting different targets.
[SPEAKER_08]: and different checkpoint planets give you specials so you get extra balls that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: And when you reach the sun you get a super special so you get another extra ball.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have the visor too which basically works exactly like it does in the arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm sure, I really hope most of you have played the legit for reals pinball, I mean pinbot before.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you have a 5x5 grid that has drop targets, and once you've hit them, the grid lights, the visor opens, and you can lock the balls there to start your multiball.
[SPEAKER_08]: And in this game, it is a double multiball.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can also re-lock balls while they're in multiball and get extra points.
[SPEAKER_08]: So with this, basically, to get such a long playfield, it actually crops it where your flippers are and the top screen moves until it reconnects to wherever it would be once they're joined.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has the ramps.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: It really is about the best.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, other than now, like on pin name or something, it really is probably... It was the only good version of this game you could get at home, apart from owning the table.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, um, I mean, I'll sit and play this sometimes, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: And one good thing about this, too, is that, um, it actually has, um, some of the synthesized speech from the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, although it pauses the game to play the speech.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has most of the music, the sound effects.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can turn them on and off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your pause is on your second controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: The first can't because you use start and select as your nudge.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, make sure you don't tilt.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of people really, really liked it because it is a faithful rendition, but there are people who did not like the enemies and hazards on the playfield as they were not in the original.
[SPEAKER_08]: They did rare reuse the game engine to do high speed, which was also based off of Steve Ritchie's High Speed, but it was published by Tradewest.
[SPEAKER_08]: by the way, Steve Ritchie is a really cool guy he did the voices for Black Knight for No Fear and he's just a really cool dude I want to do voices on a pinball game be fun stop shaking the table
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob's game would be called Girl Please.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bitch, please!
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, as far as other pinball games that came out on the NES, there was Pinball, Rollerball, Rock'n'Ball, and Pinball Quest.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really think that Pinbot is the brightest on the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pinball Quest is one of those games you kind of remember through rose-colored glasses.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, oh man, Pinball Quest was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you go back and play it and you're like, god, it was... It had so many bugs and issues, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was not good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pinbot is just solid.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a testament, I think, to early Rare games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rollerball wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rollerball wasn't bad at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: You forgot the actual game called Pinball from Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there was Pinball.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I still think that Pinbot's the best of the batch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rollerball was also... I thought there was one other I'm not thinking of.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll tell you what's funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: The actual table for Rollerball was the first game I played when I got to the expo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't know it was a real table.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's like... Was it like four screens tall or something?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I'm thinking of a different game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or maybe it was Roller Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Roller Games is one of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I think you're blending those.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I think Roller Ball on NES was like a four screen tall table.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was thinking of Roller Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know which one I always wish I would have had a release like that?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was Hyper Ball.
[SPEAKER_08]: The one where you have the major multiballs and all you do is shoot pinballs all day and all night until you hit these little side targets.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hyper Ball would have been fun, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: But...
[SPEAKER_08]: Digress.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pinbot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Classic.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can't go wrong with Pinbot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if anyone ever thinks to get a classic table, Pinbot makes a great start and it makes really good for trading up later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pinbot for the Nintendo Entertainment System.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of my favorites.
[SPEAKER_04]: A non-Sega game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I do non-Sega games all the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've done Compile.
[SPEAKER_04]: Non-Sega slash non-Termographics game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've done Irem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some folks in chat reminiscing about some of the portable pinball games that were really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fifth Dream says Pokemon pinball owned.
[SPEAKER_04]: Black Wolf says I enjoyed Metroid Prime pinball in the DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: What was the game that was on the original Game Boy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it Revenge of the Gator?
[SPEAKER_08]: That one was fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Revenge of the Gator was great.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would stay up all night playing that damn game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember playing that in 7th grade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Were you a Revenge of the Gator fan, Bradley?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, your mic cut out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, it came off the end there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was saying something even earlier than these games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if it was based on any real pinball table, but there was a pinball on the Atari 2600, like Midnight Magic or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Atari had one of their own too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it was like a really basic sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of my favorite Commodore 64 games ever was Pinball Construction Set by ECA.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what EA used to be back in the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was ECA.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pinball Construction Set was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was literally build your own damn pinball table, but people would, you know, there was no internet really back then, but you would disc trade with people and get their pinball tables and you could find some pretty epic stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of props for Revenge of the Gator in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: BlackWolf says, I loved it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ranma says, Revenge of the Gator was godly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I knew BlackWolf would remember Pinball Construction set.
[SPEAKER_04]: I knew he would.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I was actually just thinking that it would be cool if, you know, because you know, like, there's actually a pinball table for Rollercoaster Tycoon.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would be cool if they did, like, SimPin now.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, where it's, you build your pinball tables and then put them out on, um...
[SPEAKER_08]: and on something like Steam, you have the creator and you put your tables up for other people to download and compare and rate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or how about just freaking pinball construction set, but like, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think that the game you were thinking of was called David's Midnight Magic, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, there was a Midnight Magic for Atari 2600, but there was also a David's Midnight Magic.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, here's the pinball construction set.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me see if there's actual music or if there's somebody talking in this clip here on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, you can see that they're putting together their little pinball table, and they put up little ramps, and all the stuff you use to build it's over there on the side.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then let's see if we actually see a finished table here.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was David's Midnight Magic.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was also a Commodore 64 version, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it was on the Atari computers.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the Atari 2600 version was just called Midnight Magic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's going to do it for this Part A of Orange Launch Radio, but don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got more of Orange Launch Radio to come after the break.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, Crewball.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was awful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crewball, apparently.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Mailbag, the Fugle Question of the Week, your phone calls, and some more stories, including, yes, we're going to talk about that little controversy that went down between Nintendo and Evo, and speaking of Nintendo, a possible new franchise for them next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll talk all about that when we come back with more of Orange Launch Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi there, this is Elliot B, and you're participating with Orange Lounge Radio, the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I want to use my voice to tell you that Donkey Kong Country 2 is the best game ever released on the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_01]: It has musical apes fighting reptilian pirates.
[SPEAKER_01]: What more could you ask for?
[SPEAKER_04]: Boobs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, live with episode number 512, July the 14th of 2013.
[SPEAKER_04]: Big thanks to Elliot there for the bumper, even though that's the second time y'all have heard it, because I don't have any new bumpers to play, so I think you guys need to fix that.
[SPEAKER_04]: For more information about sending a bumper to Orange Lounge Radio, check out vognetwork.com, and the forums has all the information there in Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything you need to know there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm playing the new Find Me games during the break because I street passed with Bradley, who's sitting here in studio tonight, and I also street passed with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, one thing I noticed about this Warriors Way, which I'm still trying to figure this game out, it's basically like you have troops, and the troops number is based on the number of people you've had ever in your plaza.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I street passed with a friend of mine that does some of the shadow casting for movies here locally, and he's like, dude, Robb,
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you gave me 700 people for my army in Warrior's Way.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm like, yeah, yeah, you know, I've been to E3 and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I've picked up quite a few people.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's like, you helped me beat a level.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm like, all right, I'm awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a big army.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I just street passed you with Brad who came into Warrior's Way.
[SPEAKER_04]: 25,000 people?
[SPEAKER_04]: You've Street Passed with 25,000 people?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, wait, you're not... Okay, sorry, we're not hearing you for some reason.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's my fault, I didn't mute you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, Bradley.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, so that's not exactly how many I've Street Passed.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually have 1,000...
[SPEAKER_10]: A little over a thousand street passes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Still, that's a lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the army is 25,000 because as you play the game, you get more people into your army and they'll show you the actual force.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's you come in as a monarch if you've actually been playing the game and then that's when you'll see something more than a few hundred to a thousand.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why it was 25,000.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's showing what my actual armory is right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: But your people weren't like, oh, I'm going to join up.
[SPEAKER_04]: You tried to attack
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Crazy Taxi
[SPEAKER_12]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_12]: Crazy Taxi has come to Android, and yeah, it's out for $5.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's basically like the iOS port.
[SPEAKER_12]: They've got the two modes, original and arcade, and I think some of the music's back too, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sure they don't have Pizza Hut and all that stuff in there, but...
[SPEAKER_12]: Still fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I think it does support some controllers.
[SPEAKER_12]: So the first thing I'm going to do with this game is I'm going to sideload it onto the Ouya to see if it works.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that's going to be mission number one, I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: New Ratchet & Clank game was revealed this week into the Nexus.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's going to be coming out at some undetermined point, I guess holiday, for $30 on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: So look for it then.
[SPEAKER_12]: And last but not least, we have some more details about the PlayStation Plus version of DriveClub.
[SPEAKER_12]: Obviously, it will be missing a few things.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's basically the exact same version as the full version, except it's missing a few assets, such as some of the cars or tracks that will be found in the full version.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess the PlayStation Plus edition will feature online multiplayer and the single-player campaign.
[SPEAKER_12]: as well as some of the challenges, you will be able to purchase missing content.
[SPEAKER_04]: But press the R2 button to upgrade to the full version of DriveClub now.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it's not going to be as expensive as buying the full version of DriveClub, but still, I mean, if you want to check it out, it's kind of a cool thing, and you don't have to buy the full version of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, like, for example, if someone like me just wants to play it on a VOG gaming night or something like that, I don't need to buy the full version.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can just play it as is, so it'll be cool to check out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I mean, I wasn't expecting... To get a release game on the system's release for free... I mean, usually the PS Plus games aren't new stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's usually a year old.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm not totally surprised by this, that it's basically a glorified demo.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it sounds like it'll at least have some multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it'll give you a little something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this is what we get now instead of a pack-in game, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: A free download coupon.
[SPEAKER_12]: Technically, you get a pack-in thing, but it's only if you have the camera.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, the camera, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have the camera, so I guess I'm screwed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I was lucky enough to order a PlayStation 4 early, and I don't plan on changing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, moving on to other news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Capcom had some layoffs this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's always a bit disappointing.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the people affected, Christian Svensson, which is the senior VP, excuse me,
[SPEAKER_04]: of Planning and Business Development.
[SPEAKER_04]: He apparently is departing the company.
[SPEAKER_04]: Capcom said in a statement, Capcom today laid off several employees from the US office as part of an overall organizational restructure of the company.
[SPEAKER_04]: The transition to new generation of hardware and changing industry landscape have required us to adapt our business to best meet our new goals.
[SPEAKER_04]: We sincerely thank each individual for their contributions and wish them well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, this is never fun news to report.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trying to kind of figure out the why behind this, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this because maybe expectations of Lost Planet 3 and so forth are kind of low?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is this because there's no more Mega Man?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all Mega Man's fault.
[SPEAKER_08]: All Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you did Mega Man Legends 3, they wouldn't have this problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, now, no need to kick them while they're down.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Reggie Fils-Aim in a video on YouTube mentioned that Nintendo fans can pick up Pikmin 3 early at certain video game retailers.
[SPEAKER_04]: July 20th and 21st, you can actually do like a hands-on demo at over 250 GameStop and EB Games locations.
[SPEAKER_04]: They still have EB Games up and running different places?
[SPEAKER_04]: Foreign company.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, in Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the US and Canada will have...
[SPEAKER_04]: Pikmin 3 experiences or whatever if you pre-order the downloadable version of the game at any GameStop store on either of those two days so you have to go get a download code at GameStop on one of those two days you will be able to get the full game one whole day early on August 3rd
[SPEAKER_04]: or you can go to Kmart who breaks street dates or Toys R Us or apparently Walmart is the new street date breaker because you know you can get them Twinkies at Walmart yeah it's rogue Twinkies in the Walmart aisles or just wait a day it's Pikmin it's not fucking Grand Theft Auto 5 or something right I mean that's what she got you know that
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, think of the deal with the devil that you're making here.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, you're like buying a digital download code at retail to play it one day early.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they will make you sign a pact at GameStop that you will have to sign with blood.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, let's give us your email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, why don't you sign up for the card, you know, so that we can... Hey, you want to get our magazine?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't you come... You got Pikmin 2 to trade in?
[SPEAKER_04]: Truth be told, their magazine's actually pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing is ever as good as Sonic R.
[SPEAKER_04]: SuperStreetFighter4, Alina, Poison, Rolento, Hugo
[SPEAKER_04]: which are all based off of the fact that they were in Street Fighter X Tekken so I'm guessing that they'll be easy enough to bring over so those are the only four confirmed characters at the moment no word about the mystery fifth character although not it doesn't sound like it's Alex I guess there was a rumor going around that it was Alex but it doesn't appear to be Alex so interesting
[SPEAKER_04]: What is this all about here?
[SPEAKER_04]: $15 for the download.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't know what the date will be, but there will also be a disc-based version, which I'm assuming is everything, for $40.
[SPEAKER_04]: Early 2014 is the tentative release.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I'd like to see some of the EX characters make it into the new Street Fighter 4 stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty cool that this game is still going.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, thanks to updates and DLC and all that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're shaking your head over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're a hater, Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: How many times have they re-released this game?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, seriously, they've had... How many times have they re-released Street Fighter 2?
[SPEAKER_12]: I understand that, but they had Street Fighter 4, then they had Super Street Fighter 4, Super Street Fighter 4 Arcade Edition.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm talking all disc-based releases.
[SPEAKER_12]: And now they're going to have Hyper Super Street Fighter 4 Arcade Edition?
[SPEAKER_12]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: You draw the lines?
[SPEAKER_12]: Stop buying that game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's done.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just make a new Street Fighter game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or give me Capcom vs. SNK.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Capcom vs. SNK 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care what evil, satanic packs have to be formed between those companies to get this to happen, but I want that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give it to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: They're just porting the... They're not even porting the game over.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it works with controller support already.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can sideload that thing in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I have Sonic CD.
[SPEAKER_12]: I got it with my MOGA controller.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I think it's sideloaded on my Ouya, actually.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't remember if I did that or not.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it works.
[SPEAKER_08]: Saga of America saying that it's going to be soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: That same soon that we always refer to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, fans of Skullgirls can be happy that it's coming on PC on August 22nd.
[SPEAKER_08]: Being put out by Lab Zero Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I know a lot of people are totally into Skullgirls.
[SPEAKER_08]: and they're also working on five new characters as DLC which is coming directly from their Indiegogo campaign they've actually exceeded their $150,000 goal they've made $828,768 so yay more Skullgirls
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: and I'm really looking forward to this there's also a link on here to the documentaries which talks about the game itself and the development so I'm going to go ahead and actually relink this one in the chat room and if any people who are listening to the podcast want to look for it just go to Capcom Unity and look through their blog yeah they're actually going to do a physical retail release with pins in it
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a week later, though, which sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it might still be worth it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob, life is like a hurricane.
[SPEAKER_04]: It blows?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: The song?
[SPEAKER_08]: The theme song?
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock You Like a Hurricane.
[SPEAKER_08]: DuckTales Rob theme song.
[SPEAKER_08]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: God.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little slow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jeez, Rab.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, though, I listened to the Japanese theme song for DuckTales.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a song by a lady.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, time for the foogle question of the week, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't realize that was our last story.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, you got on me for being quiet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was pulling up everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now you're doing it too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was playing me plaza games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pot kettle.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pot, pot, kettle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very, very important.
[SPEAKER_08]: My butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: uh let's see uh looking at chat room at live.vognetwork.com apparently BlackWolf made a vine of me playing Pimbot Ness me meaning him while listening to OLR but vine decides not to accept the upload I guess this is why everybody ran away to Instagram sad have you guys played with the Instagram video at all no no
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob, Instagram is like so three months ago, I swear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Hipstagram.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, here, I had to hear this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need to use a top-level digital camera out of irony.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Still catchy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some things transcend language barriers, and a catchy melody is one of those things.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's get to the Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe this little theme song here is a catchy melody for some of you out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Redertainment says, There's what I call a classic arcade game that I've played that I'd like to play again, The Act.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is an extremely rare arcade game that, according to Wikipedia, only one arcade has a working stand-up arcade copy of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just so happens the one arcade with a stand-up copy of The Act is located near me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looks like I have something to do on Monday.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is The Act?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know that one.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Act is a game.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's all hand-drawn animation.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, Loki,
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, let's see, Robaba responds on Google Plus and says, I've always wanted to try Hyperball, the ball-bearing gun rapid-fire pinball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie probably has, and I'm curious as to the general object of that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spell things?
[SPEAKER_04]: Shoot them faster than they drain?
[SPEAKER_08]: I talked about it earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_08]: I just like shooting them really fast, and just because it's fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's so many, it's like you can play with so many balls.
Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_08]: You can paddle balls all day.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just took all those balls all at once, didn't you, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_08]: And I beat them.
[SPEAKER_08]: I beat those balls with flippers.
[SPEAKER_04]: With your flipper?
[SPEAKER_08]: My flippers.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game is fucking loud, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, I just want to point out over on Facebook right now, we have 572 people that like us on Facebook, which is a nice admirable number, but we're 572.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need one more like, and then there'll be a huge Bomani in joke there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, people.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more like on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody give it to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kurti K replied and said, Simpsons pinball.
[SPEAKER_04]: There were actually two Simpsons pinball machines.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it Simpsons Pinball Party, are you thinking?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's an old one and a newer one, isn't there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Simpsons Pinball Party we used to have at my house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a pretty fun table.
[SPEAKER_04]: Andy R said, I was a bit young during the arcade boom, so I don't remember, but if I can expand to non-classic arcade games, I really want to play Jubit or Reflect Beat in an arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love rhythm games like Technica, and I feel these games would be a lot more fun in the arcade than their iPad equivalents.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'd be right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sadly, I no longer live near Round 1 or Sunnyvale Golf Land, so I guess I'll have to settle for the iPad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, that reminds me of something, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what game they also have there speaking of side-scrolling?
[SPEAKER_04]: Willow.
[SPEAKER_04]: and Willow Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry for the Facebook noises.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not disabled on this computer and freaking people are setting it off on purpose.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thomas B replies and says, have you ever heard of the pinball machine Hercules?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe they used four inch balls.
[SPEAKER_04]: The machine was very large.
[SPEAKER_04]: I only played it a few times, but it was always fun to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you like big balls, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_08]: And I cannot lie.
[SPEAKER_08]: It used a cue ball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, like in pool?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and they had one at the last Classic Gaming Expo I went to.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was at California Extreme two years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: They also had that dressed-up Captain Fantastic, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: The big Elton John platform boots from Tommy.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Hercules is actually... I'm short.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a hard time playing that game because I can't really...
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't reach the balls?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I have to... It's like as wide out as my arms go.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like my wingspan.
[SPEAKER_08]: And hitting the flippers is difficult.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it moves slowly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Tetsuya says, there was one I played years ago in Santa Cruz that I'd love to chance to play again, Namco's Galaxian 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine a gigantic booth with six seats, two 50-inch monitors with a separate laser displayer for each one, and six Star Wars-style flight controllers.
[SPEAKER_04]: You fly along in your gunship, shooting at aliens as they fly in formation, while occasionally dealing with a gigantic alien boss.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's up to you and your teammates to take them down before they deplete your ship's life meter to zero.
[SPEAKER_04]: Suffice to say, it's pretty epic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you want to know something depressing?
[SPEAKER_08]: At our Roseville Dave & Busters, right by the Redemption area, there is this booth that, for a different game, but that booth was once a Galaxian 3 booth.
[SPEAKER_08]: It even has some of the decorating elements on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That used to be a Galaxian 3 booth.
[SPEAKER_04]: uh let's see um Will M replied and said an arcade game I've never played and would love to difficult to answer as I've played a massive amount due to traveling around but I can name one I'd love to play again the Ninja Warriors that widescreen was oh so damn awesome
[SPEAKER_04]: Chiggers says, I remember playing the kiss table when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ragenator said, I never had the opportunity to play the arcade version of Killer Instinct, which I regret.
[SPEAKER_04]: In terms of stuff I want to play again, it's Samurai Shodown 4, Amakusa's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hitstun says,
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds a lot like Proteus.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game's only console release is a Japanese PlayStation 2 exclusive.
[SPEAKER_04]: He could have made that up and I'd never know the difference.
[SPEAKER_04]: Codeman replied and said, I know this sounds like a generic answer, but I've always wanted to play the Tron arcade game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was Tron and Discs of Tron.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had actually Tron and Discs of Tron next to each other.
[SPEAKER_04]: Codeman, more reason for you to go to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know you have a little girl who soon will be old enough to appreciate Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you take a child to Disneyland before they're five years old, they get in free.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a game called Time Pilot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Time Pilot's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is, for what it's worth, that's on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it plays pretty decently with a 360 analog stick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just for what it's worth.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was in Game Room.
[SPEAKER_04]: and lastly Kane I Am says not that I ever played it but I really want the Elvira Mistress of the Darkness table for my house because boobies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excellent answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is a great table too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_08]: The Elvira Mistress or the Scared Steff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Elvira Mistress of the Dark.
[SPEAKER_08]: Scaredstiff, I think, is a better table.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so I know you saw this, DarkSakura, because Alan and I went out to a bar in San Francisco after the Frank Music concert on the 4th of July, or the night before the 4th of July.
[SPEAKER_04]: We went out in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_04]: We went to this bar in the Castro called Moby Dick, and they have pinball machines there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, like, literally, it was like DarkSakura and Alan Alchemy pinball paradise because they had a World Cup Sakura 94.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they had Elvira Scared Stiff Okay, I need to go there Yeah First of all And gays and booze and a pool table Like five of my favorite things together That actually is like college for me Well, keep in mind, I worked in a pool hall Uh-huh
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm very certain that my boss, even though he was a major dick, he did set off the gator a bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course, there were also the three other guys that I used to hang out with.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, I've been a hag all my life, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we had the World Cup soccer there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Across the street at Solomon's, they had the Mistress of the Dark.
[SPEAKER_04]: But did your pool hall let people play free if they weren't wearing pants?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because this place did.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, usually if they weren't wearing pants.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could wear a skirt, then I wouldn't be wearing pants.
[SPEAKER_08]: What if a guy comes in in a Utila kilt?
[SPEAKER_08]: Does that count?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't question the system because nobody wants to see me up there playing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: You should just have sequined boxers.
[SPEAKER_08]: How do you know I don't?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alan, does Rob have sequin boxers?
[SPEAKER_12]: The 1970s basketball shorts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the ones that are up to here.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have the teeny slit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like your ass literally hangs out of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to go in Columbia shorts.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not sexy at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: None of this is sexy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Columbia shorts.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was all our answers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys at Facebook and Google Plus for answering the question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you didn't get your question or your answer read this week, sorry, but try sending an email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com Let me quickly open that up to folks here in studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there an elusive game you haven't been able to play or maybe something you played once long ago you're dying to play again?
[SPEAKER_04]: Bradley?
[SPEAKER_10]: I was thinking of when I played it a long time ago, Galaxy Force 2, the actual arcade game that actually had a full rotating seat or sit down cabinet where you basically Sumo Yeah, but full rotating.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could you actually go upside down and stuff?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I would have said the Galaxian 3, but someone already said that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would be willing to try the Silent Hill arcade game, because I still haven't played that, and I know that was something that they made a while ago.
[SPEAKER_12]: So the Silent Hill arcade game would be fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: And although it's not really an arcade game, I'd love to go back and play Battletech again as part of Virtual World.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did Alan just text you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, he did, and he said no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alan!
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, is there something that's been eluding you?
[SPEAKER_08]: I would like to play Radiant Silvergun again because I've played an arcade version of that and I loved Gun Survivor 2, Byhazard Gun Survivor 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think what I would actually like to play again as far as tables that I haven't seen in a little while is a Black Rose.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I've been trying to get Dan to get us one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would love to have a Black Rose.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess my answer would be I would really like to play F-Zero AX again in one of the sit-down cabinets.
[SPEAKER_04]: That shit was pretty amazing and I missed that an awful lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'd like to be able to play that again.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we're not talking just the regular sit-down cabinets.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we're talking the ones that rotate.
[SPEAKER_04]: The ones that will almost flip you upside down, like just shy of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I missed that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was epic.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I would say maybe, yeah, I guess that's my answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: F-Zero AX.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to play that again.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there was like a table, a pinball table that I hadn't played in a long time that I actually got to see it
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Coupa Kid Jeremy Coupa Kid Jeremy
[SPEAKER_04]: like that's what old arcades smelled like and Chuck E. Cheese well Chuck E. Cheese didn't smell like cigarettes like they did ban smoking in there I think because you know kids but cheap pizza for sure at Chuck E. Cheese anyhow uh let's see Codeman says tell me about it I don't even want to know what an arcade is anymore well god I think there's somebody legit said in their answer you know I think I was kind of born after arcades were really a thing and that just made me like
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a sad for a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to offer up a description.
[SPEAKER_08]: This was the Aladdin's Castle in Mobile, Alabama.
[SPEAKER_08]: The day I went after my little brother had gotten hit by a car.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was six.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's 30 now.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, 27 right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that, you know, dates it.
[SPEAKER_08]: The walls were half-carpeted, the same way they had been since the 70s.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, this has to be like 1992, something like that.
91.
[SPEAKER_08]: The walls had brown carpet up to the side, like a roller rink does.
[SPEAKER_08]: Old wallpaper.
[SPEAKER_08]: Posters of games from the 80s.
[SPEAKER_08]: The first thing that you saw when you walked in was a Samurai Shodown 2 on the 44-inch screen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Big-ass thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: To the left would have been a hockey table.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember it perfectly.
[SPEAKER_08]: To the left would have been an air hockey table.
[SPEAKER_08]: As you go back, you see Nark.
[SPEAKER_08]: You see a four-player Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles.
[SPEAKER_08]: You see a Street Fighter 2 Hyper Fighting Edition.
[SPEAKER_08]: You see...
[SPEAKER_08]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: Chuck E. Cheese smells like pee
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember they do now that's for sure I don't remember from when I was a kid but maybe you know everything I remember I have this really early memory you know I don't remember a lot from when I was like before like you know you don't remember a lot from before you're like five years old I don't know about you guys but one thing I do remember is being I think I was three years old at my sister's wedding because my sister would have been 19 or 20 at the time because there's a big age difference between us
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: and I remember a room at Chuck E. Cheese that was nothing but a strobe light and you would dance in front of the strobe light or whatever and like it's like 80s technology like strobe lights or like this new technology.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now you can have a strobe light on your fucking phone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did yours have the day glow room?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was black lights with drawings on the wall that would glow under the black light and at my Chuck E. Cheese and this is like the old old ass one that like I think burned down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but there were the hands and feet on the wall right above the door and you go through the door and you're in this little room that's day glow and then on the other side is the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we had that too.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had the strobe room too and then we had the room with the hippo lady.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I remember the hippo lady.
[SPEAKER_08]: The party room with hippo lady.
[SPEAKER_04]: Henrietta Hippo.
[SPEAKER_04]: They still have all the animatronics.
[SPEAKER_04]: They get scarier as you get older.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we had the showbiz pizza at my place.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of them bought the other.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chuck E. Cheese bought Showbiz at one point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pizza Time Theater.
[SPEAKER_04]: Were you from this area?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm from South Carolina.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know who owned Pizza Time Theater, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nolan Bushnell.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then there was Bullwinkles that had the water show.
[SPEAKER_12]: Water Sports.
[SPEAKER_12]: They had a water show.
[SPEAKER_12]: They had a fountain.
[SPEAKER_12]: It would just do this fountain show thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: A miniature version of what you would see at the Bellagio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that like the climax of The Great Muppet Caper?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did Miss Piggy come out on the fountain?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sort of, I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Bullwinkles.
[SPEAKER_12]: All the Bullwinkles characters.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to go to an arcade, arcade, arcade
[SPEAKER_04]: So we went to some mall and, you know, because my mom liked to shop anyway, so we went to the mall and they had an arcade and I got my way.
[SPEAKER_12]: I fucking miss malls having arcades.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_08]: I miss, and actually I'd have to say that even though I hated doing parties and stuff, that was probably the most fun job I've had was working at the arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: When Tekken 3 just came out, and we had just been purchased by Namco as well, so we had shirts with Pac-Man on it, it was really cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: And went over to the cyber station that was all Pac-Man branded themed and everything, and that was really cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: But working at the Aladdin's Castle was just a touch like working in an old 80s style arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I had a good time there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I would come home with a migraine every night, but other than that, I had a great time working there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, good memories about arcades.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_08]: And also that was figuring out the right place to knee the Street Fighter Alpha 2 where I could play for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, was that like your first minimum wage job type of thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: My first minimum wage job was working for a grocery store, which I probably quit a week later because they scheduled me during my classes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dope.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't actually count that as a for reals job because it was hell.
[SPEAKER_04]: My first minimum wage job was not that bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: My second one was working in the game room at school and then after that it was working at a cookie store where I lived on cookies for a year and then it was the arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: I worked at a place called... They don't exist anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was Placer TV Video, which was a video rental store they used to rent.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, well, they were still around in the mid-90s when everything was starting to shift to DVD.
[SPEAKER_04]: And at that time, they were still renting NES games and videotapes, but they didn't really get on the DVD bandwagon fast enough, and that's kind of what killed them.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we rented porn.
Like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you have the red door?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was just on the top shelf.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was no laws prohibiting that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: People weren't so freaking... I remember... Like, trying to be politically correct and protect everybody back then.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just remember... Kids can't reach that high.
[SPEAKER_08]: My granny taking me to rent videos when I was in Dothan for a summer.
[SPEAKER_08]: And by the way, the arcade we had in Dothan was Tilt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I remember Tilt.
[SPEAKER_08]: But...
[SPEAKER_08]: She just said, okay, pick whatever movie, make sure it's a good movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd rent Star Wars like 57,000 times and just actually return to the Jedi because that was my favorite movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I once rented this movie that I think the name was in another language, but it was pretty much Tiger Shark.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it was one of those Jaws-like movies except with naked people.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I watched it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I watched the whole movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm like, my sister's with me and she's like, this movie's dirty.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm like...
[SPEAKER_08]: There's so much blood.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blood RG, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I loved being taken to go rent movies with people who wouldn't read labels.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Memory lane, memory lane, and we're not even back into gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get back into some gaming news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, so there was a little bit of a controversy with the new DSX game, The Fall, that came out on iOS platforms.
[SPEAKER_12]: Apparently, the game had a lockout for jailbroken devices.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, I guess the general thought is, well, your device is jailbroken, you're probably stealing the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's not always true.
[SPEAKER_12]: People jailbreak devices to put their phone on a different carrier or something like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: So there's that.
[SPEAKER_12]: So people that were legitimately buying the game, allegedly, were unable to fire the gun in the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Couldn't fire it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of a... I mean, it's like one of the... You hear about the clever anti-piracy things like, you know, in what, Batman Arkham Asylum, like you couldn't jump far enough to get past certain parts of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, and I can applaud for a clever anti-piracy thing, but jailbreaking your device isn't piracy.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's legal, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought didn't they come down and say that was illegal?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's gone back and forth a few times.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a mess.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, I mean, people, exactly like you said, just because you jailbreak your device doesn't make you a pirate.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: And on top of that, though, there is an app that you can get from the homebrew store or whatever that basically you can patch it so that you can play the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: It basically makes your device look like it's not jailbroken, even though it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what they should have done is they should have put this out there on the piracy sites like the hours before they put it out on the official app store.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how you get the pirates is you got to put like the version of the game up on the piracy sites and then kind of like flood the market, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it'll get ratted out as a fake soon enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: But by that point, it's already kind of saturated.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, if you know, apparently, you know, people didn't like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was the case.
[SPEAKER_12]: So they're going to patch it out later on.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: We did not clearly state that the game would not support jailbroken devices, and we'll be switching this off via an update so that all support iOS devices will be able to play the game in the near future.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I think some people are watching it while they're listening to the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's finishing up right now, I believe.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, big controversy this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Melee was pulled from the live streaming schedule at one point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Melee was pulled from the weekend event.
[SPEAKER_04]: In an update on Shoryuken.com...
[SPEAKER_04]: EVO co-founder Inkblot said regrettably we've just been informed by Nintendo of America that we do not have permission to broadcast Super Smash Brothers Melee for EVO 2013 well now this whole thing was a bit of a mess because in order to get the game featured in EVO in the first place they had to do a charity fundraiser to raise the money not for the tournament but I think to get like like the whole thing was like which fan communities can raise the most money for a good cause will feature those games in EVO that's the sense I get from this whole thing
[SPEAKER_04]: and sure enough the fans of Smash Brothers Melee raised $90,000 well in comes Big Bad Nintendo to pull the plug on this you know to not have this happen but thanks to the immense vocalness of the internet and trending topics on Twitter, Reddit certainly a bit of a PR nightmare and within hours Melee returned to be broadcast over the EVO 2013 tournament
[SPEAKER_04]: What's interesting, though, is that it did came out after that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it got reinstated.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pulled.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was reinstated.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then it came out after that, that co-founder Joey Quellar, I'm sorry if I'm saying that wrong, said about the he's a co-founder of the EVO thing and an organizer.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said they were not only trying to shut down the stream, they were trying to shut down the event, the smash portion of the event.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's their IP.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can do what they want.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't present us with any options to keep it open.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, but of course that obviously didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: They ended up streaming it after all.
[SPEAKER_04]: This does seem like a real bad case of communication and kind of the PR department saying one thing and the legal department coming through and saying another.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo is incredibly protective of their IPs and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like it wasn't really understood what was going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: EVO Evolution
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, sorry, I thought I said, sorry, yeah, Evo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought, anyway, I thought of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was reminded of a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you remember when Weird Al did that parody of Lady Gaga's Born This Way that was performed this way?
[SPEAKER_04]: And he said that he couldn't put it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was going to do it as like a single or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: He couldn't put it out because Lady Gaga said no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lady Gaga he always gets permission from the artist or at least always tries you know but if the artist says no he won't put it out and Lady Gaga said no and all these people started tweeting Lady Gaga like you know bitch it's weird out let him do the song well turns out Lady Gaga comes out and says I never heard the song one of my people to or like you know one of her legal people said no to it even though that legal person in the response said Lady Gaga said no but she had never heard it
[SPEAKER_04]: and it wasn't until the whole thing blew up on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I couldn't help but be reminded of that because unfortunately, yes, I'm comparing Nintendo to Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hear me out here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's this whole big mess of he said, she said, right hand isn't talking to left hand and this is the stuff that happens and it did make Nintendo look stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, this is all for... Well, it was done by charity for a good cause to bring...
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: Or you can say, fuck you, you're not going to get to watch this because we're just going to be dicks about it.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then, you know, now you just pissed off a community and you're like, we're not buying your system or your game, so forget it.
[SPEAKER_12]: But then they'll buy the game because, you know, they have to have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tiger Claw said that he heard that Super Smash Brothers Melee had over 130,000 people watching the live stream during the game's finals earlier today.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was the most watched fighting game in history, according to the co-founder of EVO.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting, because the whole thing did kind of work out in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I think more people watched it because of this controversy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think a lot of people wouldn't have had an idea this was happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to be honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, of course, we have our smarties in chat saying Actdeft says play this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ranma says stream this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, baby, there is no way.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will let you stream that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You cannot stream that game, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tried.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, glad they worked it out, but legal department and big companies need to figure, you know, realize that this is the world we live in.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's yet another example of Nintendo does not understand the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: This does not help their case.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is it, a series of tubes?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, right, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's these wires, and there's things on them, and they do stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about a new franchise coming from Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_08]: This was actually voiced by Miyamoto.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, he let it slip that there is going to be a new franchise, and he said this on the Japanese publication.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm glad that they're coming up with new IP.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like the new IP that they launched the Wii system with.
[SPEAKER_12]: Excite Truck needs a sequel.
[SPEAKER_12]: A good sequel.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm not talking about Excite Bots because that was crap.
[SPEAKER_12]: You don't put minigames in the middle of a fucking race.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: I shouldn't have to throw pie at a clown while I'm racing a car.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do that all the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's called going to Disneyland with Dan.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or make a sandwich.
[SPEAKER_12]: Literally, there was make a sandwich during Burger Time Racers.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't get me wrong, it's a funny idea.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, in playing the game, you're just like, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, this is silly, but it's just... We need Warriors Wacky Races.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wouldn't that be crazy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Instead of a Mario Kart, do like a Wario Kart and have it be like just completely fucked up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, this new Mario Kart 8, you're going upside down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario Kart 8 basically looks like F-Zero, which, like, it makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why can't we just have F-Zero?
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes me really happy and really fucking irritated at the same time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, Nintendo, you're fucking teasing me now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo, wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm all for new IPs, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, new IPs are fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: We built this wonderful engine for F-Zero, and then we're like, eh, no one wants F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nobody wants F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nobody wants that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, uh, Desura has actually been purchased up by, um... What was it?
[SPEAKER_12]: The Second Life company, Linden Labs.
[SPEAKER_12]: And so... What's that mean?
[SPEAKER_12]: I have no fucking clue.
[SPEAKER_12]: Other than, you know, it's changed ownership.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think it's really going to change anything as far as, you know, the distribution service goes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um...
[SPEAKER_12]: So yeah, it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe Second Life will become like PlayStation Home and you can launch games within Second Life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except with a lot more furry... No, actually it is exactly like PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly like PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be very meta because like PlayStation Home was kind of inspired by Second Life.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there are flying dicks in Second Life and not in PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there are dicks in PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not flying though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do they have rocket packs?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, you can file this in, you know, I don't know if this is rule 37 or what, but this is just the gaming community at work here.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a petition going around telling Microsoft, or I should say asking, demanding that Microsoft bring back the restrictive DRM policies that they had already rescinded due to outrage.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, there are fans petitioning Microsoft to bring it back.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually a petition posted on Change.org I hate that site Why do you hate Change.org?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you sign any petition on there and you get 50,000 spam emails from them And yeah, I'm all good for signing petitions, but not on that site I will not sign a single one on that site
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so here's the petition.
[SPEAKER_04]: to whoever, give us back the Xbox One we were promised at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sincerely, your name.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have hit 24,476 signatures.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, and a lot of those are just troll signatures too, by the way, because they're like, yeah, we want them to do this.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I'm sorry, once again, comparing the digital marketplace that Xbox One would have to Steam is just stupid.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's a perfect example of the difference right now with the Steam sale.
[SPEAKER_12]: First off, you see a lot of discounts on Steam.
[SPEAKER_12]: Steam is not the only place you can get Steam games.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can get Steam games or Steam DRM-enabled games on Amazon, Greenman Gaming...
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: and we still don't know what the fucking details were on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what pisses me off about this too.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't know what the fuck you're complaining about.
[SPEAKER_04]: All 24,000 of you, you literally do not know what the fuck you're complaining about.
[SPEAKER_04]: They never said what the rules were.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because if it was that one hour demo thing... I know this is a show where every gamer has a voice and I welcome every opinion but I can literally say this petition is ignorant.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of ignorant and change.org, I have been informed that they no longer send out the emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just fessed up to your own ignorance here on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It happens.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's because I ignored them for a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ignore ignorant.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, same word.
[SPEAKER_12]: Same combination.
[SPEAKER_12]: Humblebundle.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's another perfect example of places you can get Steam games for dirt cheap.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm just saying that's the problem.
[SPEAKER_12]: Even comparing the PlayStation Network store or Xbox Live Marketplace to Steam is just ridiculous because it's not an open platform as far as you're not going to have competing marketplaces out there.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not like the retail marketplace where everyone's competing with each other.
[SPEAKER_12]: You have one central marketplace.
[SPEAKER_12]: You buy it their way or you don't buy it at all.
[SPEAKER_12]: Origin.
[SPEAKER_04]: ShadowNextGen in our chat says, Sky, couldn't it be said that people originally didn't really know what they were complaining about?
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, no, I haven't signed the petition, nor do I plan to.
[SPEAKER_04]: I appreciate the devil's advocate perspective.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you're an Xbox fan.
[SPEAKER_04]: And unlike some of these people, I do think you do know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let me humor this opinion here.
[SPEAKER_04]: about didn't we not originally know what we were complaining about.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox made it very clear about the restrictions that they were putting into place.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had three pages of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it was that whole official letter they put out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was very clear.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was no misinterpreting that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You will have to check in once every 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: You will only be able to trade and use games through authorized vendors and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that was in writing.
[SPEAKER_04]: and you can read between the lines and see that that meant that you would not be able to sell games yourself on eBay and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem is what they didn't communicate was the positive to offset that negative.
[SPEAKER_04]: Family sharing was this big cloud out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ten people in your house can play the games but how?
[SPEAKER_04]: What are the terms?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because there's literally people out there and I bet you the people signing this petition think
[SPEAKER_04]: that it was share with people across the internet the full unhinged complete game 10 people playing it all at once now we can all pool in on our game sales I don't think any of you think that listening to this but I think there were people out there that really think that
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, they thought that they could share games.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, hey, I'm only going to have to pay $6 for this Xbox One game, and all my nine other friends are going to chip in as well, and we can all play this game.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I'm sorry, that's not the way it works.
[SPEAKER_04]: When in reality, it was probably like the GIMP to Drive Club thing, honestly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously, people, do you really think that Microsoft would legitimately put out a service like that, that they would stand to lose money on?
[SPEAKER_04]: and they got beat by Sony Sony took advantage of this yes they did take advantage of this situation that is business and it's the it's to be fair it's the exact flip of seven years ago when PlayStation embarrassed themselves at E3
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, I wanted to read this comment to... Where was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is very important from Bobby Blackwolf in our chatroom, live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Official quote from anti-consumer Blackwolf with his quotey fingers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck those fans.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll end on that note.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, moving on to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you are one of those people that signed that petition, I invite you to come at me, bro.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com In all seriousness, I can be respectful if you want to have a respectful discussion.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you have to admit that the petition is a little silly at this point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just let it be.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an online petition.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is important.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would fully support, fully support
[SPEAKER_04]: and I think this is what those people would want so before you write your angry email I'm going to meet you halfway here I would be totally okay with this
[SPEAKER_04]: with a physical disc license and a digital download license.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you want to buy your game on physical disc, then game sharing and all that stuff works the way you know it today, and everything is just like that shady PlayStation video and all that, everything you know and love about games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a digital download license would give you something different.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's kind of the place gaming ought to go, is that if you download a game... But you have the freedom to choose.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get these perks.
[SPEAKER_04]: your perk for buying the game digitally is you get it day one you can buy the game without pants you won't have to leave your house and you can give that game to a friend in New York or something cross country it would have these different licenses I am totally okay with that and I would be behind Xbox One 100% with that I just don't think it's going to happen
[SPEAKER_12]: And they can always come back.
[SPEAKER_12]: They said that later on they may implement some of the stuff that they got rid of.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hopefully none of the bad things, but you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: They could just be there trying to find a way to integrate something that won't scare people off.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I can't support a petition that is like, switch it back to the way it was because everyone's stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We want it this way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Daddy, I want the goose that lays the golden eggs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want the world I want the whole world
[SPEAKER_08]: Dear OLR, I just wanted to say, as always, that you have an awesome show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wanted to share with you a game I recently acquired on Steam.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's called Akaniero Demon Hunters.
[SPEAKER_08]: It plays a lot like Okami in the sense that you get shards for each demon you kill.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is the storyline... Learn to spell.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Straight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not with an E, with an A. From Steam.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not very good at descriptions, so I took this one from the official game site.
[SPEAKER_08]: Akaneiro Demon Hunters transports you to a world realized in a striking visual style inspired by Japanese ink, water, and woodblock illustration.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've dug deep into the history and folklore of Japan when designing our scenarios and characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mixing this foundation with an original mythology inspired by Red Riding Hood has yielded a fantastic and inspiring setting for players to explore.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was produced, I think, by Spicy Horse, who was in charge of American McGee's Alice Madness Returns, which is another awesome game, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe you guys can check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's on Steam for $10 now.
[SPEAKER_08]: The graphics are stunning.
[SPEAKER_08]: It reminded me a lot of Okami, as it looks like drawings on the screen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope you guys get to check it out sometime.
[SPEAKER_08]: And as always, happy gaming and thanks for letting every gamer have a voice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sincerely, Gigi.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I might have to give it a try if I have money.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like hearing about game reviews about games I haven't really heard a lot of.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: This comes from...
[SPEAKER_08]: Like Rob, I got caught up in the same trading cards thingy.
[SPEAKER_08]: It seems to be never-ending.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just for fun, I bought my missing binding of Isaac's cards.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then I converted them to a badge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not only did that eat all the cards, I got a booster pack soon with more binding of Isaac cards.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of the cards was a foil, and so now I have a foil badge to collect.
[SPEAKER_08]: The regular trading cards can power up my existing badge, so there's no reason for selling or trading cards unless they're duplicates.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was using $5 of my own money plus selling my duplicates to obtain a full set.
[SPEAKER_08]: I still have almost $3 left over.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pro tip, don't try buying the cards at the top of the queue on the marketplace.
[SPEAKER_08]: It will most likely be gone before you can complete your transaction.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think the trading card system was running...
[SPEAKER_08]: 2 to 5 July, and maybe the 2nd through the 5th July because I paid for hours and got no drops.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played for hours and got no drops.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lastly, the cards are worth zooming in on.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Fairy Solitaire cards are actually panoramas from the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: The artwork will probably look way better zoomed in, and that's from Addictra-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyhow, yeah, the trading card thing is fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And thank you, Ranma, for doing trading cards with me last week or this last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ranma sent an email that just said 573.
[SPEAKER_08]: So maybe we hit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did we hit it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, maybe we did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking now.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have another email that I'm just going to go ahead and read it but I'm not going to say the guy's full name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: So my name is Jeff G and I've worked at an ESPN affiliate radio station for three years.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've played video games since I can remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am interested in video games radio and would love to send in my resume and some clips of me on air.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, we're not hiring because we don't pay anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't see this email, really.
[SPEAKER_08]: If nothing comes of this email, I would still like to commend you for living the dream of talking about video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for your time, and I look forward to hearing back from you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, bless your heart, sir.
[SPEAKER_08]: If we could afford to pay, we would be paid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, unfortunately, this is an all-volunteer organization, but I will throw this out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: VOG is looking for more shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now we're looking for established shows because we want to make sure that the people we recruit aren't going to throw in the towel after you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, look to the site's credit at Voice of Geeks Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've had the same lineup for like a year.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: If you do have a show that's interested in being on the network, get in touch with me directly, rob at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would love a board game, card game, like non-video game type show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you think about, I would love, love, love a show that is like LARPing live or like playing a game live, one of those types of shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would make a great serial.
[SPEAKER_04]: So just throwing that out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have an established show along those lines, get in touch with me, rob at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, I invite this guy to just call our show some night.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're around on a Sunday night, give our show a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be happy to talk video games with you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: For free.
[SPEAKER_08]: And who knows, you know, you might find your niche in the geekdom market, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, we might...
[SPEAKER_08]: There's sports geeks out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: You said you worked for ESPN affiliates, so who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: We got sports geek talk, as long as there's no wrestling, because that would drive Bobby crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless it's like 80s wrestling.
[SPEAKER_04]: How could that drive anybody crazy?
[SPEAKER_04]: 80s wrestling was the best.
[SPEAKER_08]: And your theme song has to be Hulk Hogan's I am a real American.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, you know, anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's get to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week here on the show we... Oh, by the way, Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com If you would like to send in your mail, please, no resumes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com Here's the FUs of the week time.
[SPEAKER_08]: FU to Bitchface.
[SPEAKER_08]: She doesn't listen to the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some people know who Bitchface is.
[SPEAKER_08]: FU.
[SPEAKER_08]: And also my hip.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the stupid cough that I am now going on to week five.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_08]: Done.
[SPEAKER_12]: Uh, Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: FU to Tension and Headaches.
[SPEAKER_12]: I always get them.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I have one now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm gonna follow that up with my own F.U.
[SPEAKER_04]: to headaches, because I had a really bad one yesterday that pretty much ruined my day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will say that, but I guess shit happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bradley, do you have any F.U.s you want to get off your chest?
[SPEAKER_10]: F.U.
[SPEAKER_10]: to my back for hurting after a California stream yesterday.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then seriously, fuck you to this douchebag Wingstopper's boy.
[SPEAKER_10]: He said they wouldn't take my order because it's getting late at 10.30 when I ordered after 11, like, several times.
[SPEAKER_10]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on with a couple more news stories and then you guys can give us a call in a moment here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: You remember a time when Sony's online network was hacked?
[SPEAKER_12]: Pepperidge Farm remembers.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Sony, they...
[SPEAKER_12]: They basically got fined in the UK.
[SPEAKER_12]: They had to pay a 250,000 fine and they were originally appealing it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now they decided they're going to withdraw that.
[SPEAKER_12]: So after careful consideration, we are withdrawing our appeal.
[SPEAKER_12]: This decision reflects our commitment to protecting the confidentiality of our network security from disclosures.
[SPEAKER_12]: We continue to disagree with the decision on the merits.
[SPEAKER_12]: They disagree, but they're going to pay for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't like this, but we'll do it anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm wondering if they did appeal it that they would go, maybe there would be some sort of trial where information would come out about how shoddy their protection was and they didn't want that, so they decided to go ahead and pay the original settlement or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Water in the bridge.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although the entire gaming community had probably already forgotten about the hack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never forget.
[SPEAKER_04]: I shouldn't say the entire community, but a big chunk of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ragenator said, how about a show that combines wrestling, bronies, and furries?
[SPEAKER_08]: And I said that sounds like really bad porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Would that be Dogpile?
[SPEAKER_04]: It will air at 3 a.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: on Tuesday morning.
[SPEAKER_08]: All joking aside, as much as I say we're kind of full up on video game shows right now, I would love to see a Mega Man show.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know, but anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: Mega Man is a diehard community, and the community makes a lot of great fan projects, and one of them is on its way out, Mega Man Revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been in development since 2002.
[SPEAKER_04]: It tries to recreate the magic of the NES games.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can also, I guess, enable slowdown and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of early reaction.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game is too hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That doesn't mean to stop liking us on Facebook because the next goal would be, what would it be?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably like 5,730?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it would be 1,337.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's an admirable goal.
[SPEAKER_12]: And of course, Mega Man Revolution, I would mention that there is also Mega Man Unlimited, which was released today.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you can download that at megafillx.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that Phil like a dude named Phil or Phil like F-I-L-L?
[SPEAKER_12]: Phil like a dude named Phil.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alrighty, I guess that is about it for the show, but we do want to take an opportunity to open up our Skype line for you guys to have your say on anything we've talked about tonight or maybe something we missed.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or a username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio, all one word if you'd like to give us a call and we'll talk about whatever you'd like, within reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get to some Twitter topics and last minute stories while we wait for those to come in.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_12]: For example, there's one character that's a fish, a fish man, and all he can do is flop around.
[SPEAKER_12]: Zombie Bride, Giant Preen Mantis, Average Run-of-the-Mill Old Man.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, he's an old man who can't fight.
[SPEAKER_12]: What about Middle-Aged Man?
[SPEAKER_04]: And Female Paul.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me get to the phones, because the phones are ringing here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Jason.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Jason.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Jason.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can we go back to Nostalgia Land?
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course we can.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Nostalgia Land.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was driving back from a friend's concert and you guys were talking and we're going to the mailbag and I was just driving along the highway just going, ah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to build a house out of pixels in Nostalgia Land and live there.
[SPEAKER_04]: A fort.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will have my pixel fort in Nostalgia Land.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you want to talk about in Nostalgia Land?
[SPEAKER_04]: What makes you nostalgic?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Prop Cycle.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had one!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Prop Cycle's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not in the Prop Cycle Addams Family, but they had a Prop Cycle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Believe it or not, some of our listeners don't know what Prop Cycle is, so please explain it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Prop Cycle was an exercise game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Essentially, you sat on an exercise bike that had a two-handed flight stick, and you could tilt it forward, pull it back, obviously turn right and left.
[SPEAKER_11]: You couldn't just crank the pedals continuously because the game... I think it was basically like exertion prevention built into the game, but you just pedaled persistently and flew around popping balloons and not crashing into things.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was just a lot of fun to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was so silly looking too.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was so fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rio Rancho, my hometown, doesn't actually have a mall still to this day.
[SPEAKER_11]: The mall that got closest to us, Cottonwood Mall, is just on the other side of the city limit border.
[SPEAKER_11]: But when that was first built up, the movie theater downstairs had a very tiny little arcade.
[SPEAKER_11]: It had a...
[SPEAKER_11]: Metal Slug, I want to say a Neo Geo Multicab, and a couple of other typical things.
[SPEAKER_11]: But upstairs, for the first couple of years of that mall's existence, there was a divided laser tag?
[SPEAKER_11]: a divided laser tag meaning that you can't cross into the other person's territory and it had Sega City and that was like with the exception of the roller rink that we used to go to when I was younger way the hell out in Albuquerque Sega City was like my personal arcade back in the day and that's where I played Prop Cycle and it was one of those things where whenever we would go I would play that and it
[SPEAKER_11]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it was a great game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've literally never seen that in any other arcade to my mind, to my memory.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't they have, like, these weird hacks for Prop Cycle where they hook up Prop Cycle to other games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, wouldn't there, like, even, like, a pinball game that ran off Prop Cycle?
[SPEAKER_11]: As a matter of fact, my friends out here in Colorado, before I moved out here, hooked up a poppin' music of some sort to the proppin', uh, proppin', the Prop Cycle TV.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it was called, they called, they dubbed it proppin' music.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: I never, I unfortunately wasn't up here for the occasion but I saw pictures and it was definitely amazing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's one game, so I've never known the name of this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: My...
[SPEAKER_11]: My brain does really weird things when specific details of things go away.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I wonder if you guys know this arcade game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I seem to remember it in the roller skating rink that I used to go to as a kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Basically, what it boils down to is you play on... You're a character that runs around a...
[SPEAKER_11]: Rollercoaster collecting cherries and you have to dodge the rollercoaster.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've never been able to find the actual cars on the rollercoaster.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've never been able to find this game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that Mr. Dew's Wild Ride?
[SPEAKER_11]: Mr. Dew's Wild Ride.
[SPEAKER_12]: It sounds like it.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you're collecting cherries, it's Mr. Dew.
[SPEAKER_11]: Come on, Wikipedia, give me a screenshot and not just the box art.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, the box art doesn't.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, yeah, this is the thing that I kind of run into is that the image is ridiculously small.
[SPEAKER_11]: I seem to remember it being very, very circular with ladders that connect you to the different portions where this looks like.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm almost positive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go to Google.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check it out on Google.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do a Google search.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's so weird because my brain... Filling in the gaps now that I actually have game screenshots, this kind of seems to make sense.
[SPEAKER_11]: But my brain remembers this game looking...
[SPEAKER_11]: A little bit better, I guess?
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit newer than this actually is?
[SPEAKER_04]: The resolution on old games is going to be itty-bitty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so I think that's part of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all about the raster.
[SPEAKER_11]: The detail of this thing just seems... What I remember and what this looks like is entirely different.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking at Rob's image search.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like all these screen captures and then there's a really badly drawn cock.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says you mad on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What does that have to do with Mr. Dew's wild ride?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you, Google Images.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Google Images.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I get for turning safe search off.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one wants to search safe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can't have your search for cock interfered.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: I really want to play that again.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was like a choose-your-game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it was a choose-your-game, and you could play either Pac-Man or Dig Dug, and I want to say... I want to say they have one at the Roseville Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know I've seen one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to know where I can get the name wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's be real.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anywhere, probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I want to know what it's called, so I can get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it is like one of the anniversary editions.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember the name, but I know I've seen one, and I know I've played one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I'll have to do some Google Foo on that, because I was thinking of that game earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, it was a nice trip down nostalgia lane, Jason.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was a great 20 minutes.
[SPEAKER_11]: A good way to kill my drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I appreciate about this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a great way to kill a long commuter drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to get to see you in a couple weeks, yes?
[SPEAKER_11]: Perhaps not in Sacramento, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm surprisingly busy considering how long I'm going to be out in the Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_11]: But yes, I am definitely there for the upcoming con at the start of next month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I know you'll be, even if you're not going to GamerX, you'll be in the area, and I'll be able to meet up with you there, which gives me another opportunity to promote the little panel deal-y going on Saturday at GamerX in San Francisco, August 3rd, I think it is the date.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's that Saturday.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I am doing a panel with my buddies from Koopa Club and Game Bar and Game Buoy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know I'm leaving somebody else out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I apologize in advance.
[SPEAKER_04]: But all us guys are getting together doing a podcast cross zone panel.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're just going to be talking about podcasting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our show is kind of how we got into it and trying to enable more people to get their voices heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll have a gay old time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be a good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gay meaning happy.
[SPEAKER_11]: You need to take me to that place in Castro you were talking about earlier too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which place?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hot Cookie?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, the bar.
[SPEAKER_11]: The pinball bar.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's literally going to become that song that's you, I'm going to take you to a gay bar.
[SPEAKER_11]: and I'm choking so have a good night guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, bye Jason.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for mentioning hot cookie because now I want to go there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to another call on the line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, this is Azurame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Azurame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just talking to one of my friends about the show and he actually came up and brought up the whole looking for a new show and we kind of do a show but it's kind of based off of like
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, pimp your show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm all about supporting indie shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell us where we can find it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well, the name of the actual show is like Learning Japanese Through Music.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we kind of, you can look on Facebook at facebook.com slash groups, Japanese Through Anime.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can probably see the page there you can actually add.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have like Thursday nights, we have like a three hour show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if anybody follows the new anime Shingeki no Kyojin or Attack on Titan.
[SPEAKER_08]: That show is crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, well, we broke down the show and, like, not the show, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: We broke down the song into, like, different parts and translated it, and then at the end of the show, we kind of, like, all sing, like, on Adobe Connect.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, we also have a meet-up that we also, some of the local people kind of speak, you know, we meet up in person and kind of sing at, like, karaoke bars, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why, but I love the idea that your show ends with karaoke.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know a lot of shows that do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we need to do that here at OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: We end every night with a rousing rendition of So long, farewell, Auf Wiedersehen, good night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Second the no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm branching out and doing my own show.
[SPEAKER_05]: The lag kind of throws people off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does give you a chance to learn a little bit more about the anime or the Japanese pop band that you're probably interested in.
[SPEAKER_05]: And maybe a little few words of Japanese too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we do have a show about anime on the network called Anime Jam Session, which is a good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it sounds like you have a different approach to the way you do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shoot me an email, rob at vognetwork.com and we'll chat a little more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and then I'm sitting there and I'm leveling I think I got to level 25 and I was doing the Totema dungeon this morning which is like I mean there's only one other dungeon in the beta after that and I just I I'm not gonna be able to have enough time to get to that but I yeah I've been playing the shit out of that beta it's a lot of fun
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was wondering if you guys had a little group on here that might be doing some sort of free company LOR.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't have a link shell yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually made one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Link shells are really just chat channels.
[SPEAKER_04]: The free companies are really the guilds a la WoW or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: There will absolutely be something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least Horde House is going to lead one somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will have more information on that when we know the full server list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right now we're on Behemoth, but that could change for Phase 4, but we're going to commit to something soonish here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just want to figure out where our frenzies are going to be and try to pick the best server.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool, cool, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, so I'll just continue to just chime in on the network and find out more.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will whore the shit out of it here on OLR once the game's out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good luck with your show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Adobe Connect.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have not heard... You know, Adobe Connect, I know because during my day job, I'm a corporate trainer, so I've used Adobe Connect in meetings of that sort, but I've never heard of doing...
[SPEAKER_05]: a podcast through Adobe Connect but I'm thinking about it going well it makes sense it would work why not right it's kind of it's very similar to Google Hangout in many ways so yeah besides the payments I mean unfortunately it's kind of expensive like $80 a month and you get a chance to utilize like some of the tools like talking through a chat menu controlling the desktop and even like passing the microphone or the camera to someone else in the chat you know it's just it's a little bit more interactive I think that maybe uh
[SPEAKER_05]: If we moved to something like this, we'd probably be dying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good luck with your show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll talk to you again here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, later.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just got a tweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the interactiveness of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just got a tweet from...
[SPEAKER_04]: Gaming Nerd who goes by GNVersion2 on Twitter that says Namco Classic Collection Volume 2 is a collection featuring Pac-Man, Dig Dug, and Rally-X.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that was, yes, the other game.
[SPEAKER_04]: In both original and arrangement versions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, I'm Googling this right now to see if it's what I remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody help me fill time while I ask for more calls.
[SPEAKER_08]: I probably have that at home, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: That Namco Collection.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I mean the ones that they released at home, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I think I do remember that one because that was it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, this is it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is totally what I was thinking of.
[SPEAKER_04]: You win a cookie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how to... I'm going to shove a cookie through Twitter and I hope it made it in one piece.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is exactly the game I was thinking of.
[SPEAKER_08]: That person probably already has lots of cookies on their computer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, that is exactly the game I was thinking of.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking at these screenshots.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember this whole little one with Pac-Man in the temple and with the little jumps.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: You, sir, are a win.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: And next, hook me up with a link for a ROM.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Love the interactiveness here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the tweets.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was on my personal Twitter, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes I'm going to bring up personal stuff on the show because I had to know what game that was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to tweets that went to the OLR account and then Loki, I'll go over to you for some more last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype, Orange Launch Radio if you want to get in on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100Matt sent us a tweet that says there's a Kickstarter to help open the largest pinball museum in Southern California too.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know I got a text message on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Melody sent me a text on this and I think...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: in fact I've been to the one in Las Vegas before they moved to their newer location and the one in Las Vegas has a pinball circus and all kinds of machines you just don't see anywhere
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma sent us a link about Xbox One gets booed out of Evo while demoing Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_04]: This doesn't sound good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to bring up the story right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if the booing is just sensationalism or what.
[SPEAKER_04]: But let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently...
[SPEAKER_04]: Fucking ads.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm having a hard time bringing this up on my phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Double Helix and Mad Catz guys were at Evo to pimp fight stick accessories and Killer Instinct, which of course was originally shown at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of hostility, I guess, shown at the event, even though the gameplay for Killer Instinct looked pretty good, and there's a video on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then it says the crowd was moderately accepting of Killer Instinct, but the fact that they were booing the Xbox One at such a core event like Evo 2013 speaks volumes about what gamers actually feel about the console.
[SPEAKER_04]: These weren't casuals.
[SPEAKER_04]: These weren't grandpas and grandmas buying consoles for little Timmy.
[SPEAKER_04]: These are the big Timmy's.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: This story from cinemablend.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it just sounds like a few angry mobsters.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how much... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like there were just a few angry gaming nerds there and they unfortunately got picked up by the media.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, I heard about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: SJ100Matt is also sending us this tweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even I'm excited about this, and this says a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: NHL 14, you know, hockey, is going to have an NHL 94 mode, which is like one of the best games ever, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Complete with original sound effects, controls, and visuals.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's sad?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's totally going to sell tons of copies in that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because NHL 94 is one of the best sports games ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, before I give you all those concessions, I'm going to say this.
[SPEAKER_04]: NHL 94 is no Blades of Steel.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's still pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know a lot of people disagree with me there.
[SPEAKER_04]: AJ Twist wanted to alert us to the Ultra Street Fighter 4 game as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft is tweeting us about Main6 who created Fighting is Magic is posting progress on their new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't they have to do something where they took the license out of it and now it's like a different type of game?
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm trying to scan through the update here real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: What, did they just change the horses basically?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Magical Horse Fighting Game
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure if Actdeft had something else he wants me to mention on that, he'll yell it in chat real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: But while I'm waiting for that, I will mention Tigerclaw's tweet here that says, Valve introduces Pipeline, a program for teens seeking careers in the game industry.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to read more about this here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Valve, Pipeline.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pipeline is an experiment to see if we can take a group of high school students with minimal work experience and train them in the skills and methods necessary to be successful at a company like Valve.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's nothing there yet besides a video and an FAQ, but hopefully that's going to change in the near future, especially as we get into the new school year, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here we will teach them to make two highly critical games and then delay the third one forever, thus building infinite anticipation for said sequel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, these high schoolers will be working on Half-Life 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: The next Half-Life 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ranma in chat helping to clear up some about the Fighting is Magic new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lauren Faust is creating new characters for the game on the Skullgirls engine that they got for free after the Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I remember that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though they couldn't use those characters, the creator was going to make new characters, and then the folks behind Skullgirls were really into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're apparently bronies over there at Skullgirls, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congrats to all you fans who are going to be in that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure you guys will be excited about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: One last call for calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll check in with Loki one more time and see if there's any other last minute stories or what have you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's it for tweets too.
[SPEAKER_04]: We running out of show?
[SPEAKER_04]: Must be time to stick a nail in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I guess we're done.
[SPEAKER_04]: The skyline's not ringing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's over!
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to those that didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, well, I guess maybe I missed you when I was on another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you can always email us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or Skype could just be working.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at Orangelongerator.com Jason in our chatroom is piping up saying, Pipeline isn't going to teach them to make games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to teach them to make hats, cards, and other trinkets.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, this is becoming a more and more popular thing in high schools to take a more trade school approach.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I honestly, you know, from somebody who just, I've been open about this on the show before.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't finish college.
[SPEAKER_04]: The reason why is because the industry I was studying at the time was radio and television.
[SPEAKER_04]: After interning at a TV station and doing all this stuff in the past, I just felt like I wasn't really going to be happy doing that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: This show is kind of a byproduct of what I did get out of college, which I'm very thankful for.
[SPEAKER_04]: But otherwise, I went into the working world and just worked my way up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think being able to expose high schoolers to those really entry-level job skills, I think is a great thing for some people.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm not knocking college.
[SPEAKER_04]: College is a great thing for some people.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just wasn't for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I honestly wish that for a lot of fields, especially the one that I'm in, that it didn't go so much from paying the $50,000 for college
[SPEAKER_08]: and went more into, you know, an apprenticeship type environment.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, not an unpaid internship because to me that just seems like some form of required slavery.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, I think that it should work on, I mean, yeah, you need to go to college.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like for me, yeah, going to take art history, going to take anatomy, going to take things are all helpful.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think when it comes to actually the industry type of job, it should be one-on-one working with somebody.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, some type of, you know, you work as an apprentice, you become a journeyman, you know, like back in the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, so I don't want people to misunderstand what we're trying to like say here.
[SPEAKER_04]: OLR is anti-college.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's not it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm having fun at college.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm not going to a four-year yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's many different ways to learn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, that about does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really want to thank you guys for tuning in tonight and supporting the show and supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you like what you hear here at Orange Lounge Radio, please tell a friend or five about the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Help spread the word about Orange Lounge Radio and help grow our family.
[SPEAKER_04]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bradley, thank you very much for being here tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We didn't get to hear a whole lot from you tonight, but I hope you had fun here on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, it was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: And feel free to pop back in any time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's always a pleasure to have you on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next time we'll play a game or something you can actually have a little bit more of a say in or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: But see you hopefully in less than six months.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't be a stranger.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any final thoughts you want to get out for the listeners?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, after this show I'm going to probably go see Pacific Rim because that looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it is a goddamn travesty that that fucking Adam Sandler movie outpaced Pacific Rim.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so angry.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's so much wrong with America.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_12]: Unfortunately, they did not cancel the apocalypse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Horrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because there are a lot of dumb people.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, more people need to go see Pacific Rim.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have anything you want to... You don't really have, like, a Twitter or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have any websites you want to pimp or promote while you're here?
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't really have any of that stuff, do you?
[SPEAKER_10]: The only thing I really have that's game-related is, like, I have a backloggery thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't really have loads of people on that other than someplace, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a pretty cool place if you want to list your games, but it takes forever to put them in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because if they don't have any drop-down, you have to put it in yourself.
[SPEAKER_10]: It tells me to keep up with the million things I'm playing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have like 400 plus, let me wear it.
[SPEAKER_10]: 400 plus?
[SPEAKER_10]: 483 unfinished games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I bought more already.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can really see how far behind you and how much crap you have on Steam and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it make a competition out of who can catch up on their backlog more?
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it give you trading cards?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: They do have little icons that show up depending on what you've finished.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm confused because I have played 10 plus games at once.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds like me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well thanks again for being here and we'll see you soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess we'll go to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought is I wish I had ice cream.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought tonight is, well, maybe we can give you a Greek yogurt bar.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's not ice cream.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thought we'd offer.
[SPEAKER_04]: My other final thought is, Shane is trying to course me into doing a Let's Play tonight on one of the streaming sites, so be looking for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: He wants me to play a game called Slender Man, which is a scary game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to play that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you laughing over there?
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: So apparently that's going to happen later on, but I do have to work tomorrow, so we can't go too late.
[SPEAKER_04]: But stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once I get the show up, if I have some time, I'll maybe go to that.
[SPEAKER_12]: You should just play Surgeon Simulator.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it's just as funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_12]: And everybody should buy Surgeon Simulator if you haven't yet, 2013, because it's just...
[SPEAKER_12]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura has her own channel and I want to be able to do things that don't necessarily have the OLR name attached to it just because you know I don't want to be OLRs for all of us so we'll have like maybe hopefully I'm hoping we can bring the webcam back streaming the shows in the future and so forth but there you go
[SPEAKER_04]: uh Codeman says can you record it please uh I I'm gonna try I don't want to promise tonight I feel like I should do a test run of something else tonight and then do Slender Man but I am I am very interested in getting into the YouTube scene of Let's Play I'll leave it at that
[SPEAKER_08]: I know that the program that you were using before and the one that I'm using still automatically records.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just have to make sure I don't have performance suffering because of it, but I should.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Loki, your last, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish I had no headache.
[SPEAKER_12]: Aw, you want some Ibuprofen?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I'm gonna go home and take some.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, feel better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that does it for another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys for tuning in and supporting the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a great week, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back in seven days to do it all again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_00]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6 p.m.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pacific, 9 p.m.
[SPEAKER_00]: Eastern.
[SPEAKER_00]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next week!