My favorite headline this week involves the current arcade machine renaissance. Those
that want an actual cabinet can get them, those that want a fractional scale model but
visually identical version can, and innovators can do fun, unique things too. Like NBA Jam
Shack Edition. Despite only ever playing as the Chicago Bulls and NBA Jam, reading about
this still put a smile on my face. This is just one larger than life story. Now it's
time for your hosts Rob Roberts, Jamie Summers and Loki to tell you more about this and the
rest of the week's gaming news. Starting right now on the show where every gamer has a voice.
Hello my friends out there on the internet. Welcome back. Another week of the show where
every gamer has a voice. It is Orange Lounge Radio and we are live once again with episode number
903 of our show for tonight, February the 13th of 2022. My name is Rob Roberts and I am joined by
my co-hosts at the keyboard at the moment. Say hello to Techmaster Loki. Hello. Hi Loki,
how are you doing? It's somewhat pain but I'm okay. Oh no, all right I want to ask about that
but quickly I just want to say DarkSakura is here. She had a cooking mama emergency in the other
room. So don't worry, Sakura is fixing it right now with the cooking. She'll be right back. So
but the pre-show video thing ended. I was gonna let it go like another minute and I was like well
this is awkward. I guess I'll just start the show. The joys of being here live because of course we
do tape live every Sunday night at six o'clock Pacific, nine o'clock Eastern, right after the
Bobby Black Wolf show. Not tonight though. Bobby Black Wolf is enjoying seven layer bean dip with
friends tonight. Oh hello there's DarkSakura back from cooking mama emergency. Hey DarkSakura.
Hey. Hey did mama fix it? My couscous actually burned a little bit on my pot so since it was
a very expensive enamel dutch oven. I had to get that scrubbed real quick before I put it in the
in the dishwasher. Thankfully I can dish wash it. It's fine but I had to get the burnt couscous.
But for people on camera I have chicken and carrot and black truffle and onion
and couscous with my homemade broth and I've added cheese because that's what you do.
Did you bring enough for everyone?
You should see how much I have. I have two containers of it in the fridge. I mean I used
all my couscous thinking oh this will make a little bit no no it made it made a lot.
I would say I'm coming over but things are a little busy with my move going on right now so
I've been talking about it for oh go ahead. Well if you want something to eat like on
Thursday I'm sure there'll be some left because Dan won't won't eat the couscous. I made it all
for me so I'll bring you some couscous. I've been talking about it for a few weeks on the show but
I am moving so Bobby it's interesting Bobby's not here tonight because of friends and chips
and traditions and things like that. The Owl show. Yeah the Owl show is on well actually I
hear there was a really decent halftime show I didn't I didn't catch it but I heard it was
pretty good so um so I guess there's that there's that that's usually the way it is there's a really
cool concert that happens once a year and then there's this little football game that they play
before and after it so apparently the concert kind of lived up to it this year so. Who cares
about sports ball? I know some people do whatever I find it's more traditions for a lot of people
but anyway uh so Bobby's not here tonight we won't be here next week because uh I'm moving
uh and I've been talking about this for a few weeks on the show so technically this is the
last night in studio N7. I haven't taken down any of the decorations yet um that'll probably be
tomorrow um but uh yeah uh this this studio we've been using this probably for the last seven years
I think is about as long as I've lived here and so it's interesting because the studio space saw
the end of our run on shoutcast which was audio only and um saw the beginning of twitch
uh for video which is funny because this space wasn't really set up for twitch but we made it
work and uh here we are now taping virtually which is what we're going to continue to do
uh in two weeks when we come back uh with our next episode uh where my my setup will change
drastically from what you see tonight I'm not exactly sure what it will look like yet but I
will say that Alan and I got to go to the house and actually see everything this week and it was
it was really cool I'm getting more and more excited so uh very very cool um I do want to
welcome those of you in our chat room and and big uh thank you as I see the hype train going on in
chat right now thank you so much to all of our live folks that are that are here despite the
concert and game on tv right now uh you all are here and super appreciate that but of course if
you listen on our podcast feed uh we appreciate that as well uh I want to go back to Loki real
quick before we get into the kickoff topic because I didn't I didn't catch what's playing behind you
tonight it looks like a Zelda game but like a DS thing what's what is what is that which which game
is it I can't tell from this far back is that is it Minish Cap no no which one it's Spirit Tracks
oh okay all right what made you say I did Dr Hatta well because the the DS Zelda games are
awesome and they really should bring them to the switch um like I mean when we're talking about
like how like oh yes it would be completely ruined if we brought like a game that Nintendo made to
mobile like Mario um whereas I think actually Zelda would work very well because it worked
well in the DS it was mainly using the stylus and so I that is a possibility I still wouldn't
want to see them come to mobile just put them on the switch but like you know it would still be
kind of cool yeah um going to our chat uh over twitch.tv slash vog network pod culture says uh
ah no more live shows ever never say never never say never ever uh on that note uh yeah Loki
brought up Nintendo uh and Zelda so I think we should probably talk about the big surprise
never say never to a new Nintendo Direct because once again we had no idea it was coming and then
you know in the middle of the week they said bam you're gonna get a new Nintendo Direct tomorrow
and uh it happened and I gotta say we'll recap everything they talked about but I've gotta say
um I couldn't watch it live which was a bummer um I just had work obligations which you know work is
more important um so I had to take care of that and then I was gonna watch it like on stream
delayed to get reactions but um I got twit or uh twitter notifications pushed to my phone that kind
of spoiled the big news uh so I was like all right I guess I'll just read up on it so I admittedly I
never watched the Nintendo Direct I just saw the bullet points but it still sounded like it was
a pretty action-packed good direct uh for all things considered it was I saw some folks online
that were very meh about it which kind of surprised me I thought there was a lot of good
stuff in it um but let's let's talk about some of the big headlines that were in the direct uh do
you have it up Loki you want me to talk about it yeah so it was it was all right I mean there was
some big announcements I guess there's a lot of games I just don't play the series of so it's not
like you know I was super hyped about things but you know overall they had some stuff I'm interested
in yeah there's lots of like interesting things on there like Chrono Cross yeah that's it's
interesting to see that and there's the Tel Aviv stuff that they have for that as well which is
kind of neat um you know that one was rumored you know for all the crap we get about reporting on
rumors sometimes that Chrono Cross I remember was a thing like four weeks ago because we were
wondering why are they doing Chrono Cross and they won't touch Chrono Trigger I remember that
discussion coming up a few weeks ago on the show um so uh it does seem like those Square Enix
remasters of like Secret of Mana you know and so forth are bringing fruit although I guess Chrono
Cross is not really a remaster it's just kind of repackaged for the Switch I suppose and I would
bet mobile I don't think they're gonna only have it on the Switch it's gotta be for mobile as well
because that's been Square's mo lately so yeah so they um showed off a Fire Emblem Three Houses
um Musou game so they've got Fire Emblem uh Warriors I guess or three yeah Fire Emblem
Warriors Three Hopes so I believe that's the sequel to the last game that they had come out
I feel like those Warriors games do pretty well on the Switch like you know obviously the um Hyrule
Warriors you know has done very well on the Switch there's the Persona one I'm just so sick
of Fire Emblem but you know some people like it so it's fine well I think what's it's gonna be
a completely different style for Fire Emblem too so you know I think I think it it works for the
Musou type of you know game so I think it'll be fun um what else so uh No Man's Sky is coming to
the Switch that's pretty interesting to see that actually happening I've been asked about my
thoughts on this one because I'm kind of the resident No Man's Sky fanboy a little bit um
and uh I mean it's I'm I'm all for more people getting exposed to the game and there are people
that will get to play it on Switch who haven't played it on other platforms yet um and I know
a lot of the concern is is it gonna run on the Switch it'll run on the Switch I mean it runs on
an OG Playstation 4 and an OG Xbox One it doesn't run very well um I would imagine they're gonna be
targeting a lower resolution especially when the game is handheld um so they'll probably be able
to do some things but I I I it's not gonna be ideal I don't think it's gonna be the ideal way
to play No Man's Sky unless your gaming is largely portable if you take transit a lot or you know you
just happen to play Switch in portable mode then hey having the No Man's Sky experience portable
will be kind of nice but I I don't think it'll be the optimal way to play it but I'm all for
more people um coming on board and I hope it retains the cross-play functionality
um because it'll be one of those few games uh that play across Sony, PC, Microsoft and Switch
so it'd be be pretty cool um we have a new Mario Strikers game so that's Mario Strikers
Battle League that's coming out in June 10th which looked kind of cool um those are that's
the series I don't really care about but cool yeah as we mentioned uh Chrome of Cross the
remasters coming to Switch on April 7th um there was the announcement of Mother and Earthbound
being added to Nintendo Switch online so for the NES and SNES finally I'm alive
makes me happy yeah Live Alive that's getting uh ported and remastered on the Switch uh which is
pretty awesome and I have like voice acting in there and stuff I'm just gonna say Live Alive
I think was the biggest and best news in the entire Direct. I'm gonna say why I think the
Live Alive was the biggest and best news it's because unlike the Chrono Cross one and some
of the other things we've seen Square Enix do and I'm gonna I'm gonna kind of toot on something
I said months ago on this show we're seeing Square leverage that um Octopath Traveler
slash Triangle Strategy Engine for something really different now and I remember I remember
when I brought this up it was when I was reviewing that game Dungeon Encounters remember when that
came out um a couple months it was by the uh minds behind Final Fantasy 12 kind of created
this very minimalistic RPG um and some people are super into it and I I just I liked it but
I didn't understand why it had to be minimalistic and I said they've got this engine why aren't they
using this engine to build more things and that kind of went into the talk about what if the
Final Fantasy remasters ended up in this engine or something like that you met right but well
it's not Final Fantasy remaster but I feel like it's something adjacent is now going into this
engine and I think that's really exciting um and I you know between that and the Chrono Cross news
I think we should all cross our fingers cross our toes hold our breath that that's why Chrono
Trigger is taking so long that Chrono Trigger is going to like maybe Live Alive is like a test
to kind of port these sorts of games over and maybe Chrono Trigger is going to get the Triangle
Strategy Octopath treatment um you know I know it's a it's a wild theory but I just think that
that was the most exciting news I think out of the whole direct I I it's interesting I know people
that really love that game um I I must admit I I know of it I don't I'm not very familiar with it
so it is you know especially for those of us in this you know in the states and you know North
America who have never uh really experienced that before except through a translated ROM it's almost
like it's a new product of sorts but I I think you know it's it's neat that Square is digging
into the vaults meanwhile Nintendo kind of does the bare minimum of finally putting their Earthbound
ROMs up on the service don't get me wrong I'm happy I'm thrilled for that that's great but of
course we're all sitting here going Mother 3 when and everyone's like and they're like nope and even
the Earthbound creator was out there on Twitter going I didn't know this was going to happen I'm
really happy that folks are getting to play this yeah I'd love to see Earthbound 3 happen too
you know is in this and then of course I'm sure Reggie was fucking teasing Earthbound 3 as always
or Mother 3 excuse me as always so it's just silly I'm glad I'm glad the um I'm glad the games
are finally where they need to be I'm glad they didn't put it on the plus version of the service
or anything stupid like that and I'm really glad about Live Alive yeah um some other announcements
that they had so they have um some collections coming to the Switch they're getting ported over
so there's a portal companion collection which is portal one and two uh there's also the Klonoa
series that's getting ported over as well uh front mission first is a remake of the first front
mission game that's going to be coming out on the Switch as well uh they showed off a trailer for
the salmon run next wave which is part of Splatoon 3 uh what else oh and Splatoon 3 is this summer
I didn't know I didn't expect we'd get it that fast to be honest yeah this summer um they showed
off a new trailer for Kirby and the forgotten land um so that looked funny with the uh mouthful mode
and what else a new trailer for triangle strategy uh which is kind of less exciting after the Live
Alive announcement then um some of the bigger stuff so now we're getting a Wii sports kind of
sequel with Nintendo Switch Sports which I could have done without their demonstration of
volleyball but um cool well this is that game where it's like of course like this is what we
should have had at the beginning instead of one two switch and it's kind of surprising you know
especially with how huge Wii Sports was and you know and in my brain I went boy they really should
have done this for the Wii U and I neglect oh they did oops but the Wii U kind of fizzled out
that fast I completely forgot and I think most people did let's be real so it's it I mean this
is one of Nintendo's biggest titles it's weird to think about but it is so it's nice that Nintendo
Switch is finally like getting its due with and it's one of those things where it's like oh of
course they had to announce this someday like this seems very logical that we'd get here at some
point I just really wanted to get some comments from chat real quick Mike Deft is talking about
Klonoa which I know Dark Sakura was excited about too and Mike Deft says yeah the Klonoa 1 is
running on the same base they used for the Wii remake but they're using the old models Klonoa 2
looks like a simple remaster which I'm fine with I'm so happy we got Klonoa again and Dark Sakura
I'm sure you echo that a little bit as well uh for getting Klonoa yeah um speaking of uh stuff
also being ported over I forgot about the uh Force Unleashed is being ported over from it's
the Wii version that they're bringing to the Switch which looks it's really showing its age um
what else uh so other bigger announcements Xenoblade Chronicles 3 coming to the Switch
in September looks amazing another one of those oh of course this would happen at some point I
think for me I was more uh impressed with the speed I mean this is something I wouldn't have
expected for a couple years but um actually it came up in Discord I uh I shared that comment
over on our Discord over at vognetwork.com discord I was kind of talking about that and somebody
did say you know the the chatter is that they actually started two and three around the same
time um kind of knowing they were gonna make a trilogy the whole time so this has just been sort
of um you know finished up after two released basically so we got the news that there's probably
not going to be a new Mario Kart 9 until at least 2024 that's because Mario Kart 8 is getting more
DLC 48 new tracks that have been ported over from a remastered I guess from other Mario Kart games
including Mario Kart Tour which is the mobile game so those are going to be coming this year
and in next year and it's like $25 for the DLC and of course they're throwing that into the
expansion pass as well but smart um not a bad deal for 48 tracks over the course of you know
few years but yeah I also I see it as them trying to sweeten the pot with their expansion pass
I think I think they're overcharging for what it is quite honestly especially with no new characters
I think they're really trying to push people to that pass because now yeah they've got that
they've got of course the Genesis and you know that the Nintendo 64 stuff and then they got the
Animal Crossing right so I think they're really trying to push yeah why can't they do more
characters like that I'm surprised that they're not doing that I don't know you know have you seen
a lot of the um you know discourse about that the tracks didn't look great in the preview some folks
thought they were kind of playing well they were like this they were at least the one example they
were showing like they completely changed the way it looks and it looks a lot more simpler
from you know it's not as nice looking as even the mobile version which I'm kind of surprised
well I mean to some extent like I understand a map like what Chaco Mountain was on there right
from the N64 I think that we saw caught a glimpse of that it looked all right yeah but I mean but if
you think about it the N64 that's the problem when you kind of upskill a lot of those old maps they
were playing because the N64 could only handle so much I don't think they were necessarily referring
to the Nintendo 64 stuff I think they're talking about the Mario Kart Tour maps um being kind of
like downscaled almost um I think the stuff the retro tracks are obviously going to look better
because they're based off older versions of the game and they have a lot more room to add detail
and stuff to it so it'll make it look nicer but when you take something from Mario Kart Tour which
is probably running I don't really know how well the mobile game runs or what the hardware
requirements are for that but like you know it probably has some better fidelity to it and a
little bit more detail in the models and stuff in the tracks and so they're probably not able to
pull that down into the switch and maintain a good frame rate so they're obviously going to
make some you know alterations that kind of do that and we're talking about like what it looks
like based off of an early shot that you know who knows when this is coming out and it's just like
a few second clips so it's very subjective right now um I think it's interesting though
especially with all the rumors about Mario Kart 9 which obviously I mean it could have been people
switch I agree HD yeah it's it'll be a launch title yeah Mario the next Mario Kart is going
to be for whatever Nintendo's successor to the Switch is it's going to be the next console I
think at this point Mario Kart 8 is kind of like the full life of the Switch and uh I think Mario
Kart 8 again and we'll just make Mario Kart infinity we'll turn the eight sideways you know
well honestly I think we'd all love a Mario Kart game that just encompasses every single track
right take the Smash Brothers get in there how many how many tracks are left take the Smash
Smash Brothers approach everyone is here right every character and every track from a prior game
why not seriously think about that because like if you look at it you know a lot of the tracks
in some of the other games I don't remember when they started recycling tracks a little
maybe that's DS um but like there's a lot of the other games have just tracks from other
titles in there like I can't imagine that we're left with many unique tracks from you know
just in general and also why can't they just make new tracks you know well did they say every track
was recycled or are people in every track because no it's what they said I thought there was still
room for new tracks interesting I mean they still could put more DLC out there I think that they
should put the pass out for the tracks and maybe have like some additional characters or something
that they should throw in there like I don't know I would have thought that maybe since Mario Kart
Tour kind of ended up fizzling maybe there were some planned things for that that they would push
over that's where I thought they might squeeze some new tracks from but I guess not interesting
all right anything else um no that's I think it I'm trying to think back if there's any other
announcements that they kind of showed off there was like some updates for Metroid Dread that's
going to be coming out so they have a few different difficulty modes basically a one hit
kill one hit death mode that's going to be a dread mode that's coming out soon and then also they're
having an easier mode that's in there as well and then they're going to be adding later on a boss
rush mode that's going to be coming I'm glad to hear that Metroid's getting a Bobby Black Wolf
mode that's great yeah yeah and then they showed off a new trailer for Advance Wars 1 and 2
reboot camp that's coming out on April 8th the only thing I wanted to comment on that I didn't
catch was the portal so they're doing like portal 2 on the switch basically I thought it was portal
one and two is a one and two well yeah it sounds like kind of a repackaging of the games which
you know those I mean don't get me wrong I love portal I love that series it's cool that it's
portable but it's also like who hasn't played it at this point but you know what would be neat
about it and I didn't see this to the point but there were also those fan released level edits
that I thought they went back and put on steam and it would be nice if the switch version included
those well what struck me as odd is that you know of course there's that whole like yay let's get
uh portal portable but we have the steam deck so it seems weird that valve is lending portal over
to the Nintendo switch when I don't think so I mean but portal would still be a great reason to
get a steam deck it's just interesting that valve is doing that that's all portal portal is old no
one's going to get a steam deck for portal yeah true I guess there's that I mean on top of that
how many different versions of the orange box do they put out and you know I I it should have been
the orange box well portal portal 2 has been released on everything and then they've had all
the the edits and everything portal 2 right now is old enough that it's not going to be a steam
deck seller what would be a steam deck seller is being able to have you know some of the current
biggest games that will work on the steam deck from multiple publishers that's what's going to
sell a steam deck or for people you know like me who uh doesn't have exactly a pc capable you know
system although I've worked around it and I don't need a steam deck now but that's what's going to
sell a steam deck um I don't think portal 2 is is remotely going to be in the ballpark of it
sorry interesting pod culture and chat says well I and to to be clear I'm not exactly saying like
oh god people are getting steam decks just for portal but I just think it's interesting
that valve is giving an exclusive to nintendo at this same time that they have a console
now that they're putting out basically that could benefit from all sorts of exclusives
so additional sales it's not even really I mean it's like it's it's a game that came out on the
xbox 360 you know that several years ago yeah I I'm not sure there's a huge audience for this to
begin with except for the fact that I and I think this is the reality too and something we all have
to kind of just is that there are going to be kids out there that were eight when portal two
first came out that are now approaching 20 uh that maybe are going to be playing these games
for the first time because they were a little young for it the first time I think there's
I think that's where the audience for these games are quite honestly as shona matt says don't say
that rob sorry I it is what it is I really think that's where the audience is um pod culture says
portal three would be a steam deck seller now that would that would be too easy for valve to do
but it wouldn't be just on steam though it would be on and we know that they can't count to three
anyway well that is true how long did it take capcom to learn how to count to three
a long time but yes steam deck is not isolated in its own world but still even just the fact
that portal three you know all these years later is still not a thing is interesting to me but it
is what it is valve has their plan I guess so all right well I I thought it was a very solid
nintendo direct at the end of the day um a lot of good announcements I thought there was some
really good surprises in there especially the live alive and you know chrono cross and just
clano a lot of good stuff coming back and a lot of um you know forward-looking stuff I think the
mario kart tracks was kind of a surprise um splatoon 3 not being holiday but paying for
their service I mean like I know it I know it's like kind of stupid just to buy it outright but
I'm going to buy it out right I'm not supporting that expansion pass service yeah I'm I'm still on
the fence I mean honestly I'm not playing enough mario kart 8 I'm not sure I would even get the
tracks it's I'm on I'm on jds plan so I spent so little on it anyway that it doesn't matter
there you go all right well let's talk about the types of things that we are playing this
week nintendo switch or otherwise in how was your gaming week so uh we'll start with dark
sakura how was your gaming week what do you been playing this week I played stuff um of course dead
by daylight um they've disabled nurse which is kind of uh weird for me because I said after rank
reset which is what today yesterday today yeah that my plan was to go back and practice nurse
a lot more um although what I'm also doing is uh I've got my first p350 which is freddy
oh congrats um and I finally decided to prestige pig um so now I am doing nothing but putting all
of my points on um in in uh miss pigu so that I can uh uh make her my second p350
and for those who don't know um every time you hit 50 you can prestige but you can only
prestige three times and then you get another achievement when you hit 50 on prestige level
three I've also figured out how to rip the models from dead by daylight now and import them into
blender I saw you tweeting some of this stuff it was interesting yeah they actually redid pig's
face when they put out the new cosmetics so before that um her face was just sort of like almost kind
of flat and now um she actually like like for the the head actually goes with that outfit that I
have on her there's a different head for the mask uh you know the mask with the bear trap crown
right uh mask the bear trap crown has like a sort of a shaded kind of like under the batman mask
sort of makeup thing her regular face is all covered in blood um which she didn't even get
that bloody in the real movies hell even when she got shot in the neck she didn't get that bloody
um so uh I I thought it was really really interesting um I still haven't figured out how
to get the the skeletons imported right so that I can use some other animation stuff but really
my goal is just a converter to a uh a v tube thing anyway um and I'm going to be trying to edit the
the face mesh to uh to look a little bit more realistic I'm going to stylize it quite a bit
but right now I've got my first work done and I'm also going to rip uh a meg in the pig mask
so I don't have to animate her face interesting okay so um actually I tried to apply Jill's face
to to pig and the survivor's heads are a little bit smaller so um the eye holes are like here
like right where normal eyes are and then like the actual eyeballs just so you know oh is it
yeah oh crap okay sorry so the eyes would be like right here um you know we're normal the eye holes
would be there but like the eyeballs themselves since the eyeballs are part of the face mesh
are like under uh like where the cheekbone would be whereas you know amandas are like right in the
right place so I kind of need to figure out how to I haven't done mesh editing except for like
v tube studio which is really simple so this is going to be a test of my skills so wish me luck
but my eventual goal is to get Jill's face um applied over amanda's uh uh mask
so that at least it's a decent looking face so anyway um and going I also need to double check
what uh what eye color Shawnee had the I forgot her last name but she was the actress that played
Amanda and Saul so I need to look up her eye color and make sure that there's the right one so anyway
um going though to other games I've been playing of course I did Fantasian which I have Fantasian
Friday and uh I had to restart on a couple of things um and I also started doing a retro stream
on Saturday night after work and I played The Legend of Zelda A Link to the Past and I have
lost a lot of skills in that game because I haven't played it in 10 years so and he was like oh where
was this shit where was that shit do I get this or no I can't get the Zora thing because I need to
get the glove and so I'm on to getting the glove although I finished the first palace um I always
never know what to call what was his name like Sahasrallah the the old man so I call him
Sarsaparilla that works I call him Scheherazade once but Dan and I do that is like if we find
someone with a kind of a complicated name even though we can pronounce it we still kind of screw
it up um and then uh I actually have a translated copy of Live Alive that I intended to start
until the direct came out um the timing so right um and I also uh played Radiant Silver Gun
for Saturn fun on my Mac oh fun yeah I um I've managed to get PC Engine and Saturn games
and I think I might be able to get a Playstation 1 to work next I'm still trying to find Robit
Lundu which I would prefer to have an original of mine but you know I'll play it any way I can
games like older than some people I know um and then of course you know I played wordscapes
because that's what I do and just yeah watching friends play stuff trying to see what's interesting
you know some people are playing that Lost Ark I can't play it so oh and of course Mass Effect 2
which I was able to get running in my uh my parallels oh fun so I also got my uh my
SteelSeries controller working yay my old one my Nimbus I'm sad I missed your um retro stream I was
hosting like my gaming week is a little thin because I was hosting um show shows are starting
to come back um with precautions but I was hosting uh last night or yeah last night was
Rocky Horror and then two nights ago was a burlesque variety thing so I was very busy
out doing that but I know why you uh messaged me that you were gonna do it I was like oh darn
uh I would have watched while I was packing boxes if I wasn't out and about so
well I'm kind of getting to the point where I'm just gonna throw up the cheats on it just because
really I'm playing it for the experience of playing the game and yeah I don't care I I'm
at least using the save states because you know when you die you start over and there's one battle
that even when I was super good at the game still always gave me problems and that was that big
stupid giant worm that's in the second is in the second or third yeah yeah I hate that thing um
and uh I don't even know what it was but I always would just like it would take me for like even
the newer one the link between worlds that gave me fits too it was a pain in the ass yeah so
I'm just like I'm just cheat to win I don't care I'm playing for the story it doesn't matter I'm
the one playing the game if anyone has a problem with it fuck you all right I'm the one playing
the game and you're not you don't you don't know anyone you play you play the way you want on your
stream and that's they don't like it they go somewhere else it's just been like lately I've
seen a slew of people like complaining about how people are enjoying things I'm like it's not
hurting you yeah fuck off seriously I I I am like right now at the point where I'm just like I don't
give a shit I'm the one playing it you can deal with it there you go all right let's go over to
loki how was your gaming week um so it's minecraft um but it's also I finished playing well as of
right now because they're constantly updating the game but I have completed the entire game
of power wash simulator oh wow things have been power washed now congrats so yeah that that was
fun um but now yeah I wish there's more to do in there um and then minecraft have been extremely
busy the last week or so so I was working on a sorting system and storage system so that was
kind of this entire week and I'm putting together my new episode well I started it this morning so
I should be hopefully out in the next couple days all right um that's it my gaming week as I
mentioned was a little bit slower just with all the other commitments going on I did still play
way too much dead by daylight um I got my adept Claudette achievement today so yay yay I got fanged
to level 10 so I'm gonna get hers next so just kind of working my way through those for no
particular reason it's just a fun I need you to still help me with my Michaela adapt yeah sure
just um but I don't want to lose my 100% survival rate uh well then don't play with me because I
have had some sweaty ass I had a basement bubba today I haven't seen that gag in like six months
and I just forget how exhausting that is to like go down there and rescue someone in the basement
and then and it's like oh fucking really I have to tell you I thought of a way to do um a uh like a
you know basement uh pig but I was gonna call it um like a pantry pig and I decided instead
to call it basement bacon okay so more on that later all right um and then I've still been
playing Final Fantasy 14 been pretty much capping my red tomes every week and working on my gear
for my gunbreaker which is kind of my main class class that I play in that game uh and then
otherwise playing gps games um ingress started their second sunday mission thing officially
they've been kind of doing it unofficially for a few months now and now the official one started
this month today with the new badge so you know the the walking incentive stuff has been really
good um I guess I haven't really mentioned this on olr I've talked about on social media but you
know I've talked about some of my health issues um over the past few months um I'm down over 30
pounds at this point um with all the changes that I've made since that happened and you know
honestly awesome the gp I mean obviously I've been working very hard with you know diet and all that
stuff too but the gps games Pikmin um ingress pokemon go which I actually picked up again which
I hadn't played in a while those have been huge in like gamifying steps so that I actually get more
steps every day so that I really push myself to go out on a walk and things like that is uh very
uh very big thank you I see the kind words in chat yeah it's funny um somebody came up to me
after a rocky last night and was like oh yeah you you look great I saw you in October and yeah I
could tell that you'd put on COVID weight you know I know it was well intentioned because she was
like we all have you know she's got that kind of thing uh and then she was like oh but you you're
looking great and it's it's nice it's a very nice thing um and I didn't I didn't want to tell her
like well I got diagnosed with diabetes and it really whips your ass into gear but we do also
need to stop uh you know what's the word I'm thinking of equivocating um size with with
aesthetics right and the person I was sitting with who kind of listened all that because I
kind of actually leaned in their ear and I said I should have said I should it's a good thing I
didn't say oh I got you know the type 2 diabetes will do that to you um and then my friend actually
said this is why I don't comment on people's bodies because you don't know people's stories
you know and I that's that's kind of my approach too I don't I'm always I'm always afraid I'm
going to say something like oh you've lost weight and then shock they gained it and I'm just an
idiot you know so I just try not to comment on that sort of thing at all unless some somebody
else tells me first oh I've lost weight or oh I'm trying to put on weight for whatever it's like oh
congrats are you meeting your goals okay cool good for you I like to tell tell people that
they're looking healthy yeah exactly you know not necessarily whether or not they've lost weight but
if I see that they've got a glow to their skin and they're energetic like oh you're looking really
healthy today yeah there you go you know because that is completely independent now if they happen
to have lost weight in order to improve their health then that ties in with it happy for them I
mean I'll be honest I was feeling a little bit shallow when I lost all that weight with my
surgery but you know it's size isn't a judge of health totally agree and I you know I it's one
of those things where weight loss is a very nice side effect of all this other bullshit and that's
kind of just how I've explained it is that you know I'll take it this is far said if I'm gonna
work hard sure I'll take weight loss why not it's fun all right anyhow let's move on we're gonna
get into some other news of course I've mentioned this a few times I just want to make sure y'all
know there will be no new OLR next week I know it's kind of a random week to not have a show
but it is because the move so we'll be back in two weeks so that means no podcasts no live show
but Bobby Blackwolf will be here so for the Sunday night loyal crowd over at twitch.tv
slash vog network you will have something to watch next week and for those who on the podcast
feed there is a huge library of back episodes available over at orange launch radio.com or
vog network under orange launch radio if you want to listen to an oldie moldy episode of
OLR to pass the time next week all right let's get into some news and let's talk about a game
that a lot of people have been playing this week and I wish I had had time to download it install
it play it myself but I said I'm gonna wait till after this moving stuff to get sucked into this
so Loki tell us about this yeah so the new uh I guess new for us MMO lost arc has reached a record
number of players on steam with 1.3 million online at peak and that is the third most game or played
game in the history based off active concurrent players um just not bad not bad at all um and
then of course I guess also well I actually now as of when we're looking at this I think it even beat
out um csgo because csgo had their record was uh 1.3 it was like 1 million 308 000 and I think now
they're just past that as well so uh pub g's through the roof right because you know when pub
g yeah like g's like 3.2 million three fortnight there were a ton of people playing uh pub g so
yeah so uh not those numbers anymore but yeah at its heyday it was you know pretty high up there so
um that's pretty great for a brand new mmo for lisa the us and europe I know this came out
originally in south korea in 2019 but um yeah it looks pretty cool well you know it's um I can't
take myself into an mmo at this point it's it's free to play which is you know that's a huge part
of why a lot of people are able to get into it um amazon has been doing a huge push through twitch
you know you probably saw an ad for lost ark before you got here on olr tonight um because
you know well that and that's smart that's amazon leveraging you know the fact that they run twitch
to put in some ads and you know get the hype going for this game which also seemed to work
well for new world uh you know even the new world kind of went like I feel like new world was very
much a flash in the pan so that I know it sounds really harsh but like honestly like it came and
went like sorry to fans of that game you know you don't need my validation to have fun with the game
but it just definitely seems like you know lost or new world was kind of you know the it girl for
like a weekend and then suddenly you know faded out real quick so I'm curious what the staying
power of this is gonna be if this ends up you know going ended up being a tide that comes in
really heavy and then recedes really quick or if this really does end up being something that
stays around and that's part of the reason I've been waiting a little bit to jump on board with
it I mean my personal life doesn't really give me the time right now to download fight queues and do
all that with something new um but you know if it's still relevant in a couple weeks and my
friends are still playing it uh I would definitely want to check it out um looking at some comments
from chat quest buster says launch was also delayed by several hours because of the demand
on the 11th but founders were able to get in a few days before that quest buster continuing uh who
also had commented that they've been playing a lot of it this week um it's a ton of fun but the first
few hours are a bit slow they tightened some of the experience up from what I had played from
the Russian version so it is also interesting that a game that's technically already existed
for quite some time yes in other parts of the world and other localizations it's interesting
that it's so popular and now I'm curious to see because of this what else is going to suddenly
show up that's been out for a long time in other places we'll see any interest in lost ark uh
I think dark soccer already said pass but loki did you you have any interest in lost
art no I I can't jump into it well I can't oh oh there's no uh mac even though yeah it's not
I don't think it runs on windows arm either oh bummer all right all right well moving on let's
talk about call of duty because of course with the pending purchase of microsoft to
buy activision blizzard a lot of people have been presuming that call of duty is going to end up an
exclusive and it certainly would make a lot of sense that it would go that direction however
this is very interesting the president of microsoft brad smith made a blog post saying
microsoft will continue to make call of duty and other popular activision blizzard titles available
on playstation through the term of any existing agreement with activision and we have committed
to sony that we will also make them available on playstation beyond the existing agreement
and into the future so that sony fans can continue continue to enjoy the games they love
we are also interested in taking similar steps to support nintendo's successful platform
we believe this is the right thing for the industry uh for gamers and for our business
uh many folks that are a little more skeptical about these sorts of things and i don't blame them
thinking that this might be microsoft's way to sort of respond to the fact that the ftc is all
up in this business uh for the approval of the takeover and so forth so perhaps um sony or
excuse me microsoft committing to supporting sony platforms is um gonna help them get through this
i guess or what have you um now maybe i'm just being a jerk but i don't think i am i would still
be highly skeptical of all this not i call of duty will come out for playstation you know if
they said it they're gonna do it but it doesn't mean it's gonna be the version you want because
i think we're definitely gonna see the extra maps extra characters extra stuff is going to be the
definitive version will be the microsoft version the sony version will be an afterthought uh
as will honestly probably nintendo's um just because of the limitations of the platform
now of course in a couple years when we're talking about nintendo's successor platform
that's a different conversation but um i i i still think microsoft would be foolish to not
have call of duty be the must play experience on their own platform and will sony do the same
thing with destiny and whatever bungee has cooking for the future abso-fucking-lutely
abso-fucking-lutely and of course microsoft also gets call of duty on game pass which is going to
be huge and they can continue to charge 60 bucks on playstation at launch i think a lot of it is
just that illusion of supporting everything equally um and i'm not so sure it really is
but i guess that's nice for people that never ever want to get a
xbox or play on their pc i suppose so all right let's move on dark sakura
i had to unmute my my mic every time i click it it actually immediately remutes itself is so weird
any rate um i remember going to e3 and always finding like the america's army area and they
were like always like oh play play this you'll see you know and then and then sign up for for
the rest of your life um well they and honestly it was a really revolutionary idea to use a video
game as a recruitment tool 20 years ago um now though they have uh uh you know it's free to play
it was really successful a lot of people said it was really fun but as of may 5th this year they
are going to shut down the servers and uh it's going to be retired so uh it i mean the the thing
with this particular with this particular game and and something like it is that it really was
a novel concept when it came out you know yeah we all knew oh this is a recruitment tool but
it also was supposedly a really good game i mean right and i mean we had so many different you
know military related games come out over the years but you know america's army was only supposed
to last for seven years but it was so successful that they uh actually the pentagon approved
spending more than three million a year to uh to promote the game and expand upon it
um i mean and right now the uh their recruiting budget i think is like eight billion
so that's not i mean that's only a small percentage of their recruiting budget but still
it is a big chunk of change um and then they said you know there was a study in 2008 from
uh the massachusetts institute of technology so mit um that said that thirty percent of all
americans ages 16 to 24 had a more positive impression of the army because of the game
and the game had a large impact on recruiting so it was clearly successful i mean the army has a
twitch channel well yes i know about that but that that hasn't always been good news because
that was the one where people were going in there and asking about war crimes and so they would get
banned but then it was like well the government can't ban people it's freedom of speech right so
it started that whole interesting conversation and how there are protocols on that but um going
back to the game itself yeah i mean i've i've heard i've i've no interest in the game i'm not
going to play it or or really cover it on this show beyond these um interesting pop culture
uh and gaming culture notes but um everything i've heard is that for what it is you would expect
that it's a shitty game usually these types of games are pretty shitty like you know when
corporate corporations and the army in a sense is a corporation trying to catch the corporation
yeah trying to cash in on what the cool kids enjoy right is usually kind of doesn't work out very
well but apparently this was a pretty decent game from what i heard so um that's part of why it was
successful is that you know and and i realize people have their criticisms and and it's fine
but it seems like the people that were making this game were actually listening to what gamers kind
of wanted to play and actually developing a game that would be fun and not what like research
groups said would be fun a boring recruitment tool isn't gonna it won't recruit anybody
right so well the other thing too is like the federal aviation administration um had a hiring
campaign they were looking for 4300 air traffic controllers in about five years and they focused
on gamers and they met they i think supposedly are already well on their way to um to hitting
their goal but a lot of you know these different institutions now are eyeing
games and gamers for their their hiring base you know because certain skills hand-eye coordination
you know of course would carry over and then they also you know can judge mindsets by what type of
games people are playing you know so there's a lot of you know very interesting psychology that goes
into it but you know and of course there's also then putting out you know i call it the the last
star fighter syndrome who all remembers that movie it's been a long time where you know they put out
the arcade machine and it was a test to see who was going to be the next star fighter um and then
then the guy gets kidnapped and goes to outer space and you know and then his robot twin makes
out with his girlfriend but anyway um they're using different games also as sort of uh disguised
tests for certain skill sets and so you know i i just still think it's very interesting that
we have so many government facilities that are like oh games are bad and the army's like fuck
yeah games yeah we're gonna use these games we're gonna get some more some more grunts i had no idea
about the air traffic controller thing and then i think about like something like flight simulator
where it's like okay maybe flight simulator is not anything like actually flying a real plane
but it really is educational as to what all goes into it like if you actually play flight simulator
on you know simulator mode you're really thinking about especially this new one that Microsoft put
out not that long ago um really gets into the weeds on like here's everything that goes into
takeoff and you're taking classes at your computer basically um and again i'm not trying to say that
like oh i played flight simulator i can fly a real plane suddenly no but you'll have an absolute leg
up on somebody who's never uh touched that you know if you were to uh want to take actual you
know plane flying classes so uh very interesting uh with gaming as a recruitment so i'm going to
our chat for some additional comments sg100 matt says geez 22 years old since this was in beta i
remember seeing america's army at digital life i wouldn't have guessed it was still going on yeah
i thought it had faded out a few years ago but i i felt it still had an impressive run um so you know
i mean i again games like this usually come out are laughed at and fade away within a year so the
fact that this one lasted over 20 years pretty fascinating to be honest yeah yeah and with
constant development so pretty cool yeah pretty cool all right let's move on loki all right so
of course with all the acquisitions that microsoft is making everyone is kind of asking so you know
all these games go in the games pass isn't that gonna raise the price of games pass you know it's
gotta happen at some point because where's all this money gonna come from that they're buying
all these companies with well apparently phil spencer was trying to kind of uh point out that
no no no no they don't have plans right now to raise the price of game pass um so kind of
addressing the rumors that it was going to go up in price i feel like i can't prove this negative
um people ask one is the game pass price going to go up they're buying all these studios you know
it's inevitable even though it's been for what now four years we haven't raised it but it's like you
know it's coming when are they when they are number one they're gonna start doing all these
exclusive deals like that you know xbox has history and all i can do is make decisions that
are in front of us and try to be explicit about what our goals are so it sounds like that they're
trying to at least be pretty transparent with it um that they don't have plans to raise the price
of games pass and i'm sure when they do that they will let everybody know yeah they'll raise it
eventually don't kid yourself or i mean they'll they'll absolutely raise it eventually i what i
hope does doesn't happen is i don't want to see them go into tears that would be really crappy
um so i really hope microsoft doesn't go that direction but um because then then you end up in
the nintendo problem the lowest tier gets hardly any love i mean i guess hooray we got earthbound
um but you know what what other bones are they going to throw at it over the next year um so
yeah i don't want to see microsoft tear it i think we should all prepare for the price to
go up and let's also be real if you are a smart shopper trademark patent pending um you'll never
pay full price for game pass and i've talked about it here on the show is that obviously you know i'm
sure you all follow those gaming deals whether it be you know the cheap ass gamer wario 64 all those
types of put that when those cards go on sale and they will go on sale and i'm sure there are plenty
of you show of hands how many of you on black friday or around that time will stock the fuck up
on uh your cards for you know playstation microsoft and so forth for the next year
i'm sure there's people that do that for sure um uh and uh i've also talked about that i use the
microsoft rewards app uh now and i i understand why people might be adverse to using that because
essentially you're allowing you know extra data to go to microsoft and all this stuff and you
actually have to use bing which some people might fear um but i use it casually and i would say
one out of every three months i get comped through microsoft rewards you end up getting 12 000 points
and get a free month and so you know i i hope they would keep things like that into place if
nothing else you could probably get a discount so you know again if you're if you're a choosy choosy
shopper you'll never pay full price for these things so uh pod culture and chat says i loaded
up on black friday yep uh mike def says maybe uh sj100 matt saying i'm glad i have game pass
locked in for the next two years that xbox live gold trick oh that's probably also keeping them
from raising the price these people that are still locked in that won't have to pay it i wonder if
they're gonna wait another two years for everybody to be out of that that would be very interesting
uh fifth dream points out i think i have playstation network for three more years
so again kind of loading up uh maybe when it was cheap and you know what how how far out can you
load up xbox live like three years or something like that i mean if we think it's coming maybe
load up your account the next time these things go on sale something something to think about
but i also know that's a big you know that's a big uh cost and not maybe everybody's super into
game pass i don't know but uh i think it's great i love that they're building the cloud stuff into
it too so uh i plan to stick with it for a little while so all right uh did your mom says you can
load up to five years if i recall correctly uh as shown her matt says three years uh i wonder if you
know we might be talking about conversion uh that whole thing versus how much you can actually load
up i don't know i'd have i have to look into it i'm not sure the answer but it would be at least
i'm sure it's at least two three years that you can load in advance um something to think about
if you're that worried about the price going up um anyhow let's talk about a new playstation 5
update that's coming out uh since we've been talking a lot about microsoft let's show a little
love to sony after all isn't uh i think horizon forbidden west is this week isn't it that's uh
that's a big deal for sony so i'm sure there's a lot of people that are going to be on that this
week um so uh anyway there will be a new system update for place actually sorry i i my mind
derailed again but i wanted to say i heard the speaking of horizon forbidden west i heard it is
two discs on playstation 4 you don't hear that one very often what year is this well it's because
it's a 90 gig install so uh laughs in call of duty updates yeah well yeah it's a lot but i'm
i mean there's two ways to look at it there's one going uh it's gonna eat so much of my space but
then you also go that means it's a fucking big game well also like if it's a 90 gig install at
least they have it on disk and they're not like saying hey you can download that first or you can
you know download that first 10 from the disc but you gotta download the rest from the cloud
good luck yeah i am so excited y'all my new internet that i'm gonna have as of saturday
no limit no limit yay i i can reconnect my xbox to automatic updates again i'm so excited
download all of the updates update all you want i cannot wait to download the shit out of everything
i can finally run my steam updates that i've been backlogged for like years it's fucking exciting
y'all all right anyway yeah or as to 100 matt making the classic bemoni reference going no
no limit no no no limit all right um anyway uh as 200 matt also used google fu to find out 36
months is the max you can load up uh xbox live but interesting mike def says it depends on the
region because mexico is only two and a half years oh that is interesting it could be by region too
all right sorry we derailed i wanted to talk about this new update for playstation 4 and playstation
that is going to be adding new accessibility and quality of life features including voice commands
uh right now a beta is going to be made available to english-speaking users in the u.s and uk
that will let you say hey playstation and sorry if i woke yours up but i don't think this beta
is actually out yet but it will be soon you can turn this feature off just like all the other
home assistants if you want and then you can use your voice to launch games whatever apps
open the system menu control media playback and so on and so on i have to say i i never saw myself
really using a lot of the voice commands but i have found it awfully convenient for the bedroom
tv which has a google chrome cast on it to say hey you know the word smart assistant um uh turn
on my television and launch twitch and it's nice to just have it all come up there while i'm you
know you know brushing my teeth and other stuff and then i can crawl into bed and watch twitch
before uh i drift off so it's just kind of kind of neat uh so they're building the same thing into
playstation why not there's a lot of media and stuff on playstation and if you want to launch
games that way sure why not also group chats will now be known as parties and you can decide if you
want them to be private or public parties so there's that uh if you leave a party public and
open your friends can join their friends can join so it definitely will be a party
also you'll now be able to filter games by genre and have five of them on the console's home screen
for quick access apparently trophy cards are going to be redesigned on ps5 and there will be more
screen reader languages which is great for accessibility and some other changes as well
you can opt into the beta test if you want over at playstation.com but get on that uh
wednesday is when they're gonna uh send out the emails on if you got in or not but that's pretty
exciting so uh let's see fifth dream in chat says that was always a good idea but usually muscle
memory and clicking buttons to launch games and whatever it's just quicker yes and no i do agree
with you but sometimes they change the interface uh and playstation is done at least on playstation
four because like you have to launch everything through the tv and video app when it comes to
stuff like twitch and stuff like things move around so it is and then like it it starts it's
not as fast as it used to be so like i have to launch it and wait for the icons to show up so
i can see where twitch is today or if it got rearranged or whatever at least that's been my
experience i just it's just easier to tell my uh you know a home assistant by uh g o o g l e to
sorry i'm really trying to not launch all of your assistants i have to remember that in this day
and age you you could call it uh call it gurgle yeah sure sure so i can say gurgle uh do this
thing and uh yeah it's just easier i think you just you you adapt the muscle memory i guess
all right uh up next oh it's this headline again we always like to hear this person in the news
because it makes for a funny headline right dark sagra yeah so um bowser has a 40 month stint to
do in prison yeah but not the bowser you're thinking uh unless you are thinking of the
hacker gary bowser so um he was the the person that had the switch hacking group team uh
executor um and so uh of course he's not doug bowser just saying even though they got their
names mixed up in the original version of the article oops um but he was part of a collective
that uh sold devices that you could use to pay to play pirated games on your switch um
they the fbi arrested him in 2020 and he agreed to pay 10 million to nintendo
for a civil privacy lawsuit and then another 4.5 million for restitution
but the sentencing today um not today but when they were doing the sentencing uh he was facing
up to 10 years in prison um and also because video game publishers apparently have lost more
than 65 million thanks to what team uh executor did they were wanting to to go for that instead
he is getting he got 40 months so that's still you know a big chunk out of his life and they're
still looking to find um his accomplices so that's really about all we know now but but yeah he's
being sentenced assisted well in 40 months maybe is when they'll release super mario odyssey 2
because bowser will get out of prison and kidnap the princess yet again uh dart tetsuya in chat
says i know everyone is taking up pitchforks against nintendo but i heard this guy had
malicious code in his mods i don't know if i can feel too sorry if that's the case um i don't know
if i'd believe everything i read on the internet but at the same time i also don't understand the
pitchforks against nintendo for this i mean this guy was pretty cocky from what i understand like
nintendo had slapped this guy down a couple times before and he was kind of continuing his stuff
thinking he was invincible so it kind of sounds like he got what was coming to him like exactly
and and the thing is it's one thing that if they're you know giving something away for for
free you know right but the fact that he was making money off of someone else's work pretty
much you know or as a uh an exploit to get around somebody else's work i mean it's i and now you
know i'll be honest i had like you know an r4 back in the day and and all of those but at the
end you know those for active systems those are things that are that are taking you know money
from the developers from from the people who are making the games and at this like if it was you
know say oh we've put out this you know the everdrive you know for a snus that's one thing
it's an old system they're not really making any money on you know obscure you know import games
unless they're going to put them out you know on the e-shop or something right so that's one thing
but for a modern active consistently updated and having released games for system that's many
hyphens in that phrase by the way um it makes perfect sense um and then to go around and be
oh i can't do shit to me and me and i'm like no do shit to him please yeah do lots of shit to him
and don't get me wrong i'm all for you know homebrew on consoles and you know unlocks to
do that and i realize it can be a slippery slope with piracy and i don't think we should be
pirating games i think we should you know support where we can the developers of worth but i'm all
for homebrew and things that open that up but when you're being very flagrant that you're doing it
for piracy which i kind of get the sense this guy was then it's kind of one of those why are we all
acting shocked that nintendo did this i i don't think you know we we nintendo is known for very
being very um aggressive to protect its shit but usually they're not going to try to send you to
jail they might shut you down like that youtuber um a few weeks ago but they're not gonna they're
not gonna go after that person to jail because they weren't like trying to flagrantly make money
off nintendo and pirate games and things of that sort and i think that's where uh this you know bad
bowser went wrong to be honest only sonic and chat says yeah modded my we too just a few years ago
yeah i modded mine and i'll also say it's the one time i did advocate for piracy because i did it to
play a game that nintendo refused to release here um and the sing star abba it uh i did end up doing
that but it was the xena i remember that's when tiara was visiting we came over it was xena blade
did it and then they ended up doing the game stop exclusive agreement which i still thought was shit
so i think in those circumstances i think it's a little more justified um but i mean like again if
i can walk into a target or other similar store you know and pick up the item off the shelf i
you know i'm probably gonna i'm 99.9 times out of 100 that's what i'll do but in those extreme cases
where you know what there's a game i want to play and the company refuses to release it in the us
i don't feel bad about piracy whatsoever in fact i would encourage people to pirate mother 3
oh um i i have a cartridge yeah i have a translated cartridge so but i will say to
companies credit even past where we were at with the nintendo we so many years ago i feel like
companies are finally realizing we live in a global sort of environment and we see more stuff
get released here um i think taiko no tatsujin is a great example we're seeing a lot of those
games ending up releasing here when you know uh we all remember a time when those were very uh
nuanced you know japanese releases only that never saw the light of day over here and now we're
seeing them because i think these companies realize oh yes we live in a global economy
economy so uh mike deaf says sing star abba was ps3 there was a comparable one on the wii um there
was it was a it was just dance maybe or what yeah it was just dance there was a comparable abba game
on wii so yeah i think it was no it wasn't just dance it was like let's dance abba or something
like oh yeah it's even worse knock off something oh like we sing abba yeah yeah we sing abba uh
orange right says i would have never guessed taiko would be a worldwide release game that
would get announced on nintendo directs back in the 2000s exactly so things are getting better
in that regard so that's why you don't hear me like you know this show has been on for 20 years
so you could probably go back and find rob roberts advocating piracy in certain scenarios
but these days the the reasons to do it are not you know the games are available for you to pay
for them and pay the developers for their work and i think that's what you should do in the case of
mother 3 that is not an option for us so steal away in this case it's a political protest you
know yeah in a way yeah you are protesting the fact that this game has a high demand in the us
and they aren't releasing it so we're taking matters into our own hands at the end of story
i will be happy to pay for it once it's made available to me indeed same absolute same all
right uh yeah as 200 matt says i mean we all modded our playstation ones to play ddr titles
well i would argue that konami konami is or you use the plug right but i would argue that konami
is one of the worst offenders and this is why i think that it's actually you bring that up
i think that's very relevant to the history of our show let's really send off studio n7 tonight
and take a look back at the 20-year history of the show in the early years of the show the only
way we could play ddr was to either pay excruciatingly high import fees for games or to mod
or to steal them essentially and i'm i'm sorry not sorry we stole them because that was the
only reasonable way to play them but you know what every time they released a mix here even if
it was subpar when ddr the original one came out on playstation the us version bought it konamiks
which i think turned like 22 years old this week i saw a tweet or something like that konamiks when
that came out bought it and all the other stuff bought those as well so um you know i would
support it when it finally would show up here uh and as joe and her map points out i remember it
was a big deal when the ds was region free yeah orange right says i even bought beatmania us
hey that control same but the controller was better remember uh yeah i well how many times
did we shave our 2dx japanese controller buttons and they think that you know mine actually had
the little pad mods underneath them um but then they constructed the new ones i think with
there's something very similar to those mods i heard there were some japanese players that
imported our version for that reason to get that controller yeah yep i i have a couple of friends
actually who were like hey can you send me a controller and i'd be like uh i'll see where i
can find them if i find oh well we just had someone so important for us sorry about it like
okay well i didn't buy it so fine i just i still have mine uh they just turned up in the garage
uh our old controllers for that so i have honey i actually need to find my copy of para para because
i have my biscuits and i don't have a game oh so and i wanted to bust it out and play it the other
day i actually was planning on hooking up uh uh 2dx uh fourth style so i could get no what no
was third style that had the right version of the safari oh yeah the slower one yeah the right
version of the safari not the crappy speedy one all right anyway let's move on too far down memory
lane but good times uh let's move on loki yeah so you know we've talked about how battlefield 2042
is kind of bad and because of that there is a change.org petition asking electronic arts to
offer refunds on all platforms for their players and they already have more than 150,000 people
that has signed that petition because it is pretty bad and they're losing players every day so
we'll see if that ends up happening the thing to note though is even though they have 150,000
signatures other campaigns have gotten a lot more signatures like for example making shaggy dlc in
moral combat 11 381 000 signatures so we'll see uh what pardon my ignorance on this but we all
know i don't usually play these type of games so what's wrong with the game loki can you translate
to gay for me yes i will translate so it is a very rushed and buggy put together game
for example some of the complaints that they have in there there's balancing issues with the
vehicles in the game hovercrafts are like way too op you can drive up the side of buildings with
those you can constantly respawn them um they may go from mass effect the very basics like a gun
play are just broken like you can literally empty a full clip into somebody and it doesn't register
a hit against them like just ridiculously stupid things like that so it's just it's very much broken
all right thank you for translating it sounds sounds like a hot mess it is a hot mess all right
um also a hot mess uh countries that don't support uh equal rights uh for all lgbtq people and we're
seeing that play out with a sims 4 wedding expansion and uh this expansion is not going
to release in russia because of federal laws over there that will not allow it to release
uh there was a law passed in 2013 uh that uh some folks uh outside of uh russia sometimes
call it the russia gay propaganda law um so basically uh maxis in a blog post called our
commitment to you a letter to our players from the sims team mentions that because there is a
wedding themed storyline involving a same-sex marriage between two characters uh it's a quote
not something we could freely share around the world and so the team wanted to quote explain the
decision that we've made not to release this pack in russia and it basically came down to the fact
that the team could either tell this story or uh they could uh and avoid the russia market or they
could change the content to meet those sorts of federal laws and they've decided to say uh we'll
just choose not to release it there at all um so this would be and i know we have listeners over
there so this would be a great this is one of those great opportunities where uh you could just
pirate it and play it anyway uh because not but i mean in this case it sucks because we should
support the developers but also it's funny because dark sakura talked about sometimes piracy being a
political protest and i feel in this particular case it really is right so very interesting so
but hey props to maxis first because you know other companies would have just said okay we'll
change the gender of the character um which they could have easily done um but they didn't do it
so that's great uh dart to see it says uh i remember that being a whole thing back around
the time of the winter olympics back then yeah so all right let's let's go back to
a simpler time shall we and uh revisit uh this segment that we love to do on our show
and now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where i'll dive into the vault and pull
out a classic and tell you about it it's time for the classic game of the week
and what did you pick for us this week dark sakura jockey crush as they say in the intro
of it jockey crush it is well you remember xtifer playing all the alien crush he could possibly play
yeah he he really loved your guys's old place yeah that was on we virtual console yeah
um well jockey crush is the third in that whole series so of course the uh the first one being
alien crush and then devil's crush well actually dragon's revenge is also i guess would sort of be
the third one that came out that was the the uh genesis one that wasn't as great as the others
but jockey crush is continuing with that sort of uh otherworldly theme in the fact that it's an
ogre themed uh jockey is a type of a japanese demon um but it's another pinball game virtual
pinball game this one came out on the super famicon it never came out in the us um and it's
an it's an excellent game if you like you know virtual pinball uh one of the the great things
about this one is that it has a lot more in common with devil's crush uh in the fact that
it has these uh six hidden stages um and you also have alternating two player play um different
options where you can have different control control configurations your ball physics things
like that you know different speed settings um you also have um you know different tiers like
i was saying in the in uh in your levels the third level has like moving targets and uh
different lanes that lead you back to the second level you know all kinds of ways that you can get
around through there um it's it's really a very beautiful game as well um it is a little on the
dark side but dark and vivid if if that makes sense um and in in fact it's actually even
considered you know an equal to any of the others in the series you know even slightly crisper in
terms of its uh its uh design and color scheme but uh jackie crush uh came out in 1992 uh again for
the super famicom put up by an access soft um and it's again in the whole crush series um it also
you know i'd have to say that
if you've got a way to play this game and you have not i would actually do it yeah this is
actually the official third game because that uh that genesis one that came out i don't really
think it was actually part of the part of the series like an official part of the series more
like a spiritual successor type game but um i i also you know it's got a like story to it
and everything about like you know the magical pinball from hell or something um and the the
sad thing about it is that while there are a lot of enthusiasts who do recall alien crush and
devil's crush um they don't know about jackie crush because it didn't come out over here i
know i've mentioned it on the show before fifth stream was talking about demon's tilt and demon's
tilt is an absolute spiritual successor to the series i i've actually streamed a decent bit of
this game as well um i jackie crush in fact i i might actually just bust this out later this week
and show it off um maybe on my wednesday night stream but it's really worth playing um of course
also developed by compile and compile has given us one of the other best games in the universe
the guardian legend so and on top of that too the music is really good
yeah i noticed the music in this is great oh yeah the music in this game it just really sets
the entire tone for it and on top of that you know there's uh gosh it's like this one
uh stage on the table where it's sort of like this sort of purple rocky
side and it's got this uh the jackie in the center of it you know in red and white and it almost
makes me think that it's like in this sort of abyss where everything else just has that sort
of red outlined and and it honestly feels like there's some true depth in the game even though
it's two-dimensional so i i have absolutely been enamored with this game um i wouldn't mind owning
an original of it and i've played it you know uh quite a few times i really enjoy it but i
just think that there's like a sort of crispness to this one that is missing from quite a few other
uh uh pinball tables and in fact uh the one on stream right now is always the mode that i called
uh space invader mode sort of um but i think that there are so many different variances in
in gameplay between the multiple stages that you have enough to keep you interested in it it's got
a good enough challenge to it that the replayability is absolutely there um okay
sorry to the podcast listeners but this mode that we're looking at on twitch right now this creepy
as fuck yeah it has sort of like this uh almost like kind of reminds me of miss nude world
the face in the background is sort of like almost like a type of no mask i think um but uh you also
have like these little spheres that are coming coming out almost like little uh scarabs what it
looks like and then uh you you're sort of arcanoid style except you've got your your paddles and so
you're shooting the little uh demon ball around and trying to destroy them all and then you have
to the eyes on the background start blinking in red and you have to shoot the ball into one of
those eyeballs and as you go through it the face changes more and more to the style of a hanya mask
if you don't know what that is go look it up um where it gets more and more demonic as you know
well i'd say more like you know traditional ogre style masks like
like i said like a hanya and it's really well detailed and absolutely gorgeous the the shading
i mean it's for pixel art it's good artwork wouldn't you say yeah see and and and like in
the level it's on now like the face is getting more orange and it definitely looks a lot more
like the traditional hanya so i i absolutely love this game especially you know bringing in the
mythos of this particular one i i absolutely love it um so i will talk about um the others in the
series just a little bit because i think i have talked about alien crush before and devil's crush
i think i've done them both as a classic game um the other game that i mentioned is dragon's revenge
which is sort of like a genesis answer um it's not really as good the ball physics are
not great i mean it's it's it's an amusing play i'll put it that way but it isn't great but there
was a uh a we wear release uh updated version of alien crush called alien crush returns
and it was pretty neat i mean i'll probably talk about that as a classic game later
but you know this is just one in the series i mean every game that's in the official crush
series is absolutely worth playing and then if you want the modern take on it like we're saying
earlier um there is a uh a demon's tilt on steam it is also available uh on mac on steam absolutely
absolutely a good way to satisfy that uh that'll crush pinball uh craving if you get it
so that's what i'm gonna throw in there jackie crush if you get a chance to play it absolutely
do and if you do play it let me know because i wouldn't know what you think of it it's one of
one of my favorite uh virtual pinball games great there it is your classic game of the week uh jackie
crush uh and i gotta say you know i'm kind of with the chat like i knew of course about aliens
crush and devil's crush like those are very hard games to miss especially if you followed the
terrific 16 at all um and i'm sure i think i feel like you've probably mentioned this in passing
because i just know you love this series um but i've not really sit down and watched it and listened
to it before and it's pretty cool like i wonder how this one kind of got lost i guess maybe maybe
it came out and later in the super nintendo's life or something i don't know it was 92.
oh yeah weird i just feel like it didn't come out in the u.s compared to the others
i mean if you think about it this way it's a pinball game number one which is a little bit
more obvious you know a genre for for a video game true and it didn't see the light of day outside of
japan back in you know those days it was much harder to get those imports and then of course
by the time importing became the big thing that it is like i didn't buy my first import game until
like 95 yeah i take that back 94 my first import game that i bought was uh the sailor moon s
fighting game um which actually now uh gwen has it i think i think i sold it to gwen um but uh
but going back to it i mean importing was like when i imported my sailor moon game i did it
by literal magazine mail order cod oh my god yeah so um it it's it was a different
is a different world than for for you know importing and we didn't have you know
emulators at least that were as sophisticated as this in fact i didn't think i actually even
had my first emulated game until maybe the late 90s late late 90s so i mean this game
came out when i was in 10th grade it was that long ago but it's i i mean i i know that i have
certain games that are like oh yeah play it it's fun and something i'm really like you gotta play
i say if you really if you like the the first two crash games you absolutely owe it to yourself to
play this one because this is an excellent game it's a wonderful addition to the series and i
honestly would love for them to put out like a crush compilation that has that kind of like the
monster boy treatment remember where you can switch back and forth between the old mode and
like a new updated mode um and i think that that that would sell i would buy i would buy it or
where you can play the switch vertically i always thought that was really cool for the um pinball
simulators that do that yeah well i mean the wonders the wondrous one the wondrous one color
back in the day was set to be played vertical horizontally because a couple of the clindola
games worked that way and you know they could easily do that with the switch but
when when all right opportunities all right there it is your classic game of the week great pick
very very educational for the folks tonight especially if you like pinball fan or if you
like pinball at all or like pinball inspired um games you know of which there's there's been a few
uh through the years you know uh even things like pinball quest or i think of like you know the
translations like uh pinbot and high speed that were so weird on the nes because they did shit
that you can't actually do physically uh and then music yeah which the originals really didn't have
anything like that i i i thought that someone did a rom hack of pinbot to turn it into jackpot i'd
have to take a look for that but the thing the thing with these that are like this in particular
and this is where my point is going on this is that these were made solely they're not a
translation they're not a recreation like you know pinmame or uh or pinball effects or something like
that these are virtual pinball that is meant to be played in that kind of environment it's built
for a console and so you get an experience on a table like that that you cannot get at all unless
you have like again one of those you know uh uh pinmame cabinets that has you know that a game
would be programmed for something like that the closest we even have to i mean that would work
something like that would work if you had where it would just move the the tables back and forth you
know on a virtual screen something like that would work but you also then miss feeling the
ball i guess and being able to control your tilts and whatnot but that's actually one thing i have
to go back and say about demon's tilt is that it actually does have a pretty decent tilt function
in it so um but i i could i could go on about this all day but that's the thing that makes these
games special is that they were programmed this way this is their intent and they're so unique
in that that it it's you can be a fan of pinball you could be a fan of puzzle games i'd put it that
way too and this game is definitely a test of your hand-eye coordination and it's challenging
in a way that conventional pinball isn't well i don't know if you'd want to play this table in
real life those those demon faces are scary as fuck i'd run out of the building screaming
i don't know i don't think they're that scary but maybe if it was like bleeding all over the place
and yeah maybe all right great pick let's get into some other news uh rapid fire style with
some rapid fire news loki to go to go along with the announcement and release of earthbound on
the snes um nintendo online service uh you can actually download the nintendo strategy guide
the official strategy guide for the game for free that's right it's available on nintendo's
japanese website under their manuals for earthbound and thankfully though the strategy
guide is in english the player's guide but uh you can check it out it's a pretty awesome strategy i
remember getting a bunch of those back in the day when you know they were putting them out for
different games uh so let's check it out and then uh we have some more announcements for tmnt
shredder's revenge so there's a new playable character with splinter joining the roster along
with april and neil who was previously announced so that game looks pretty awesome and supposed
to come out later this year can't wait to check it out um dark tatsuya and mike dept in our chat
room both talking about the earthbound strategy guide being a part of the wii u release as well
i'd forgotten i did download that pdf like right away yeah that's that's still neat you know nice
little blast in the past i remember there's yeah i mean it's just nice to have yeah so let's move
on yeah so um well shakila neil and arcade one up is doing an nba jam shack edition arcade machine
so uh just in case we haven't had enough uh enough shack going on back in the day we have some new
shack um they are uh they had an announcement at shacks fun house which a concert experience in la
um this weekend um actually they made the announcement on friday but um he is uh gonna
be doing the uh he's actually uh gonna be playing the nba jam on that custom one up and so it will
be a 65.8 inches high uh which is taller than their existing nba jam with a 19-inch screen
wi-fi enabled and three playable games just nba jam nba jam tournament edition and nba hang time
and of course he was in the original nba jam with the orlando magic uh moving on uh cloud from final
fantasy 7 will be available in chocobo grand prix in their first season pass uh and uh have a 800
mithril login bonus oh my gosh this model is so freaking cute um like how can you be an adorable
chibi and still look that constipated seriously um but anyway um he is a season pass exclusive
so if you were playing that go for it
i just don't like that i'm hearing about 800 mithril season pass and i'm like oh god how much
you know games as a service crap are they loading into this because i was really looking forward to
this but i'm not looking forward to all these microtransactions is it a free-to-play game
oh is it oh i didn't know i thought i just assumed it was a purchase game
if it's free to play i guess it's a little less annoying i like i like it's having options like
the free-to-play mmos but if you pay the subscription and you get a few bells and whistles
you know something like that is perfectly acceptable no all right um let us travel around
the world and check out some games that are coming out probably sooner than chocobo gp
because they're coming out this week and we'll start in the us uh to clarify apparently chocobo
grand prix is going to be on the switch as a full game or they're going to have a free-to-play
version so cash tapes up huh that's interesting yeah interesting so neat uh anyways so for us
release dates we've got king let's see here uh river city girls zero on nintendo switch
yay dynasty warriors nine empires on pc nintendo switch playstation 4 playstation 5 xbox
1 and xbox series uh star wars the old republic legacy of the sith on pc
assassins creed the ezio collection on nintendo switch you mean ezio ezio ezio tomato tomato who
cares um get to fuma den undying moon on pc uh king of fighters 15 on pc playstation 4 playstation
5 and xbox series uh token rambu warriors on pc and nintendo switch total war warhammer 3 on pc
mac and linux and see voice of cards the forsaken maiden i almost read that as the forsaken madden
uh that's on nintendo switch and playstation 4 and last but not least horizon forbidden west
on playstation 4 and playstation 5 that's it all right going over to japan and looking at the
releases there on the nintendo switch this week um that same token rambu muso warriors uh is out
in japan this week as is assassins creed the ezio collection is also out and uh a game called the
table game deluxe pack is also out on the switch to japan and uh looking at it it's
kind of just your generic board game collection but you know things are also a little more
regionalized to japan uh and not just uh americanized stuff that you would see in a game
like clubhouse games or something like that um hopping over to the playstation 5 excuse me king
of fighters 15 is out on the playstation 5 this week uh and uh japan also gets horizon forbidden
west on the 18th uh in regular regalia special collectors all those different types of special
editions so um pick your pick pick how much you want to spend on the game uh with all the extra
stuff in it and that is your japanese release dates how about the uk dart sakura on the 17th
we have king of fighters 15 for playstation and xbox we have uh i think for pc total war warhammer
3 day one edition on switch we have assassins creed ezio collection um also on the 17th and
then on the 18th we have horizon forbidden west on playstation and that is it we have a lot of
common threads all throughout the world this week so busy week all right let's get into some more
stories and then we'll be taking your questions and your calls um i know the live turnout is a
little lighter tonight can't imagine why uh but we'll get to those that want to um uh participate
further with the show in our listener round table in a little bit uh but first loki it take to be
working on a new midnight club game some people like to think so because the developer visual
concepts who has worked on the nba 2k and wwe 2k series they are recruiting for an open world
driving game and immediately everyone thinks midnight club because you know rockstar has
that and stuff the work could be a new ip we don't know but there is a new driving game coming from
take two so we'll just have to see what it is at some point will it be midnight club who knows
how would you feel about a new midnight club it's not rockstar working on it i'm kind of
disappointed with that but meh whatever it's been a long time yeah it's been a while so i i
want i don't want to see some video see it in motion see what it looks like all right yeah
definitely dark sakura so uh there is a series that i i would probably say a lot of uh people
who are into import games especially dating sims know very well um tokimeki memorial which is uh
konami's a big dating sim it was the big one that everyone knew about um so there is an independent
uh retro game translator known as retro translator that um has uh his team working uh has sorry their
their team working on translating uh one of the tokimeki memorial games into english and it's
almost complete but here is uh the thing it is not uh tokimeki memorial forever with me which
is like the playstation one the one that everybody likes it was the one that was like the best
improved of them it's the snes one or the super famicom one uh which is uh tokimeki memorial
which translates to heartthrob memorial under the tree of legends you know i actually have
the tokimeki memorial oav on laserdisc um but it's it this is the big game i think that brought
dating sims to the fore like i mean they were already kind of big in in japan um and the i'm
sorry it's not forever with me it's forever with you um it was actually the upgraded version from
the pc engine super cd rom one the turbo graphic cd the snes one came out after the playstation one
and uh it didn't have any voice acting of course because it was this mess and it was just like
really watered down um so this is this is this is a toki memo that is just really not the one
that everyone wanted of course you know i think it would be easier to do a translate a translated
copy of the the snus one which for the record several already exist just saying um i yeah
um on top of that too you know some other people are like well why not do uh toki memo pocket you
know the one of the uh uh you know a handheld one to bring with it but at the same time you know
it is what it is for some people this is going to be the way that people start off with toki memo
um i personally would uh would like to see a translation uh an official release of uh
toki memo girl side where basically you play one of the female characters dating the boys
you know which as i was i thought it was pretty cool that you know in all of the world of boy
date girl you know dating sim thing they did in the toki memo series they did one where the girls
can go after the boys um i mean now of course we have a slew of you know various different
options for for dating sims including the very popular uh boyfriend dungeon and uh dream daddy
and uh uh the colonel sanders game which i still need to play blink blink but i i think
i'm glad i'm glad it's being done i'm not trying to to uh poopoo on the attempt it's just there's
better toki memo games to do the playstation one would have been absolutely astounding to have
just even the japanese voice acting is fine you know but have it translated into english you get
an authentic experience but in dialogue that you know that a westerner can understand
i'm sure also just i think you kind of addressed it just the tools kind of being easier and a
little more accessible for the super nintendo probably made it the one that was just like
the easier one to translate maybe so but hey making the game available for more people to
try out but like you said i guess translations already exist so but well there there are a few
other um fan translations that are coming out sort of a quote officially uh one of them is uh there
was a japanese exclusive yakuza game that came out on psp um that's called uh yakuza black panther in
english or uh i'm gonna mispronounce this uh um which yeah because a black panther um and then
uh another game called uh miser uh miserna falls so it's a ps1 game that where you can pet a dog
apparently that's uh that's getting a fan translation too um i also thought it was very
interesting that there's a fan translation out for uh the biohazard uh 1.5 almost a fully playable
version so pretty cool what a lot of like you know modders and translators are doing to make
more of these games playable by more people around the world pretty cool power of boredom and wanting
to play a game yeah well meanwhile while these folks work on new technologies and new things
that are great for games we have other big companies doing the exact opposite right loki
yes it's your weekly disappointment in the game industry your depression if you will of
the future that is coming the unwanted nft future that ubisoft is just running full speed ahead
into a wall with um so apparently one of the things that ubisoft is doing is they're
collaborating with the sandbox which is a game if you will um that's more of like a virtual space
that you can buy real estate in and walk around with avatar it basically looks like playstation
home if they monetize the crap out of it and made it blockchain made it stupid um so that's kind of
what that is and of course ubisoft's like yep sign me up for that uh so they've brought the
rabbits to it because everybody needs that um and then of course you know ubisoft employees
are still telling um their you know higher ups that nft suck and that they really shouldn't be
in that business um you know one of the there's some fun comments from the ubisoft employees like
are we competing with ea for the most hated game studio by the public uh because this is how you do
it i think the kids call this entire comment session um being ratioed um you know what else
makes a lot of money uh making fun spectacular groundbreaking blockbusters why don't we focus
on that instead you know what else is great in the company not sexually harassing your employees
but hey you know ubisoft gonna ubisoft so what can you do they just just play by some different
rules that's all you know if they could meant sexual harassment into the blockchain i'm sure
they would try to do that as well uh uh as she 100 matt and chad says i love that ubisoft's
internal employee forum was filled of employees dunking on the company's stance on nfts hey
that's why and you know shout out to those frontline employees at ubisoft that are fighting
the good fight on the inside because you know we've said this time and time again these stupid
decisions are never the fault of the hard-working you know frontline creators of these games it's
always some dumb fuck executive who shouldn't even be in this business uh who's making these calls and
it's it's very apparently clear with what you see with what's going on at ubisoft and uh good on
them for ray showing uh these these stupid things that people don't want um if yeah anyway um and
then of course a little bit more details regarding the whole team 17 worms nft announcement thing
that we kind of talked about i think last week um talking about how basically the employees
had no idea that this was even happening aside from the higher ups um you know and the qa
developers of course at team 17 are really not paid very well between 20 000 25 000 annually
and while they're yeah and so while they're struggling to pay bills you know there is
people that um they're going out there and trying to make a few extra bucks off of some
of their assets from the company so obviously um that's not a good look so wow yeah all right
uh well uh let's hope these ubisoft executives i get put in their place real soon and stop driving
the company in this direction or they're going to just drive them right out of business
um for our last uh official story tonight i thought this was a fun one to go out on uh
the fact that uh maim uh known as the multiple arcade machine emulator is what maim stands for
uh just turned 25 years old uh believe it or not its debut was the feb February 5th of 1997
if you've never heard of maim that's kind of surprising uh it's an emulator that runs all
sorts of old um arcade emulation uh and a lot of a lot of stuff than throughout the years i remember
i mean i'm dating myself obviously but whatever i remember being around when maim kind of first came
out and it was a lot of the really old like namco boards and atari boards where they first started
but then obviously you know maim started to get into you know newer and newer stuff when they
started getting stuff like street fighter 2 and uh mortal combat and then you know even beyond that
uh it really became its own thing and of course i wish that they could still do the hikaru
software that would have been amazing uh of course maim does state on the official maim website their
purpose is to preserve decades of software history uh and maim prevents important vintage software
from being lost and forgotten uh achieved by documenting the hardware and how it functions
the source code to maim serves as this documentation so um yeah again you know a lot
of people might jump to oh these bad things you know maim leads to piracy and all that but
you know again there's a lot of rights and a lot of things that get lost out there throughout the
years also games are just not available i mean like where are you going to find like it it's
like if you want a certain type i mean granted they have you know arcade went up for a lot of
things but there's a lot of games that are very obscure out there that good luck finding hardware
for that and some old creators from the 80s uh made public domain their roms basically who had
the right rights and license to do so and were like yeah maim's pretty cool and so you can uh
distribute this however much you want so there are there are there is a set i don't know how
many games are uh technically public domain but there's a set of you know at least 10 games
probably more at this point it's been a while since i've looked that are absolutely free to
get maim and use them and have fun with it and experience some old arcade games
and then what also was interesting about this uh the 2021 release capcom arcade stadium which is
relatively i have that on the switch apparently it was using code from maim in it so not a huge
surprise i'm sure uh interesting how that's come full circle the surprise was they actually
credited them which is nice yeah that is true yeah that is nice so but also apartment just being a
nice gesture it also does sort of cover their tail legally right because i remember i feel
like there was something that didn't do that and it became it was oh yeah yeah no i thought there
was something that's obs yes but i thought there was something involving maim too but yeah that
was a kind of an adjacent issue for sure yeah it's the same thing you know if they had they
weren't supposed to use obs in the name or they were supposed to credit or something and none of
that happened uh dart to see is talking about the public domain games talking about robbie
roto off the top of my head but there's a few others yeah i think that's the one um they
released that uh on like the of the phone stores and uh that's the it was a full running copy of
maim that they and you were able to load it basically on your um uh devices and play games
that way that's how i have uh on my ipad my old ass ipad at this point uh a version of maim
basically is uh from from that being available for like a week uh but orange right says maim
preserves so many games that we would have never heard of absolutely uh dart says uh capcom arts
arcade stadium has its issues but i do fire it up now and then for some classic arcade fun yeah
it's it's like everything else i've talked about when they do like legal versions especially when
they you know enhance it a little bit which you know capcom arcade stadium has like the achievements
the online leaderboards you know they they some different graphical ways of looking at it they
tried to sweeten the pot a little bit i supported it because i like retro gaming it's fun and i like
when the companies dip into their back catalogs i wish there would be another midway arcade treasures
collections there's some really good stuff in there but um we haven't seen those releases in
a very long time so holy crap hmm ivan reitman died oh gosh yeah i i i just saw the the posting
about it from associated press it's like just now huh well i didn't mean to derail everything with
it but uh but yeah wow no that's fine wow all right time to watch ghostbusters yeah gosh okay
uh moving on let's get to our listener round table uh we invite your uh emails at participate
orange lounge radio.com and i think i saw one come in uh we do have one so let's get to it let's get
to our emails first so it's one email and you'll know who it is email singular and you'll know who
it is the moment i start reading it you ready hello lr hi it's been a while but i've been
listening to the podcast for just about this whole time congratulations rob to you and alan on the
new place i'm looking forward to seeing the new studio smiley face rob you were right we you did
in fact release in november of 2012 when it launched with a really really fun tech demo
a 2d mario game and a bunch of third-party games that would most likely uh already played on other
platforms i would argue that the unexciting launch lineup and the many long stretches between big
game releases did as much to hurt the wii u as its awful name i kept defending that name you
know that and i still kind of defend it um despite this i do still actively have mine hooked up
primarily for don't laugh at me we fit you that now that name is funny i'm just saying no i i and
i wouldn't laugh at that either i mean it was a great fitness title right yeah i know i know a
lot of people have kind of graduated for lack of a better term to ring fit but i also know it's a
different like ring fit and we fit you are are very different games so um no i don't i don't
fault you i'm not gonna laugh at you for keeping that hooked up and i um and i have a hard time
believing that switch sports will top we sports club but i guess we'll see soon enough i was
delighted that wolfenstein 3d was mentioned during the classic game of the week segment recently
i was also happy to hear that both the mac version and the modding community were mentioned you
probably already know this if you watched my yyr game's 10th anniversary retrospective videos but
only a handful of people did so i'll tell you that i was a member of wolf addict software the largest
modding group for the mac version during the mid to late 90s 1990s we actually sold several scenarios
created by our members including new levels graphics audio and more because the mac version
of wolf 3d came out later it featured higher resolution graphics and an engine capable
of more things than the original it was super fun to be a part of this but what's really surprising
is that there is currently an ongoing effort to bring the mac wolfenstein 3d mods back to modern
systems it's called mac and wolf and i highly recommend that you google it if you are interested
in checking out some vintage classic gameplay that's m a c e n wolf have fun everyone i'll end
on this note i am normally an optimist so um and i would normally never cast doubt on something
i truly love but i am sorry to say that unless olr moves to a more frequent broadcast schedule
it will never reach episode 9000 with its current hosts well that is unless you're good to go for
another 156 years or more if you miss more than a few weeks um i'm sorry to have to deliver the
bad news but honestly thank you for another week of this show that we all enjoy so much and enjoy
your week off looking forward to whatever is next erin yyr well you know we can number these
episodes however the fuck we want to so when we numbering is arbitrary when we want to do episode
9000 we will well you know and and you know um there's another podcast out there um gamertag
radio who crossed a thousand episodes even though um they started two three years after we did sorry
i don't know the exact day is not i'm certainly not here to shade anybody there's a lot of work
that went into that um danny and the crew over there work very hard on what they do um but they
also put out multiple episodes a week and i think during e3 a lot of episodes like usually like
historically so um they were kind of able to and so a lot of people assume that that is the longest
running show because they have more episodes um we could have there was a time when i was uh
clipping up some of you may remember this some of you longtime listeners where i was clipping up
olr and i was putting out the first half on the feed on like monday and the second half on like
wednesday to try to kind of fill the week but the big feedback i got after about a year was like
stop doing that we just want to listen to it all in one you know go and i did kind of go like why
am i doing that but it's funny because you know maybe if i counted those as separate episodes
we would have hit a thousand by now but i'm not out to yuck somebody's yum like it's just you know
it is what it is we've done a we've done a weekly thing and and uh pissing in the cornflakes exactly
exactly so um but uh if but i guess my point is aaron if you do want us to hit uh 9 000 episodes
i guess i could start uh chopping up the show into five minute chunks and releasing those all
as separate episodes but i'm not sure what the podcast folks would think about that so uh pod
culture says there was also olr to go the interesting thing about that is that um before
the shows merged so our live show in the podcast merged around episode 180 i want to say question
mark it's probably on the wiki somewhere so yeah technically there were 50 episodes or so of the
show that weren't like counted accounted for somewhere else but i think there would be other
people that would argue well the shows that weren't actually a podcast that we did on live
365 shouldn't be counted and i i beg to differ because they exist and we've been doing them but
again it's just it's it's arbitrary just like dark soccer said it's all in what you choose to
do and how you want to do it so uh as 200 matt says each story is an episode you'll hit 9000
no problem uh and yes dark to see absolutely he just wants the chance to make the over 9000 joke
absolutely um you know what one of these days over 9000 words spoken that's right
so where are we on that uh uh the guinness thing i already they they sent it back remember oh
because we have to do it as a as a company i didn't resubmit because i we need to have uh the
like some sort of company way to do it i think we could probably submit it under vog network but i
think there'd be a charge with that so we'd have to figure that out there's there's still going to
be a free when the charge comes if you want the accelerated application oh okay um maybe we can
do that then i'm i've got to dig into it but i've had real life stuff going on too so it might my
health issues have taken priority because i'm still dealing with that whole uh narcolepsy
diagnosis crap all right uh yeah pod culture i remember that we'd record pod culture in a chunk
and i'd chop it up yeah and it just you know it just is all depends on how you want to do it no
no biggie all right um let's see uh let me i didn't check discord to see if we had any callers over
there if you want to give us a call you can just head on over to vog network.com discord and join
our green room uh nobody's there now and i know we just we just have a smaller turnout live tonight
because of things that are going on on television even though my understanding is it's over now
but i'm sure folks are still with their you know friends family and people they hang out with on
days like today so it's probably just going to be more of a podcast heavy week and that's okay too
we love our podcast audience feel free to say hi to us either on social media like twitter's
a great place to say hi at olr uh and of course the email bag as well like aaron did this week
participate at orange lounge radio.com is the place to send us an email uh let me check in
with loki and see if there's any last minute stories yes there is one so there's a game coming
out called martha is dead um it's coming out on pc playstation and saw this on discord yeah
so on the playstation version they're actually censoring the game uh because there's a very
sensitive scene that's being depicted in the game um spoilers they cut off someone's face and then
put it on um so that apparently is not going to be on the playstation five and playstation
four versions um but the other versions will be just fine this game sounds like a bit much for me
yeah it sounds like that said though like they had really violent stuff though in like last of
us two and stuff so like did they cut off someone's face i don't know i didn't play last
wasn't there also something about like the sister
it's there was something like really weird sounding and i was just like this game isn't
for me that's all i was i read it i was like this game isn't for me um sj100 matt in chat says people
are so mad about this well then don't buy it on playstation yeah it's like it's pretty simple um
sia tabirian chat says it's not as if they were renaming at martha's badly maimed uh fifth dream
says oh it's your sister's face that's gross what a weird game but what i hey y'all are into whatever
you're into enjoy your horror porn if that's your thing i will be watching over here off once
already so it's it's all good i think that was a little different all right uh if there's no other
last minute stories then i think we will move to close up shop tonight i know it's a little
bit earlier we still broke two hours but um it is what it is so uh let's go around and wrap things
up uh first let me say thank you uh of course for listening to orange launch radio this week
whether you were here live or on our podcast feed we appreciate you being here thank you so much for
being a part of our show um don't forget emails are great and uh joining our discord throughout
for the conversation throughout the week is also great as well vog network.com discord if you
enjoyed what you heard here tell a friend about the show help us spread the word because we are
the show where every gamer has a voice but we need more voices here to diversify all the opinions
so a nice five-star review um or a shareable link wherever you're listening to this podcast be it
itunes spotify google podcast whatever it is uh please share the link spread the word uh appreciate
that as well um i think that's all i've got to say here so i'm gonna go to final thoughts
and dark sakura i'm sure you're getting an early start to uh miss debbie delight tonight so
we'll go to you first your final thoughts it would be nice to to be done with debbie a little
earlier tonight than usual because i always do three hours um but i i've really missed my retro
gaming and i'm glad to have a chance to get back into it so um if anyone has a suggestion for
something that they'd want to see me play um apart from the legend of zelda you know let me know hit
me up tell me if you think i should play something i'll give it a go sounds good easy not easy i'm
easy in the video game sense all right also my house smells like chicken have a good stream
tonight dark sagra we'll see you in two weeks all right you're the ends all right and uh we'll go to
loki your final thought tonight i keep saying i need to get in the streaming i need to get back
in the streaming yes you should yes you should all right uh and for my final thought tonight i
guess i'll i'll change the shot here and you may see some unsightly things in the shot oh no it's
still pretty in pretty decent shape here but uh there it is uh the studio and uh the last hurrah
from this particular studio that served us well um over these last few years about seven years
uh thank you all for being a part of it whether uh you've been here on twitch uh as we made the
transition to go to video on twitch or whether you were here through the uh um uh shoutcast
years as well because this place was really only set up to do audio uh but we've seen all the
changes and so forth as well so a big farewell to studio and seven i am really looking forward
to the future though i appreciate everyone's support as we get there uh i know uh some people
really want us to all be back in person uh it's just one of those things we'll have to play by ear
because again the new space is going to be a little weird for that especially with twitch
um but we'll see i think we're still having fun here um the way we're doing things i really can't
wait to be in the next space though and i'm really excited to share it all with you um so i'll see
you in two weeks if not maybe a little sooner on my personal feed we'll see maybe maybe but no
promises so have a great week two weeks everybody we'll see you next time here on orange lounge radio
good night you've been listening to orange lounge radio orange lounge radio is a production of
olr studios to join us for a live show tune into fog network.com sunday nights at 6 p.m pacific
9 p.m eastern the views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those
of the staff of orange lounge radio or vog network but you know they were all still true
see you next week
you