Orange, Lounge, Radio
With your hosts, Dark Sakura, Sky, and Loco
Tonight, October 19th, 2008
LittleBigPlanet generates some big controversy
Download content comes to SoulCalibur 4 that will surprise no one
And could Marvel vs. Capcom 2 soon be re-released?
Orange, Lounge, Radio
I'm sorry to hear that
I guess we'll have some good rants tonight
Careful Chat
I didn't do it, did I?
You love me, right?
It's groups of people
Maybe we'll catch on a little bit about what's going on later
If I don't feel better about it by then
Alright, we'll see
Also, say hello to the one and only Loki
Hello
How are you, Techmaster? Loki?
I'm fine
Are you having a good week?
Yes
Are you mad at certain groups of people too?
Maybe
You're perpetually mad at somebody
No, I'm just kidding
Alright, I feel fine
I'm having a good week
I'm not really mad at anybody
Well, I guess that's a lie
I'm mad at some people
But I look past it
For the sake of the show
Where we talk about just the games
And kick them back and have a little bit of fun
And in order to talk about the games
We gotta talk about our gaming weeks
And what we've been doing lately
If you want to join us
chat.orangelandradio.com
Is where we are reading comments from you guys
In our chat room
On this lovely Sunday evening
As we always do when we tape live
Alright, let's start off
DarkSakura
How was your gaming week?
I played Rock Band 2 and Ragnarok Online
How was Rock Band 2?
It was very good
Yeah?
What is your instrument of preference in Rock Band 2?
I don't have one
You like to play a little bit of everything?
I really don't prefer to play
Oh, you like to watch?
No, my shoulder hurt
And I was in a lot of pain
So they made me play bass on a song
Gotcha
Alright, well, hey
How did you like it compared to the first one?
I saw no difference
It's more Rock Band
Yeah, more
Hey, if it ain't broke, don't fix it, right?
More songs, I mean, that was okay
But, you know, I wasn't
It wasn't anything to be impressed or
Displeased over
It was just more Rock Band
Alright
Well, if there's nothing else
Then we'll move on to Loki
How was your gaming week?
Hi
Oh, the clothes in it suck
Better Barbie mode in the first game
Alright, Loki, how was your gaming week?
Well, they actually still have some of the same
Clothes from the first game and the second game
Didn't really add that much
The GWAR outfits were kind of neat
Let's see, this week I played
Singing Zero 2, actually
I'm thinking about
Almost 50% done with the game
It says I'm only like 37%
Or maybe it's 47% done
Basically, I've gone through two of the gangs already
I've finished the Brotherhood and the Son of Samedi
And
That was a weird gang
And then finally now I'm starting to run in a little bit
And
I don't know, it's pretty cool
I still think, though, out of the three gangs so far
The Brotherhood have been
I think that storyline was the most brutal that was in it
Played a little bit of the multiplayer
And they actually have a game mode
That's pretty awesome
It kind of mixes up
Different modes of the single player game
Some of the activities it can do with multiplayer
So basically it's team based
You start off and you have about a minute
That's just pure deathmatch
And then an activity will start
So the first game I played, there was a mayhem activity
So basically
You have to go and destroy as many things as possible
Just the environment, cars, other people, etc.
And so we did that
And then after about, say, five minutes or so
The activity stops
And then there's a break in between it
Like another minute where it's just a deathmatch
And then a new activity will start
And then the new activity, I think, was insurance fraud
So we had to throw ourselves in front of cars and stuff like that
Or you can hit your own teammates and you get points for that
But all along, while this is going on
There's also different tags you can spray paint
To give your teams different abilities
Like double damage or double money for killing other gang members
Or a smokescreen, stuff like that
So really cool gameplay
The actual deathmatch mode's pretty fun
Doing some of that
I like the shopping mall level that they have
That's kind of fun to play around in
And then, what else did I play?
I got a random off-the-wall question for you about Saints Row 2
I know we have a news story coming up later on
About some of the controversy this game is generating
Which game do you think is more violent
And has more potential for controversy?
This game or Grand Theft Auto?
Seeing as they're very similar and appeal to the same audience
Maybe this game a little bit
Because they don't really get into
I mean, there's corrupt police in Grand Theft Auto 4
In this game you can actually dress up or impersonate a cop
In this fictional cops type show
Called, I forget what it's called now
But it's, oh, The Fuzz
That's what the show's called
And you basically go around beating up
Like Hot Fuzz?
Yes
You go around beating up people dressed up as cops
While they're filming it and stuff
And it's one of the activities
Unless there's a level where you break into a police station
Do a bunch of stuff like that
If anything, I'd say Grand Theft Auto San Andreas
I think was more
Kind of showing cops in a bad light
But both games, I mean, the kill count
As far as police officers go
Is going to be pretty high
I would think if anything Grand Theft Auto
Might be a little bit higher just because
You don't really have gang members chasing after you
In Grand Theft Auto, it's mainly just the police
Whereas in Saints Row, you have gang members
And the police chasing after you
So, you know, just out of sheer numbers
I think Grand Theft Auto 4, probably the percentage
Of police officers killed would be a lot larger
You know, I'm somehow not surprised by that answer
Because I would think if I'm the designers
Behind Saints Row 2
And I want to kind of break through that
You know, ceiling that Grand Theft Auto
Has kind of put out there where, you know, Grand Theft Auto
Is the creme de la creme of these sandbox games
You know, it's by far and wide the most popular
I'm not surprised if I'm the developers of Saints Row 2
And the people behind this game
I know one of the best ways I'm going to get at
And get close to that number is to one up
The controversy they're doing
Because that's half the reason why Grand Theft Auto sells
God, people need to understand
It's fiction, it's not like
I go and go shoot the cops in the game
Because I wish I could go shoot real cops
I mean, that's not what happens
It's just the opposition
It could be Nazis running this entire city
And it doesn't matter
If, you know, they're still coming after you
Well, it's funny
That you mention that, you know, this might seem completely random
But it is related, you know, I was at the movies
The other day and they were showing that little
What's that thing they do before? Like, you know how they play commercials
Like 20 minutes while people walk in
Okay, whatever it's called, the 20
Well, I was only like half watching and I was kind of distracted
Talking to somebody else and I look at the screen and go
Oh, what's this movie? This looks neat
And then, like, I saw some guy that looked like they were on fire
And I'm like, wow, I'm kind of surprised I can show that in a trailer
It was Fable 2
Like, I thought it was like an actual movie coming out
But it was a Fable 2 commercial
Yeah
I mean, games are getting...
They've come a long way since combat, let's put it that way
But, yeah, I mean, it's just if
Yeah, if you want to look at it like it's realistic
Or something like that, then yeah, okay, sure
I guess it's offensive to cops or something
But you have to understand, games aren't meant to be
A simulation for real life
I mean, granted, you can make a game that's like
A simulation of real life
If you want, but then again, you can also make
Pure fiction that's just way over the top
Which is what Saints Row and Grand Theft Auto are doing
You know, to an extent
And Grand Theft Auto is a little bit more grounded
But still, it's pretty over the top
I don't know
It's just
You can find controversy anywhere
And then, the other game I've played
Which also has controversy, I guess, involved with it
Would be Little Big Planet
And Little Big Planet is amazing
That's easy to say
I mean, it's just an amazing game
The fact, from the very beginning of the game
Even through the title credits sequence
Which I might add is all in-game engine
It's just incredible
It's just all of the stuff that was actually
In the game was made with the creator
In the game
So, you know, just going through
Each of the levels of stuff in there
They kind of have a basic tutorial
To walk you through of how to play the game
As time goes on
And then
Each level, they actually have a storyline
That continues on
And it's really, really cool
Mildly offensive, but really, really cool
I think some of the levels are
As we were talking about during the break
They're characters of
Different sections of the world
So, like, the African level
Is all like
Think Lion King, basically
Whereas the
British level
Is the
British levels
Are all knights in castles
And that kind of thing
So it's a little bit racist
But in the way that it's a small world
Is racist, where no one's gonna possibly be offended
Because it's so damn cute
It's incredibly cute
Now, my thing with Sony, if they were smart
This sucker would be
In the next bundle that they're doing
This would be a bundle that's out
This holiday
They need to be bundling this game with the system
Because I'm telling you, this game will sell systems
Easy. You just get this out
People are gonna look at this and they're like
Oh my god, you know, that's just an amazing game
It's way more amazing than Wii Sports
And I think it's gonna appeal to everybody
Game of the year?
It could definitely be a contender
For game of the year
Anything else in your gaming week this week?
Umm
No.
I hate to take it back to Saints Row because you talk about that game an awful lot
But, a good question from chatroom
At chat.orangesonsrady.com
First chat comment of the night goes to C-more Booty
Since you guys are talking about Saints Row 2
Are you having any problems with crashing or freezing
In the game? It crashes my system every time
I try to save manually
Umm, not really
I've had it lock up a few times
But it's just random
I mean, it's just like any other game
It's...
You know, I haven't really had any problems saving manually
Because I do it all the time
I want to quit or something
At that time
No, not really any problems with it
Alright
My gaming week, not a lot of new stuff this week
Sadly, I'm sorry to disappoint
But I've had a lot going on in my personal life
But I will say this, the new WoW 3.0 patch came out this week
Of course WoW being World of Warcraft
Had a huge content upgrade this week
And you guys know I'm the resident Warcraft addict
On staff here
Just having a lot of fun with that
There's been a lot of new things added into the game
With regards to talents
I don't know how much I mentioned this on the show
But I play a balanced druid as my main character
And so our class really got a lot of love
We have some new talents that are just awesome
I was using Starfall and PvP today and it's great
And one of my favorite new talents is something called Typhoon
Where when you click it, it's like this big blue sploosh
That goes across the screen and everybody gets knocked back
So it's kind of awesome to use
That and PvP around the world
So, achievements as well have finally
Come to World of Warcraft and a lot of time
Kind of spent getting the achievements and new titles
To come with them
One of the first things my guild did as soon as the patch went live
Probably about an hour of the patch going live
We went back to Ubers and the old WoW content
And got ourselves the Jenkins title
Because you can now, you know
WoW has this funny way of working in pop culture references
About WoW into WoW
And this whole Leroy Jenkins thing
Is now Leroy is an achievement
And if you get that achievement you can have Jenkins as your title
So that you're like, you know, if your character name is
Sky
You would be Sky Jenkins
Which is kind of funny
So there you go
Other than Warcraft and experiencing the new patch
I actually, I took a trip
And you folks that have been listening to the show for a long time
Since we were about music games will appreciate this
And you guys here in studio
I went to Milpitas Golf Land this week
I went to good old Miggle
It's changed a lot
Since, you know, I hadn't been there in quite a few years
Last time I was there I think they still had Derby Owners Club
Which is now at our Miggle
And at Milpitas Golf Land
You know, you have to remember
This is like the holy land of
BeatMania and the Bobani
Between Milpitas and Sunnyvale Golf Land
You know, these were
I guess you could say Arcade Infinity to an extent
It was like the trinity of California
Northern California
Well, Arcade Infinity is southern technically
You know what I mean though
It's like one of the west coast hubs
Of where DDR got big
And it's interesting to see, you know how
Milpitas
Used to have DDR in one of the rooms
That room, it's like two rooms
This arcade is like two separate buildings
One building now is nothing but ticket games
Like I remember when we were first
Going there, like half of it was ticket redemption
It was slowly spreading, well now it is
Nothing but ticket redemption in one room
But it's interesting because they've turned the other room into
You know, like all the music
Games are on one wall
Then all the driving games are over here
And all the fighting games are over here
So it's kind of like you have just different little sections
It was kind of interesting, but I did play
I played Midnight Maximum Tune 3
And I played Keyboard Mania
Even though it was sticking on the keyboard
But a new game I played, Dance Dance Revolution
Supernova 2, it's been out this whole time
And I have not yet played it in arcades
And it was really the same damn thing as the last game
There wasn't much difference
Just some new songs, yippee
And some little flashy graphics when you get combos
Forgot to let you know
This is totally local news
Remember that one store that we went to
That's right there by the Folsom Theater
The Gamer's Empire, whatever
They got a Supernova machine now
Oh, nice
It's untouched, you know, basically
Nice, well this is the other thing that surprised me
Miggle is selling their DDR Extreme machine
They have a little sign on it that says
For Sale, guess how much they want for this
Miggle machine, DDR Extreme machine
As is
$12,000
No, a little high, very high in fact
It's a used machine, no much higher
$8,000
A little lower
$7,000
$6,000 is what they want for this machine
$5,999 to be exact
If you can take the machine, retrofit it
And upgrade it, I mean
That's always interesting
So that was it, and then I actually played miniature golf
Which in all the times I've ever been to Milpitas Golf Line
I never have played miniature golf there
But I did this time
So there you go
Miniature golf, the real game
That's it, not a lot of whole other console games I've been playing
Just, you know, experiencing wow this week
And, you know, some of the same old console stuff I've been playing
Like Rock Band and all that, good stuff
Alright, let's get into some housekeeping real quick
It is episode number 299 tonight
Which means next week is episode number 300
If you can believe it
And what we want you guys to do is
We want you to leave your messages for us
We're going to play them during next week's commercial break
If you want to say a few words about Orange Launch Radio
Just try to keep it a minute or less
You can call the Skype line anytime when we're not live
Don't call right now if you're listening live on Sunday night
But if you're listening to this in the podcast format
Give 1-877-GAME-OLR a call
And leave us a message about
What you think about us making episode 300
And we'll play it on the break next week
Otherwise, it's going to be a good old fashioned show
You never know what kind of guest might show up
Also, we have some games planned for next week
It'll be a good time, there you have it
Yeah, and something that
Loki has a huge surprise, we'll say that
We'll say that much, Loki has a huge surprise
And let's see, what else do we have coming up?
If you've been listening to the show this year
You know I've had some medical issues going on
I'm going to be having surgery right after episode 300
So we probably won't be having a show the next week
So we might have a little bit of a break after episode 300
We'll have more details on that next week, that's all
So we'll talk about that
And don't worry, the surgery is nothing major
It's gallbladder surgery, a million people have had it done
I'm not that worried about it
I just kind of want to get it over with at this point
So, that's it for housekeeping
Visit our MySpace, visit our Facebook
Visit our live journal, our Twitter
Let's get into tonight's gaming news
Loki, start us off
Yes, anyways
So, this is kind of interesting
Not too surprising because they haven't been doing well financially for a while now
But Infogrames has finally now finished purchasing Atari
They made an $11 million stock purchase of Atari
And previously they had owned 51.4%
But now they are done with the purchase
And we'll see where they take it
Hopefully in the right direction
And not, I don't know, into the red again
This is the same company that brought us the Epic 2600
And my how times have changed, right?
This is kind of, I don't know, kind of sad in a way
But you kind of saw it coming
Because what has Atari done in the past five years
That's been really huge
Besides maybe their flashback consoles
Which are really cool, actually
Dragon Ball Z
I guess, alright
But, I don't know, in a way it's kind of the end of an era
Did I say error?
No, I'm thinking of something else
The end of an era, you know what I mean?
So, it's kind of sad, but there you go
Hey, LittleBigPlanet has been stirring up a lot of talk this week
And one thing that's got people talking about LittleBigPlanet
Is the new license agreement that Sony has
Sony actually recently changed the PlayStation Network terms of use
And basically to make a long story short
Long story short
Sony says now in the user license agreement
You also authorize us and our affiliated companies without payment to you
To license, sell, and otherwise commercially exploit your user material
So if you don't like it, don't use it
If you create a LittleBigPlanet level in the game
And Sony decides they're going to sell it on a compilation later on
Like maybe a best of for people that don't have online access
As I could possibly see forthcoming depending on how big this game is
Too bad you're not getting any money for it
And if you don't like it, don't play the game
You know, I like how they actually have exploit in there
An interesting word
I will rape your mother!
What? I don't know
I don't think that'll be a LittleBigPlanet level
Could be
It's kind of not surprising
I know a lot of people are looking at this as a
Oh my gosh, Sony is so big, bad, and evil corporate
But is it really that surprising in a way?
No
Not really
I would hope that they still give you credit for it at least
Or say, hey, you know, it's going to be in here
At least send you a free copy of the game, shit
That's the least they could do
I mean a lot of people would probably be like, hell yeah, go ahead and put it in there
I mean, I don't think they
I don't know, I would be like
Hell yeah, go ahead and put that in there, just give me credit
But if you don't like it, you don't like it, don't use it
Don't play the game
I guess, I mean
I don't know, if you were really expecting to profit off LittleBigPlanet
I think you might be playing the game for the wrong reasons, right?
Yeah
I don't know
Anyhow, we'll see how Sony plans to exploit user-created levels pretty soon
Well, moving on to
I don't know if this
Well, exploitation just really isn't the best word for this
I call it hypocrisy
But, you know, as we discussed with Bobby earlier
Speaking of which
This is
LittleBigPlanet is being recalled
Because of religious content within the game
And technically, what it is
Is two expressions from the Quran
Have made it into the game by means of a song that was licensed to be in the game
That came out a few years ago
And one person in the beta found it
And apparently took offense to its presence
And therefore wrote a letter to Sony
Which I have right here
Because I love pulling up, you know
Archived content off of message boards after posts have been deleted for days
And I'm not even going to bother pronouncing any of the Arabic
Because I can't
We'll play the clip in a little bit
Well, this is to Sony Computer Entertainment and Media Molecule
While playing your latest game LittleBigPlanet
In the first level of the third world in the game titled Swinging Safari Smiley Wink
I've noticed something strange in the lyrics of the music track of the level
When I listened carefully
I hit the fair by accident
I was surprised to hear some very familiar Arabic words from the Quran
You can listen to the track here
We'll play it in a second
The words are in the 18th second
It's to translate
Every soul shall have the taste of death
And to almost immediately after in the 27th second
All that is on earth will perish
I asked many of my friends online and offline
And they had heard the exact same thing I heard easily
When I played that part of the track
Certain Arabic hardcore gaming forums are already discussing this
So we decided to take action by emailing you before this spreads to mainstream attention
TOO LATE
We Muslims consider the mixing of music and words from our holy Quran deeply offending
We hope you would remove the track from the game immediately via an online patch
And make sure that all future shipments of the game do not contain it
We'd also like to mention this isn't the first time something like this has happened in video games
Nintendo's 1998 hit Zelda Ocarina of Time contained a musical track with Islamic phrases
And was removed in later shipments of the game after Nintendo was contacted by Muslim organizations
Last year Capcom, Zach and Wiki and Activision's Call of Duty 4
Also contained objectionable material offensive to Muslims that was spotted before the release of the final games
And both companies thankfully removed the content
We hope that you act immediately to avoid any confusion and necessary controversy
And we thank you for making such an amazing game
Now I think the letter was very well worded
However, I'm going to go back and read a particular line from this, if I may
We Muslims consider the mixing of music and words from our holy Quran deeply offending
So why aren't you offended at the artist that, you know, recorded the song in the first place?
Don't you think that's just a little bit of hypocrisy right there?
I mean, shouldn't you actually take issue up with the songwriter who, by the way, is Muslim, right?
Yeah, and the song has been out since 2006
Exactly, so why don't you do your homework first?
Okay, and to be honest, I mean, who is this really offending?
It's not like, you know, death to America, woohoo!
You know, it's not, there's nothing like that
I mean, most people are not going to know what it means
They're just going to hear it and they're going to say, hey, that sounds African
Hey, that fits with the level in the game
Because that's what I heard and that's what I thought
I'm like, hell, this song is fucking awesome
So put this in context to the game of why this music would be here in the first place
Like, you know, in the Africa level you hear African style music
In the South America level you hear South American style music
So in the, you know, in a level that's appropriate you hear this music
It's world music, basically, so you're traveling to different parts of the world
But somehow this slipped under the radar where, you know, people didn't realize that this could be offensive
Even though the song's been out there for a while when nothing's said
Well, keep in mind also, this is what I drew a parallel to
Why aren't Christian groups being offended at Rock Band 2 for having System of a Down in it?
They probably are
Why did the game come out then with that song in it if people are going to be offended?
Probably because Christian groups don't care because they have their own music with lines for the Bible
And they're, you know, it's Christian rock
And they're just like, hell yeah, spread the word, you know, but, um
But it's the same equivalent is what I'm saying
But I'm just sorry, I mean
If I get, you know, pissed off, okay, if something I find offensive in a game and I write Sony a letter
They're going to be like, fuck off
If I say I'm Arab, then they're like, oh, oh, now we're going to listen to you
Double fucking standard
I disagree, I disagree, I completely disagree
And especially something that's going on in the country
Especially over here is that we're seeing people catering to different ethnic groups
Because of this whole perception of oppression
That really should not exist in America in the modern world
I am going to put together a letter then to Sony and Media Monocle
And I'm going to tell them how deeply offended I am that they are censoring the game
You know, when, I don't understand why if we offend one person
I don't get why it's a big deal if we're offended
I actually do wonder how Sony would have reacted if the letter came that had absolutely no reference to the person sending it being Muslim
Or if they specifically said, I am not Muslim, however
Their reaction would have been different
There is a freaking double standard, I'm sorry
I'm going to, just to give some context to this
I'm going to play the clip from this game
It's hit the gaming blog, somebody recorded it off their phone
I'm going to give credit where credit is due
We pulled this from Kotaku where I believe one of their users got the sound clip and posted it on the site there
I'm going to play it, if you think for whatever reason this might offend you
I urge you to not listen to the next minute of the program
But I just want to give this some context
And so that our listeners can understand kind of where the controversy might be spreading from
I'm going to play the clip
So it definitely sets a certain type of world mood, right, this music
And there's an awful lot of ignorant Americans out there that are not going to know anything what was just said
Not going to know any of that, just going to think, oh it matches the mood
I know three words in Arabic and I couldn't say them off the top of my head
So how was that?
Look, I want to present a different opinion here
Because I think although I do see the overreaction going on here a little bit
And I think you're right, there are other religious things that are offensive that are in video games
I think in a way Sony's doing us all a favor by pulling this game
Is it a little bit hypersensitive? Yes, but is it Sony's fault? No
Whose fault is it? The media's fault
Because unfortunately if this had gone out and the wrong person had heard about it
And instead CNN, Al Jazeera, MSNBC gets a letter about this
Then it's suddenly going to be all over the mainstream press that
Oh my gosh, video games are teaching children passages from the Quran
And it's over, you know what I mean at that point
It's just another outrage of the violence in games and the messages that games are teaching us
Now it's religious text
Well who's going to say that it's not going to happen anyways?
And now let's see, how about the people representing Mexico saying that they don't like the way that Mexicans are portrayed in this game
Or how about the way that South America is portrayed in this game
Or how about the way that, you know
I see Sony sees smoke and they're trying to put out the fire before it spreads
I kind of, and forgive me for going to a comedian on this one
But I kind of want to quote Carlos Mencia about talking about people being offended about the Taco Bell dog
He's like, the Taco Bell dog sends out messages for people that Mexicans are stupid
He's like, no, it's sending out messages to buy more tacos
You know, it's people looking to be offended at something
It's people that are trying to find an excuse to, I really do think it's people just trying to find some sort of excuse
To put a little drama into their lives, to break up the monotony
Instead of trying to just say, hey, it's in there, I don't care
You know, why, it's not, if you're going to be offended at it being in the game
Be offended at the person that recorded the song to begin with
And in a way, yeah, I'm kind of like, well, where is the stink about this back in 2006
But then again, us being gamers, you know, maybe we didn't hear about it
Maybe there was a fuss and we didn't hear about it, I don't know
But I highly doubt there was or, you know, it would have been on the news
And I think all of us watch the news on a regular enough basis
We would have heard something about it, especially considering the guy who recorded this won a Grammy
However, I don't think the mainstream media would have given a fuck
I think they would have placed blame on the game
And I think Sony is just trying to put out that fire
It's sad, but that's the world we live in
It sucks, but
No, I agree with you that Sony is straight
But I also do think that it would not have gotten as much attention from Sony
Had it not specifically said, I and other Muslims are offended by this
Because we do have that double standard
That if you are some sort of oppressed group, and I say oppressed in quotes
That you automatically have to have someone throw you a bone
I'm sorry, that's not how it works
Was this dude like the only Muslim person playing this game?
You know, in the beta or something?
It was one person in the beta, he posted about it
And found other people in his religious group that were equally offended
Were they playing the game?
I have a hard time believing he was the one and only Muslim in the beta
No, that's what I just said
He was talking to other people in other forums like he said in his letter
To his credit, his letter was well worded and very respectful
That I do have to commend him on
And he wasn't asking for the game to be recalled
And I don't think we're placing any of the blame on this guy at all for maybe bringing it to light
I believe it specifically said, future releases not contain it
Patch the first releases, future printings, don't include it
That's acceptable, and that's part of what the beta is there for
To weed out offensive material, to weed out bugs
To make sure that you're releasing clean, safe content
Relative to the content you're releasing, you know what I mean?
To be honest, that's about the equivalent of what they would have done had, granted that I was San Andreas, come out on the Xbox 360 or Playstation 3
They would have patched it, and then they would have made sure that all additional copies would not contain that content
But I am going to, like I said before, I don't know that Sony
I think he was right
The guy who sent the letter was right to voice his concern
If he felt like it was a big enough concern, he was right to voice it
Because what's one thing that I always say?
Nothing changes until you put forth the effort to make it change, am I correct?
I think though that the recall should be voluntary
Because if you are offended by it, then yes
They should give you the opportunity to send in your copy of the game so that you don't have to hear that
But if a person like me, who thinks the song is pretty kick-ass and doesn't really care what it says
Wants to keep it, then I don't see what the big deal is
And see, that's part of what I-
Because now they're oppressing me and my desire to have this song in the game
For my own personal use
And they're oppressing me to benefit somebody else
That is my problem
I don't have a problem with someone being offended by it and they're fixing it for them
But I want to be able to keep my game the way it is
That's the point I was getting to
If you are offended by something, then sure
They should give you the option to remove the offensive content
But for those who are not offended by it, those who don't care
It's pointless
You're wasting time and money
You could just put out a patch
Why should one-
Because one group of people is offended by content that does not offend
Now, especially when the content is not attacking another group
Now if this was content that was saying
We hate all of so-and-such's group, kill them all
Then, yes, it should be removed, don't you think?
But if it's just something, not even a specific statement just saying
Oh, well one day the Earth is gone and all this stuff is gonna happen
Well it's just like reading Revelations, really
I mean, that-
It's nothing that's directed towards a party that anyone who is not in that faith
Would really get the reference to
You know, I just don't think there's an easy answer to this
I think this whole story is just a reflection of the world we live in
People are just too fucking offended
I know
But you know, I'm sitting here thinking, it's live radio
And sometimes I'm giving a lot of these stories a lot of thought
As we're sitting here talking about them
And I'm thinking, there's a story coming up later in the show in Part B
Where we're gonna talk about something that's coming out in an upcoming game
That kind of offends me a little bit
And although I can take offense, I know how to be offended or whatever
It's just kind of one of those things where, gosh
You know, even I look at some of the things that happen in video games
And I go, this is so stupid
Like, I wish games would kind of learn how to, I don't know
Address some of these things more appropriately
And in a way I feel like a hypocrite kind of sitting here going
You know, well everybody should just kind of learn to deal with it
When I'm thinking about, well come think of it
There are some things in video games that offend me
And exactly, but do you think that you would get equal representation
If you had emailed that company that makes that game
Hell to the no
Exactly, exactly my damn point
I'm sorry, there's, what about Redneck Rampage, okay?
Now while I personally don't consider myself to be a redneck
I do consider quite a number of my relatives to be purely
Jeff Foxworthy defines redneck as someone completely lacking in sophistication
I agree, that's most of my family
Not my immediate, but aunts and uncles and cousins and what have you
Anyway, but then, so if I said, you know, I'm from, you know
Mobile, Alabama and I'm offended at this game
Or I'm offended at how you've portrayed this southern person in this game as being stupid
Just because they talk a little slower and have a thick accent
That doesn't mean that their IQ is any lower than anybody else's
You know, I could say I'm offended at that
Or I could just laugh and go, I'm related to people like that
Which is basically my opinion towards Larry the Cable Guy
Basically, just watch South Park, there was that one episode basically saying
You know, about pulling a family guy off TV
If you do it for one person, then what's, you know, you have to do it for everybody
You know, I don't know, I don't know if this is a can of worms I want to open
But what the hell, we're here, we do this show for a reason to talk about things
But, you know, the story I want to talk about later has to do with an upcoming game
That just reinforces gay stereotypes I wish would go away
You know, and as a gay man, it gets really old after a while
You know, seeing some of these gay stereotypes in games
So I just kind of sit here and go, God, I wish I would just, you know, fucking grow up
You know, some of these people that program the games
So I'm thinking to myself, but at the same time, you know, maybe there's people that are Arab
That are sick of some of these stereotypes that are in the game
About, you know, the, you know, the verses that are being said
I don't know, you know, in a way, I just don't want to be a hypocrite here
But see, that's the thing
There's quite a bit of difference between what you're discussing and what's going on
This is just
Well, at the same time, CNN would never run a story either
On the fact that this other game comes out and offends gay people
That would never happen, never happen
Because it's stereotypes that a lot of people think about
Well, going back to the massive double standard
About what's considered bigotry and what's not, really
You know, it's like I was just saying in the chat room
You know, racism is racism
It doesn't matter
Like, I brought up an example
We did a diversity class at my work
You know, any corporation does diversity classes
And I brought a situation
And I think I said it on the show
When I worked in Alabama at Aladdin's Castle
Where this black lady and her children wanted me to change out quarters
Give them, you know, make change for them
And I said, I'm sorry, I can't make change for you because you're not a customer
She just wandered in from the store across the street
And not across the street, but across the aisle
And she's like, you're just doing that because I'm black and love
I'm like, no, I'm doing it because you're not a paying customer here
If you want me to make change for you, there's a street fighter machine right there
And she shut up and walked away
So, but you see what I mean
Racism is racism
Bigotry is bigotry
And as long as we perpetuate, you know, that type of thought
And as long as we keep getting offended
Instead of just learning to roll a little bit with the punches
Give a little, take a little
Then what's going to happen?
You know, we're breeding a different kind of intolerance
Don't you think?
That's a reasonable answer, thank you
Alright, let's go see what the Twitter had to say
Every week we like to post something on OLR
And obviously this is a story that's generating a lot of buzz out there in the gaming community
And just, I think it's invoking a reaction that goes a lot of ways beyond gaming
So I'm kind of curious to see what happens over the next couple of weeks
Of course then this game will come out censored
And people will forget years from now
But anyhow, the question we asked our folks on Twitter
Twitter.com slash OLR
Did Sony overreact by recalling LittleBigPlanet due to the controversial music in the game?
Why or why not?
And here's some of the responses that we got on our Twitter
Starting off with Dark Tetsuya
Yes, since the fix was the simplest day one patch
There wasn't that much of a need to delay the game a whole week
But let's not forget, not everybody has online capability
Crows says, of course they didn't overreact
This being America, everyone sues for anything
Sony wants to avoid a lawsuit
Point, but this was also a worldwide recall
Let's not forget that
And I don't know about lawsuit
I'm not trying to prove all our listeners wrong
I'm sorry, but I just want to say
Look at this too
Geekboy2424 says, yes, nobody would have noticed if they wouldn't have mentioned it
The person who heard this had to have scanned it
Well, he was a beta tester, right?
Not to mention that he's also probably very familiar with the Quran as well
I don't know about you, but if someone quotes Bible versus me
I don't know what the hell they're talking about
Well, I do know, and this is just a little bit I know
Because one of my co-workers is Muslim
Is that their prayers are done in Arabic, if I'm correct
And so you do end up learning a little bit of Arabic as you study
Let me read some of these other responses
Marin Marvel says, I think that it was overreacting a bit
But I can understand because of not wanting to offend people
Especially in this too happy day and age
Dust Stories says, wait, we have to please everyone and offend no one
We better stop the world now then
Big overreaction
Peter Uno says, hell no, oh fine, enough of that
To be honest, political correctness is going overboard
It seems silly that nobody cared until launch
Gold Anthro says, yes, with the game being awaited for so long
Just to remove it for something so small seems unnecessary
DJ Tyrant says, no, it was something that needed to be removed and caught earlier
Not everyone is connected to the interwebs either
The SEG says, considering worldwide reactions to cartoons, absolutely not
Recalls are less expensive than riots
Interesting point, interesting point
Decipher13 says, with people suing for less these days, Sony didn't overreact
Receiving the game at work and it being recalled in the same day was odd
So there you have it, some of our comments from the Twitter
At twitter.com slash OLR
And I'm sure this will go on for quite some time
I'm curious to see what kind of emails we get this week
I don't know, again, I think this is the type of quandary to where there's no easy answer
There's no easy solution because unfortunately there are people that will get offended
And it could affect gaming's perception out there as a whole
And it's just a shame, it's a shame
It's just, I really, my last two cents on it really
Is just, I'm not looking forward to a world where no one can have any sort of free thought or opinion of their own
Without someone else trying to strike them down for being wrong
My final thing is, I don't have a problem
He wants to make a comment, so do I
Don't be oppressing me, woman, seriously
Estrogen Brigade!
Now, I don't have a problem with them fixing it for the people that want it to be fixed
But I do have a problem with them fixing it for the people that don't really care
Or want it to be fixed in the first place
All I gotta say is they better replace it with a damn good song because that really fit with the game
And, I don't know, make an instrumental version of it or something
Perfect, perfect solution
Alright, well, we'll see what happens
I don't really have a final thought on this because I think I'm still developing one
So, let's go back to the Dick and Fart jokes
They should totally put in Two Knock Two Knock
Well, I don't know if Dick and Fart jokes were included with these
But PS3 and the PSP have received brand new firmware updates
The PS3 at a whopping 2.50
And PSP at, now, 5.0 firmwares
Some of the brand new features included with that
The PSP version is getting the PlayStation Online Store now
Which is pretty awesome
Also, the PS3 version, Flash 9 support
Oh boy, that's gonna be some good stuff
That probably means that some of those Flash IRC chats work now
Or what about some of those Flash emulators?
Or some of the Flash emulators
That's where my mind went instantly
Half the reason people bought a PSP in the beginning was to play Nintendo emulators on them
And now everything kind of comes full circle
Well, I was kind of disappointed that Flash 9 is not on the PSP
Because that makes things a lot easier
But no, just on the PS3
And also, I guess, they're including support now for the official PS3 Bluetooth adapter
Because they're now releasing a new headset that's gonna be with SOCOM and stuff
You can set your system to automatically shut down after downloading stuff
And then, I have to remember what else was added with the PSP
Probably just some minor fixes and stuff
And trying to fix it so that no one can crack it
Oh darn, too bad that failed again
So apparently the day after it came out
It was already cracked and the custom firmware 5.0 was released
Ah, Sony, you try, you try, but you fail and you fail
So, uh, oh well
Do you think somebody's gonna come up with a patch to patch the offensive music back in LittleBigPlanet?
Not to go back to that story, but
You know, with people that want to keep breaking Sony, what Sony destroys
I did want to mention though, there was a story that we didn't make it in there
One of the things that was included with the new PS3 firmware
Is there's a recovery menu that you can access now by holding down the power button
Until you hear three beeps
And that'll allow you to fix bad firmware updates
Say your power goes out or something like that while it's installing
Or god knows something happens
And a bunch of other things
So you can actually help recover your system so it doesn't break
Which is nice, I'm glad that they threw that in there
Alright, well hey, you know, some of the things that they're also kind of reformatting on the Sony side
Especially when it comes into the store and how things are being presented on the online store
It looks like companies are now starting to get their own little special stores
Capcom is one of the first that we're hearing about
Capcom has their own little like company version of the Playstation store
If you go to the Capcom store you can get all of Capcom stuff kind of in one little place on the Playstation Network store
You get the Capcom demos, their games, their themes, it's all in one spot
Now funny enough this wasn't an idea of Capcom's, it was actually Sony's
Who I guess must have presented the idea to them
And if you think this is going to be only in the Sony side of things
Guess what, they're saying that the new Xbox experience that's coming out
Means that Microsoft will be able to do something similar for their companies
So it's going to be very interesting is that you almost now are going to go from one
It's kind of cool in a way, in my mind I'm envisioning now that online shopping for these networks
Is now going from one giant everything stop shop that the company owns
Like Microsoft's Walmart or Sony's Target
Is now going to be like a strip mall
Where you can go into the Capcom store and go into the Konami store
It's going to be interesting to see what each company has to offer
It's going to be very very interesting to see what this does for like company branding in the video games
You know what I mean?
Like what stores will people visit first?
And who puts out what product?
Because you know back in the days of the NES
I don't think a lot of people followed these things
Most people didn't even know that Konami and Ultra were really the same company
They just would follow a particular series or whatever
But it's very interesting now that we have this very company branded atmosphere
That these online stores are going to create
Could be interesting
Of course I could be talking a whole lot of nothing
What ends up being really no big deal
Because it still is going to be one centralized place too I'm sure
But who knows? We'll see when the new Xbox experience comes out
When more of these stores launch on the Playstation side
I had to make a response to Geekboy2424 in the chat room
What did he say?
He disagrees with me that parents shouldn't please let their children play
Yes they should
It's the parent's job
However
Don't miss out that I have said parents need to be educated
And actually research instead of making a blanket assumption
It doesn't mean parents should put the ban hammer down
I think Geekboy2424 is a rather younger listener of ours
Which is why I think he might get a little bit hurt
That we're saying your parents need to be watching or whatever
But we're not saying the parents need to ban everything
The parents need to be watching
And the parents should at least know what you're doing
As far as this show is concerned
I don't think folks of a certain age should necessarily even be listening to this show
Without the parents kind of knowing what they're listening to on the internet
I like to think we're a good influence and not a bad one
But your parents have a right to know
This is my suggestion, this is what I used to do with my mother
True, it was over NES games when I was much younger
But why don't you find a review of the game
Find some video clips of the game
And then say, hey, this is the game that I want to play
Do you mind if we pick it up?
And being an adult, hopefully they should be able to make a decision
Whether or not they consider what you think okay is okay
Recognize some of your passion behind it too
Exactly
Maybe you'll get props for like, wow, our kid actually put together a whole little prosecution
Instead of just going, but I want it
Which was, I've tried that a couple times too
Yeah, me too
Then they'll say, well, you've obviously put some thought into it
Maybe I should think that maybe you're old enough to have an opinion
I'm sorry, kids, we've got smart kids out there
People who definitely have an opinion shouldn't just be discounted because of their age
Right?
That's true
So help your parents make an informed decision
If you truly think that you should have this game, put some effort into it
Let them know why
So my next story
Yeah, go ahead
Sorry
There has been a little bit of a tease now
That those who finished the PlayStation 3 version of Bioshock
Get a little teaser trailer saying Bioshock 2 Sea of Dreams
Is supposed to come out sometime in the future
And there's actually, I think, some video up around this
Up on Joystiq if anyone wants to take a look at it
And it's your typical teaser
I watched it just because I thought the first Bioshock was pretty graphically stunning
Just to tell you the teaser is your typical teaser video
It's nothing but, you know, the one shot of the girls standing on the beach or whatever
And the one line, it's a teaser in every sense of the word
On the Atlantic Coast
And just the fact it's coming
And it gives you that tagline, Sea of Dreams
And that's it
Yeah
That's what a teaser is
So in other words, Bioshock 2 is coming
Duh, you know what I mean?
They needed some teasing to do that
I guess now you have a subtitle, so there you go
When's it coming out? Soon
Soon, someday
Actually I don't think it's coming out too soon
A few years, well maybe
Soon is a blanket term
Summer 2010, I don't know, that's a guess
I say summer 2010
I like that, we'll just use that from everything now
What?
Summer 2010
That's when all the games are coming out
That's when Final Fantasy 13 is coming out, summer 2010
We'll be lucky if it comes out by that time
Alright
Release dates
Well there are other games coming out
This week at least
Starting off, we've got
The World of Goo, which is coming to PC
Fun little casual game there
Did very well on a
I think it's on the Wii already, I'm not sure
As part of the WiiWare
And of course, today
Rock Band 2 finally made it out on the PS3
Also the special edition bundles for PS3 and Xbox 360 are now available
The Naked Brothers Band is coming out
With a game, a karaoke game
Playstation 2 and the Wii for that one
Hooray
Penny Racer's Party Turbo Q Speedway
Apparently that got delayed from last week
And that's hopefully coming out this week now
Spongebob
Featuring Nicktoons and the Globs of Doom
Will be out on Playstation 2, the Wii, and on the DS
Let's see here
Back at the Barnyard, slot bucket games for the DS
We have Midnight Club Los Angeles on Playstation 3
And the Xbox 360
Also Midnight Club LA Remix for the PSP
Midnight Club is a pretty awesome racing game
I'll play that a little bit at PAX
Pass the Pigs, coming to DS
That's that old dice game, Pigs, if you remember that
Oh, they would land in the certain formations?
Oh my god, okay
Yeah, whopping 20 bucks for that
Why would you play a dice game on a video game?
I don't know
It's a good travel game
You can't throw pigs around in a car
They'll get lost
Alright, fair enough
Why do people buy Uno on Xbox Live?
I throw pigs around all the time, just letting you know
We actually have a Dwarf Potbelly
That we throw around on long trips at semis
Wow
Lovely Lisa on DS
Yes, it's an import doll game
Yippee
Hooray, it's like a little doll that no one knows
Wii Music is coming out finally on the Wii
I know everybody's excited about that one
I am
Why?
I liked it, I'm getting it for free anyway
What does it matter?
If you had to pay for it, would you?
No
Okay, that's what I thought
I'm getting it for free
Are you smarter than a fifth grader?
Make the grade, coming to the DS and the Wii
Let's see here
Disney's Sing It, their karaoke game coming to the Wii
Spider-Man Web of Shadows on the PSP, PS2
PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii and DS
And probably PC
A bunch of girl games with Energy Jim Rockets
It's a gymnosim game
They have Think Fast, which is a Disney trivia game
Coming to the Wii and PlayStation 2
The Legend of Spyro, Dawn of the Dragon
On PlayStation 2, PS3, Xbox 360, Wii and DS
Dance Dance Revolution Universe 3 coming to the Xbox 360
Oh, I had no idea that was coming out this soon
I thought for some reason it was in January
Well, they do a really good job advertising their games
Go Konami
Clash of the Ninja Revolution 2 for the Wii
Let's see here, Dancing with the Stars
Wii Dance coming to Wii and PlayStation 2 and DS
Energy Horse Rider for DS
Yet another horse riding sim
And if that's not good enough for you
Barbie Horse Adventures Riding Camp
That's PlayStation 2, Wii and DS
Build-A-Bear Workshop, Fur Seasons on the Wii
God, there's a lot of crap coming out
Anything else big?
Other than that, we'll just move on
Well, yeah, just small games like Far Cry 2 on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360
Fable 2 on Xbox 360
And High School Musical 3, Senior Year Dance
Because I know everybody's looking forward to that
Whoopee
I think that's all the big stuff
Taking a quick look here
Let's travel over to Japan, take a look at the Japanese release dates
There's not a lot to speak of on the Xbox 360
NBA Live 09 gets its Japanese localization on October 23
That coming out from EA over in Japan
Heading on over to the PlayStation 3
I imagine they're getting the same thing, and they sure are
Also, by the way, on Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3
Gundam Musou is getting a price reduction on both systems
So if you haven't checked that out yet, you can
Moving on to the Nintendo Wii in Japan
The Happy Dance Collection comes out from Namco Bandai this week
As well as Gensai Table Games Wii
Pro Golfers Saru and Tenchu 4 comes out
Monkey!
There you go
I guess
Also coming out on the PlayStation 2 this week
Devil Summoner, a new game in the Devil Summoner series
Comes out on October 23
As well as Ever17, the Out of Infinity
Although I think that might just be a price reduction
Yeah, that's just a price reduction
Also, Hakugen no Soryou Contract to Future comes out as well
And NBA Live 09 on PlayStation 2 as well
And a game called Never 7, the End of Infinity
Also gets a price reduction as well as Remember 11
And Sakura Taisen 3 also goes into Sega The Best series
So lots of price reductions this week
Price reductions this week
Didn't it get out to like 5 in the Sakura Taisen series?
I don't know how far they got, but it's just number 3
I think 4 came out on Dreamcast, didn't it?
3 was out on PlayStation 2, I guess
I don't know if that was a newer version or what
Could be
On the Nintendo DS, Dragon Quest Monsters Joker gets a price reduction
As does Final Fantasy 3 and Final Fantasy 12 Revenant Wings
Both getting price reductions as well
As far as new games go, you got Katsuie Death Label
As well as Kimi no Yuusha comes out from SNK Playmore
On the DS, as well as Soul Eater, Medusa no Inubu comes out
And Wakamama Fashion Gals Mode
Because I know you were looking forward to that
That sounds funny
That is a first party title in Japan, so go figure
Quickly looking at the Sony PSP to see what comes out this week
Bleach Soul Carnival looks to be a big title they're getting
And I know a lot of Bamani and music game fans are very excited about this
One of my really good friends is obsessed with DJ Max
And there's a new DJ Max game coming out this week on the Sony PSP
From what I understand, there also is going to be a US version of this game before November
I want Soul Eater
So there you go, what's that?
You want Soul Eater?
I was going to say their one small game I missed
What's that?
Coming out a week from today
Guitar Hero World Tour
It will be coming out on everything
Well that's because it's not a Tuesday game
It's a Sunday game
And it's going to be epic I guess
By the way, to specify, DJ Max is the Classic Y edition
There already is several DJ Max games on the PSP
This is the Classic Y edition
By the way, one other game I want to point out on the PSP this week in Japan
From Sega, Garnet Chronicle comes out as well
DarkSaga, take us to Europe
Here are our European releases
Well at least as far as the UK is concerned
We have on the 21st EverQuest seeds of destruction
I just like saying destruction, that's pretty freaking awesome
A name with destruction
Destruction of destruction?
This should just be ultimate destruction
Destroying the destructors
Or something
New game from OLR Studios
On the 24th we have Dead Space
Looking forward to that
Disaster Day of Crisis
Dungeon Maker
Fable 2
Which actually my husband has to work for the midnight launch tomorrow
So I'm going to laugh
We also have Legendary on Xbox 360
Well I don't
LittleBigPlanet is given the 24th date
Although we know that's not going to happen anymore
Exactly, but I'm just saying
Also Midnight Club Los Angeles on Playstation 3 and Xbox 360
As well as Midnight Club Los Angeles remix on PSP
Star Ocean The First Departure on PSP
Not too bad, huh?
Not a bad week at all
And it's just going to get busier and busier as we get closer to the holiday
Well that one last game that I had mentioned
Guitar Hero World Tour
Is very similar to another game series, Rock Band
And Rock Band of course is getting
You don't say
Yes, I don't say
Rock Band is getting a brand new download pack as it does every week
And this time it's Nirvana
You get 7 songs from Nirvana
Including Breed, Lounge Act, On a Plane
Polly, Something in the Way, Stay Away, and Territorial Pissings
And each of those is available for $2
Or you can save $3, buy the whole pack
For $11 or $880
But isn't it interesting that it's completely missing
Like the biggest songs on that album
Smells Like Teen Spirit and Come As You Are
I think was on that album too
Isn't that strange?
Yeah it is a little strange except
I think Smells Like Teen Spirit is in
Guitar Hero World Tour
And I'm not sure about the rest of them
Yeah but it's not like games haven't shared the same songs before
Well they may have exclusive rights to that song
Money talks
I guess
Alright well hey if you have opted for Guitar Hero World Tour
One of the things you can look forward to downloading next year
That's right they're announcing download stuff for next year
On the Guitar Hero side
The brand new Oasis album Dig Out Your Soul
I had no idea that Oasis was still putting out music
I haven't heard much of their stuff
There's probably some British folks over on the other side of the pond
That are like bonk to me
But they don't play them on the radio at all here anymore
Not since Wonderwall back in the mid 90's
But they are still cranking out music
They have a new album coming out Dig Out Your Soul
And that will be coming out next year
Some of the singles from that album
Bag It Up, Waiting For The Rapture, The Shock Of The Lightning
Are all coming out on Guitar Hero World Tour
So if you are an Oasis fan
And you're mad at me for my comment of not hearing them lately
You at least have that to look forward to
There you go
Well
Here's some more rumors
Hey wait a minute, you're the resident Blur fangirl
We haven't heard a lot of Blur
Like, I love Blur talk on the show lately
Didn't Blur and Oasis have like a feud thing years ago?
Did they ever get over that?
I think that, well since Blur is basically disbanded
Because Graham Coxon got really offended when they told him
STOP DRINKING
And he's like, well screw you guys
You throw me out of the band, I'm never coming back
You knew that was the story right?
Did he call them all bloody wankers?
Because if he did, that's too good
Probably things a lot worse than calling someone wanker
However
Graham Coxon has gone off to do his own thing
Damon has Gorillaz and also has The Good, The Bad, and The Queen
Which is pretty freaking good
Well I was thinking maybe if Guitar Hero is getting Oasis
This might mean Blur for Rock Band
If that whole little feud is totally on
I would totally love it if we had Blur for Rock Band
You know, we need to do a list list just for me
Of what Blur songs do we want to hear in Rock Band
We'll put that on the list of things to do
I'm sorry, we can move on now with news
Speaking of music games, there's a trailer
A trailer that doesn't really have much to do with anything as far as I'm concerned
But it's the Guitar Hero Metallica trailer
Obviously taken with a shaky webcam or phone cam
Or, you know, has no gameplay shown, no nothing like that
And those look good, Rob
What I'm eating, by the way
Orin Sam's Foodio for a minute
I found these when I was in the Bay Area this weekend
And I about crapped myself
I was so excited
They're flat fortune cookies
So they're fortune cookies, but they're just ironed out flat
And without the fortune, obviously, in them
But I love the taste of fortune cookies
And I know there's probably some of our listeners going
Big fucking deal
But you can't get these here, anywhere
I've looked
In the factory in the Bay Area to find them
Or Long's Drugs, apparently
Go figure
Sorry, random thought
I was just looking at the golden shiny goodness
Would you like one?
I would love one now
Here you go, I'm bringing it over
It's like a pancake, it looks like a freaking pancake
Hold up to the camera
Those of you that are watching on Justin TV, I'll give you a cookie too
While Jamie reads the story
Anyway, there is a very shaky teaser trailer
Up for Guitar Hero Metallica
Which I had been hearing
Them speak of before
So I don't think it's that far off
But it's saying
The trailer is supposed to come with Guitar Hero World Tour
And it has
A Ride the Lightning
You know, 2009
Something, so
Cause that's not cheesy or anything
I think Metallica has finally
Gotten off of their music
And electronic distribution
And just said, cool
Though they still have to do that
To be edgy, you know, but
They're going, so
And I do also have to say that the Metallica tracks
In Rock Band 2 are fucking hard
Maybe they just like playing Rock Band
In Guitar Hero
So they decide, you know, when Guitar Hero comes and says
Hey, we'll do a whole freaking
Game about you guys
And they're like, cool
Or they saw what they did with Aerosmith and were like, we want that shit
Well, and Metallica
Is the epitome of awesome
Rock before they sold out
So
Well, I hope
For their sake that they learn
They learn from Guitar Hero
Or not Guitar Hero
They learn from Rock Band and decide to
Go ahead and allow each of those
Games that they release separately
To be able to be downloaded
So that you can play tracks
In your Guitar Hero World Tour game
Cause that would suck otherwise
Especially if there's
A lot of games coming out like they were saying that they were gonna do
I don't know
Oh well
Well, something completely un-Guitar Hero related
South Peak
Has now bought the small independent
Game publishing company
Gamecock
Who apparently acts
I don't know, they act crazy
But they do release a lot of
Like a cock?
Yes, crazy like the cock
Apparently though, they release a lot of independent
Games of course like
I think actually
This week, I can't believe I forgot it
Legendary
Should be coming out
And that's one game that they're publishing as well as
Velvet Assassin that's gonna be coming out later on
I'm sorry, but they did that Pirates and Ninjas
Dodgeball game that was horrible
No, that's South Peak, yeah
South Peak did, I'm talking about Gamecock
I thought Gamecock did that game
No
I don't think they did
They're publishing it, whatever
They don't make the games, they just publish them
Yes
The Pirates and Ninjas Dodgeball
Maybe not exactly the glowing
Example of their portfolio
Legendary looked good
And Mushroom
Sort of okay, but there's
A lot more games they're putting out
And they're increasingly getting better
So that's nice
South Peak on the other hand, they've been releasing
Overlord
That's pretty cool
Overlord is pretty sweet
They had some other stuff, X-Planes
I think that was one of theirs as well
I wonder if Bang Mini
One of the first orders of business at South Peak
Is gonna be telling the guys at Gamecock to sit down
And shut up, cause you know, they're kinda
Known for just making a lot of noise, you know what I mean
They just make noise, and some people don't
Get it, like sometimes you kinda look at them and go
They're just kinda weird and need to shut up
I don't think that they're like
I get the sense Gamecock kinda runs
Themselves like a fraternity
And for real, I get the sense
That they have raging kegger parties at some of their
Company things, events, right
Yeah, I wouldn't doubt that
It seems like this giant gaming fraternity
And I'm sure it's a fun as hell place to work
But sometimes you look at that and go
Okay, they have to remember
That in every good frat party movie
That there's always a
Montage sequence where they have to pull it
Together and act a little bit less
Like a fraternity and more like
A brotherhood and actually come together and do business
Instead of just fuck around all the time
And they haven't really gotten to that point
In the grand scheme of things
Gameguru in chat wants to say
South Peak didn't have anything to do with
Pirates vs Ninjas Dodgeball, Gamecock published it though
I thought I saw their logo on that game
And I'm sorry
We talked about this, I think
Last week or two weeks ago when Dark Star Wars
Classic Game of the Week was the dodgeball game for Neo Geo
That I thought
The Pirates vs Ninja game was kind of assy
Compared to Neo Geo
I thought it was a dumb idea to begin with
Oh, Pirates vs Ninjas, we're gonna settle this match
Once and for all with Dodgeball
And I'm like, lame
Tune out
SSJ100Matt in chat says if Gamecock has
Kager parties, then OLR has pie parties
Not true, tonight is a flat fortune cookie party
Pancake cookie
And they taste like pancakes too
They're delish
They taste like yummy
Awesometasticness
Also pretty awesometastic
Is the game Soul Calibur 4
But what is less awesome
Is that we all saw this coming a mile away
They swore up and down
Oh yeah, Darth Vader, Yoda, exclusive
To their respective consoles
Even though there's that big gap in the character
List select screen
And there was video and screenshots of them playing
No, it's totally exclusive
Well, sure enough, they've confirmed this week
That due to
Overwhelming fan response
Mhm
That soon you will be able to download
Darth Vader and Yoda
In Xbox 360 and Playstation
Three, you know, the respective versions
That are missing it
You'll be able to download them on October 23rd
I'm not sure if that's a US or a Japanese date
But you know it's gonna happen everywhere
I mean, come on
October 23rd, you know that's almost exactly three months
From the game's release
What a coinkydink
You've had an exclusive deal for
Three months
It'll set you back $5
That's 400 Microsoft points
Or in Sony terms, $5
I'm sorry, in Sony terms, $4.99
So you have
Because Sony's not gonna like
Do anything with that extra penny
Yes, isn't that wonderful
You have to put full amounts
Full dollars into your account
But they charge you $4.99
So there's always a remainder
Oh, cry
You know, I'm a consumer whore
I'll probably get it anyway
Just charge even amounts, god, who cares
$4.99 may seem cheaper
But seriously, people know how to do math
They understand it's only one cent cheaper
I'm glad though
I can say I told you so, I told you so
To my friend that said I have to get the Playstation 3
Version of Soul Calibur because it's the only way I'll get to play
Vader, and secretly I think
He just wanted to play me online
And I'm like, just wait
There will be download content
It's inevitable, and I'll bet you what
You know what, I bet you money
I will bet you money, significant amount of money
This is not download content
It's pay to unlock content
Money
I posted a picture in the chatroom, by the way
Of the view from where I sit
Well, thank you for that
It's of Rob's head
Oh, great
And one of your pancake cookies
Speaking of yummy
Resistance 2
Kids like aliens
Kids should not be playing the game
Because it is mature
Oh
The beta
For Resistance 2
Began on Friday
So
For those who got in, let us know how it is
You know what you can tell us
Some opinion here or there
It's going to be
Going from
Actually
The 20th of October
So I guess actually that's
I'm sorry, that's in Europe
It's starting on Monday the 20th
And it's going to be going on until Thursday
The 13th of November
And there will be keys that are given out
From IGN, but there's no date
As to when those keys will be given out
So keep your eyes on IGN for
A little bit more on that
I like how the beta is going longer than actually the game
The game is coming out in the middle of the beta
That's the UK
Dates
Loki, you try to get into betas that you probably don't belong in
Are you going to get into this one?
I'm not even going to try
I didn't really play much
Actually, I didn't play any of the multiplayer
In Resistance 1
In fact, I sold my copy back
Yesterday
But you still enjoy the game, right?
Yeah, the game was awesome
And I will plan on getting it
I'll enjoy the game
I'll have to wait a few weeks
There you go
But, yeah
I don't know
The last few multiplayer betas I've been in
Call of Duty 4 didn't really play much
What else did I get in?
Battlefield Bad Company
I didn't even play that at all
I'm a horrible beta tester
For what it's worth, I played the Wrath of the Lich King beta once
I went through all that patching and all that crap to play it once
And that was it
Doesn't that mean you don't have to patch it later?
No, it was a completely separate thing
No, because you still have to buy the retail copy of it
And you know, they're going to change some things
From what was in the beta
Well, it's finally here
For those people clamoring to play
A translation of Mother 3
You can now download the patch
For your ROM
That you may have of Mother 3
Of course you would
Need to have an import copy of the game
Because, you know
To make it legit
You can now download the patch
The update, which has been worked on
For a while now
Is finally available
So that's pretty awesome now that you get to play
Mother 3, which, I don't know
I don't know why they don't just translate it
Seriously, why do they refuse
To put that game out over here?
I mean, it is literally
A refusal on Nintendo's part
To just put that game out here
And remember how
How long it
You know, the fans put effort into
Doing second to three and we never got it
So
It's just weird how adamant they are
I mean, I can't imagine it costs that much money
To translate, but maybe it's because then they have to
Produce the game, I don't know, it's just
It's just sad
And you look at some of the stuff that is coming out from Nintendo
On these systems and you just go, why?
Personal training cooking
That is awesome
Not only are they
Little behind in putting that out
Because there's going to be about four or five
Other cooking games coming out around the same time
I don't think anyone's going to buy it
I mean
I'm sure there's people out there that actually
Purchase every single Nintendo game that comes out
But, dude, seriously, you might start
Questioning that
Alright, one more story before we get to the classic
Game of the week and get to our break tonight
Hey ladies
If you're still looking for a Halloween costume
You know your gamer man
In your life might enjoy the sexy
Lingerie
With Ms. Pac-Man's likeness on it
It will look like that
Pac-Man and Ms. Pac-Man are eating your boobies
Because that's what this bra looks like
Is that you actually have
Pac-Man and Ms. Pac-Man
Just click on the show roll link
And you can get this picture
But it looks, I mean, they're sexy little outfits
I get that
And I like how when the model
I don't know what you want to call it
Gladiator style skirt with little flaps
And if you lift up the flaps
It reveals Inky
One of the ghosts, or maybe it's Binky or Pinky
I don't know, but on your panties
Right where your cooter is
So, nice little surprise there
Like, ooh, ghost
And I would like to point out
That the ghost is blue
Which means it is an appropriate time
To munch it
For 200 points
Anyway
3wishes.com is where you can
Buy Ms. Video Game
Hey, while you're at it
You can also pick up their Chun-Li outfit if you'd like to
I think I shall be
Clicking on a linky
Are you going to be buying
Ms. Video Game for Dan this Halloween?
Not for Dan to wear, but for
No, I'll just be buying it for myself, it's freaking cool
There you have it
And no, listeners, you cannot
HasPix
No, you cannot
Not just a no, but a hell fuck no
Alright
Hell fuck yes, though, to the classic game of the week
Right, DarkSakura?
Hell fuck yes, let's check it out
We're going to travel gaming's history
To find a game that DarkSakura
Thinks you all should be playing
It's the classic game of the week
And I think this week's classic game of the week
Is probably one a lot of people have
Played, I'm guessing
If they haven't, they suck
Or maybe we're too young
To see it the first time
But you need to go find this game
Right, DarkSakura?
We can get it on PSP, shit
Alright, well, tell us about it
What is this week's classic game of the week?
We have two games, but they're together, one's a sequel
It's Parappa the Rapper
And Parappa the Rapper 2
Parappa
How do you not know this song?
Seriously, the demo came with what?
I think it was on one of the old Sony magazines
It was, and I played the fuck out of it?
Anyway
You basically play
It's all done in sort of a 2D flat style
For all the characters
And you play as a little dog named Parappa
Who has to believe, because I gotta believe
And basically
He goes around rapping
Against different people
So it's really a music rhythm game
It's like Simon Says, really
Where they, the words that
Whichever the masters that you're going against
Their words have a pattern of button presses
And then you have to repeat it for yours
Or do something that corresponds
That's actually more Parappa 2
And of course the better you do
The better your score
If you start sucking, then
You go to bad, you're not rapping cool
If you get from
Rapping good to rapping cool
Then the stage just completely goes off
And you take over and you just have to keep pressing buttons
Randomly until the stage is over
Which was actually the only way I passed the stage
From Jeremy Lammy, which we'll get to later
So
The game was made by
Masaya Matsura
Who was
Actually
One of the, the leader of the Hyperpop unit
For
But he was also, the company
That brought out the game was Nana Oncha
So
If anyone remembers
Nana Nana Nana Nana Oncha
I played this game literally a million times
And Unchan Malami
I love these games
You have the meter like I was saying before
You have the rapping good
That's when you're doing okay
When you're doing as you're expected to
If you're rapping bad, the music gets a little worse
If you're rapping awful, it's just
Depressing sounding
And the stage is rain
And it gets awful
And the better you do, it starts going back to normal again
You know, like you'll have this little
Minor, you know, chord
Baseline to it
So
The art was done by Rodney Greenblatt
And um
He's got a website that's just got
Tons of his art
But it also did have a sequel
Which we're getting to the music of next time
And we will hear the music from the sequel right now
Well this is just the start of it
This is from Parappa 2
I didn't put Unchan Malami in here
While even though it plays the same
It feels differently, I think, don't you agree?
Yeah, I mean it is a different game
It's like um
It's not a sequel but an equal, if that makes sense
Yeah, and um
Unchan Malami and friends make an appearance in this game
But I had to pick the best music in
Parappa 2
I think we get a cut scene with this one
I don't know if it goes straight into the song
Hey everybody, watch out for those flying noodles
Cause if you don't do well here
All you get to eat are noodles
And here we go
So you can find Sister Mustachio
I will
But anyway, the reason why I had to put Parappa 2 up on there
Is because the music is just
A lot better
Different styles
I really love the Parappa 2 soundtrack
And um
But I had to pick that particular level
Cause there's one stage where Parappa has to trap himself
In a video game or else everybody in the universe has to eat noodles forever
And that's
As far as I'll say without spoiling the rest of the story of the game
If you haven't played it
God knows why you haven't
But um
It also really goes there
A lot more stylistically
As far as having stages
Where you change perspective
Within your 3D environment
Like the
Ant guru
Or um
You know where you uh
That's the first Parappa
Oh I thought you wanted this movie show
The one from Parappa 2
What stage number was it?
4 I think
Well this is one of my favorite songs from Parappa
When I say boom boom boom
You say bam bam bam boom
I love this song
If you sort of freestyle a little bit with it
It increases your score
And if it's good enough
That shoots you into cool mode
Pretty much
You know so
Now going back to this I mentioned it before
Is um
That there is a PSP version
And I happen to look into my copy for about 13 bucks
When a Hollywood video
Is going out of business
Um
But uh
It's the same thing
You've got lots of different versus modes in it
Um jammerlami
We will definitely be
Yeah here's another one
And who can forget the bathroom rap in the first game?
God I know
Um especially as often as it's been quoted
Um
But this is why I think that um
Parappa 2 though
If you can just listen to the difference between
How much more complex the music is
I really like it a lot better personally
Um
Jammerlami was another
Game that's in the same vein
And I was saying I'll probably cover it
On another one because it honestly is
I think different enough
Within the style of music that it can qualify
As a different game
But there was Parappa mode in it
And Parappa mode was pretty freaking cool
Because it turned all these rocking songs into rap
Um
There are some differences
A few lines that were changed
As far as
You know one released to the other
Um
There was an anime
A Parappa anime that I thought was really really cute
Um it came out
In Japan it actually has a really cool little intro song to it too
Um
But for anyone
When I was speaking about the uh
Um
I was talking to a guy named Rodney Greenblatt
His uh website
Is um
Wednesdayload.com
W-H-I-M-S-Y
Load L-O-A-D dot com
That's all one word dot com
Um and
While his artwork may seem fairly simplistic
He's got some really nice and complex stuff on there
Uh some uh
Uh sculpture
Um different uh
You know medium he uses
Work you know
Given you know my recent educational career
I know all the lyrics to these today
I remember driving around San Francisco one time after
Picking up somebody and um
He had brought the CD and we listened to it
In the Rain or in the Snow
Um
We've often referred to as um
The After Effects of certain
Eating at Gem Boys as
The Funky Flow
Nice
Um really not joking
But um
That's their game
Parappa and Parappa 2
There you go here classic game of the week
Parappa the Rappa and it's sequel Parappa the Rappa 2
Two for the price of one
I couldn't mention one without mentioning the other
Right it's like a necessity
Personally I like the second
Parappa better
As a game and music wise
But you cannot mention the second
One without mentioning the one that started
At all right you know
You sure cannot alright there you have it
Your classic game of the week and that means it's break
Time folks and when we come back we haven't even
Really touched a lot of the Microsoft news going on in the world
Microsoft might be giving out
Some free memory cards
Soon so we're going to be talking about that when we come back
From this break and some other stuff
Including that story I referenced a little bit earlier
About something in a game that pisses me off a little bit
And this is something
We actually found ourselves
Here at Orange Lounge Radio you will not have read about
This on any blogs yet
Kind of some I guess you could say exclusive news
But I don't like using that term it's just kind of one of those
You may not have heard of this yet
We'll be talking about it in part B when we come back
After this break
Orange Lounge Radio
Hail to the king baby
Hey welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio
And thanks J-Rod for that new little commercial there
I love it when other people do the commercials for us
If you have a promo you want to run for your
Nonprofit website or if you have a
Podcast you want to plug that's independent
You can always send us a commercial
Or if you just want to do something cool for Orange Lounge Radio
Like J-Rod did
You can put that together and send it to us
At Orange Lounge Radio there's more information available on the forums
Meanwhile we're coming back to our show
After a pretty fun first half
Which I must say for this show
Was surprisingly intelligent
Considering we were talking about the Quran
And the controversy around the little big planet
And all that
I think we're pretty smart
So this is the Oscar clip
Tonight's episode
Episode number 299
It's going to be a big show next week
Hey that fart over there must be
Mean that Fart Princess
Is joining us here in studio
Who just surprised us
By joining us during the break I had no idea you were coming tonight
Hi Fart Princess how are you?
Hi I was just supplementing the Oscar material
Oh thank you
And by the way she's no longer Rice Princess
She's Fart Princess
You're a liar
And also joining us tonight
I haven't seen you in a long time
Now what are we calling you these days?
It used to be Casper the Gay
But I now go by The Doctor
Now The Doctor
I've got a Sonic Screwdriver right here
Oh and our guests are extremely loud tonight
I'm very sorry
I left mine at home
I'll adjust the volume
As we move in
We actually have a listener called The Doctor too
And now there's going to be some confusion
Let me see your Sonic Screwdriver
You've got the little one?
It's not Sonic then
No but after the show
I'm going to play with Captain Jack's Sonic Screwdriver
Oh my
You know that's actually what I was planning on doing for Halloween
Is getting a blue suit
And tie and wearing my con verses
And going as Chick Doctor
Oh my god that'd be so awesome and then we would match
Because I'm going to be Doctor Who as well
I've got the black ones
I was actually either going to do the blue suit
Or do a different color suit and be Chick Doctor
That'd be so awesome
It's nice to have guests in the studio it's been a long time
Especially considering episode 300 of this program
If you can believe it is next week
Oh my
Yeah episode 300 is next week
And we're doing nothing special for it except soliciting congratulations
And whatever memories from our listeners
On 877 Game OLR when we're not live
You should do something special
We might do some games next week
So you kids should come back
So there you have it
This is some gaming news if you guys want to comment on the news
You have a microphone feel free to comment
Just refrain from fart noises fart princess
Do we need more fart noises?
Alright
I love that I come back from break
And talk about what an intelligence show we're having tonight
And then fart princess shows up
To fuck the whole thing up
What are you talking about?
What?
We have to go from extremes
We have to keep the listeners guessing
And Rob?
There's the show I was missing somehow
Yeah great
Oh how much lower can we go? Yes
Did you ever see that skit on the state where they had the high brow side
And the low brow side
Shifting over to the low brow side
I think I vaguely remember yes
The state was a cool show
I had the guy who had to put his balls and stuff
Can we get back to the news please?
No we're supposed to make the show crappy now
Loki some gaming news for the love of god
So yes
There is this rumor
Going around that the next
Xbox system
Will be forwards compatible
Yeah I know you've heard
All about backwards compatibility
Oh but we got the brand new forwards
Compatibility
It will play the games of the future
No really what it means is it will
And I think this technology is already available now
It will make your Xbox
360 games better
Same you know either at a higher
Resolution or
Make them play smoother
I don't know like the Playstation
Isn't that the exact same fucking thing
The 360 was supposed to do to original
Xbox games? And it does to a certain
Extent it does you know
Smooth out the graphics a little bit
And it also
You know kind of up rezzes it
A little bit same with the Playstation 2
It kind of made it a little bit smoother
Decreased loading times
Depending on which option you chose
So how is this any different
Than backwards compatibility? In fact I would say
It's exactly the same as backwards compatibility
Just with a different name to it
Because obviously your Xbox 360 is not going to be able to play
New games
I don't know I'll tell you the last system that had
True forwards compatibility was the Dreamcast
And I'll tell you why
Because with every new game
They would load a new version of Windows CE
That would have an improved running environment
For each game that came out subsequent
So in that respect
That's forward compatibility
We haven't had a system do that since
But it's also firmware updates
And you know they have those
Available now and you know with
Each firmware update it could make your
System run smoother
Isn't it just a bunch of
Marketing mumbo jumbo?
It is a bunch of marketing mumbo jumbo and rumor
Marketing mumbo jumbo might I add
So who cares
The system isn't going to be out for a while
Anyways and we'll listen to all the marketing
Mumbo jumbo when that actually happens
Moral of the story?
Sega is awesome
I'm not sure how we got to that but okay
Dreamcast
Let's read some comments from chat
Our first half of the show tonight was missing
Too much of the chat room. Let's get some comments from chat
Make up for it part B here
Redertainment says forwards compatibility sounds like
New things can be promoted and such
Backwards compatibility sounds old and dated
So like with forwards compatibility
Yoda and Vader will already be unlocked
Is that what it is?
Maybe?
You don't even know what the hell I'm talking about
I'm sorry we're like acting right now
Alright
By the way if you're not watching Justin TV
All rice princess and the doctor
Are doing are beating each other up on cam
For your entertainment so check that out
That's all we're doing
Hey I want to talk about a little bit of news
And actually this might be something you guys might have an opinion on
I don't know and this is not out there yet
This news is not out there yet
This actually was my buddy Shane
You know he's been on the show here before
Plenty of times he actually works at a game store
And he sent me a picture
From a strategy guide coming out for Fable 2
And it's the Brady Games
Strategy guide for Fable 2
And there's a section in it that talks about clothing
There are plenty of quality
Tailors scattered throughout the cities of
Albion and most of them are
I'm sorry and each of them are
Cable of crafting some fine handmade clothing
Etc, etc, etc. Let me get to this part
Many items are unisex
But those that are designed
Specifically for one sex
Carry a cross-dressing rating
Should the other sex wear them
Heroes wishing to experiment with gender
Play should consider wearing up
Clothes of the opposite gender
Especially if looking to start a same
Sex relationship
Interesting
So that's what I can infer from this
From the strategy guide
Is that in Fable 2
If you want to start a same sex relationship
Because you know the game will allow you to basically
Have whatever types of relationships you want
The way to do that is by cross-dressing
You have to trick them
Apparently
That's wrong
That's crazy
This is what I was talking about in the first half
Where even I looked at this and I went
Okay I'm a little bit offended by this
Because we've been trying to combat
For years and years and years
When they splash images of the pride parade on the news
And that's what people think
The culture is all about
Well some of us don't even like that kind of stuff
And it's like
Nobody applies logic
It's like you're gay and you like men
Not women
Hello
That's like the epitome of being gay
And maybe I'm just being a little hypersensitive about this
And letting the trigger figure go off
Too soon on this and being offended
But I'm just kind of like come on people
Is this really the way the game
Has to be designed is that if I want to impress
People of the same gender I have to cross-dress
I'm sure the designers will come back and say
Well you don't have to cross-dress
You don't have to do it
But I'm sure it improves your chances and to me that's wrong
Yeah no and it's just
I'm not mad about it
Yeah it's dumb
That's what people think though because it's like
This one girl in a club was like
Oh do you wear panties and I'm like
I'm not a woman
I don't wear panties
No that's what they make mantis for
Yeah maybe mantis
Well it's
For all we know
And I don't know how much further
Into the strategy guide he looked at it
It could be possible
That maybe it's just a small
No apparently later in the guide
Each article of clothing
Is actually has like a cross-dress rating
Okay
So cross-dressing is a facet of the game
And I don't know if it's the guide
I don't know if it's the game
I'm assuming the guide is just reporting on how the game was designed
You know what I mean but that sentence to me
Stings the way they say that
Is that if you want to improve your chances
In a same-sex relationship you gotta cross-dress
Then make it sound like that's an integral part of it
Reddertainment in chat says
Can I attract people of the opposite gender while cross-dressing
Dude I know in real life
There's a lot of women that do find that hot actually
Hell yeah
A man who's comfortable with their sexuality
All the teenage guys that go to cosplay dressed as like Japanese school girls
Like I'm sure there's a lot of chicks there
That get off on that
I almost became a cosplay stalker
Because of this one guy dressed as Utena
There you go
And he looked freaking gorgeous
I was like I'm gonna follow you now
Oh my
AcidicVampire in chat says
At least you can have a same-sex relationship in The Sims
Exactly I think The Sims is a game that does it right
The game is not about
Same-sex relationships
The game does not force you to do same-sex relationships
It's just there
Just like in real life
Or like in Bully
In Bully you have to dress up a little bit
You have to wear your aqua-weary vest to get a kiss from a guy
But that's not too bad
Well at that point it was just like
We'll take what we can get
Sauce brought up Manfay
And she can
She can put Manfay right away
Nobody is attracted to Manfay
Okay that's
You don't want to know
The doctor just asked what is Manfay
Did you watch Cowboy Bebop?
No he doesn't
Don't even bring up the picture please
Rob do it
We need a reaction shot
This is radio
Can you describe what Manfay is while I pull up the picture in chat here
The character Fay in Cowboy Bebop
Has been cosplay
Yes a woman
Has been cosplayed
By many pretty women
And one hairy man
That is Manfay
Rob share the picture in the chat room please
Sailor Bubba is a close second
Oh yeah, oh god
Shut her
There you have it
I've been at conventions
Where Manfay has been present
And see look look
Manfay we're all sitting here and laughing at
And that's why I don't like this in the game
Because we sit there and laugh at crossdressers
I don't know
And I don't think that should be associated with same sex
This one person is
It's crossplay
Crossplay I like that
I know plenty of female cosplayers
Who do male characters
To comedic effect
And that's hot
Sometimes
I've even considered doing a couple of costumes myself
I wanted to go as Richter one year
You know with the Ryu hairband look
And everything
But you know I have a friend of mine who's very tall
Who went as
Larva from Vampire Princess Mio
So
Alright Shauran in chat says
My friend saw Manfay at her first con
I feel so bad for her
Alright getting away from Manfay and all this funny stuff
For right now
We were talking about the other story
You know it's hard for me to sit here and go
People should not find this offensive
When in the same breath I'm looking at this story
And I'm going you know what I'm kind of sort of offended
At this story
I think it's different though
It is but I can't put my finger on it
Why should I be offended
The difference being is that
This is a specific component
Integral to the game
This is something programmed specifically
Into the game
As a facet of gameplay
The other is background music
That was made
By someone of that faith
It's
Now if that had been programmed in by
The most flaming of all gay people ever
Would you be as offended
Yes
Because I think that person should know better
Okay but if that person
Personally thought it was
Funny and wondered why people would be offended
I mean I'm not like offended
Offended is not the word
I'm disappointed
I'm disappointed that it's 2008
And this is what I'm reporting on
Is that cross-dressing in the game will help your chance
With same sex relationships
Can't we just move on
Why can't it just be
If this game wants to be so big
You have the character you want
And you program the same way
Why can't you just be
Why can't you just be the hero
With muscles and I don't know
Whatever wearing manly clothes
That attracts a lot of women
And 10% of men
You know what I mean
Why can't we just have that
You know what I think it should be
And keep in mind also
Not everyone who cross-dresses
Is gay
We know this
Not everyone who
Who is gay cross-dresses
Also importantly true
Exactly and there are people
Who want to be that gender
I think that if they were
Going to incorporate something like that in the game
And true it would be some very
Complex programming I do believe
It should be
That you have the option of how you are going
To make use of that option
You know what I mean
If you want to cross-dress because you want to be a woman
You should have that as an option
I want boobs
Solid Goomba in chat says I want to be a man
In a dress and have a relationship with a woman
More power to you
I do think the game should allow that
If that's what you want
You know what I mean I don't think cross-dressing should have a bearing on it
I don't know maybe I'm just
Maybe I just need to cool it but it just seems a little silly to me
And you know if the designers
Take issue with how I'm reporting on that
Well look at the strategy guy the official strategy guy for the game
That's where it comes from
I agree that's boring
It's like oh my god we got another flamer
Is the gay character in the game you know I don't know
People need to get on with it
I'm just kind of getting sick of it
Like one of these days I would just like to have
A normal person
Who happens to be gay in my video game
Just like you know in TV and all that
You know and even if sexuality
Is not a part of the game's device at all
Then fine we have no defined sexuality
In the game that's just fine by me
But amongst these RPG love stories I would like
One day for there to be
A same gender one that is not stupid
If that makes sense
And you know that actually
Goes back to what I was talking about
About the sort of
A
Singular directional bigotry
You know what I mean
I think that
Every you know
Every relationship is going to have its moments
Of dysfunction
Every relationship is you know some may have
A very odd origin you know
I ordered my husband on the internet
You know
I think that
It doesn't have a quirk to it
The quirk should be there because of the people involved
Not because of their orientation
Right
Um
Just one other thing though
I think though that having
An active
You know I don't even think it should be
An active choice I think you should just
Start up your character and be born gay or not
Because really isn't that
For the most part you know
I think it's genetic
Progress
I think that
As far as it being a part that does
Determine a lot of who your character
Is
But it does not
Define who your character is
Um let me read some comments in chat here real quick
Because they're good
Acidic vampire says play indigo prophecy
There's a normal quote unquote
Gay male in it
And no I haven't and that's one of those Xbox games
That like I should have played but I never did
Fair but you know I guess maybe we
Need a little more of that
SG100Matt says I'm still waiting on a video game
Hero who happens to be Jewish
Fair enough
But how often does religion come into video games
Of course then again
Saying all that with what we talked about earlier
But you know just
And then immediately follows
That up and says just because they always grab coins
Doesn't mean they're Jewish
See
I like that you can have a little fun with it
Alright
Look let's just move on
And you know everybody's talking about
They want to see representation of themselves
GS68 I want more Filipino
Filipina characters dammit
I'm sure there's a lot of people saying I want to see a little more
Of this in games so maybe it's time
For diversity the game
I don't know it's a small world the game
Who knows I don't know
Let's move on there's plenty more gaming news to talk about
If you want to talk more about it email us
Call us later
Take us to a game that has nothing to do with sexuality, religion or race at all
This one's about falling into holes
That could be construed as sexuality
Yeah but how many holes do people really fall into
I tripped there's a vagina
You might wake up with a hangover
I think I fell into a hole while I was drunk
Anyway sorry go ahead
Okay anyway
Portal Still Alive
Is going to be on the Xbox Live arcade
It will be
It will
Be up on Wednesday October 22nd
And
It has the
One that came out
Earlier
Plus 14 new exclusive
Challenge maps
And 6 advanced maps
And new achievements
So in other words if you bought the orange box
Just for this game
Haha sucker you're going to buy it twice
But is Portal a game that you really
Mind buying twice I mean it is pretty freaking good
There are different levels to be fair
Yeah to be fair I know
There needs to be more GLaDOS
On the PC
First there will be cake and then you will be baked
There's no story in the extra levels right?
They're just kind of there
It's just more crazy
Will you be taunted by GLaDOS in these bonus levels or are they just extra puzzles or something?
What's the point of not being taunted?
I don't know
That's why I'm curious to see like
How
How milked is this game?
That's what I want to see like are they really just milking it
Or did they actually put a little thought into it?
That's what I'm really curious to see
Who knows
Well
One thing that you can probably store that brand new game on
Would be a hard drive
Or a new memory unit
And remember Microsoft was saying with the new
Xbox experience
That you would need some sort of storage
Device in order to download it because it does take
128 megs of space
Well their solution
For people that
I don't know how they went about
Existing with an Xbox with no storage whatsoever
Because that means you can't save games or anything
They are offering
A free 512 megabyte memory unit
Or for 20 bucks
You can buy a 20 gigabyte hard drive
Now in order to qualify for this
You have to have a core system
Or some arcade systems
May qualify as well
Basically just go to their
Website
They have available for that
Which is xbox.com
Go to their support page
And there is a memory update thing
Where you enter your serial number and console ID
Into the program
And if you are eligible
Let you buy them
If you are not eligible and you happen to have an arcade system
That's the other option
For $29.99 you can get a 20 gig hard drive
And a 3 month live card
Which is not a bad deal either
Now my question
When I got my xbox 360
I have a core
Because I got my system during that time
When xbox 360s were really hard to find
So I just ponied up the 20 extra dollars
Or whatever it was to buy the hard drive
And the core system separately
So is Microsoft going to know that I have had a hard drive this whole time
Or do you think you will qualify for this
Sweet! I get a free memory card
Right?
Awesome!
I'm good! Why not? It's free!
Microsoft doesn't know that I have a hard drive
And even though I do
Why should I be treated differently
From the other owners that bought the core
Early on, early adopters
Yeah!
For 20 bucks you can get a 20 gig hard drive
That could just be the drive I install
Final Fantasy XI on and never use
Or it could be
Or better yet
Because I only have a 20 gig hard drive as it is now
I could have two drives and one of them
Can be like the movies drive
Or it could be the games drive
Why not?
To be honest, I think that's an awesome solution
For their problem
And really, I mean
Who would not have a hard drive
Or a memory unit
I mean, seriously, I could see some people that may have
Only a 64 megabyte memory unit
Say they bought it back when the
Xbox 360 came out and stuff
And they're only using it for, say, save games
But, I mean
I can't imagine someone that would have
An Xbox 360 that actually plays games
That you have to progress in
That does not have a way to save their game
Because that would be kind of retarded
You have to start over every time
I didn't even know they made Xboxes without memories
Well, they don't anymore
I have several people telling me in chat and
Aim and everywhere that, hey, Microsoft's gonna hear
What you just said and you're screwed
But, actually, it may even be before that
No, it's not
Henderson Man in chat says, Sky, I have a core
But it would not let me have a free memory card
That's from Henderson Man in chat
I don't think it's gonna, eh
Now I'm really curious, I'm gonna try it
I'll let you guys know what happens next week
Well, I've got about five different ones we can try
We'll see what happens
I do, actually, I want to get a bigger hard drive
But if I can get a 20 gig hard drive
Another one for cheap, I'll do that switch out idea
I think it's a great idea
So, we'll see
Anyhow, thank you, Microsoft
For giving us some free stuff
Right?
Alright, moving on to some more news
And talking about the Xbox 360
A little further, and the Zune
I don't know how many folks out there actually own Zunes
I know it's got a loyal following
There's a few people out there that own the Zunes
But, you know, they're
They're trying to increase
The amount of flexibility that
Or, I should say, compatibility that occurs between the two
You know, with the media sharing
And, you know, the things that go on between the 360 and the Zune
Well, actually, recently
Some folks were
Over at Gizmodo were talking about the new Gears of War
Zune that's coming out
And they were actually talking to Microsoft's marketing director
And the marketing director
Was talking about that there is going to be a big
Step up
Happening in the Zune 360 integration within
A year
So, that's all, it's a very vague statement
But that supposedly
It's going to step it up within a year
Any thoughts as to what that could possibly be?
Well, they already have the XNA
Support that's supposed to be coming to it
They're going to flesh that out a little bit more
And maybe it would be kind of cool
They actually put some games on there
Like, you know, they could even be like
The Pocket Station stuff where you play a little mini game
You earn points for a game or something
I have a thought, and I bet money I'm right
Movies
You're going to be able to play movies on the Zune that you bought on Xbox
I could see that happening
It's going to be how they're going to compete with iPod
Rob
Remember when they were talking about the Zune E3?
Right
Didn't they bring up something to that effect
That it would be like a multi-entertainment
I remember going in there with my camera
And them telling me to turn it off
At the Xbox 360 thing
And they were talking about having portable content
So perhaps this is what they intended
Cobra Kid says more XNA games to it in chat
That's true, they have that whole XNA thing coming out soon
That could be a big part of it too
So maybe it's all of it
It could be just as much as the iPhone interfaces
With your Mac or even your personal computer
Maybe the Zune will interface with the Xbox 360
Who knows
Will there be enough people that use it
Or just a quick question in chat
Let's say the Zune could do all of those things you suggested
Let's say the Zune can do the XNA games
Let's say the Zune can do the movies
And all that stuff
Would you be interested in a Zune chat room
As opposed to an iPhone
Or any of the other stuff that's out there
Let's say you can only have one player
Would you pick Zune
Comment from Tigerclaw
Tigerclaw says doesn't the Zune have built in Wi-Fi
They could make apps for it
Like for example someone would eventually make an internet radio app
To tune into the shotcast streams over the Wi-Fi
We'll see
We'll come back to that story
Just after we get this next story out of the way
This actually makes me a little bit happy
Even though I already own the game
On multiple platforms
Marvel vs Capcom 2
Which
Honestly I thought the first one was a little bit better
But um
It actually has an ESRB rating now
For PS3 and Xbox 360
So that leads speculation
That it's going to be a
Downloadable version
Maybe like a
Xbox Live Arcade
Or something like that
And that's pretty cool
I mean it's a good game
So I'm looking forward to that
It's a fucking awesome game you mean
By good
It's all about
Playing a Strider hear you anyway
Okay looking at chatroom comments
From the last story because we asked you guys would you get one
And would you get a Zune if they
Implemented all these features
VxJsonXV says Zunes blow
Rama says yes
GameGuru says maybe but I'm more interested in PSP right now
Sharan says sure why not
VxJsonXV continues I have my iPhone
And I'm happy with it
Redertainment says does it do much better than my current touch
If not no I need a gross incentive to jump over
That's how I feel
There's got to be something really big to get me to have a Zune
As well as an iPhone
Cobra Kid says I would have to get a bigger Zune
Deekman says I'm telling you they'll merge the music card and the gamer tag
I didn't even think of that
That could be so we'll see
Alright
So Marvel vs Capcom 2 hopefully coming soon
As it says
Meanwhile some other news
Right Loki?
Sorry someone was stepping on my mic
Are our guests being unruly?
They are being very unruly
They need to be punished
We're playing naughty tic tac toe
Anyways
If you live in Europe you're going to
Be in for a lot of holiday bundles
For the Xbox 360
They are getting quite a few
In fact starting
Well last week actually
The value packs that are available
Pretty much all around the world
Are available for them as well
That includes of course the games packed in
Lego Indiana Jones and Kung Fu Panda
For both the Elite and Pro
And the Sega Superstar Tennis
And of course the Xbox Live arcade games
Starting
Looks like
November 7th
They're going to be getting two more bundles
Both with the 60GB Pro system
And either Gears of War 2 bundled in
Or James Bond 007 Quantum of Solus bundled in
And those are going to both be available
For 269 euros
Starting
The 21st of November
There's going to be another one with
Tomb Raider Underworld
And that's also a Pro system
The 60GB with a 1200
Microsoft points card
And that's also available for 269 euros
And then finally
The Last Stitch effort before Christmas
There's another 60GB Pro system
Bundled with
Prince of Persia
And that will also be for 269 euros
So
A little bit more expensive than your normal games
Your normal Lake Pro system
I mean
Basically you're kind of paying for the game itself
Anyways
But hey that's kind of neat
I guess if you're shopping for the holidays
Lots and lots to pick from
Why do you think so many bundles over there
Are supposed to here?
I think it may have been just
And I'm not even sure if it's actually
It could very well be
Like different
Say bundles that are being
Done by retailers and stuff like that
I don't know if these are official
Or what the case may be
I don't know it's interesting
I guess
Alright well hey one game that they aren't
Bundling in right now is Castle Crashers
Maybe someday
Some people will tell you Castle Crashers is still borked
That it's online multiplayer mode is still
Not that great and we've been waiting and waiting
And waiting for a patch well
Guess what Behemoth the developer of the game
Has just posted on their site this week that
They have figured out how to fix the problem
They have finished the patch and it is
Currently waiting on certification
For Microsoft I'm sorry they are currently verifying
The updates and then they're going to be sending it off to Microsoft
For certification which has probably
Already happened
Kind of took them long enough in a way
I mean with as long as this game took
To come out I mean couldn't they just kind of like
Fix this before it came out
I mean I don't know I guess you know they didn't know
They tested the game they didn't find it
Mistakes happened blah blah blah
But it's a little bit frustrating this game has been out how long
And you still can't really have a multiplayer game on it
But I guess to their credit
You know a lot of people bought this game anyway
And hearing about this patch is just going to cause
Another wave of people
Running out to get this game
Whereas a lot of Xbox Live Arcade titles kind of have
One shot the week they come out
And then they kind of slip into obscurity
Maybe it was pre-planned who knows
I doubt it though
Alright
Well something pre-planned on Orange Lounge Radio is that
Every week we are going to take some time to read your
Emails that you send us to mailbag at
OrangeLoungeRadio.com
Why are you boycotting the mailbag?
I will get you a damn cookie if you read the emails
Hey FartPrincess
Doctor do you guys want
I have flat fortune cookies
They taste like pancakes
Oh my
Well Dark Soccer reads us some email
There is an email that I should have sent in response
To you directly Rob
And I don't know if I should read it on air
Well if you read this first
Then I am going to have to wait on the cookies
Okay you can just read it at your leisure
Well give me a brief idea of what it's about
It's from Spazinator
Hi
Telling you what games you should get for PS3
Oh
Didn't I say, I think I said a while back
About something like I need more
Games that I should
What games?
LocoRoco
Cocorecto
How are there, Lemmings, Elephunk
EchoChrome, WipeoutHD
Everyday Shooter, Super Puzzle Fight
Are you farting glasses?
What are you doing?
Knock it off
Trying to do a show
Wait did they just list
Every game that's not
A list of 36 games Rob
Just basically all the PS3 exclusives
Some
Some are not
To be fair I am going to get a PS3
LittleBigPlanet is out
Sooner rather than later
There is more tips on what else you should get along with
And what you should look for
I am having surgery soon
So you know
Probably having a blu-ray player will be a good thing
As they recover
So let's go on to the next email
While I go get the cookies
The next email
Is actually from
Did you lose a sock?
No I know where my socks are
Cookie!
Bye
Now
Rob
Heart
We love you
So excited for the cookies
Okay
Never mind I was told not to
Read this email on the air
So I've already addressed this situation
Multiple times before
So stop reminding me I know
Heart
And then
We only really have one other email
And it's actually
From
Dan Shadow
Hey guys my nephew's birthday
Was last week so I missed the show
Took him to the movie of his choice
And he chose, wait for it, quarantine
Yeah it sucked so bad
I mean it was so bad
That people would start talking during the movie and no one
Cared, fucking rabies
Anyways
Been trying to catch up on my OLR since I had
To leave in the middle of another episode
Just got one episode on Friday
And I'm sure
I guess you meant to have the word
Rob
I'm on the last email
Rob's gay
I'm sure I'll get the other one soon
Been playing Dead Space this week
I recommend it to anyone who has a good
Sound setup
Thank you, ooh cookie
It's not as scary visually
As much as it is audibly
The visuals are great
They're just not as scary as the
EA's, as EA's been telling all of us
Man can you believe the news this week
LittleBigPlanet gets delayed, Ghostbusters gets
Picked back up and Obama's appearing in video games
Didn't a caller bring that up a few weeks ago
Oh and before I forget
Ballhair says hi
He's got a last name now and he's doing well
He's got a guild and we're at guild level 14
At this moment
And we're talking keeps
And we're taking keeps
Is it Ballhair Jenkins? Oh wait no
Ballhair was a Warhammer character right?
Yeah I'm looking
Ballhair Trimmer
The Dawnbringer
Nice
Ballhair Trimmer
That's lovely
And Ballhair got a guild
Congratulations
That's it for email?
We have one from
Entertainment
Less email, more cookie? Oh yes
One more email
I mean this is actually in response
But we were cc'd on this so I'm gonna read it
Alright
I brought, this is from Entertainment
I bought LittleBigPlanet
On Friday
And found out about the recall right before I sent this message
What the expletive deleted
For Bobby fuck for OLR should I do?
Should I contact Sony
Wait for a patch or keep the game as
A collector's item and buy another copy?
Thank you for your time
Entertainment
Yes that's an awesome idea, let's call Sony
And tell them not only did you break street on the game
He didn't break street, the person that sold it
Broke street
Keep it
And then buy another one
Keep it, collector's item, maybe the serial number or something will be different
Do not open it
Yeah well he probably already did because he didn't know about the
Change
Just hang on to it, Sony's gonna patch it out
Anyway so you're not gonna really have a choice
Cause they're doing both but
The serial number on that box will make
It's gonna be like those pennies that have
Like the misprint on the back
You know those type of things, that's what it's gonna be
If you wanna play your copy
That's been unedited then
Just come in from the internet
Yeah entertainment's in chat right now
It says he already opened it cause how would he know
That it was gonna be recalled so
Can't say I blame you there
Alright let's get back, if that's it for Mailbag
Mailbag at OrangeLawnsRadio.com
While we chow down on cookies
Loki the cookie hater
Here's one more thing
Ow I hit myself in the face with the microphone
Was that the thing?
You know what Rob
One thing that I
Every so often will get an email on
And I'm meant to plug it during my classic game
Of the week
Was a review done by
Sauce
Oh yes I was reading about this on Twitter
And I am getting the link now
Cause if you go to Twitter.com
Slash Mar and Marvel there is a link to it
And her review of
The week is Actraiser
For classic game review
I know isn't it great
We just had an exclamation of
I love Actraiser
So go look at it I'm linking it in the chatroom
And I'll link it on our Twitter
Irene's god name in Actraiser
Is Poop
Oh Actraiser I love Actraiser
How funny that's what I named Link
In Legend of Zelda was Poop
Wow copycat
I named him GGG cause I was lazy
Nice
I named him Zelda so I could get the extra
No I'm kidding
Back to news cookie hater
Okay
Well there is some controversy
Around another game Saints Row 2
Apparently New York
Police unions condemn Saints Row 2
Because well you kill policemen
In the game
And according to them
New York's powerful police unions say that
A violent video
Or a violent new video game called Saints Row 2
Is an abomination
In the game the players control a gang member
Who can steal do drugs
Kill as many characters as possible
Including police officers
Well you said it right there
They're killing everybody so you know what
I'm pissed off at Saints Row 2
Because they're killing doctors
And prostitutes
And college students
And cookies
Do unions for college students coming out
You know
I'm a college student and I'm offended
Or taxi drivers
Or rednecks
Do unions for students exist
They have the student union
I guess that makes sense huh
The whole thing is just like
Okay this doesn't take place in New York
So
God yeah
Because you know what before this game
No one's ever thought hey you know what
We can kill cops in it
This is the first game to ever do that
Thank you for pointing this out
This also I might add
Comes from
WPEC
News 12 now
As you know
They're a CBS affiliate
And I would assume
The New York area
But I could be wrong
Redertainment in chat says I'm mad because they can kill
Redheaded dorks
Me too I should be angered about that too
Actually
So is the doctor he's waving his hand over there I'm pissed too
Yeah I don't even know where the hell this
Takes place it's somewhere on the east coast
That this um
Actual uh newscast is from
To which the legend of Zaku
Promptly follows up and says yay I didn't know
You can kill gingers in the game
Like it's incentive to buy it now
Oh gingers
Alright
Oh North Carolina
Not even close
Rama in chat says news channel 12 is a local
Cable news network
I don't know
Alright well look um
This kind of just dumbass-edness
Always brings on our FUs of the week
And especially since Saints Row
Is a game that Loki loves and adores
How dare the police department condemn it
You can condemn it all they want
Dark Sakura FUs of the week
The election season
All of it
And um
Sarah Palin for thinking she's funny
Loki
Um
God I had something early
That I was mad at about
But I don't remember so
FU to news 12
Because they have
Looks like a
Cast of douchebags that run this thing
They're all kind of ugly in weird ways
Um
My FU of the week goes to still not having
Like a solid date for my surgery
Like I think I know when it's gonna be
But because some people haven't gotten to my
Paperwork I only kind of know that it's
Probably gonna be not
This coming week but the next week
So there you go
Uh fart princess do you have any FUs of the week?
The doctor? Somebody?
I'm the doctor
And I'm mad
At poop
I'm the doctor
Thank you doctor
The parent has one
How about the real doctor?
My FUs is all the
Crazy yes on 8 signs
In Amador County
No you don't even know
It's like a gauntlet you go through town and there's about
70,000 of them
I already went off on Prop 8 last week
So fuck you to everyone in Amador
County who's gonna vote yes on 8
Protect my rights bitch
If it makes you feel better
I already voted and I voted no
Absentee
Fart princess do you have any real
FUs?
FU to poop
Alright
The ferret has one
Oh ferret yes ferret would like me to FU
Thank you very much
I agree with you ferret
The ferret is saying to vote no on 8 as well
Exactly
Alright let's get back into some gaming news
Sellers of Catan you guys know this game from
Xbox Live or you probably know the original board game
Hello
It kind of broke
I found some walls when it came to Xbox Live arcade
Because it was the first, besides Uno
It was the first really in depth board game
To really come out
On Xbox Live and that was really cool
But now it's not gonna stop there
Sellers of Catan is coming out on the Nintendo DS
As well
It's actually gonna be a version of a mobile
Game that's coming out called
Catan the first island but of course
The graphics and such will be much better than they are on mobile
So there's even a trailer up for it
On YouTube and you can take a look at it
And of course if you don't know what Catan is
It's a game about bartering and trading
It's kind of like Civilization and board game format
Except it made no sense to me
When I tried to learn how to play it
But I have a limited attention span for these types of things
What? I was more of a Carcassonne fan
What? Exactly
Who? Yep, you got it
What about carcasses? No
Just no
How about games we do understand
Games where we just shoot and kill things
Well kind of sorta
We have ratings
For the ESRB for stuff to come out on Virtual Console
And that would be
Metal Slug 2
You can ride a camel in it
And the camel has a gatling gun
Watch out, they spit
This one spits bullets
Out of his hip
Awesome
Best camel ever
The other game is
A boy and his blob
Trouble on Blobolonia
This is a DS version that was supposed to come out
Did it ever come out?
I don't think it ever did actually
It never came out
Maybe the publisher went under, I don't know
Get those jelly beans ready
Jelly beans
That's it
Nobody gets that
You have to feed him jelly beans
No, I get that
It may actually have come out
I'm looking, there's a little review
Here
It's actually come out
I'm looking here to see
Oh no, it was cancelled
They had a box art and everything
And the release was cancelled
That's sadness
It didn't really peak my interest anyway
When we went to E3 and we saw it
Rob, that makes my heart hurt
I know, it makes my heart hurt too
But we have a new one coming out
Well the Virtual Console one
Yeah, that's ok
It's the same damn game I've already played
I should just play the Nintendo
Before we get back into some news
I want to take a little detour because you guys got to the show late
You didn't get to talk about your gaming week
But you were telling me, Fart Princess
That there was a game you wanted to talk about
Yes, there is
I've been playing Hello Kitty online
For real, this isn't a joke
No, why would it be a joke?
There really is a Hello Kitty online?
Yeah, didn't you see that person
Post a link in your livestream?
Yes, but it's for the sake of the radio
Rob, I'd appreciate it if you stopped farting
That's really rude
Shut up and tell us about the game
No, I haven't checked it out
Tell us about the game, what do you do in the game?
Do you get to play as Hello Kitty?
No, you play as a boy or a girl character
Do you have a mouth?
I don't remember
I think you do
I'm pretty sure you have a butt too
You can like
You're interrupting me, Rob
What?
What's so funny?
Nothing, go ahead
Rob!
Jeez, Rob, close your eyes
Knock it off, gaming news
I'm not going to let you talk about Hello Kitty
If you don't get to it
Hello farty
You level the traditional sense of an MMO
But there's no
You can't kill anything in the game
Unless you fart on it
The way you level in the game is
Fatal flatulence
Yes, that's totally it
You forage for stuff
Like you gather plants and stuff
And then when you eat it, you go
That was a long fart
Wow, that took all of my breath
My butt breath
Your butt breath?
You're derailing the show, Rob
And you fight enemies too
But you don't kill them
Are they giant enemy crabs?
They are, they're crabs
Or do they just give you crabs?
They might do that too
They might also give you gas
Like
Stop it, Rob
New from Squeenix, fatal flatulence
And that's basically
The gist of the game
Look what you did, Rob
You should be ashamed of yourself
Now I'm thinking there actually should be a game
Called Hello Farty
Alright, stop it
People in the chatroom are complaining about their speakers
They should be complaining about the smell
Can we get on to some gaming?
I thought I would actually learn something about Hello Kitty
I told you about it, all about it
You just farted a lot
You didn't even listen
SSJ100Matt says Rob's gonna write a hate letter to the show
That is true
Uh, Loki
I'm gonna make sure that before the podcast goes out
We strip out all the fart noises
Then it wouldn't make sense
We're gonna patch it for day one release
So that anybody who does obtain the podcast early
Does not get to hear the fart noises
I'm gonna be replaced with birds chirping
Aw, that'd be great
Then we'd be giggling at birds chirping
Alright
I'm gonna be Hello Birdy
How about Rock Band?
Rock Band 2 is coming to the Wii in November
And with it
All the features that you love in Rock Band 2
On the other platforms
Including, you will be able to download
The Rock Band 1 tracks
As well when they become available
And also
That the Guitar Hero 3 controller
Will work with the game now
So that's kinda cool
And of course any additional download content will be available
On the network as well
And you can store them on your SD memory card
So that's kinda cool
Sweet
I played a demo of this and dare I say
I pwned at the drums
Good
Because I suck at drums
So we should start a band
Wait, so you have Rock Band on the Wii?
No, but they had a demo
Oh, I see
So you haven't really played Rock Band
You've been in a Best Buy band
Alright
Anyhow, let's move on and talk about Wii Music
The other type of band game
Wii Music is doing very well in Japan
I know it's been getting a little bit of negative press around the fan
Well actually
Here's what I'm curious about
Doctor
You're a big giant Nintendo whore
Like you love everything Nintendo
Now we're kinda not feeling Wii Music
Nope
By Wii
He means himself
And Loki
I would like to point out that Dark Saga has said she wouldn't pay for it
No
I might have paid for it if I didn't know I was getting one for free
Anyhow
The Doctor
Are you interested in Wii Music at all?
Why not?
I am the biggest Nintendo
And I'm just like
I'm kinda bored with these completely novelty games
Like
You know, there's so many cool things
That they could do on the Wii
And they're just not
And I'm just like, okay, here's another game
Where you get to wave the Wii mode around
And I'm just like, ugh
Alright, well guess what
The country of Japan disagrees with us
And agrees with Dark Sakura
According to Famitsu
I'm sorry, according to Famitsu's publisher
50,000 units were sold on
Day 1 in Japan
So the game is doing huge in Japan
And sold a lot
Like it or not, it looks like this game
Will probably have similar success
Over here, but again, you know
To recap what we've kinda said before on this program
At least myself
If it gets young kids interested in music
It's not a bad thing, but for this old kid
No thank you, I'll pass
So
More gaming news
Just one more
Then we're gonna open up the Skype line pretty soon
At 877-GAME-OLR
Nice plug
Well, this goes back to a series
That was one of the first ones I ever played
When the Playstation first came out
In fact, it was one of the
First games that anyone played
On the Playstation when it first came out
It was Toshinden
I love Toshinden
Actually, the third one was great
Because it was awful
It had the butt monkey in it and the guy with the chainsaw
Named David
He did the butt monkey dance!
Okay
No, he was like a baboon and he had a big red butt
And whenever he went
He would do this little clappy dance
With his butt
So anyway
There's actually news
In Famitsu that says
Takara Tomy is going to be bringing
Out the Toshinden series on the Wii
So maybe they'll actually
Make it better?
Who knows?
You get to spank the monkey's butt
But it looks kinda cool
I love Toshinden
You know, I guess
Retro games making a comeback is nothing new
In this current gen world
I need to go
That just means I need to go find that issue of Famitsu
Wario Land is pretty good for that
Wario Land?
Have you bought the new Wario Land?
It's very good
It's this great 2D animation
It's good
Anyhow, sorry
Let's talk about PC games a little bit quickly
No! Boycott!
Well, there's no boycott
Yet
But Far Cry 2 is going to be bundled with
Everybody's favorite sport
Digital Rights Management
You can get Securom
Technology
Along with Far Cry 2
It will be
It will have these restrictions
The purchasers will have up to
Five activations on three
Separate PCs
Uninstalling Far Cry 2
Refunds in activation
This process is known as a revoke
As long as you properly uninstall the game
You'll be able to reinstall it an unlimited
Number of times on three machines
A computer
Can be upgraded an unlimited
Number of times using revoke
Ubisoft is
Willing to provide additional activations
If necessary
Ubisoft is committed to a long term support
Of their games
And you'll always be able to play Far Cry 2
So apparently
This is what they're going to start doing from now on
I don't understand why they're still using Securom
Technology since it can be so easily broken
And people just hate it in general
But do people as a whole
Do they really seem to care?
Well, not according to EA who says that
With a small percentage
They're claiming that 99.8%
Of consumers will never notice
The digital rights management
That's in the game
Which I think is kind of sad that they don't notice
That it's in there because it could potentially
Harm their system
Especially when it comes to
CD burning software and stuff like that
Whatever that it interrupts
And the fact that these people are unaware
That this game is actually causing this problem
That they will go take it in
And cost them money
But either way they say we can eliminate piracy
By essentially blocking the online service
From the pirate
It's called the future of
Digital rights management
Well, that's nice, you know, but some people don't really care about
The online portion of your game
And they will still pirate it
In fact, I think there was quite a few copies
Of Spore that were pirated
And to be honest, all they're losing
Is the online portion of it
And if you really don't give a crap about seeing other people's penis monsters
Then you can still play the game
LegendofZaco in chat says
Gotta love EA pulling voodoo stats out of their asses
Is that what this is?
I think so
I mean
I don't know, we don't know for sure how many people actually know about it
So we have to take their word for it
It's not necessarily that they're pulling it out of their ass
It's just the way they report the numbers
That's just politics
Anyhow
It's like they think that people that are complaining about it are gonna go
Oh, well, okay
So not that many people are complaining about it
I guess I'll just stop complaining
You're right
No, that's not gonna happen
Anyhow, one more story
Then we're gonna get to some calls on the skype line
And this one has to do with Ghostbusters
You know that game that we hear things about it
Then it goes away, then it comes back
Well, people are talking about Ghostbusters again
And it's all thanks to Dan Aykroyd
Which of course is one of the actors in the original movie
And he was on a Dallas radio station this week
105.3
And he talked to the radio station
And actually confirmed that the Ghostbusters title
Has been picked up by Atari to be published
And said that the game
Will be less than a year away from being released
So apparently
It is confirmed that Atari
Has picked up the game
And Atari will be publishing the game
Don't expect to see it tomorrow, though
They're saying the polish and cleaning up the game
Could take as long as May of 2009
So you'll see this game
At some point next year
That could also mean Christmas 2009
That's crazier than a
Vaporous full torso apparition
Thanks
That makes me giddy
But we're talking about piss in the chat room
Um, okay
Exactly
Chat.orangelandsradio.com for an experience
That really can't be described
Oh my
It's talking about scientific fact
That urine is a sterile solution
Do you ever talk games in the
Area of medical curiosity?
Do you pee on your video games?
Someone brought up peeing in the shower
And I was
I was making fun and doing the girly thing
Who wants to stand in their own piss?
1877 game O.L.R.
Now is a great time
Now is an excellent time
I hope Sigourney Weaver is in the game
Yes, the acidic vampire
Is a very good point
And of course Dark Tetsuya brings up
O.L.R. is like pissing in an ocean of piss
Will the game be nearly as cool
As the Commodore 64 version
Of Ghostbusters? That's what I want to know
Dude, you are red
I love that the first
Half of the show was really smart
And intelligent and the second half has been nothing
But piss and fart
God
This show is just so strange
Maybe our caller
Let's go to the phones
We have a caller, let's see if they're gonna
What IQ level they're at tonight
Hi, you're on Orange Lodge Radio, who's this?
This is Ranma, who is just as immature
As everybody else in the studio
Oh, hooray
Ranma, what's on your mind?
Not much, Rob
I have a bone to pick with you
Oh god, what did I do now?
I'm offended by how you pronounce people's names
Yeah, you know, I find it pretty offensive too
That I can't learn to fucking read
Especially with all the languages
In the world that people derive their names from
I'm very offended that I just don't, like, fucking know
Because, you know, sometimes
You read things one way in one language
And they read another way in another
And I'm offended by my lack of edumacation
You know we love you, Rob, right?
Yeah, I know
Are you just trying to be a smartass about something?
Yes
And what?
But the whole little big plan is just
It's ridiculous, that's all it is
And why do you say ridiculous?
Everybody gets offended over something
And the problem is, not enough people in this world
Is open-minded to realize it's nothing to be
It's nothing that serious
That's all it is
I'm just saying, in a way, how Muslims are kind of being
Like, subjugated
About what's going on in the news and the media
So, of course, something like this they're gonna pick up on
And they're gonna lose their minds about it
Is that really Sony's fault, though?
Because, you know, kind of like I was saying before
If Sony doesn't do anything about this
And then the mainstream media picks up on this
I mean, it's gonna do a lot of damage
Whereas Sony's trying to put out a fire here
Before it gets too big
But why should they?
I mean, it's a normal song, big deal
Sadly, it's the world we live in
And I'm not saying it's alright
It's just, you know, it's what it is
Yeah
What else is on your mind?
Have you been to any cons lately you wanna talk about?
Yes, I just got back from a convention
About six, seven hours ago
You are the con king
What con did you go to this time?
I'm a con whore
I went to Zenkai Con
Where is Zenkai Con?
Valley Forge Convention Center
Valley Forge, Pennsylvania
It's where Classic Gaming Expo was a few years ago
Ah, okay, so how was it?
Was there a lot of gaming stuff to be seen there?
Or was it mostly anime, or what?
It was a mix of A and B
But it wasn't that many video gaming cosplay
But I will say the game room was nice
It was...
It was great
Did you get to play anything in the game room you hadn't played before?
I pretty much, I played the new Bleach game for the Wii
That one I had not played yet
What'd you think?
I thought it was pretty good
I liked the fact that to attack
You actually shake the Wii mode to attack
You attack in the game
Which is something I've never seen in a Wii game before, really
Yeah
Never heard of that one
Well that's cool
What do you think about anime games
On gaming consoles in general
Because a lot of us kind of write them off as crap
Just like a lot of movie and TV show game translations
Are there anime games out there that seem to transcend this
Or are they just crap too?
It depends
I mean, when I got into Ranma 1.5
And then the video game came out
I thought the game was good
But looking back, I kind of hard battled
The only one that came to the states
That was a good one
It didn't really follow the story line though
It was good
Nowadays with a lot of anime games
They're actually taking the story lines
And putting it into the game
If you notice how all the Dragon Ball Z games are
Even though they're rehashes
But they're actually taking the story line
And following along with this
Why there's like five different sequels to a game
What system was this?
I've never played the Ranma
I played a Ranma game on Super Nintendo
That's the one
There's also one on PC Engine
There's an RPG on PC Engine
Which I've played a little bit of
It's kind of hard
On Playstation there was a Ranma 1.5 Battle Renaissance
Which I've got and it's kind of fun
Rice Princess is like Ranma
Because if you pour water on her she goes
Shut up
Did you play Battle Renaissance?
Yeah, I played it
The engine was a little bit loose
But it was still fun
I love actually kicking people's butts
There you go
Yeah
Alright, well any other comments before we get some more calls?
One thing
You'll probably get a real kick out of
I'll have pictures uploaded soon
We had a samba de amigo dance party
At the convention Friday night
Oh dear good lord
How exactly does one go to a samba de amigo dance party?
You get
You show up
You grab the maracas
You start playing
You start freestyling and dancing
First few minutes no one really showed up
But as the music started blasting
We had a line going all the way down
People just wanted to get up and have fun with it
We were giving out little maracas
As prizes
We had sombrero hats giving them out to
Where we could do the best funky dance ever
You should put that on YouTube
Promptly
If it's not up now it should be up by later this week
And I will find images and links
And I'll send it to you guys
Alright Rama we gotta let you go
But have a good one buddy
You too enjoy
Our username on skype is OrangeLoungeRadio
If you want to give us a call
Hi you're on OrangeLoungeRadio who's this?
Hello OrangeLoungeRadio
Is he who seeks to replace
The train wreck of the general masses
With the train wreck of his own choosing
Hello
R
Introduce yourself
Bob Adrian of Hydra
I know who you are
But you have to introduce yourself to the listeners
I'm Jason
Alright what's on your mind
Since we ever so briefly touched on it
I thought I'd add in a couple little comments
Since we didn't really go onto it
Two side notes before I do that
Jump Superstars while it wasn't really
An anime game to the same extent
You were talking about
A good game, it was a very good fighter
Not one that I've really
I'm not much of a fighter person but I had a lot of fun with Jump Superstars
I played that a little bit and it is fun
And the other side note
Has anybody even played
The DR Universe series?
Yeah I have the first game
I don't have the second game
I have the first game and although quest mode
Was awful awful awful I like the song list
And steps of what there was
When I bought my
Xbox I have quite a few
Other games as well but my initial reasoning
For wanting to buy it was pretty much purely
The UltraMix series
And they were great
And then E3 came around with the
Universe redone banners from
Boring hell
And I've just never cared to play the
Universe series at all
Yeah but past the banners it's kind of nice to have the game
In high def and wide screen
It's a neat little change for the game
It probably is I don't doubt that
But I mean UltraMix was never
The most visually appealing game in the first place
I don't think anybody is going to deny that
It played really well past the first one
But it never looked that way
Universe 2 was kind of just like Universe 1 from what I
Understood but Universe 3 is supposed
To be a lot different so I'm
I'm curious I'll check it out probably
Funny all this from
The Bimani series
The Bimani show that was and
Is only a footnote now
Yeah well you know and a lot of shows
Still don't even talk about it at all and a lot of shows
Would just say oh it's another
DDR game they're all the same and to some
Extent they're right but there are
There are definitely those differences out there
Well now it's time to talk about it
And in the process talk about me
Kind of, not really
Funny story, have you guys heard of the
There's a sim file that DMSura
Made quite a while ago called DeltaMax
Ever heard of it?
Yes, vaguely, I know what DMSura
Is but I vaguely know
The gimmick so to say about it
Isn't it that you hit all four notes
At once or something?
That's an old gimmick but that's okay
I don't
The gimmick is that it's a
DMSura remix of the Max series
And it starts at I think
130 beats per minute
And ends at 573
Is that the one, oh okay
Is it the one that rolls backwards because I remember that being
A gimmick too, alright
Okay so it starts
It's all progression, 130 to 573
It's kind of like a
BPM per measure
But it speeds up
The speed is not statically
Increasing, it is very variable, it goes with the
Tune, it's actually really cool
There's a step mania cabinet
That a friend of ours built into
The DDR machine down in Colorado Springs
That there's a tournament going on
At next month, not that anybody
Hey if you're in the Colorado area come down to Mr. Big's
Next weekend rather, not next month
There's going to be a lot of cool people there
Ding, that's my plug for the day
So he has a step mania
Cab with all of the official DDR songs
A ton of sim files, delta max
Being one of them and a couple of other little
Bonus extras like in the groove
I was very very
Disappointed to hear that
Delta max in universe
3 isn't going to have
The sim created background
Video, because if it
Did I could have claimed a
My own little piece of assistance
Property in a DDR official game
Why did you do
Something with this?
There's a person nicknamed
Tora that I
Believe he actually did all of the background work
Basically, I don't even remember what the
Image background is, but he
Created a series of text of all of the beats per minute
All the BPM numbers
And they have this
Shaky fluid effect
And he put the
Videos for that together amazingly
But what I did was I wrote out a quick
Little script to actually put
In the changes that he wanted to
And again it goes up
It was a pain in the ass
Too
Just the changes in the videos
The fact that it's not just linear straight up
Calculating which measurement and time that it happens on
I barely even remember
That was like 3 years ago
But it was a very awesome video
It was very simple
But Konami came in and changed it all?
They want to do their own thing probably
It'll be flowers and sparkles
No it's
Universe, it'll be spaceships
And Uranus
On that note
It'll be a lot of
Delta triangles flying over the screen
Because you know, Delta and
Triangles
Oh my god, trigonometry, no!
Well sorry to hear you just missed your chance
For remote video game stardom
Hey you have OLR stardom
Any other things you want to say
Real quick before we move on?
No I think that was my excuse
For calling in tonight
Well Jason take care, thanks for your comments
Alright guys
We'll take one more call
1877 game OLR, username on skype
Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call
And then we have some last minute stories to do
Before we get on out of here, hey live listeners
You'll want to stay tuned tonight
Past the show, we have a little treat for you guys
We'll get into that in a little while
Be sure to join us next week for episode 300
Do you think though that they might have
Lasted a lot of sales chance because a lot of the
People that would have been interested in this are just going to go to
The fan translation? I guess let me rephrase
How many of the people that end up playing the fan
Translation do you think would turn around and buy something official
From Nintendo?
That's a good question
I myself would buy the official thing
If it were to come out
In fact the translators encourage
Buying the official
Merchandise and stuff
But as far as the
Nintendo side of things I just hope that
If they
Decide to do something like sue the translators
Or something like that
It means that
That they're working on an official translation
That they're not just going to leave it
Dead. You know I think a lot of people
Are like you and you know if they're real true
Fans of the series they would buy an official
Translation anyway but do you think there's some people
That would feel so slighted that once they play
Through the translation they're just going to be like
Yeah screw the real one
Yeah that's a good
That's a good point
Kind of like when I
Like I used to download
A lot of like money songs
They're like buying it and stuff
Nah screw buying the real thing
I'll just keep it
Especially with the import stuff
Well I guess we will see
I'm very curious to see if it does
Catch the attention of people in Nintendo
I'm waiting for the cease and desist myself
Any other thoughts for our listeners tonight
Yeah
Sky you're in Milpitas Golf Land
Damn we need to come down to Sunnyville Golf Land again
Um you know I know I knew
I was in the area just it worked out
So that we were at Milpitas and I didn't make it over there
But I'll get to Sunnyville at some point
I'm sure
Yeah maybe the NorCal division of the
All-Armor can meet up there
We'll see we'll see you know um
With the surgery coming up and everything it won't be anytime soon
But who knows maybe by the end of the year
Yeah I was saying
We're going to Svega Lailies
For Popin' 16
Oh hey I like popin' music
It's certainly better than beatin' groovy
Yeah I've gotten back into it recently
Yeah
I might get a job
Like I'm possibly getting a job
Where in the winter I might use the money to get a desktop arcade
So I can play the real thing at home
Instead of frickin' 9 key 2DX
Good times good times
I wish I
I wish I had that kind of disposable income
But then again I'm looking at my new iPhone
When I'm saying that
We all have priorities
Alright GS6 here we gotta let you go
But have a good one buddy
Alright bye bye
You know Dekeman in chat has a good point
He says they've had two years to give them a cease and desist
Sometimes it's not until you start getting noticed
Like hello in the groove
Remember that?
Nobody cared until they tried to put out a home version of the game
Alright anyway
Last minute stories
DarkSoccer anything for us tonight for last minute stories?
Yeah
What?
Fire
Loki you always have something for last minute stories
Yeah a few more things real quick
We know that Guitar Hero they're talking about
Making god knows how many games next year
Well there's yet another one that's been
Discovered
A trademark has recently been placed
For the title
Guitar Hero Modern Hits
And no word on exactly what that is
Of course the term hit is relative
Exactly
Who knows
If I were to take a guess I think it's another DS version
It sounds like a DS version to me
That's a good point
It's pretty vague
Alright
Grand Theft Auto San Andreas will be coming to
Xbox Live Marketplace
As an Xbox original
Starting well actually
This Monday October 20th
So you'll be able to download the full game
For $15 or
1200 Microsoft Points
So that's pretty cool
Also
Fable 2
You should definitely go to
Microsoft's website
They have a special website made for Fable 2
Xbox.com
I believe you just go to the Fable 2 page
They have a little game that you can play
Including Chicken Kickin
You can actually win prizes
For your in-game character
So you can win gold and different prizes
In Fable 2
Playing this Flash game
Which I think is pretty cool and hasn't been done before
So hopefully you see some more
Website integration with different games
If it's not another week
With another movie announcement
Based on a game
Well Grant Morrison is now
Doing the Area 51 game
You know what though? Max Payne was number one
At the box office this week beating that very
Hyped W movie
So there's money to be made
Yeah
So interesting
Area 51 the movie
Hopefully it's cheesy and motion captured
Then there's
Going to be some new download content for Mega Man
9 coming soon including a brand new
Bonus level with a bonus boss
Fake Man
And you'll be able to purchase
That for 100 Wii
Points
Will it not be impossibly hard?
Probably not
But it's a brand new special stage
Oh my god I can't play that game
And lastly to kind of talk a little bit about
Another game that
We'll be seeing a little bit more pretty soon
Little Big Planet
They actually have some more videos from the beta
Someone has actually recreated some of the levels
From Mirror's Edge
In this game
So you can actually play some of the Mirror's Edge
In the beta and of course the full game
When it comes out because all those levels are
Being transferred over which is pretty
Freaking awesome
And that's it
Well that's going to do it for tonight's episode of
Orange Lounge Radio but before we
Finish the show tonight we got to go around and get everybody's
Final thought
Fart Princess thank you for coming to the show
When you did and everything
Do you have a final thought for us?
Even though you were late
Vote no on Poop 8
The Doctor
Do you have any final thoughts?
Don't vote for McCain
He's crazy
We're getting a little political tonight
Loki do you have
A final thought?
My costume
Is freaking awesome
And you may see it next week
Is it Tingle?
It's a video game character
Okay
My final thought is
Mentos
Fresh and full of life
Darsakha your final thought?
I fucking love Ichiban Khan
Ichiban Khan
USA.com
I shop there every time I'm in San Francisco
Sounds good
Alright next week episode
300 of Orange Lounge Radio
What guests and surprises await the crew?
What messages
Will you guys leave for us on our skype line
When we're not live?
Will it potentially be a fuck show?
Who knows all that to be determined
In one weeks time
Come back for episode 300
Of Orange Lounge Radio next week
Hey if you enjoyed what you heard tonight
Tell two friends about the show
That's how we spread the word
And if you don't have any friends
Just kidding even if you do
Buy them
You should post a review on our iTunes
On the store and I'll post the link in chat
And leave us a nice 5 star review
Yes every little bit helps
The more listeners we have the better
Because it's not about awards
It's about listeners
About you guys that show up every week
So thank you guys so much
Have a good one we'll see you next time here on Orange Lounge Radio
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio
Orange Lounge Radio
Is an Orange Lounge production
To join us for a live show
Visit www.allgames.com
Sunday nights at 6 pm Pacific time
The views and opinions expressed
On Orange Lounge Radio
Do not necessarily reflect
Those of the entire staff
Of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com
But we're probably right anyway
See you next week!