[SPEAKER_19]: Votants!
[SPEAKER_19]: Ready your breakfast and eat hearty.
[SPEAKER_19]: For tonight, we dine in hell!
[SPEAKER_26]: 2008, E3 as we remember it is coming back, has PlayStation Home been hacked, and zombies are invading some of our favorite games.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's episode number 300 here in studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you believe it?
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's just a crap ton of people here in house.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the neighbors are going to call thinking that we're getting broken into or raped or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orgy!
[SPEAKER_07]: We are the...
[SPEAKER_07]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_22]: How many of us are not wearing shoes?
[SPEAKER_07]: Officer.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think there's an orgy going on next door.
[SPEAKER_22]: We are officially a Mississippi orgy.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a no on eight sign in front of their house.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a gay orgy going on in our neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_22]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Laundry.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was the most gay I've ever heard you sound ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not me, where have you been?
[SPEAKER_07]: Believe it or not, we're a podcast dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle, and it is just madness tonight here on Orange Lounge Radio in the studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: My name is Rob Roberts, and joining me as always, say hello to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_22]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_07]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: and also say hello to what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Say hello to Sackboy Loki!
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, the visuals for this are just too much.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're watching tonight on Justed TV, Loki is actually wearing a ginormous Sackboy costume.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, he's finally dressed up for the listeners.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're very excited.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately, it's not Tingle, but he is wearing a Sackboy costume.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if he sounds a little muffled, that's because the microphone is like inside the Sackboy costume.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: And not in a dirty way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_22]: That would give a whole new meaning to talking out of his ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is horrible radio, but the visual of it is just way too funny because Sackboy's mouth doesn't move.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's why people need to be watching Justin TV.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, podcast listeners.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess this one just isn't going to make much sense to you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Also joining us tonight... They can go on Justin.TV and check the highlights.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, because I know the listeners are highlighting this on Justin.TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our username is OrangeLoungeRadio.
[SPEAKER_07]: All one word.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have a lot of guests here in the studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some new faces and some old faces.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to quickly introduce folks, because you might just... I guess we have introduction music.
[SPEAKER_22]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you, program.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, look.
[SPEAKER_07]: What show would it be without a technical fuck-up, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: In the first five minutes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, say hello to some of our guests tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Joining us, representing the women here, holding it down with DarkSakura, say hello to Mel!
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi Mel, you can grab the mic, it's okay, it won't bite unless you ask.
[SPEAKER_07]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think you've been on the show before, if it has been a long, long time.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, I haven't been on the show before.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so quickly, what kind of games do you like to play?
[SPEAKER_23]: A lot of shit on my DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo DS fangirl.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, also joining us tonight, a very familiar face from the past, say hello to Drew Nami.
[SPEAKER_07]: Madness?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is Orange Lounge!
[SPEAKER_07]: Now the cops are really going to get called.
[SPEAKER_07]: Say hello as well to The Doctor.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm The Doctor.
[SPEAKER_07]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's 300 shows!
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm naked!
[SPEAKER_22]: Really?
[SPEAKER_22]: And you're on camera.
[SPEAKER_07]: Say hello as well to a person who has not been here in a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: When was the last time you were here?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, two or three years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: Say hello to Arcadian42.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yes, a dark shadow from the past returns for destruction.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what kind of, since you haven't been on the show in so long, what kind of games do you like?
[SPEAKER_07]: I like Adventure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sega, Sega, and more Sega.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Sega.
[SPEAKER_29]: I haven't played some Sega games in a while.
[SPEAKER_29]: But I have loads of Saturn games and Genesis and all that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: And when he grows up, he wants to be Sega Tassanchiro.
[SPEAKER_07]: His house really is like a Sega museum, I just want to point out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, is this gentleman going to introduce himself too?
[SPEAKER_07]: And you are?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hiccup Boy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hiccup Boy?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that your online name?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hiccup Boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of games are you into, Hiccup Boy?
[SPEAKER_04]: RPG and first-person shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the best RPG of all time?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ever?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to have to go with Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get out of my house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy VI, way better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about points?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I go with 9?
[SPEAKER_04]: 9 runs number 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: 9 is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least you didn't say 11.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: No me gusta.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, no, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: We like having a variety of opinions here in the studio, even when they're wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, let's welcome the chat as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com, joining us as they do every week here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: If it's your first time listening to Orange Lounge Radio, pardon the madness.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a little crazy tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yes, we started this show on June 23, 2002 on our live 365 feed.
[SPEAKER_07]: And here we are six and a half years later on All Games Radio with our 300th episode.
[SPEAKER_07]: So a big thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_22]: It was a big fable.
[SPEAKER_22]: I didn't do much playing in it, however Dan did, and he's been throwing fire at people and showing off his trophy, which I think is entirely, and flipping everyone off, which is just the best ever.
[SPEAKER_22]: His guy looks kind of like a gorilla, with a red coat, and it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I've decided that when I play Fable 2, I'm going to make the biggest raging lesbian ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're still a chicken chaser, you chase chickens.
[SPEAKER_22]: I've, okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: And, but he had to do the thing where he had to wear dreads and mutton chops and the dress and they said it was the wrong dress.
[SPEAKER_22]: And that was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I've been playing Ragnarok, of course.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I got my DS, finally.
[SPEAKER_22]: However, it's not here.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's at home.
[SPEAKER_22]: But Dan got me a black DS.
[SPEAKER_22]: Much, very similar to Melchon's black DS.
[SPEAKER_22]: You have a blue one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except Melchon has like a little Star Wars thing on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Little stickers.
[SPEAKER_22]: I could totally bust out my Miyamoto stickers, though, from E3 a few years ago.
[SPEAKER_22]: But, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I have a nice one.
[SPEAKER_22]: I babysat yesterday too Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes Did you play any games with the baby?
[SPEAKER_22]: We went to the jungle gym and played Let's Splash All of the Water in the Fountain
[SPEAKER_22]: and um baby's gonna slide down whether you're at the bottom to catch him or not and let's see how many times catch the baby and it was also let's let's see how often Julian will run back to the swings and beg to be in it only to not do anything but look at the other children
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the Orange Lounge Radio official game should be something a lot like WarioWare where all the little micro games are like little in-jokes from the show and there should be one where DarkSakura is there with a big net and it says catch and babies start falling and there's babies falling from the sky I do have to say he's such a good kid that he's the reason why I'm no longer afraid of most babies in small numbers, namely one do you want to eat them like Shane?
[SPEAKER_22]: No.
[SPEAKER_22]: Shane has subscriptions.
[SPEAKER_22]: We heart you, Shane, but you've got subscriptions.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's not listening.
[SPEAKER_07]: He hates this show.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, he hates everything that he likes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_22]: High School Musical!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Lord.
[SPEAKER_07]: My God!
[SPEAKER_07]: You're cut off.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, Sackboy, SackLoki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't play that much this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mainly, I played LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually... I'm now in the Japanese level, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm dressed up like a ninja, and I've got a... I'm a ninja pirate, because I'm wearing the ninja head, and I've got the pirate outfit, and I'm carrying a frying pan.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And how is Everyone's a Little Bit Racist the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty good, but apparently it's not going to be as racist soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_07]: We were looking at it on Justin.TV last week after the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like a little present for our live listeners.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we saw a bunch of like, you know, the Africa level is all the Africa stereotypes.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, the South America level is all those stereotypes.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, the America level was hot dogs and cheeseburgers.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, actually it was race cars and jazz.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you got them out of Casgar, will they shut down everything?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I'm glad, though, when they did fix the song, that they didn't actually remove it from the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just edited out the lyrics, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the song itself is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to be honest, if the lyrics aren't in there, I'm not sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: But other than that, I've been playing Saints Row 2 multiplayer, because that's fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still glitchy.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, we found a new trick now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, if you throw satchel charges on people, because you can actually stick them to other players.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I, for example, stick multiple satchel charges on them, when they respawn, they still have the ones that haven't exploded yet, so you can detonate them again and kill them again, which is kind of a boo-boo there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, oddly enough, I've been watching someone play Fable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you guess who was playing Fable 2?
[SPEAKER_05]: Harvey.
[SPEAKER_05]: My wife.
[SPEAKER_05]: is playing Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, your wife, the game hater, is playing Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, she's playing Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's how it happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: She saw the commercial for it that they have now where the guy's playing with the little, I forget what you call those things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Balls?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not balls.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's all, yeah, set it up for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I set it up for her, kind of helped her walk through it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now she's way further in the game than I am.
[SPEAKER_05]: But granted, I've only played the game for like less than an hour.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, but she was like literally when I was leaving today to go finish my costume before I came over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: She was just like, okay, I got to quit in like half an hour because I have to go to the gym.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she's just seriously contemplating not going to the gym to play the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just getting to that point.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know it brings back memories of Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, a proud gamer moment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you a proud gaming husband now?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think she's going to get bored of it because she's not paying attention to any of the storyline or any of what's supposed to be going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's like, kill, kill, die, die, die, kill, kill, die, die, die.
[SPEAKER_05]: It keeps giving her helpful hints like, you know, her life is slow, you should go find an inn or some potion.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's like, I don't know where the hell the inn is!
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, go to one of the towns!
[SPEAKER_05]: She's like, I went to the towns, there's no inns there!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's read some comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com By the way, I know we have a lot of people on Justin TV tonight because of Loki being Sackboy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what it is, if Justin TV highlighted us or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: But please keep in mind we only read our regular chat room at Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com That's not because we hate you guys at Justin TV, but it's because, well, it's partially that.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have a real hard time reading two chat rooms at once because we are trying to do a show here.
[SPEAKER_07]: So chat.orange.com Redertainment in chat says the last time I skipped the gym to game was five years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't been back to the gym since.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm assuming that's it for Loki's Gaming Week, so I'll talk about my Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I finally bought a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why are you booing?! !
[SPEAKER_07]: because Wizards and Thugs at least there's good games out now at least you didn't buy it just because oh I want to play there's two good games out now no now now there were finally games I wanted out I want LittleBigPlanet even though I wasn't able to get it yesterday contrary to popular rumor but I have it all set up I have a blu-ray disc at least I have Edward Scissorhands on blu-ray because that movie is awesome
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to get an M before Christmas, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: It looks good on the ring.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'd like to mention, though, that last week I was concerned that I may have to return my copy a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: You motherfucker, it's my turn.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I didn't have to, thank God.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I get to keep the slightly offensive version.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so yeah, I finally took the plunge and got a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: For SingStar ABBA as well, even though that's not out until December.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I did buy SingStar PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, the game itself is kind of crappy compared to, like, Rock Band and other songs you can sing in.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I will tell you the best thing about SingStar PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, there's a couple good things about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a really good party game because it has the music videos in the back.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a good game for non-gamers, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, it's a good game for people to just pick up the mics and sing and have fun with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: and there are a lot of songs on the sing store even though I haven't heard of half of them there's like 300 songs on that store but I'll tell you the best part is that part that's like YouTube that you can go in there and look at the community videos I don't have a webcam myself thank you very much I don't want to put myself on there I do no don't worry about it but
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess this is growing up
[SPEAKER_07]: She's so cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so that's the best part of the game is just going on like the YouTube type thing and looking at that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I had fun with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not for everyone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get it if you have a lot of parties.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you're a solo gamer, I don't think there's a lot here for you unless you like to sing to yourself.
[SPEAKER_07]: Otherwise, I'm just holding out for LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'll probably be going back to the 360 in the meantime.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, I will say this.
[SPEAKER_07]: PlayStation 3 has... I gotta say, that Blu-ray player is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it does upscale the old movies pretty good on DVD.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the media server, I thought, was a lot easier to use than Microsoft's.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, the media server's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was really surprised.
[SPEAKER_07]: That kind of surprised me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was thinking that the 360 media server would be a lot easier because, you know, hello, Windows, Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, the PlayStation 3 one was disgustingly simple.
[SPEAKER_05]: However...
[SPEAKER_07]: here's a word of advice for you folks don't run the media server and your internet connection at the same time because your internet connection can't hold it on the Playstation 3 that's the one thing about it so
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was pretty much my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Otherwise, I haven't played a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aurora Faint on the iPhone, which is pretty awesome for a free game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game is all kinds of awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: I had another game.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_22]: I downloaded Pole Position Remix.
[SPEAKER_07]: How'd you like that?
[SPEAKER_22]: It's actually surprisingly easy to play, but I still suck at Pole Position.
[SPEAKER_22]: But the crashes and everything are fantastic.
[SPEAKER_11]: I suck at Pole Position.
[SPEAKER_07]: BlackWolf in chatroom says, confirmed, Rob likes parents exploiting children on the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you don't do this, you don't get to eat.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Ross D.O.U.T.
[SPEAKER_07]: says, Rob, I have media server and internet running at the same time, no problem.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Congrats to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, it didn't work right for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob's special.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, my special.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now I have all the next gen systems.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did get, you know, if you got Pole Position on the phone, I will say I got Pac-Man on the iPhone, which is kind of neat because you can do motion.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can tilt it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, you play it once and then it's over, so just get the free trial.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't pay for it.
[SPEAKER_22]: But the pull position one, though, honestly, it really is playable.
[SPEAKER_22]: And on top of that, not only can you have it use your tilt to turn left or right, you can choose to have your accelerator or your brake on screen.
[SPEAKER_22]: Or you can actually have a steering wheel on screen to steer with.
[SPEAKER_22]: Or you can use a slider.
[SPEAKER_22]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm looking in chat, and I lied, I looked at JustinTV chat for a minute, and a person by the name of SonyPS3Sucks, who I'm sure is just thrilled to hear my news this week, says that Jelly Car is on iPhone for free.
[SPEAKER_07]: I forgot about that, I read about that somewhere, and that was actually a really awesome game on the XNA service, the little beta thing they had there, so I really want to check that out on iPhone.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_23]: it's actually pretty neat it's got an interface that you can trace the writing so you can really learn your brush strokes and stuff it's got a bunch of fun little games to play that actually really have been helping my memory and helping me remember the shit that I learned a few years ago when I actually did take Japanese class
[SPEAKER_07]: Would you say that it's something that somebody could pick up and learn Japanese with, or is it better as a supplement to an actual Japanese class?
[SPEAKER_23]: I think it's better as a supplement to an actual Japanese class, but it is nice because it does have a dictionary and a phrase guide thing built into it, so if you are somewhere and you need to say something that you don't exactly know how to say, you can look up real quick and be like, this is what I need to say, this is how I have to say it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Drew, what's one thing you've been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: World of Warcraft, The Burning Cr- Brains.
[SPEAKER_07]: Brains.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have a story coming on that later, but how's Wobbengal?
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you excited about Lich King?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, very excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been leveling with Chimera lately.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks to that Recruit a Friend thing, triple experience.
[SPEAKER_03]: She and I are going through Outlands as Mage and Warlock.
[SPEAKER_03]: 6G3 so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a blast.
[SPEAKER_07]: What are you most looking forward to about Lich King?
[SPEAKER_03]: Death Knights.
[SPEAKER_07]: That and motorcycles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Doctor, who by the way brought us some mushrooms for the studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if you can see them on Justin.TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you hold one up for the Justin.TV folks?
[SPEAKER_07]: What the mushrooms look like here?
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And those are awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you make those just for this, or did you steal those from your work?
[SPEAKER_11]: Last year at my work, we did Mario as the theme for Halloween.
[SPEAKER_11]: So one of my coworkers made them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, thank you for stealing them and bringing them here.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's one game you've been playing this week, Doctor?
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, Hiccup Boy's gotten me back into DDR, which, oh my god, that's like the best exercise ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've lost some weight, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, maybe.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, just today.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, because my hand's all sweaty from DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: What kind of DDR?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's old school DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like
[SPEAKER_11]: Arcadian, Sonic Chronicles DS
[SPEAKER_07]: DS, and that's like what, it's all the old school Sonic games?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's a new RPG.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I thought it was actually called Sonic RPG.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, how is it?
[SPEAKER_29]: Good?
[SPEAKER_29]: It's pretty good so far.
[SPEAKER_29]: I've played like three or four hours.
[SPEAKER_29]: Halfway through the second mission.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is there any other RPGs you can kind of compare to?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's a little bit different because you're kind of moving around with the stylus.
[SPEAKER_29]: Actually, because there's an interesting system where if you've got to chase the enemies or run away from them, so you basically have the characters running away or running towards the...
[SPEAKER_29]: Subtitles by the Amara.org community
[SPEAKER_29]: from hitting the boxes so that they can catch up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sounds like this game might be redeeming the Sonic franchise a little bit after a relatively last few weak years.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I haven't played any of the games in a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's for the best, Bradley.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to stay a Sega fanboy, you probably should stay away from them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's also ask KickUpBoy, what's one game you've been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I kind of haven't gotten over COD 4 at all yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, a shooter fan.
[SPEAKER_22]: Isn't that game good?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except you get those people that are just like, oh, on one-on-one I can kick your ass, and then we go on one-on-one and they leave shortly after that.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would you say is the singular best thing about that game?
[SPEAKER_04]: The best thing has got to be just... There's not just one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you looking forward to COD5?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yes and no.
[SPEAKER_04]: They kind of went back in time, so I'm kind of like, oh, I feel like back to the future kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's something they need to do in COD5 they didn't do before?
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to make sure no juggernaut is allowed because that's just kind of wimpy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our username on LiveJournal is Orange Lounge Or on MySpace, we're Orange Lounge Radio On Facebook, we're the OL Army And now on Twitter, we're OLR Yes, that's four different sites and four different names Go figure, it just never works out Also, I want to say this Since we've been doing this diligently for 300 episodes We are taking next week off There will be no show next week So there you have it Because we earned it We will be providing live footage of a colonoscopy
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not having a colonoscopy, but you guys might remember if you've been listening to the show this year, I had some medical issues back in April that kept me out of the show for a week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm having surgery Wednesday, and that's why there's not going to be a show on Sunday because I'm still going to be recovering.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm having a gallbladder removal.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure I mentioned this a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other people have had it done.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's laparoscopic, so it's not going to be a big deal, but I am planning to pretty much be out of everything for a week.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So now you'll understand.
[SPEAKER_07]: So no kicking and screaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take a chance to play some more games or listen to one of our other wonderful shows that we co-broadcast with on All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: So let's move into some gaming news then tonight, I think, if we're ready.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you may remember the new PSP 3000 was announced and has finally made it to the market.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although it's not really being received that well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Problem is, apparently the new advanced LCD screen that's on it is causing some issues with scan lines.
[SPEAKER_05]: Noticeable scan lines and it looks very bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is now a little bit brighter, and the colors are a little bit better, but the scan lines look like crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Sony is apparently looking into the problem right now, but no sort of fix is being done.
[SPEAKER_05]: And since this is a phenomenon that is caused by hardware characteristics, there is no plan to fix it with the system software update.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you might want to hold on to those PSP-2000s and forego the built-in microphone and, I don't know, better, questionably better LCD screen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or maybe just wait a little while for it to get fixed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it possible that they're going to, like, kind of fix these?
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to have to replace them if that's the case.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, what's kind of interesting also is that it seems like there might be some type of very quiet under-the-radar recall going on right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess it's because people are complaining about this, and apparently the description actually got this slight word change going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Instead of saying the system features an improved LCD screen, it says the system features an advanced LCD screen.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can kind of see that they might be kind of admitting that there's something going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of reminds me of, was it, if anyone's watched Invader Zim, when he's introduced to his sidekick, Gur, he's like, he kind of looks broken.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're all, he's not broken, he's advanced.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's the other interesting thing is that Amazon.com just suddenly canceled a bunch of pre-orders for the PSP 3000.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some folks had the limited edition 4GB memory entertainment pack for this thing reserved.
[SPEAKER_07]: Amazon sent everybody emails that said that the item was not available from the sources, so that they canceled all the orders.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, in fact, we got something similar to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were expected in...
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: Play it in stores and see if it's something that bugs you that bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I bet to a lot of gamers, they're not going to give a shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: To be honest, it looks pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's a lot of PSP 2000 systems out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And really, all you're supposedly improving is the LCD screen, which obviously is not improved this time, and a built-in microphone.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if microphones aren't really a big deal for you, I mean, you can go buy one for like $20.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I would just maybe hold off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do you need to buy another system?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, after all, the last system update came about a year ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well.
[SPEAKER_07]: What was that, Meltan?
[SPEAKER_07]: She didn't have a mic.
[SPEAKER_23]: I said not to mention there's hardly any new PSP games coming out.
[SPEAKER_23]: They're like, here's a bunch of new systems to throw at you.
[SPEAKER_23]: We've got like 20 games coming out in the next six months.
[SPEAKER_23]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we'll see what continues to develop over there and hopefully some PSP games.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of good stuff in 2009.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_22]: That could possibly be, but honestly, you know my opinion on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_22]: Actually, it's the same opinion I have on any system.
[SPEAKER_06]: It stinks.
[SPEAKER_22]: Only as good as the games that are on it.
[SPEAKER_22]: It does have Popolocross, which is a cute game.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, this comes as an absolute surprise to no one.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because, what?
[SPEAKER_22]: Do you just like gasping into the microphone as if you're in a porn?
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm no one.
[SPEAKER_22]: Do that a little bit more throaty.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_22]: Now, you have to mimic the master here.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway, well, the game was trademarked in July, but there is going to be Star Wars The Old Republic, which is the MMO that's based off of KOTOR, Knights of the Old Republic.
[SPEAKER_22]: Also the term coined by our friend Krista Skrotor when she worked for Lucas back in the day.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway, with this, it's supposed to be 300 years after Knights of the Old Republic 2, which is 3,500 years before the film, and you can choose between either the Republic or the Sith Empire.
[SPEAKER_22]: You can either be light side or dark side, but you can be one of those alignments within whatever your faction is.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I guess you could be chaotic neutral or lawful evil or, oh wait, wrong game.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: There's two classes that have been revealed already.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's the Sith, the Jedi, and they use lightsabers, and the Force, and we have no idea when it's coming out or what it's coming out on.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, but, but, can I kill Jar Jar Binks?
[SPEAKER_22]: Jar Jar has not been born yet or conceived.
[SPEAKER_22]: She could probably find... Can I find Jar Jar's super great grandma and kill her?
[SPEAKER_22]: And cut off the fishy cock.
[SPEAKER_07]: The fishy cock?
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you just tell me to go slice off the fishy cock?
[SPEAKER_11]: Fish do not have cocks.
[SPEAKER_11]: They deposit their eggs into the ocean.
[SPEAKER_22]: But they're supposed to be humanoid creatures, so I assume that there's some cock involved.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's always talking about... They're aquatic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, needless to say, the internet and the gamers on the internet all had a... Needless to say, the collective internet gamers had a giant orgasm when this game was announced.
[SPEAKER_07]: All their fish cocks went off at once.
[SPEAKER_07]: In a fountain of... There's a lot of people definitely looking forward to a KOTOR MMO.
[SPEAKER_22]: In a fountain of... Tamago.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've heard there are people that are going to leave WoW for this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just like you and I are going to go play Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_22]: but I'm not leaving well because guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I am.
[SPEAKER_22]: I already left.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck your KOTOR.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got Star Trek MMO coming out.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're going to have some Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a Star Trek MMO coming out?
[SPEAKER_11]: Where the fuck have you been?
[SPEAKER_11]: Can I cream my shorts right now?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I love Star Trek so much.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can you stand up so they can see?
[SPEAKER_22]: Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is called Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_11]: But what time period?
[SPEAKER_22]: After current.
I think it's set like 35.
[SPEAKER_07]: 35 or 40 years after Nemesis.
[SPEAKER_22]: So you get your own joystick for your ship.
[SPEAKER_11]: No!
[SPEAKER_11]: And Janeway's dead and Picard's dead.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, Janeway could still be alive.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: You can do customizing on your ship.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you can calibrate the Dilithium Crystal.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I want there to be an achievement called Redstrip Massacre.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh wait, if it's set in that series, okay, if it was red shirts first and then yellow in Next Generation, then what color are they going to go to for the next series to come out?
[SPEAKER_07]: Magenta.
[SPEAKER_22]: Magenta shirts, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I'm going to get some comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: RossDLUT says, what I'm concerned about with Old Republic is that A, this virtually guarantees no KOTOR 3, and B, Bioware's never done an MMO before.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't shake the idea that they might try to ape WoW.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, WoW's a good game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see, we also have GS68 says, I was going to get a PSP 3000 for Christmas, but I think I'll just save for a desktop arcade poppin' con.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: SJ100 Matt says I'm waiting for the OLR Starfleet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's move on with some more news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Back to PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, PlayStation Home isn't even out yet and it's already been hacked.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently he has decrypted over 9,000 files belonging to it, and this is supposedly going to lead to better understanding how PlayStation 3 games and the PlayStation Network works and its structure.
[SPEAKER_05]: So apparently it's all back-end stuff, and they're going to hopefully allow it to lead to other exploits and possibly custom stuff for the cross-media bar and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, right now it's a whole bunch of nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's progress, and progress is always good, I guess.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know what I think is hilarious?
[SPEAKER_22]: That these people do this as a hobby.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know what, I bet the best way to end all the hacking and everything is to offer these guys jobs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh no, they wouldn't do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would actually be original content.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't want that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pay them.
[SPEAKER_03]: We want rehashes of everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but how long before Sony tries to close this gap?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, the home's not even out yet, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, not very long.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, hey, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's fun to say, hey, look, I hacked home.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I'm SkaterFU.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hacked home.
[SPEAKER_05]: But what's kind of neat though, speaking of the home beta, if you do want to get into the home beta, just keep an eye out for the next issue of Core, which is going to do some features behind the scenes regarding home.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're also going to have home beta entries, so you will be able to test home before home launches, whenever home actually launches.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although it's probably going to launch soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, do you remember on last week's show, there was a big to-do about the whole censorship in the game LittleBigPlanet, and how one of the songs controversially quoted the Koran in its lyrics, and Sony was going to patch, they were really nervous about this, they were going to patch the game, take the lyrics out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of an interesting follow-up to this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: We were kind of waiting for comment from the other side.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, hmm, what's the community going to think?
[SPEAKER_07]: What's the rest of the Muslim community going to think if this word gets out there that this is in the game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you might be surprised at what happened.
[SPEAKER_07]: M. Zudi Jassir, MD, and he is the president of the American Islamic Forum for Democracy.
[SPEAKER_07]: He talked to a website called Edge Gaming or the Edge Podcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: Game Network, and he said something kind of interesting here.
[SPEAKER_07]: He said that censorship and Sony being willing to bend at the request for censorship is counterproductive to the freedom of speech.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me give you this quote.
[SPEAKER_07]: "...to demand that the game be withdrawn is predicated on a society which gives theocrats who wish to control speech far more value than the central principle of freedom of expression upon which the very practice and freedom of religion is based."
[SPEAKER_07]: The fact that the music writer is a devout Muslim should highlight that at the core of this issue is not about offending all Muslims but only about freedom of expression and the free market.
[SPEAKER_07]: He says he himself does not endorse the use of the Quran verses in non-educational video games but he says in this case basically that the First Amendment takes precedence and that the Islamic Foundation stands against all forms of censorship.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think that's beautiful and isn't that sort of what we said last week?
[SPEAKER_07]: In a way, in a way.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it is kind of interesting to see that now Sony has almost a little bit of egg on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: They just can't win with this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rice Princess was called and she said censorship equals... Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is she coming tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, she's six, so she's going to try to make it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't she Fire Princess now?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, she is Fire Princess.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, she's six.
[SPEAKER_11]: She's going to try to make it, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, everybody say, Fire Princess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's move on and talk about some... Oh, by the way, just a real quick note on LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_07]: The 1.02 patch is out now.
[SPEAKER_07]: and it basically just strips the lyrics out of the song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it doesn't take the song out, it just removes the lyrics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I didn't understand what they meant anyway, so we're right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't they have a big to-do about this way back in the day with that game War Gods?
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't one of the tracks in that game quote the Koran or something and they took that out?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, who knows.
[SPEAKER_03]: This has been an issue for a while with other games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'd think people would learn.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just seems like bullshit to me the whole time.
[SPEAKER_22]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I should be watching my language.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, fuck that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's like I said last week.
[SPEAKER_22]: If they wanted to be offended at somebody, they should have been offended at the artist that made the song.
[SPEAKER_22]: Which I think is completely retarded anyway since he himself, as stated, was a devout Muslim.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but isn't that... So he was a Muslim, the guy that wrote the song?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because there's like, you know, there's Ninju, and that's made by a Jewish guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like...
[SPEAKER_11]: Have you seen Ninja?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, before we unravel more conversation on the program tonight, let's get to some release dates.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take us to the UK.
[SPEAKER_22]: In the UK, we have Jesus Christ Super Cop.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you say Jesus Christ Super Cock?
[SPEAKER_03]: Cop.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, cop.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, someone did these episodes on TV, on some internet TV site that's called Jesus Christ Super Cop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say that's a rip-off.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's also Frat Boy Jesus on Conan O'Brien.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, can we get our release dates?
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_22]: In the UK on the 29th, we have Penny Arcade Adventures on the Rainslake Precipice of Darkness Episode 2 for PC and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_22]: And on the 31st, we have Command & Conquer Red Alert 3 on PC, which we just got a salute in the back.
[SPEAKER_22]: and then Fallout 3 on PC, Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_22]: On the 31st also we have Final Fantasy Fables, Chocobo's Dungeon on Wii, Hail to the Chimp on Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3, Legendary on Xbox 360 and Me and the Horse I Rode In on 2, I'm sorry, My Horse and Me 2 on DS, Wii, PlayStation 2 and Xbox 360, My Sims Kingdom on Wii, Pro Evolution Soccer 2009,
[SPEAKER_22]: and Valkyria Chronicles on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the U.S., there's quite a bit coming out this week, starting off with today, of course, Guitar Hero World Tour came out on pretty much everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: We also have All-Star Cheer Squad coming out on the Wii this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_05]: Poker for Dummies on PC The Wonder Pets Save the Animals on DS Fallout 3 on PC, PlayStation 3, and Xbox 360 Command & Conquer Red Alert 3 on PC this week FIFA Soccer 09 Allplay on the Wii SingStar Vol.
[SPEAKER_05]: 2 on PS3 See, just to think that you just bought SingStar Vol.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1 and you could have waited a few more days and...
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's my life in a nutshell.
[SPEAKER_05]: Barbie Horse Adventures Riding Camp on PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also my life in a nutshell!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: Bella Sarah, yet another horse riding game on DS and PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ben 10 Alien Force the Game on DS, PSP, PS2, and Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: No horses involved.
[SPEAKER_05]: Imagine Party Babies on Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stay away from that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's evil.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you don't think that's evil enough, then there's also My Baby Boy and My Baby Girl on DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you say Magic Party Babies?
[SPEAKER_05]: Imagine Party Babies.
[SPEAKER_11]: Babies with a Z. Why would you have a party?
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the coolest names for a DS game ever, Little Red Riding Hood Zombie Barbecue on DS this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: He has the best name ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Monster Jam, Urban Assault on DS, PS2, and Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: MotoGP 08 on PC, PlayStation 2, PlayStation 3, and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Motor Storm Pacific Rift on PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: My Sims on PC and My Sims Kingdom on DS and Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Neverland Card Battles on PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ninja Town on DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Onimusha, The Essentials on PlayStation 2, tons of stupid pets games, Pets Rescue Ocean Patrol and Pets Rescue Wildlife Vet on DS, Popstar Guitar on PS2 and Wii, with yet another peripheral that looks stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: GS68 in chat says, all we need now is Let's Ride Babies Forever, Yaris Party of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: But instead, you're going to have to get pro bull riders out of the chute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quell Tipo says, I imagine teachers every night in bed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_22]: Are you hot for teacher?
[SPEAKER_05]: Pro Bowl Riders, Out of the Chute on PlayStation 2 and Wii, yes you can play the bowl in that game, Pro Evolution Soccer 2009 on PS2, PS3, PSP, and Xbox 360, Seen It, Box Office Smash on Xbox 360, Score International Baja 1000 on PlayStation 2, PlayStation 3, Wii, and 360, Shrek's Carnival Craze on DS, PC, PS2, and Wii, SingStar Country on PlayStation 2, SingStar Legends on PS2,
[SPEAKER_05]: Six Flags Fun Park on Wii Spider-Man Web of Shadows on PC The King of Fighters Collection The Orochi Saga on PS2 and PSP Travel Games for Dummies on DS
[SPEAKER_05]: Zens' Ocean and Zens' Rainforce on DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first game that actually is shipped in recyclable packaging.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go green.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoopty shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Too bad the game sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ultimate Eye Spy on Wii and Goosebumps Horrorland on PlayStation 2 and Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: SBK08 Superbike World Championship on Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Witch's Tale on DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: and let's see here, Sherlock Holmes Mystery of the Mummy on DS and exclusive to Walmart the ACDC Live Rock Band Track Pack on PS2, PS3 and 360 you're going to have to find that at Walmart a week from today and coming to Xbox Live Arcade this week wait, I have to go into Walmart?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, you have to go to the Walmart because it's exclusive to them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Penny Arcade Adventures on a Rainsick Precipice of Darkness, Episode 2, and the new Meteos games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Meteos Wars is supposed to be out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about Japan?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go over to Japan and look at the release dates over there.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the Xbox 360, Brothers in Arms, Hell's Highway, Fracture, and Grand Theft Auto 4 all coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, that's Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the PlayStation 3, I imagine very similar stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Fracture is also coming out on the PlayStation 3, as is Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess some type of... No, is that the new one?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, we're waiting for 5, aren't we?
[SPEAKER_07]: So I don't know why this is just now coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Grand Theft Auto 4?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm getting confused because right above it I'm reading Gran Turismo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so yes, Japan finally gets their version of Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gran Turismo 5 Prologue does come out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Spec 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Little Big Planet also makes its way to Japan this week on the 30th.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gran Turismo 5 Prologue hasn't come out in... This is Spec 3, so it's probably like... What the hell's the difference?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's probably different cars to get people to buy it again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, now, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry if you didn't get to see that turn, but that's gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need to play something for Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need to play something for Loki here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yo, yo, yo, check out this shit, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Right?
[SPEAKER_26]: That's so gay.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's really gay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Look at those pants.
[SPEAKER_00]: Please don't say that.
[SPEAKER_00]: What?
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't say that something is gay when you mean that something is dumb or stupid.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's insulting.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like if I thought this pepper shaker was stupid and I said, man, this pepper shaker is so 16-year-old boy with a cheesy mustache.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_00]: When you say that's so gay, do you realize what you say?
[SPEAKER_00]: Knock it off.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the Nintendo Wii, never mind, I'm not going to get political right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo Wii, My Sims Kingdom comes out this week, as does Bokujou Monogatari, Waku Waku Animal March.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: As well as Hula Wii, Mina de Furo Oduro, and Shape Boxing, Wii Day Enjoy Diet.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's probably everybody Hula Hoop, which would be a very interesting game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yumeimi Hakusho, Second Dream
[SPEAKER_07]: On the Nintendo DS, Chocobox comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dr. Slump and Arale Chan.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is Chocobox Chocoball Boxing?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because that would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dr. Slump was done by the artist that did Dragon Ball and Dragon Ball Z. Ah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is Chocoball Boxing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get back to boxing with Chocoball.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chocobox is not a game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a case for your DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: What are they making Chocoball Boxing?
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tales of Innocence gets a price reduction and a game called Vitamin Y comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lastly, on the Sony PSP, is there anything coming out this week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you actually would be surprised.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, there's quite a bit coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cardinal Arc Portable, Monster Hunter Portable 2nd G gets a price reduction and the best, as does Rockman Rockman.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would just be, you know, you know how they remade Mega Man 1 for PSP?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, that's it for Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go back to some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_22]: Do we gotta?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, we gotta.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, this is about death.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ultimate, final character death.
[SPEAKER_22]: A 43-year-old Japanese woman was arrested for killing her virtual husband on MapleStory.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know, where's our stupid person music, Rob?
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, did she kill him in game?
[SPEAKER_22]: She killed him in game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: But she got arrested for killing him in game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or did she kill him for real real?
[SPEAKER_22]: Here's what happened.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, she killed him in... This is what happened.
[SPEAKER_22]: She's a piano teacher.
[SPEAKER_22]: 43-year-old piano teacher was furious because she had been divorced in game.
[SPEAKER_22]: So she accessed his login and deleted his character.
[SPEAKER_22]: So she killed him in-game.
[SPEAKER_22]: She's in jail in Sapporo, and she's facing charges of illegally accessing a computer and manipulating data.
[SPEAKER_22]: Her in-game husband was a 33-year-old office worker, and...
[SPEAKER_22]: I really don't know what he thinks of it.
[SPEAKER_22]: There's no comment about that.
[SPEAKER_22]: But this happened last May, and the woman could pay fines and potentially a five-year jail sentence if she's convicted.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope I can't be held accountable for all the people I kill.
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Dark Knight says it's a huge crime in Japan.
[SPEAKER_22]: Look, this is the thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: I understand it, and honestly, I would want some sort of retaliation.
[SPEAKER_22]: She did break the law.
[SPEAKER_22]: She illegally accessed his information and she broke the law.
[SPEAKER_22]: However, I just think it's so fucking retarded that this is Mabel's story!
[SPEAKER_22]: It's free!
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, I would be pissed off if someone did that to my Ragnarok account.
[SPEAKER_22]: I would be pissed off if that happened on my Ragnarok account.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know.
[SPEAKER_22]: But...
[SPEAKER_22]: It's not the end of the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: Five years in jail?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, God, pissing you off is bad enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you imagine the phone call?
[SPEAKER_22]: What do you mean pissing me off is bad enough?
[SPEAKER_22]: What the fuck is that supposed to mean, Rob?
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly as it was intended.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you imagine the phone call?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd like to report a murder of my character.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, see, I was thinking of the World of Warcraft South Park episode.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's like, and he's killing people's characters.
[SPEAKER_16]: Mom!
[SPEAKER_16]: Bathroom!
[SPEAKER_07]: I am such an achievement whore now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, hey, let's move on with the news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I've been distracted because the doctor has boobs now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And boobs are distracting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's what kind of doctor you are.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the doctor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, Doctor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, Guitar Hero World Tour is facing some drum issues, as some other hosts so viciously described.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are some issues with the drums.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sensing the hits.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, that's to come later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ignore that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I let the audio run too long again.
[SPEAKER_07]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shame, shame.
[SPEAKER_05]: The fucking drums aren't fucking working right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, so the drums aren't working correctly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, they're either not sensing hits or they're just plain not doing anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're faulty like this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're very faulty.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, personally, I kind of called that they were faulty, but for whole different reasons.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, the thing looks like it's made out of PVC and was seriously like rocking when people were playing it and not rocking in the good way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think as Bobby Blackwolf put it on his show, if they're going to brag that their instruments are better than rock band's instruments, then maybe they should work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's start with the working first.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the only sound my guitar hero drums will make.
[SPEAKER_22]: I have pumpkin-y goodness in me, by the way, Rob.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're eating pumpkin bagels here in studio, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are?
[SPEAKER_07]: I am.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, eat that Halloween candy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't have the candy, and John doesn't want it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So bring the thing out here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make everybody eat it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give some to Justin TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, big news this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_07]: Huge news about something we here at Orange Lounge Radio used to cover every year and then kind of stopped.
[SPEAKER_07]: E3 is coming back.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: E3 2009 is coming back the way we know it, not this whole, like, scaled-down show we had.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, E3 is going to be just like it was before.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, that doesn't mean that anybody is going to be able to get in.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not public.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just, you know, it's going to be back to the same audience.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: When it was originally going on anyways, it was almost public.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, I work at Walmart or I know someone that works at Walmart in the garden department because they, you know, it's like the six degrees of Kevin Bacon or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_05]: I work in a store that looks at video games, and therefore, you know, I should be able to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a crappy podcast on the internet that's been going for six years.
[SPEAKER_07]: I get to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_22]: This means that we need to get our business stuff set back up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we gotta go.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's gonna be tough.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm gonna try to get the wife to let me go, but, uh... Ooh, ouch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell her Fable 3 will be there.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is how it works at my house.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey, Dan, I'm going to E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but you can do that.
[SPEAKER_22]: He can come with me.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's his thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: He's come with me every year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Drag the intern.
[SPEAKER_07]: The website Joystick, that's Joystick with a Q, actually interviewed the president of the ESA, Doug Lowenstein, and he actually said, they asked him, if you had to give E3 a six-letter word or less tagline, what would it be?
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm sorry, Doug Lowenstein was the former president of the ESA.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now it's Mike Gallagher.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: When it was an industry-only thing, it still was going down the tubes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you had better things like, I don't know, Leipzig and PAX as the true gamers' conventions.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, even for the industry, it's just not that good anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kind of curious what effect this is going to have on PAX.
[SPEAKER_07]: If that's going to cause less people to want to go to PAX now because they'll want to use their vacation on E3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because not everybody can take vacation all the time, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_22]: Honestly, if I had to choose between the two, though, to be perfectly honest...
[SPEAKER_22]: I want to go to PAX again.
[SPEAKER_22]: I really want to go to PAX again.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, PAX was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: PAX was more of like the gamer show, but I'm a greedy bastard.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to go to both.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, no, I'd love to go to both.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'd especially like to see what this E3 revival is, you know?
[SPEAKER_22]: But if I had to pick between one or the other, I would pick PAX.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Orange Lounge Radio, live from E3 this June.
[SPEAKER_22]: However, if we do go to E3, we're totally freaking going to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_22]: We are.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_22]: But it's during the summer.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Teacups.
[SPEAKER_22]: Teacups for the win and California Screamin'.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's move on with the news or we'll never get to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what Disneyland could use more of?
[SPEAKER_05]: Zombies.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what Call of Duty is getting more of?
[SPEAKER_22]: Tell about my story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: You were just talking about Disneyland and I stopped listening.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, with E3's revival, what happens to E for All?
[SPEAKER_22]: It gets flushed down the toilet!
[SPEAKER_22]: Whee!
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have a toilet flush noise, sorry.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yep, there's no more E for All, and I'm laughing my ass off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why all the negativity?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's too much cynicism in here tonight.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck you, I'm going to PAX.
[SPEAKER_07]: it was pretty cool plus I got to meet Jonathan Colton and Will Wheaton and I couldn't do that at E for All Janai in chat makes the mandatory joke here that I think is pretty clever E for End did you hear that one Jamie?
[SPEAKER_22]: E for End aww that's perfect I was telling Mel about Will Wheaton signing my iPhone and it rubbing off by the end of the day but you saw it I did see it I said now my phone is an extra limited edition and so he put a 1 slash 1 on it that was pretty funny
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, now we can talk about zombies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that's what you're going to see at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_07]: A bunch of unshowered, unslept zombies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_22]: We should hand out care packs.
[SPEAKER_22]: We should hand out con care packs like they did at AX that one year.
[SPEAKER_22]: Where they handed out deodorant and soap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but unless you're going to put it on them yourself, it's not going to do any good.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Cans of Axe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Axe smells freaking good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Axe is better than Confunk.
[SPEAKER_22]: Confunk is... Confunk is... No, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know what smells better than Confunk?
[SPEAKER_22]: Cat piss.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll take your word for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about zombies?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, zombies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently the megaton bomb that was dropped by GameTrailersTV was that Call of Duty World of War is going to feature a four-player co-op zombie mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: That totally doesn't rip off of another game that's very similar having a four-player co-op zombie mode in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Left 4 Dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess, hey, they want to make sure that people know that their game has zombies too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, that's so World of War.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember the zombie wars back in World War II.
[SPEAKER_05]: My grandpa used to tell me all about those, how the zombies would attack and everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, yes, the zombies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank goodness that we defeated them and showed them democracy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Democracy, bring it to the rest of the world.
[SPEAKER_05]: and no zombies, because zombies are bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But thankfully, though, Treyarch is able to come back and tell the lost battles of zombies, the part that was left out of the history books.
[SPEAKER_05]: Conspiracy, I say!
[SPEAKER_05]: Brains or no brains?
[SPEAKER_22]: Actually, I do have to say, there's something that completely bothers me about zombie games.
[SPEAKER_22]: About games with zombies in them.
[SPEAKER_22]: How you don't have a stench meter.
[SPEAKER_22]: In zombie movies, in zombie games, why is it that you can't tell where the fucking zombies are by how much their decayed asses stink?
[SPEAKER_22]: Their decaying bodies are gonna smell like rotten meat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe someday there'll be a smell-o-vision.
[SPEAKER_22]: But, you know, nobody in zombie movies are so surprised that the zombies are there when they should have been able to freaking smell corpse in a stench.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, you have games like, I don't know, Thief with sound meters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why can't you have smell meters?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe there's a lot of zombies and so because they all smell like rotting flesh, the whole place smells like rotting flesh so you can't tell where it's coming from.
[SPEAKER_22]: It should still be stronger the closer you get to that much contained stench.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's like an anime con.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just like last night.
[SPEAKER_22]: You can tell when you're getting close to the dealer's room by the stink.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can tell when you're getting close to the cosplay competition.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like a Dave Matthews band concert.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can tell when you're getting close to the smell of marijuana.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, when you're getting close to the cosplay competition is when you stop smelling funk and start smelling other things.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if you heard, Drew, but the Grateful Dead, the one guy's keeping on trucking in heaven.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's gratefully dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow... Unless he's a zombie!
[SPEAKER_05]: In which case, you need to know how to defeat zombies by playing this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Left 4 Dead, or Saints Row 2, or any other zombie game.
[SPEAKER_07]: World of Warcraft, which has also started the zombie invasion.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Zombie invasion has been hitting World of Warcraft, and there's been just craziness going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Earlier in the week, there was infections going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you would kill an infected critter, or...
[SPEAKER_07]: or the like, you would get turned into a zombie in 10 minutes, and then you could create other zombies, and it was like a disease that was spread around.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, as the week's been going on, now it takes 15 seconds to get turned into a zombie.
[SPEAKER_03]: 15 seconds?
[SPEAKER_07]: That was one minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that happened to me earlier today.
[SPEAKER_07]: It took me 15 seconds to get turned into a zombie.
[SPEAKER_03]: The more you get hit by zombies, the faster they shave off times.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got to visit an Argent healer if they haven't been turned into a zombie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or you have a priest or a paladin remove the disease.
[SPEAKER_03]: All last night I was going on my priest through Orgrimmar making sure all the auction house dealers were clean.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently they don't like the people who are cleaning up after the zombies.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't like the priests.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't like the pallies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you're ruining our fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you guys are going to low-level zones and killing everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, does anyone find this slightly offensive that there's people walking around into, I don't know, public buildings and exploding?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: There's zombies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't blame them, there are zombies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everything is okay when it's zombies and green blood, because it's not real.
[SPEAKER_03]: There were zombies that ate too many Twinkies.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if some zombies flew a plane into a building, that would be okay too?
[SPEAKER_05]: There's zombies!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just checking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because this is the World of Warcraft game that you're playing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't see any recalls on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: We did have people getting infected and then flying to other cities and then exploding when they got there.
[SPEAKER_03]: They zombified in mid-flight.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't explode in mid-flight?
[SPEAKER_03]: They can't explode in mid-flight, but they can explode as soon as they land.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tenris Murkblood is a new boss that you can fight in Karazhan.
[SPEAKER_07]: My guild just took him down today, and it was actually a fun fight.
[SPEAKER_07]: But only you're going to be able to see him for 10 days, which basically means if you don't play him tonight or Monday, you have one chance because of the resets in Kara.
[SPEAKER_07]: So he drops an axe that is awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: He will drop this axe every time.
[SPEAKER_07]: He only drops two things, a little bat pet for everybody in the raid, and an axe.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: X-Link Grand Theft Auto 4 Zombies
[SPEAKER_05]: Talk about non-news, but they decided, hey, we're going to jump in on the zombie fun as well, even though this has been around forever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to point out, since we just started tonight's show, a new phase just kicked in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Phase 5.5 just started tonight as we went live.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: apparently what's happened now there are quests all of a sudden available in the main cities that send you to the faction leader and at some point you are going to be whispered by some type of either a frozen shade or a plagued brain that's going to be taunting you to join their forces and there's some type of quest going on to hopefully clean the world of the plague interesting so it's all going on right now in the world of Warcraft bathroom bathroom
[SPEAKER_07]: Brains David Hasselhoff
[SPEAKER_22]: And, um, he, uh, he actually thinks that it's completely, he actually said that it was hysterical.
[SPEAKER_22]: He's quoted as saying that.
[SPEAKER_22]: And that, um, he thinks that, uh, it's really great that he gets to be in it.
[SPEAKER_22]: And there's also, um, his version of Do You Really Want to Hurt Me?
[SPEAKER_22]: As, uh, the, uh, title to an in-game track.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I think that's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, you know, that's just, uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob's computer farted.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, hello Rice Princess, glad to see you just arrived.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, I want to point out there's a new song available in Pain.
[SPEAKER_19]: I can't stop this feeling deep inside of me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Girl, you just don't realize what you do to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I couldn't resist.
[SPEAKER_05]: You gotta love a guy that actually is famous for doing that shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder if he's just like, what can I do that's so ridiculous that people would still like me?
[SPEAKER_05]: And he keeps making these songs and he's like, okay, people gotta hate me now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they're still buying his albums and he's still rich and putting them on TV shows and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: He's still convinced that he's instrumental in the Berlin Wall coming down.
[SPEAKER_22]: They love him in Germany.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ranma in chat says, I actually like this song.
[SPEAKER_07]: I only read that so that our, you know, thousands of listeners could hear that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's Ranma, R-A-N-M-A, likes that song.
[SPEAKER_07]: DSSJ100 Matt says, we got half rolled.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, you did.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, a little more gaming news than the Classic Game of the Week and then a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you bought Rock Band 2, you'll know that on the back of your manual, it says you can get 20 free tracks available at a later date.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that later date is now November 4th, and there are 20 different tracks you can get.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to be honest, I don't know any of these artists at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, real quickly, I'm going to read them off.
[SPEAKER_05]: The 88, Sons and Daughters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Authority Zero, No Regrets.
[SPEAKER_05]: Between the Buried and Me, Prepare to the Sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Cab with Bounce, The Chevelles, Get It On, The Cocktail Slippers, Give It To Me, Dealership with Database Corrupted, End Ever After with I Wanna Be Your Man, The Ghost Towns, Ashes to Fire, Hollywood Undead, Young, The Cutlass, The Feeling, The Lend Price 3, If I Ain't Got You, Leslie Roy, I'm Gone, I'm Going,
[SPEAKER_05]: Opiate for the masses, Burn You Down, Semi-Precious Weapons, Magnetic Baby, Shamius with Like a Fool, Magnetic Baby?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: TheNuno2, Crazy Tuesday, TickleMePink with The Time Is Wrong, Under Oath with Desperate Times, Desperate Measures, and X Japan with Ivy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no idea of any of those songs, but hey.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know that actually we were really excited about getting some X Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: But hey, at least they're free, and free is awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: No bitching.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there might be some cool songs in there that you've never heard of before.
[SPEAKER_05]: So make sure that you register before the 4th.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you probably can afterwards, but if you want to make sure you get it day one, register at rockband.com slash bonustracks, and they will send you an email with your code to download them once they become available.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kiss Them For Me, and Killing Jar
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's all by Suzy and the Banshees, which is like one of the greatest bands ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dammit by Blink-182, that song that Rob was talking about the little girl singing earlier in SingStar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like Metal Onan by the Silver Sun Pickups.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well Thought Out Twinkies by, or Twinkles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Twinkies would be funny though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well Thought Out Twinkles by Silver Sun Pickups and Pretty in Pink by Psychedelic Furs.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it has Suzy and the Banshees in it, so all the rest of that is just crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, Rob, are you straight now?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I just love Suzy and the Banshees.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: She was on the Basement Jack song, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: They had a really cool video on top of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's Kish Cash.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's funny, my band right now, thankfully, because I'm not playing Rock Band 2, but my friend is on my account, so it counts.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we're in the top 600 now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm very pleased at my progress in the game.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, just to let people know, our band name at my house is Detachable Penis.
[SPEAKER_22]: Like the King Missile song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did it not get banned?
[SPEAKER_22]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: The one I've been playing in mostly is actually Shane's band.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Emergency Kittens.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the name of our band.
[SPEAKER_11]: Does the Sassy Squad sing backup?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's just a Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_11]: But is Fluffles Chainset III the lead singer?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, hey, by the way, if you want a real band game, you know, the hell with Rock Band or Guitar Hero, get Rock Revolution.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just so kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, you want this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Strong Bad Episode 3, the baddest of the bands, is coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Episode 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: It comes out on the PC and WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_07]: When?
[SPEAKER_07]: Right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or Monday, for those of you listening live.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_07]: October 27th.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be, as always, 1,000 Wii Points or $10.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's coming out from Telltale Games.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Those of you that are enjoying the Strong Bad games probably want to pick that up.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you haven't picked up a Strong Bad game yet, you might want to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yes, I'm talking to myself because I still have not played the Strong Bad series.
[SPEAKER_22]: I really need to.
[SPEAKER_22]: Is the ban over, Rob?
[SPEAKER_22]: No, you know your boycott's not over yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I can play it on PC.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's what I plan to do.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, your boycott because your memory's full.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm boycotting the Wii download stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But although, well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm iffy on it because they have announced the remedy for it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, have you already announced that on the show, what the remedy is?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, they did announce they are going to let you run things off SD cards.
[SPEAKER_07]: But when's that happening, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's going to be a patch, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, probably a patch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, anyhow, hey, we're not even halfway done with this show yet, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to take a break here pretty soon, but first, we always like to end Part A of our program by taking a trip to the past and revisiting the archives and trying to pick out a classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, as I understand, though, tonight's game, because it is Episode 300, DarkSakura had to pick, like, a fucking epic classic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Am I correct?
[SPEAKER_07]: You sure did.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well, let's get to it.
[SPEAKER_22]: My classic game, actually I'm not going to say the title of it to begin with.
[SPEAKER_22]: It should begin with the intro to the game.
[SPEAKER_22]: Which everyone will get from the first tones.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I'm getting grins from over here looking at my laptop.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh yeah!
[SPEAKER_22]: Do we get it yet, kids?
[SPEAKER_22]: No, it's not Castlevania!
[SPEAKER_22]: It's Guts Man!
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh yeah!
[SPEAKER_22]: Tora is the first person to guess.
[SPEAKER_22]: And stop spamming the room now, please.
[SPEAKER_22]: You get a no prize!
[SPEAKER_22]: Stop it!
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, someone kick Tora out of the chat room, please.
[SPEAKER_22]: Right the fuck now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you read about the classic game now?
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: The classic game is Final Fantasy VI, which we got over here on Super Nintendo as Final Fantasy III.
[SPEAKER_22]: Play the best music in the game ever, please.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is the overworld music, which is also called Terra's Theme.
[SPEAKER_22]: Although in the Japanese version, her name was Tina.
[SPEAKER_22]: Best music in the game.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's just my own opinion.
[SPEAKER_22]: And Sauce's best game ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think this is probably one of the best video game songs ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Period.
[SPEAKER_22]: This game is the reason why I skipped a week of high school.
[SPEAKER_22]: While I had the flu, but that's beside the point.
[SPEAKER_22]: My flu was prolonged.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, no, I started off having the flu, and my grandma rented the game for me, and I ended up just having the flu a little bit longer than I really did.
[SPEAKER_22]: But the one thing about this one is it was the first in the series that was not done by Sakaguchi, it was done by Yoshinori Kitase and Hiroyuki Ito.
[SPEAKER_22]: And this is considered pretty much the pinnacle of it, although I really, really like Final Fantasy V a whole lot, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: um it has the largest playable cast of any Final Fantasy game to date so um pretty much it's it's standard Final Fantasy you know you have your overworld map and you have your dungeons and you have your towns and um you've got your chocobo and you have your airship and random encounters on land um this one also has um your espers which are you know give you your magic and you keep improving and
[SPEAKER_22]: and it's still menu-based combat.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, it's Final Fantasy, basically.
[SPEAKER_22]: There were a few different innovative attacks, like Sully's had the runic attack, which could reflect magical attacks back at somebody, although I'll be honest, I rarely ever freaking use that, except for that one battle where you had to.
[SPEAKER_22]: Um, and I'm actually still playing this right now too.
[SPEAKER_22]: Um, but this has, um, for the active time battle system, you actually can pick any character that has filled up their action bar and you don't have to pick the first one that pops up.
[SPEAKER_22]: You can actually change out which one you want to use as long as their bar is, is their first.
[SPEAKER_22]: Um,
[SPEAKER_22]: and this actually was incorporated into later ones you could customize your characters by your relics to change their stats you could you know work with their spells a little bit you could equip their magicite which is like I was saying is basically some of the espers helps with magic they have the magic acquisition points for each time you gain a
[SPEAKER_22]: AP as you level up.
[SPEAKER_22]: This particular game is where basically you've got this one girl named Tara in the Japanese version, it was Tina, and they find her and she can do magic and everyone's like, oh my god, magic!
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm gonna barf!
[SPEAKER_22]: And then the rest of the story goes off.
[SPEAKER_22]: This also has Kefka, which is the most annoying...
[SPEAKER_22]: laugh in a video game ever.
[SPEAKER_22]: Somebody poison the water hole.
[SPEAKER_03]: But he had the best boss theme ever.
[SPEAKER_22]: Actually, I really like Jenova's better, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: Um...
[SPEAKER_22]: The one other really cool thing that I thought about this game is that it's very steampunk.
[SPEAKER_22]: Really, it is.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, you've got steam-powered mecha in the game.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's all very early industrial.
[SPEAKER_11]: Magitek.
[SPEAKER_22]: You have your Magitek armor.
[SPEAKER_22]: You've got, you know, the Empire in that is pretty much a magical, industrial-type mesh.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know, it's so fantastic.
[SPEAKER_22]: And you have toilets in it.
[SPEAKER_22]: You can use the toilet.
[SPEAKER_22]: Did you know that?
[SPEAKER_11]: What if you don't use the toilet?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because in Sims, that's not good.
[SPEAKER_22]: No.
[SPEAKER_22]: If you're in the Empire Castle, whatever, and you're in one of the cells, you can actually sit on the toilet and squat down on it.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then when you hop off the toilet, it flushes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do they take down their little pants to do that?
[SPEAKER_22]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, they have a trap door.
[SPEAKER_11]: They do?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Also, Saw says it has the freakiest clown in a video game ever.
[SPEAKER_22]: But you've got some of the best characters in this.
[SPEAKER_22]: Like, you've got... I actually really liked... Go-Go.
[SPEAKER_22]: I really liked Go-Go.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because of the weird stuff he did.
[SPEAKER_22]: I loved Gal, who was the little...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know why we're having mic issues in the studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll keep it away from the speakers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_22]: But Rob, do me a favor and...
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, I'll try to find it.
[SPEAKER_22]: But this game had the single most hardcore awesome character in it, which was... We'll get to him in a second.
[SPEAKER_22]: But the main characters you have, Terra slash Tina.
[SPEAKER_22]: You've got Locke, who's your thief.
[SPEAKER_22]: You have Sillies, who's... Treasure Hunter.
[SPEAKER_22]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_22]: You have Sabin, who's your martial artist.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a special rendition of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, no, wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_22]: But here's the man.
[SPEAKER_22]: Shadow the Ninja, who we used to call Snake Eyes.
[SPEAKER_22]: And you have, Realm was cool, she had the drawing attack.
[SPEAKER_22]: And you had her grandfather, who's the Blue Mage, and you had What's-His-Face, who looked like Billy B. Williams.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who was the Doma Castle guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Cyan.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: But he looked like Billy... We used to call him Billy Dee.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sorry, he looks like Billy Dee Williams.
[SPEAKER_22]: He doesn't drink cold 45.
[SPEAKER_05]: Edgar was the best.
[SPEAKER_22]: I bet he does.
[SPEAKER_22]: Edgar was awesome because it was all about the autocross bow.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the autocross bow.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the chainsaw.
[SPEAKER_05]: The drill.
[SPEAKER_22]: The graphics actually were... The characters were designed by Yoshitaka Amano and they were actually converted to sprite.
[SPEAKER_22]: And...
[SPEAKER_22]: There were also, in the PlayStation version that came out later, the actual videos that were in the game were directly from Amano's designs.
[SPEAKER_22]: I thought it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: And it was one of the, it's not the first one that used Mode 7, but it used extensive Mode 7 in this for lots of scaling and scrolling.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was really fantastic.
[SPEAKER_22]: When it was localized, there were changes like a little bit of nudity, for example.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the painting bosses.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, one of those.
[SPEAKER_22]: Also, different characters for their full names.
[SPEAKER_22]: They romanized them differently so that they would fit a six-character slot.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were also changed quite a bit from Terra to Tina, from Mash to Sabin, from Kyan to Cyan.
[SPEAKER_22]: but I think that they picked it in the way that people would most be able to relate to it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Text.
[SPEAKER_22]: A lot of dialogue was shortened because, again, it could only store a certain number of characters and I'm sorry, Japanese lends itself a lot easier to extended conversation within a limited character allotment because it's syllabic and English isn't.
[SPEAKER_22]: This
[SPEAKER_22]: is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is the opera scene, which is, to this day, I think, one of the most memorable ever scenes in any video game ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It brings tears to most classic game shows.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_22]: Did you see, I saw where they did for the Dear Friends concert, Rob, where they did the opera scene in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_22]: I saw YouTube of it.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was just fantastic.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was so beautiful.
[SPEAKER_22]: And here's actually one that we should realize about the music.
[SPEAKER_22]: We've kept bringing up the music during this.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was actually done by Uematsu, who wrote all of the music in the game, did everything for every location, all the battles, different themes.
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually use the music from the games in Japanese music classes in Japan.
[SPEAKER_22]: Also, they wanted to use an actual voice for the opera, but the SBC-700 chip would not allow an actual voice track, so that's why they used...
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, it would basically be the Vox Organa, or Vox Humana thing for organ, is what I recognize it as.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the sound chip itself didn't support the voices, but later on you had games like Tales of Phantasia and Star Ocean that did have actual voice samples.
[SPEAKER_22]: But we're talking about full vocal track.
[SPEAKER_22]: It wouldn't support a full vocal track.
[SPEAKER_22]: It would support something that was short.
[SPEAKER_07]: True enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Last Metroid is in captivity.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Galaxy is at peace.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's about as much as you can get.
[SPEAKER_22]: Or the Clay Fighters opening.
[SPEAKER_22]: But for the Final Fantasy VI Grand Finale album, it actually was rearranged as an aria using an actual singer in full...
[SPEAKER_22]: Accompaniment, and this version was also in the full motion video in the PlayStation version, so it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: You can actually get, I've got the full soundtrack to this, you can get all kinds of arranged versions, but there's also some pretty good versions of some of the music in the game in some of the Final Fantasy compilation discs.
[SPEAKER_22]: Although I still think that the best of the compilation ones, which I don't think has any from this game in it, is still Celtic Moon.
[SPEAKER_22]: And Prey.
[SPEAKER_22]: Prey was very good.
[SPEAKER_22]: Prey had some stuff in here.
[SPEAKER_22]: We did, like I said, we got a PlayStation version, but there's also Final Fantasy VI Advance, which came out on DS.
[SPEAKER_22]: There's four new espers in this one, which is Leviathan, Gilgamesh, Cactar, and Diabolos.
[SPEAKER_22]: Cactar!
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was on Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sorry, that's the Game Boy Advance one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish it was on DS, that'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, well that's the one I've been playing through until my DS broke.
[SPEAKER_22]: Also, for this game, as of March 31st, 2003, it shipped 3.48 million copies worldwide, which is 2.6 million in Japan alone, and 860,000 overseas, and continued to be one of the best-selling games.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_22]: and this is what made me all hyper is that when I don't know if you remember when the Nintendo 64 was in production or sorry in testing they actually made a demonstration for the Nintendo 64 using the the cast from Final Fantasy 7 in a big battle I think versus Bahamut which I found video of finally and it's freaking crazy looking
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is what we're looking at right now in studio.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was going to be too expensive, right, to put it on a cartridge to do the game, right, for Final Fantasy VII?
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, basically, it was actually done on Silicon Graphics hardware when they first put it out.
[SPEAKER_22]: But Square hadn't yet committed, and the technology in the game was not up to their parts.
[SPEAKER_22]: They actually wanted to move it to PlayStation for the sake of full motion video.
[SPEAKER_22]: Which the PlayStation of course could easily handle But the demo actually had Terra, Locke, and Shadow And it was controlled actually through using a mouse
[SPEAKER_22]: instead of, you know, actual, like with a control.
[SPEAKER_22]: There was also Final Fantasy VI, the interactive CG game, which was actually also called Final Fantasy X, not a Final Fantasy X, Final Fantasy X, which was the same demonstration, but with better textures.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not for the Philips CD-i, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: This was basically... We're going on an adventure, Zelda!
[SPEAKER_22]: But this was basically what they were using.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was a sort of a touchdown version they were using for the Nintendo 64 demo test.
[SPEAKER_22]: But this was more to demonstrate the actual use of CG in the thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: So that's our classic game is Final Fantasy VI.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh good, because I was running out of music.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was long.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's worth it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game deserves it.
[SPEAKER_22]: I knew that this game would require a ton of attention, so how could we not dedicate more time to it?
[SPEAKER_22]: And it's episode 300.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, hell, we have to pick the pinnacle.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how you're going to follow that next week.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because it's not better than Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy 6 Final Fantasy 5 Final Fantasy 6
[SPEAKER_22]: A whole lot, and I'll probably do that as a later game, because of how customizable the job change system was.
[SPEAKER_22]: And Final Fantasy 3 was the first one to do that, of the Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_22]: Which was actually really fun, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: If anyone can find a translation of it, play it.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, they've got it on DS.
[SPEAKER_22]: They have it now, but I mean like the old...
[SPEAKER_22]: The old one.
[SPEAKER_22]: Final Fantasy 6, I think, for storytelling, for just how drawn in it brings you into everything, for all the detail.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, flushing toilets.
[SPEAKER_22]: A first for any Final Fantasy game.
[SPEAKER_11]: With the opera, by the time you get to the opera, there's like this epic, crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so much has gone on already, and you're like, oh my god, this is some crazy adventure.
[SPEAKER_22]: Plus, it's all about the X-Zone.
[SPEAKER_22]: Vanish Doom Vanish Doom or Vanish X-Zone Both of them But it was all about that, hi
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, we gotta wrap up or we're gonna have no time for Skype calls in Part B. We're gonna move on and take a break, but hey, don't go away.
[SPEAKER_07]: There'll be plenty more of Orange Launch Radio, some more news coming in Part B. We've got a new technology Microsoft might be building so that people will stop swearing on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't wait to see what people have to say about this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aw, fuck.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: So anyway, we'll be talking about that when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: And for those of you guys listening live tonight, we have, for tonight's free break, your shout-outs from our voicemail.
[SPEAKER_07]: So enjoy.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be back in a few minutes with more of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, all our crew.
[SPEAKER_14]: Happy 300th day.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's the turn of more albums of all our lessons for you, year 68.
[SPEAKER_14]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_14]: This voicemail is brought to you by the All Our Tavern, on the never-ending transport and DMN case.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, hey, hey!
[SPEAKER_15]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_15]: Dan Shadow here.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, 300.
[SPEAKER_15]: Episode 300.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow.
300.
[SPEAKER_15]: Really?
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't even get one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can I get one?
[SPEAKER_15]: Just one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Really?
[SPEAKER_15]: No?
[SPEAKER_15]: But 300.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow, man.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
300.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, hi, it's Gold Ampro.
[SPEAKER_18]: I haven't really left a message to talk to you guys for a while.
[SPEAKER_18]: And even though I'm probably going to be there, I'm probably not going to be there because of stupid school reasons.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, I hope you guys, the 300th episode is really good and I'll listen to it on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, real quickly, I want to tell my game spots to stop scoring.
[SPEAKER_18]: Basically, there's one for the whiteboard.
[SPEAKER_18]: I went to my mom a couple months ago, and what happened was, um, well, um, I got sent.
[SPEAKER_18]: We were waiting in line, and the lady was, we had to wait there 10 minutes, they were ignoring us, and we were at the front of the line at the counter.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then they had to nerve-jack, um,
[SPEAKER_18]: In order to ask, do you want to buy an Edge card with that?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because it's a 10% discount.
[SPEAKER_18]: And Mom's like, no.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then we walk out.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, after making us wait for 10 minutes, we could tell they were pretty much deliberately ignoring us.
[SPEAKER_18]: And, you know, I know today's busy, but, I mean, it's just so annoying.
[SPEAKER_18]: So there's one for the game's spot, stop, whatever, message board thing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sorry it was a little over a minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's up Orange Lounge Radio, this is Tire Claw.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd like to congratulate you all for the 300th episode.
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep up the good fight and take care, alright?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, happy 300th!
[SPEAKER_09]: Or, how do you say it in French?
[SPEAKER_09]: Joyeux 300th!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh well, hell.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, hi there Olar, this is Aki Ripper just calling you to say Happy 300!
[SPEAKER_09]: Eller Gratulerar p 300-programsdagen!
[SPEAKER_09]: That was Swedish.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, hello, hello.
[SPEAKER_09]: Y'all just had a later date.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello there, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is DMN, co-host of Under Sedation Live 4.0.
[SPEAKER_13]: And host of the old DMN Sanity.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeehaw.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways, I'm calling to congratulate you guys on 300 episodes.
[SPEAKER_13]: That is a fantastic milestone.
[SPEAKER_13]: You guys are amazing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I look forward to 300 more.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I know everyone else listening is...
[SPEAKER_13]: Congratulations once again on 300 and don't rob too much kids.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways, take care.
[SPEAKER_16]: Congratulations to Orange Lounge Radio for its 500th episode.
[SPEAKER_16]: We hope there are more, many more.
[SPEAKER_16]: Many more.
[SPEAKER_16]: I hope you continue entertaining us in the near future.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is Actdeft from Mexico.
[SPEAKER_16]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_16]: If you didn't understand that, well, it's basically Actdeft from Mexico, your favorite neighborhood, Mexican.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I want to congratulate All Around Radio for their 300th episode, so congrats!
[SPEAKER_16]: And keep the episode coming!
[SPEAKER_16]: So, basically it's that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Congratulations!
300!
[SPEAKER_17]: 300!
[SPEAKER_17]: Cue the music, Rob!
[SPEAKER_20]: Hey, it's Misty.
[SPEAKER_20]: What?
[SPEAKER_20]: You knew I was going to call in.
[SPEAKER_20]: Congrats on episode 300.
[SPEAKER_20]: You know I'll heart you guys forever.
[SPEAKER_20]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hey, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's DJ Tyrant.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just wanted to say congrats on 300 episodes.
[SPEAKER_17]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_17]: Shout out to all the Be My Fans out there in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_17]: You guys rock.
[SPEAKER_17]: Keep playing Be My Games.
[SPEAKER_17]: Keep playing music games.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's do it.
[SPEAKER_17]: and congrats Rob on getting PS3 off the hatchet.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyways, great 300 episodes so far, looking forward to the next 300.
[SPEAKER_17]: Have a good week guys.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hello, this is Roger, and I'd like to wish you guys a good 300th episode of OLR.
[SPEAKER_28]: So I will not, unfortunately I will not be listening live tonight, I'm going to set out to actually play DDR in a few minutes, so I will try for today for a special AAA for you guys, so...
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey guys, this is your listener, JRod, and I'm calling to tell you that Orange Lounge Radio is the A-show when it comes to gaming podcasts.
[SPEAKER_28]: And I really don't understand how much the show does mean to us fans.
[SPEAKER_27]: 300 episodes, guys.
[SPEAKER_27]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_27]: Looking forward to more awesome shows in 2009.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_20]: What?
[SPEAKER_20]: Did you, like, um... Did you upload the thing yet?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm working on it right now, but before I get to upload it, there's one thing we gotta do first.
[SPEAKER_20]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: We have to wish Orange Dawn Radio a happy 300th.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, let's get it going.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm DJ Ranma S. And I'm Kuro Usagi.
[SPEAKER_10]: And on behalf of the staff at Anime Jam Sessions, which is me, Kuro, and Sailor Flurry, we want to congratulate Rob, Jamie, and Loki on an awesome 300th episode tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh my god, 300 episodes!
[SPEAKER_24]: What are you guys gonna do now?
[SPEAKER_24]: Like, go to Disney World?
[SPEAKER_24]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've already done Disney World.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, it's so overrated.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, but tonight, I'm gonna listen.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm gonna have a drink based on each one of them.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it'll be some awesome fun tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: You're gonna, like, be totally plastered.
[SPEAKER_24]: I feel bad for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not gonna be plastered.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes, you are.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or... Hey, why don't, instead of arguing, why don't you come into the chatroom tonight?
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_24]: It depends.
[SPEAKER_24]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, Rob, Matt, Jamie, have a great show tonight, and you know I'll be there and see you for episode 301.
[SPEAKER_10]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_10]: Can you tell we're excited?
[SPEAKER_24]: A little bit excited.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just a little bit?
[SPEAKER_24]: Just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a good show tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: See you later.
[SPEAKER_19]: From StepSquad to OrangeLabs, this DDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_19]: Holler!
[SPEAKER_07]: Welcome back, everybody, to episode number 300 of Orange Lounge Radio on this Sunday evening, October the 26th, 2008.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just a reminder, there will be no show next week just due to the fact that, hey, we deserve a week off after 300 episodes and the fact that I'm having surgery and I'm being held up by Loki dressed as Sackboy, which you can see on our Justin TV feed at justin.tv slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is orange-tipped gunny-o.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's holding up the Justin listeners with a gun.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's lovely.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where did you get a gun?
[SPEAKER_22]: It's his airsoft.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, where in the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: Who got you a gun?
[SPEAKER_22]: Rob, I have airsoft guns.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: The little Resident Evil pistols.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, I know we want to get to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got a lot of people who want to call in tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to try and take as many calls as possible.
[SPEAKER_07]: But first, we've got a little more news to get to.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Loki, you ready?
[SPEAKER_07]: Situated there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ready to get us back into some gaming news?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, starting things off as I kind of hinted to earlier, Panda Arcade Adventures Episode 2 is coming to Xbox Live Arcade and PC on October 29th.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome news.
[SPEAKER_05]: No word on PS3 yet, probably just because they just finally got the first episode, so give it a little bit more time.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it will be $15 on both platforms, and it will be all sorts of awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It better be based on that recommendation.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first one was kind of fun, so we'll see why the second one wouldn't be as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, one thing you might not be getting to do when you play this game online, even though you don't really play this game online, but other Xbox Live games would be, you probably won't get to swear much longer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, the US Patent Office has granted a patent to Microsoft for real-time censoring of audio streams.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, this is...
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty self-explanatory, probably what Microsoft wants us for is they want to be able to censor what Xbox Live is probably most known for, is the fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, you know, and all that stuff that you hear when you go on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, they can't censor this show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ha-ha.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuckity, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck!
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: A writer on Ars Technica, though, Jonathan Gitlin, though, brings up a really kind of scary point.
[SPEAKER_07]: Think about this, because this is the technology, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: I can also envisage a much sinister role, however.
[SPEAKER_07]: Imagine the same system applied to digital telephony.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then think how valuable such a system might be to an authoritarian regime.
[SPEAKER_07]: As we've seen to good effect in Burma and elsewhere, the ubiquity of cell phones has been a good thing for dissidents who need to get their message out or organize themselves.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Great Firewall of China already blocks objectionable web content from reaching Chinese computers.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's to stop cell phones from censoring anti-government conversations too?
[SPEAKER_07]: That is kind of a scary thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's hope that this isn't used for, you know, anything pushing the limits.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can imagine this is...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be a scary thing if it falls into the wrong hands.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jani brings up an interesting point.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that in chat?
[SPEAKER_03]: Imagine censoring the angry video game nerd.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, still, just anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: It kind of threatens free speech.
[SPEAKER_22]: His powers are beyond Microsoft's comprehension.
[SPEAKER_07]: If in the wrong hands.
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, in this country, since free speech is in our constitution, I don't think it's going to be a big problem, but it could be interesting to see the effect this could have in other places.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the guy makes a good point.
[SPEAKER_07]: What if it falls into the wrong hands?
[SPEAKER_07]: But also, I can't imagine that this is going to be...
[SPEAKER_07]: That accurate.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: There'll be ways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Will it catch me if I say frack?
[SPEAKER_03]: The thing is... What if I'm talking about my shih tzu dog?
[SPEAKER_07]: Am I going to get censored?
[SPEAKER_03]: The thing is, Rob, about free speech rights... Yeah, the government can't inhibit your free speech rights, but companies sure can when you agree to play by their rules.
[SPEAKER_22]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_22]: As long as you've signed the agreement saying that you're going to use their...
[SPEAKER_22]: proprietary software, and I guess the hardware too since we're referring to the Xbox, then they do have a right to censor any content that comes through their own equipment.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's just like a private organization denying people the use of their facilities.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I get that, I get that, but still, I'm going to be very disappointed since I pay for Microsoft service if I can't say fuck.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, knowing Microsoft and based on track history only, I'm going to assume it'll probably be a switch that'll, you know, help keep it safe for kids, which I'm cool with, you know, if parents want to turn it on, but they shouldn't rely on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the other dangerous thing, is I don't want parents to rely on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would love to see it like, you know, some of those TBS comedies where they replace it with, like, stupid words, just like ordinary things.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the freak?
[SPEAKER_05]: What the fruit?
[SPEAKER_05]: What the French toast?
[SPEAKER_05]: Shove it up your baloney.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or kazoo.
[SPEAKER_22]: To be perfectly honest, the whole reason that swear words are considered swear words in the beginning is because people have given them the power to offend.
[SPEAKER_22]: And what is it that I have been saying for a very long time now?
[SPEAKER_07]: You find this show very offensive.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_22]: Learn to be offended.
[SPEAKER_22]: The less of a big deal you make out of it...
[SPEAKER_22]: The less it's going to matter.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, really.
[SPEAKER_22]: The whole reason that I think little kids think it's fun to go out and cuss from their little kids is because their parents say, oh, that's bad and you shouldn't do it.
[SPEAKER_22]: The less you're allowed to do something, the more you'll want to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: People do that because it raises eyebrows.
[SPEAKER_22]: But if no one gets offended, why would they want to do it anymore?
[SPEAKER_07]: I would love to see Microsoft I would love to see Microsoft just try and censor this next segment of ours.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, Fuse of the Week.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck you with something hard and sandpapery to, um, certain, um, closed-minded, tight-assed, bigoted conservatives that have been, um,
[SPEAKER_22]: F you to other things that are personal and F you to my hair
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fe to Sackboy for being so fluffy, because fluffy equals hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're kind of fluffy, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am kind of fluffy.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why I didn't have to pad the front, just the arms.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, no needing to pad myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that is really friggin' hot, but actually, luckily the sweatshirt is quite thin, so it's not too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually have, like, jeans under the pants and another t-shirt under this shirt, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the head's really fucking hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't do anything with the head.
[SPEAKER_07]: My turn?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to say F you to the people that decided to call me faggot yesterday while I was out protesting Prop 8.
[SPEAKER_07]: We were out there on the streets holding signs.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I had a big thing that said, you know, protect civil rights and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was a group of us out there and some guy as he drove by decided to yell faggots and throw candy corn at us.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that's the world we live in, folks.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't know whether to be angry or happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like,
[SPEAKER_05]: And one hand, I'm offended by what you said.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the other hand, candy corn!
[SPEAKER_05]: Not when they've fallen on a dirty-ass street.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's just unacceptable.
[SPEAKER_07]: So not only did he say faggot, Loki, he wasted candy corn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, no!
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't waste candy corn.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm sorry, is it wrong for me to mention that we're supposed to learn to stop throwing things and having food fights when we're in kindergarten?! !
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and then, oh, yeah, and then the lady as she was coming out of the drive-thru.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, here's the best one, the lady coming out of the drive-thru.
[SPEAKER_07]: Faggots, you're all going to hell.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what she yelled at us.
[SPEAKER_03]: They should have thrown Skittles.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, you know what I said?
[SPEAKER_07]: I yelled back, I said, God loves a bigot too.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I said back to her.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then she drove off, pissed off.
[SPEAKER_22]: Good.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: and so don't sit there and tell me this proposition isn't about hate and discrimination because I'll tell you what, I've seen it right in the face and it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some real quick FUs from our guests because we have a lot in studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll start with Drew since he has a mic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, F you to my student government for being assholes about the whole proposition thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't vote them in.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're trying to speak for the entire student body and I don't like it one bit.
[SPEAKER_22]: Actually, to go with this, I might have mentioned this earlier.
[SPEAKER_22]: There was a girl who was driving in front of me leaving school.
[SPEAKER_22]: We go to the same school.
[SPEAKER_22]: And she wrote on her car, no to Prop 8, the ARC student council does not represent me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I approve of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: but also F you to people who are taking the zombie event in WoW a little too far and taking hordes and hordes of zombies people taking WoW too far?
[SPEAKER_03]: into the lobby zones and killing all the lobbies who are trying to start out that's not cool I mean, yeah, it's zombies and it's brains but it's not cool don't be a dick alright, Hiccup Boy do you have any F yous of the week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to send an FU toward the bimbo of politicians everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't even think I need to go any further with that because everybody should know who I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I shall pass the mic on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Arcadian42.
[SPEAKER_29]: Fuck you to 65-hour work weeks.
[SPEAKER_29]: They suck.
[SPEAKER_29]: They put me way, way behind on everything.
[SPEAKER_29]: Oh well, getting money is good.
[SPEAKER_29]: Money is good.
[SPEAKER_29]: Doctor.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, take us back to some gaming news
[SPEAKER_22]: Stuff happened, the end.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ubisoft is actually working on the latest Anno game and actually have had to push it back a little bit.
[SPEAKER_22]: As well as one that they have literally called an as-yet-unannounced franchise.
[SPEAKER_22]: They were going to release it 2008-2009 fiscal year, but it's actually going to be 2009-2010.
[SPEAKER_22]: we don't know what this is but I know 1404 is a settlement building game that speaks for itself there's a trailer around if someone wants to look at game trailers I'm sure there's one there but the other one they're not saying what it is but they said that it's an unannounced one so maybe it's a brand new franchise could be
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, something that unfortunately hasn't been delayed is an update to the Wii firmware that's now disabling the Homebrew channel from being installed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other possible problems faced with that are some Homebrew programs not running.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, the video player that they had that also allowed you to watch DVDs is not working as well, the M player.
[SPEAKER_05]: and um right now though if you do have the homebrew channel installed you're fine but you won't be able to install it if you um you know do 3.3 also in Japan um they have um the shop channel down right now for maintenance as they're changing all the references to Wii points to Nintendo points and other uh pre-DSI maintenance isn't that a little deceiving though because the points aren't going to be interchangeable that strikes me as kind of dumb it is deceiving yes um
[SPEAKER_05]: And then also apparently right now, if you don't update your system, you will not be able to access the shop channel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is ironic because if you think about it, if they're not able to access the shop channel, they won't buy your crap that you're selling online.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know, with the homebrew stuff, it is easy to, I don't know, pirate said games that you're offering on the service.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would think that you would want to allow people to be able to purchase your games and let them have fun with the homebrew stuff since...
[SPEAKER_05]: Give these homebrew people jobs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, there's a lot of might-be-crap games on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I can see the other side, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: People stealing other people's work by pirating such games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't lie.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is what a lot of the quote-unquote homebrew people do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can see both sides of it, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you remember the old school game show Supermarket Sweep?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, that's this.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's the greatest ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look, there's a little trailer here we're playing in studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lifetime, Lawnmowers Unpacked.
[SPEAKER_07]: But look at this.
[SPEAKER_07]: You actually run around the supermarket with your cart, but you pick up plungers for some weird reason, and you run into other shoppers.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, it's everything you've always wanted to do in the supermarket.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're all kind of crazy anime characters.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like Supermarket Sweep meets Jet Set Radio or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, according to Juan Grill, who's the studio manager for the developers, Joju Games, he says that MartRacer was inspired from the shape of the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_07]: He says, quote, The first time I grabbed a Wiimote, instinctively I grabbed it with both hands like a bar.
[SPEAKER_07]: That made me start thinking on a game where you can maneuver it like you would be grabbing a bar.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you want to play with a classic controller, you can.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I guess it's probably more fun with motion controls because you can imagine that you're pushing that cart just like a bat out of hell up and down the aisles of Safeway.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, what are some other things we can download, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, there is a few games coming out on WiiWare in the UK.
[SPEAKER_22]: There's the Incredible Maze, which is 500 Wii points, and it's different.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's mazes and has balance board support, so you actually steer a ball around the maze and dodge traps.
[SPEAKER_22]: Basically, it's Marble Madness with a balance board, from what I understand.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: there's also interior design well an interior design game called Home Sweet Home that is you basically take rooms and redesign them sort of like a bizarre puzzle and it's a thousand Wii points and then there's Tetris Party which is twelve hundred Wii points that is mini game Tetris using the balance board and it has online multiplayer for up to six people
[SPEAKER_06]: Click in!
[SPEAKER_05]: Other than stuff coming on to the WiiWare service, there's some interesting stuff if you happen to own a Super Nintendo system.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, a German programmer took it upon himself to create a new console game that supports eight players.
[SPEAKER_05]: His creation is a brawler called N-Warp Daisuken, or it looks like Daisakusen, and allows you to plug in two multitaps in the SNES
[SPEAKER_05]: And, yeah, it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can also, if you don't want to, I don't know, say, find a cart for it, since it doesn't look like there is an actual cart, you can play it through an emulator.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, I don't know, that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eight-player brawler game for Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to download it, the website is gra.deforce3000.de So that's where you can get that wonderful game.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, for those of you looking forward to new Nintendo products, Animal Crossing City Focus coming out pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a bunch of videos have been kind of shown up around the Internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's revealed a lot more about the game, a lot more details about the new Animal Crossing game.
[SPEAKER_11]: And somewhere Rice Princess is going...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: She loves Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although I'm kind of surprised I'm going to be buying this game for the third time.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they have made some changes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's starting to sound like an MMO though, like a patch or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: At the new auction now, she can't put up fruit or tools.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: New chirping birds will appear in your village.
[SPEAKER_07]: You get clovers brought over in the DS version.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of the objects like fossils, tools, and accessories show up as 3D objects.
[SPEAKER_07]: The villages are going to go back to having two different elevation levels like they did in the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: You have stone bridges in the game over the lakes and rivers that are now wider, probably to hold four people when you're playing on Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mr. Asetti can actually show up in the city.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's more grass in your city than dirt, unlike the DS version.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nook's Cranny and Nook & Go are back as Nook upgrades in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's going to be a Tom Nook apron shirt.
[SPEAKER_07]: Skunk is a character that will shine your shoes and change the color of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: And how's that WeSpeak thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't come with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's optional.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I can run around going, You're a towel!
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can go around in these little kids' towels and just go, Fuck!
[SPEAKER_03]: And they'll bleep it out.
[SPEAKER_22]: I wonder if I can get my village lesbian back.
[SPEAKER_03]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, on the GameCube one, we had our village lesbian.
[SPEAKER_22]: What was her name?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: She was an aardvark or something.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, she wasn't an aardvark.
[SPEAKER_07]: She had the huge nose.
[SPEAKER_22]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: See, and now you can put a no on eight sign.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because we outed her.
[SPEAKER_07]: Outside there, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be great.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't wait to put political messages inside Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's going to be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: My God, it's going to turn into Second Life.
[SPEAKER_07]: Vote for me.
[SPEAKER_22]: Remember when we were doing bottle messages to advertise the station?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to throw a furry at you.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: With signs.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's also totally fun, interacting with our listeners.
[SPEAKER_07]: And every week, you guys send us emails at mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we read some of our emails live here on air, as DarkSakura is going to do right now.
[SPEAKER_22]: First email.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dun dun dun.
[SPEAKER_22]: Congratulations!
[SPEAKER_22]: You have made it to 300 episodes.
[SPEAKER_22]: Bonus round.
[SPEAKER_22]: Another 300.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ready, set, go.
[SPEAKER_22]: By the way, U is spelled Y-O-U, not the letter U. Thank you.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, really.
[SPEAKER_22]: I, please capitalize your I, must say 300 episodes is freaking epic.
[SPEAKER_22]: You guys are awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: Awesome has an E in it, by the way, after W. And... God, what am I doing this for?
[SPEAKER_22]: And by far the best gaming podcast out there.
[SPEAKER_22]: You are the most intelligent and comedic, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: If you don't want to read this part, then don't, but I must say, I was listening to back episodes, and if I lived in Cali, I would join the rebellion against Prop 8.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_22]: It is stupid and no better than racism.
[SPEAKER_22]: Off to a better note, I have been playing Jet Set Radio Future for Xbox.
[SPEAKER_22]: I remember this playing back on my uncle's Xbox and it was freaking nostalgic.
[SPEAKER_22]: Nostalgic is N-O-S.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_22]: The game is as good as any 360 game and in some ways better.
[SPEAKER_22]: By the way, if anyone knows where to get the freaking awesome music for JSRF, tell me.
[SPEAKER_22]: I want it now.
[SPEAKER_22]: Um...
[SPEAKER_22]: By the way, just to let you know, they did actually do a soundtrack that they released in... Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: America.
[SPEAKER_22]: Rawr.
[SPEAKER_22]: I have the Lion Suki on my head now.
[SPEAKER_22]: But you actually can get the soundtrack for that, and we'll talk.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'll see about making sure that you acquire this.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sincerely, Geekboy2424, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_22]: the youngest OLR listener.
[SPEAKER_22]: 300 for the win!
[SPEAKER_22]: Actually, I have to say, how young are you, dude?
[SPEAKER_07]: 14, I think he is.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's actually not too bad.
[SPEAKER_22]: The email really not too bad.
[SPEAKER_22]: Just common little things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still think Sakuramax beats him as far as youngness.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sakuramax is 13, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they're the same age.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they had a birthday.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they're both 14.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_22]: They had a birthday.
[SPEAKER_07]: You must fight to the death.
[SPEAKER_22]: One is the evil twin.
[SPEAKER_22]: Look for a kid with a goatee.
[SPEAKER_03]: Two men enter.
[SPEAKER_03]: One man leaves.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hello, OLR.
[SPEAKER_22]: Don't know if you've already covered this in the 299th episode, but just in case, I get a smiley face.
[SPEAKER_22]: It says, here you can get the game.
[SPEAKER_22]: And this is from Ilya, aka 13nextforever, and it's actually about a Metroid 2 remake.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's Project AM2R, where they are...
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm really not sure exactly what's going into it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, they're remaking Metroid 2, like the Game Boy one, in color, I think, looking very... Super Metroid-ish.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, it's very Super Metroid-ish.
[SPEAKER_22]: But the graphics are actually really pretty.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen the remake so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very, very well done.
[SPEAKER_22]: I've sent a link to that site in the chat room, by the way.
[SPEAKER_22]: Misty, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_22]: Don't, you don't, you shouldn't feel old.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, nuh-uh.
[SPEAKER_22]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: The chatters were talking about how old they were when they started listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was making the hosts feel very old.
[SPEAKER_22]: How old was I when we started doing Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_22]: I was 26, 27.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was 23, but I was like three days before my 24th birthday.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was 26 when we started doing this show.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_22]: Shoot me, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bang.
[SPEAKER_22]: My mom's turning 50.
[SPEAKER_22]: Happy birthday, Mom!
[SPEAKER_03]: You should call her.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, we won't be here next week to do it, so... We should call my mom later.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh yeah, email, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, thank you for that kind, kind email.
[SPEAKER_22]: 13X forever.
[SPEAKER_22]: Next one.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, God, I don't know who this person is.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's just sauce.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey there, OLR.
[SPEAKER_22]: Congratulations on 300 episodes.
[SPEAKER_22]: In honor of episode 300, I wrote a song for you guys to the tune of Hey There, Delilah by the Plain White Tees.
[SPEAKER_22]: There's a link here.
[SPEAKER_22]: The song runs over two minutes, however, and Rob said to keep it under a minute if we send anything in.
[SPEAKER_22]: She don't have a recording of it quite yet, and she did give us lyrics to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: She posted it on Twitter and I read the parody and it's very cute.
[SPEAKER_22]: I could read it right now unless Rob wants to read it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to sing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have the song also, which is part of the problem.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can read it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: You want me to read it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how I find it on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, go for it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey there, OLR, what's it like in Sacramento?
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm 500 miles away, but now I'll listen to your show just for you No other podcast outshines you, I swear it's true
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey there, OLR, don't you worry about your ratings.
[SPEAKER_22]: Your fans will download your podcast and share it with our friends.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll tell, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: There's no place else we'd go for news.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know it's true.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, 300 episodes, chorus part.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm not going to repeat it.
[SPEAKER_22]: 300 shows seems like a lot, but don't you stop.
[SPEAKER_22]: Give it a shot.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know this show is running kind of late.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura needs to read FUs, and Loki's got some gaming news, and Bobby makes Sky start the show real late."
[SPEAKER_22]: We have Rob Snicker to that.
[SPEAKER_22]: OLR, we can promise you we'll make comments in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey there, Delilah, what's it like in York City?
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm not singing.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: OLR, we can promise you we'll make comments in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_22]: We want new gaming news every Sunday.
[SPEAKER_22]: You make our day.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey there, OLR, you stay cool and keep podcasting.
[SPEAKER_22]: Record 300 more episodes.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll keep on making history like you do.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, Rob gets a hug.
[SPEAKER_22]: you know it's all because of you that we get all our gaming news hey there OLR here's to you this one's for you chorus part again oh sweet I'll link this in the chat room even if this song has a giant vagina this song sucks I like the song this is coming from Miss Metallica I like the parody I like the parody a lot it was very cute I am a Metallica fan that likes Vagina Rock the next time I would like a parody with Britney Spears Womanizer
[SPEAKER_22]: I also just finished playing the new Spider-Man Web of Shadows video game that came out this past week.
[SPEAKER_22]: I played the DS version, which is slightly different than the other versions, but it was still super fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: I wrote up a review for your gaming leisure, and I'll just tell this online for everybody.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's AvengersTower.com slash question P equals 38 and I'm going to get the chat room.
[SPEAKER_22]: Definitely go play this game.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's a ton of web-slinging, wall-crawling fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anywho, congratulations on 300 episodes, you guys.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm looking forward to 300 more.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sincerely, Martin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I am going to... Wow, if we did 300 more, we'd almost be 40 by the time we got to that point.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, Rob, I would be 40.
[SPEAKER_22]: So shut up.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, I wouldn't be 40, would I?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Almost.
[SPEAKER_22]: God.
[SPEAKER_22]: Rob, I'm feeling old now, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, join the club.
[SPEAKER_22]: Excuse me, Mr. Three years younger than me.
[SPEAKER_22]: Two years younger than me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know death is coming for me.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh my god, Sauce had the best suggestion.
[SPEAKER_22]: To do womanizer to Loki's tingalizer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's an excellent idea.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Glad to see you agree.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now do it.
[SPEAKER_22]: This one comes from Dan Shadow.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've already gotten most of the games I'm looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess the only thing I have left is Resistance 2.
[SPEAKER_22]: Resistance 2 is a good one.
[SPEAKER_22]: Mel, do you have anyone you're looking forward to?
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyone else?
[SPEAKER_22]: Left 4 Dead.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I want zombie action.
[SPEAKER_22]: Speak into the microphone if you're going to make a decision.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, what'd I miss?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Last Remnant.
[SPEAKER_22]: What game are you looking forward to that hasn't come out yet that you don't already have?
[SPEAKER_07]: LittleBigPlanet Fallout 3 I'm also looking forward to Last Remnant though even though I was not a fan of Infinite Undiscovery The beginning was awful I didn't want to play it past the first hour
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course we know about the new game coming out, Halo Recon, or Halo 3 Recon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently though, Bungie's Halo team is moving on to other things once this is done.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I don't know, maybe another game from Bungie that's, say, not Halo?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe a, I don't know, a marathon game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Something like that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Malo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Marathono.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have they said this before?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, oh, we swear we're not doing another Halo.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said this before, like after Halo 3, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says, basically, they were saying that they want to work on different territory.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they said, but I think when this project wraps up in a couple months, that it will be time when the team moves on to something else.
[SPEAKER_05]: And part of the team will move on to something else, and part of them will probably be absorbed into one of the other projects that are already on the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like what Deakman suggests in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: A game called J-Lo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have my love.
[SPEAKER_07]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, you know how the PlayStation 3 has trophies?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, according to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: official PlayStation magazine, Sony might actually be giving out more than just trophies pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a little quote from the magazine that people were reading way too much into.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says, quote, We've heard that SCEA is mulling over some sort of trophy reward system.
[SPEAKER_07]: We doubt it'll be cash or the equivalent, but we suspect it might be exclusive access to early betas and the like.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, trophies are like PlayStation 3's version of 360's achievements.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wouldn't that be interesting if suddenly you could use your trophies to now get into betas and stuff?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think Microsoft should do the same thing because I play a lot more Microsoft games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you know, and I agree with the people that wrote this story on the net.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got no problem if it's early demos or what have you, but just to give exclusive?
[SPEAKER_07]: That seems kind of wrong to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just encourages people to do nothing but play games all day.
[SPEAKER_05]: but then again this whole thing could be just something retarded similar to what Gears of War is doing you know where for example if you have different achievements in Gears of War that you get shipped for Gears of War 2 could it be something like that?
[SPEAKER_05]: that would make sense I beat LittleBigPlanet when LittleBigPlanet 2 comes out or something like that I get some stupid costume or something that works that works
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe more to come from Sony probably in 2009.
[SPEAKER_22]: I doubt that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sony's going to explode.
[SPEAKER_22]: The end.
[SPEAKER_03]: It already exploded.
[SPEAKER_03]: It puked out something called Star Wars Galaxies.
[SPEAKER_07]: BlackWolf has a good point.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got to read this in chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, Sky, what's better?
[SPEAKER_07]: Giving exclusive betas to people who have lots of trophies or giving exclusive betas to people who buy core?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll take option three.
[SPEAKER_07]: Giving exclusive betas to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Here, the cheat has a trophy!
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: In other words, the fanboys will never be happy.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, there is a boy named Brandon Crisp.
[SPEAKER_22]: 15 years old who went missing after his parents confiscated his Xbox.
[SPEAKER_22]: Microsoft Canada is adding $25,000 to the reward information that will hopefully lead to his safe return.
[SPEAKER_22]: So they're basically doubling the amount that's already out.
[SPEAKER_22]: They're working with the Barrie, Ontario authorities
[SPEAKER_22]: Looking for IP addresses of anyone who would come into contact with him through Call of Duty 4, which was his favorite game.
[SPEAKER_22]: And Microsoft is really, really putting forward a lot of effort into trying to get this kid back.
[SPEAKER_22]: So basically... Oh God, I hate this person.
[SPEAKER_04]: How is it Microsoft's problem?
[SPEAKER_22]: He who shall not be named has involved himself What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought he was gone.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let me finish.
[SPEAKER_22]: Making an offer to help the cops try to find it and making up some crap about video game addiction or whatever the fuck he's on.
[SPEAKER_22]: Um...
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm so disgusted with him
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm just completely disgusted.
[SPEAKER_22]: I can't even call him a human being anymore.
[SPEAKER_22]: Really, he's just disgusting.
[SPEAKER_19]: He's a fart.
[SPEAKER_22]: At any rate, for anyone who might have some information on his whereabouts, call the Berry Police at 705-725-7025.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: I hope that someone can find this kid.
[SPEAKER_22]: I just hope that, you know, he's okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Stop being an asshole and get out there and look.
[SPEAKER_05]: Someone needs to find him before Jack does.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because if he finds him, we'll never hear the end of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at all the good I do.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm just disgusted.
[SPEAKER_22]: I really am horrified, you know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who does he think he is?
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, he seriously has caused so much harm to so many people and he can't stop.
[SPEAKER_22]: He's already being punished for it and asshole hasn't learned his lesson yet.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, seriously, the only thing that's going to stop this guy is to lock him up in a padded room and have him yell his insults to the wall that does not care.
[SPEAKER_22]: The end.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's just hope the wall doesn't have a blog.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's hope the wall fucking bitch slaps him.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, I'm a wall, and even I hate you.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: More news.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to open up the Skype line very soon at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Legendary Pictures, the company that has done wonderful movies like The Dark Knight, Batman Begins, and of course some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can only remember the Batman stuff right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they are also putting together a non-Batman movie that is going to be Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going along with that, Variety is reporting that Legendary Pictures may also be in talks to buy Epic Games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unreal 3 Town Unreal 3 the RPG
[SPEAKER_07]: Tiger Claw would like to point out that Legendary Pictures also did the upcoming Watchmen movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did they also do 300?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would imagine.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, is this some softcore porn?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, woo, porn!
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, anyway, one more story for you guys tonight and then we're going to open up the Skype line and that story has to do with Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: Street Fighter 4, it's coming out this winter for sure, says Capcom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now keep in mind, Loki's...
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Got a real good idea when this game's coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the rumors have all been now that, I mean, originally it was supposed to be like January sometime, but now they're trying to time it with the release of the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, probably around the time that the crappy movie comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, winter does not mean necessarily this year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Winter is also January and February.
[SPEAKER_05]: Winter, December through February.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, the movie itself is being released in that time period where all the stinker movies are released, which is like...
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, agree, the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: By far.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure the movie will be a surprise and it'll be this epic, awesome movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no, except it won't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm with you.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, let's go to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_25]: It's GS68.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hi, GS68.
[SPEAKER_25]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_25]: I got around to playing the new Castlevania this week, which I'm surprised you didn't mention on last week's release dates.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, did you?
[SPEAKER_25]: No, didn't we get mentioned at the end?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we did.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we did.
[SPEAKER_07]: The podcast is a little behind, so make sure you have the most current episode.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, I don't.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, I'm not downloading the podcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well, I think it got mentioned.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyway, okay, so I haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you think of the game?
[SPEAKER_25]: It's like the other DS Castlevanias, more or less.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, I like how they have a lot of new areas now, such as one big area.
[SPEAKER_25]: How does it compare to previous Castlevania games?
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, the maps, for example, they're smaller now, but there's more enemies, so it's more difficult, and you'll usually be so busy fighting enemies that you'll hardly notice that the maps are smaller, especially because...
[SPEAKER_25]: For this game, I hardly use the map.
[SPEAKER_25]: I usually have the second screen for checking enemies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do we have any really bad B-movie dialogue in the game?
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, the English voice acting kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_25]: And there's a Japanese language option, but for me it doesn't make it any better.
[SPEAKER_25]: All it does is make it into a language that I'm not very fluent in yet.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, well, do you recommend it to fans of Castlevania?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: That doesn't sound like a very solid yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of like a, yeah, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if you have nothing better to do, I guess you could do it.
[SPEAKER_25]: If you're looking for a game that's more action-oriented and exploration-oriented, this is a pretty good game to try out.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else you want to talk to our listeners about today?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not much, really.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we're going to let you go so we can get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoy Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have fun playing it while I can.
[SPEAKER_25]: See you.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you'd like to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: His name on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's up, everybody?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, what's up?
[SPEAKER_10]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_10]: Before I begin, I have here on my table three drinks.
[SPEAKER_10]: One for each of you awesome hosts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you going to drink them all right now, live on air?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's drink number one?
[SPEAKER_10]: Drink number one is for Jamie.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a, uh...
[SPEAKER_10]: It's something straight forward and hard.
[SPEAKER_10]: Straight to the punch.
[SPEAKER_10]: A shot of Jack Daniels.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope you're being responsible.
[SPEAKER_07]: There went shot number one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I heard that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shot number two?
[SPEAKER_10]: Shot number two is for you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Something nice and fruity.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange juice and peach schnapps.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_22]: That is tasty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds quite gay.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have to make it more hype.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what is shot number three, Pray Tell?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I asked a friend of mine who came over to make the drink.
[SPEAKER_10]: I call it the Loki because Loki is unstable, so I don't know what's in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm so fucked up right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm so fucked up right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: How's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, anything else you wanted to share with us tonight besides drinking live on air?
[SPEAKER_10]: Kicked up Rock Band 2 and Guitar Hero World Tour.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, at the same time?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: And which one's better?
[SPEAKER_10]: The jury is still out, but I will say this much.
[SPEAKER_10]: When it comes to Bon Jovi living on a prayer, Guitar Hero World Tour is a lot better.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the thing though, Guitar Hero World Tour actually made Bobby say fuck on his show.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I mean, that makes me really worried.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, not even Rock Revolution did that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we're going to get Rock Revolution soon, but we're going to probably wait until a used copy pops up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you notice that Rock Revolution has a real basement Metacritic score?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was getting like threes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's disturbing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still want to get it because I'm sick, but I'm waiting for it to go on clearance because you know it's just a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Same here, definitely.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yo, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're waiting for clearance.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yo, drink for the guests, dude.
[SPEAKER_03]: We deserve it too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, Ranma, we gotta let you go for more calls.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello there, Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is Akiriper.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, my friend.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm doing just fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, what did I call?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I was quite surprised that at last the downloadable pack this week for Rock Band, in the sense that it was a few Sushis and Banshees songs, were really like my best news of the week, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I know, I'm very excited about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's nice to see a nice eclectic mix of music and rock band.
[SPEAKER_08]: My problem is, though, that of the three songs that are there, only one of them is good, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you actually are to be picky.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no peekaboo or anything, which would be rad, but I can't imagine actually playing that song in a rock band, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, well, that you're mentioning peekaboo is like, if you know the history behind that song, you know that it will be quite hard in one way, since the whole song is played backwards.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since they have to learn how to play it all backwards.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be a fun challenge mode, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: The notes can scroll the opposite way.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else is going on in your gaming world this week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not much, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not much at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really a sad thing in one way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I bought Warhammer Online when it came out, and
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I have played it like... The number of times I have actually played it, I can count it on one hand.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, me too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm in the exact same boat you are.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I started thinking in one way, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't check out WoW, went back to WoW, actually, but I did see the new logins frequency, the login screen, and that actually made me go,
[SPEAKER_08]: Wee, who?
[SPEAKER_08]: Big Frost Worm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is very pretty.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like... It's like... Yay, cute!
[SPEAKER_03]: We just got mushroomed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whoa, we just had a... We just got hit by a flying mushroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Behave, boys and girls in the studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, our guests are getting unruly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, well... Mushrooms are funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mushroom growing in your head.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're a little distracted here.
[SPEAKER_07]: People are throwing things at each other in the studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, other than that, well, I'm starting to get sort of in one way pissed also, since at the current state, I have no TV whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but then again, and that's starting to annoy me, really, since I want to play on my retro, I'm sort of almost really utterly want to play on my PS1, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: since I haven't played on that one for a long time.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, well, I want to play Front Vision 3, damn it!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you know, you could do that whole thing where you download things to the PSP, but I don't know if they have that game on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have a PSP yet, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And with the thing that the Model 3 has come out, and with the problem that that's causing...
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorta like, now, just wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really, uh, just wait as usual, so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, hey, Aki Ripper, we gotta, uh, we gotta let you go to get some more calls, but, uh, good luck on the quest for the television.
[SPEAKER_08]: But still, uh, I, I, I, on my short, on short notice, in one way, in one way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought of when I was starting to listen to OLR, and it was... That was weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Skype just crashed on us in the middle of that call.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why you heard the remix.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was strange.
[SPEAKER_07]: I swear I didn't do anything to provoke that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, if somebody else is on the line, I'll go to voicemail right away.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're going to sign back in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry to Aki Ripper, who got cut off.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was very weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, um, well, I guess we're open for business again.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1-877-GAME-OLR What?
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: Rice Princess just sent me a text, and she says, Tell everyone I said hi, and I said my love, and congrats on 300, and also... Alright, that's lovely.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, we have another call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: This is Kitsune.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, Kitsune.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you calling us from inside your own Sackboy outfit?
[SPEAKER_07]: You sound very distant.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I'm calling from Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I guess maybe that might be part of the distance.
[SPEAKER_22]: We chat on AIM sometimes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, right on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, what's been going on in your gaming world this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the other week I went to Tokyo Game Show, which was really exciting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell us about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: How was Tokyo Game Show?
[SPEAKER_07]: What kind of stuff did you see there?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, it was huge and very exciting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tons of people.
[SPEAKER_01]: The biggest booth is probably Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think Xbox 360 is going to turn around in Japan?
[SPEAKER_01]: I believe so.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, they had a pretty big booth and tons of people waiting in line.
[SPEAKER_01]: They had a 105 minute wait for one game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, what game was that?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it was...
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kind of not surprised at that, yeah?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that would be the game that is supposed to cater to the Japanese audience.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why E3 can't go public, you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: 105 minute waits just to play one RPG?
[SPEAKER_07]: Imagine what those Wii lines would have looked like if it was open to the public.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would have been nutso.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm glad you're having a good time.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is a DS game I want to talk about called Time Hollow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it is a Japanese game, but it was just released in the States, and it is amazing.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you ever heard of Shadow of Destiny for the PlayStation 1, it's much like that game in which you have to change the past, and then it causes something else to change, but you've got to go back and change again.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it has real anime videos throughout the whole game, and I loved it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it sounds kind of like a puzzle game, but with anime cutscenes?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not a puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's an adventure game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Meltdown's calling it Butterfly Effect the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I might have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, there's a lot of these games that really don't show up on the radar like that that I wish would get more coverage so I know to look out for them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you very much and I'll check out Time Hollow for sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: You take care.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bye bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like getting phone calls from far, far, far away.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Username on Skype is Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, it's a random bitch that finally got her 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Misty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Misty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, Misty, did you say you finally actually got a 360 this week?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, finally.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, I migrated my account since the day I got the system.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to send me a message.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's the same gamertag from last time, my LJ name, so you're already on my list.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay, that's right, that's right, that's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I forgot you had the old Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just that I hardly ever saw you on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, what games did you get for 360?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_21]: Main one was Portal's Still Alive.
[SPEAKER_21]: I caved and downloaded Beat and Groovy for the fuck of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really not worth it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have not downloaded Beat and Groovy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does have a couple good songs in it, but the price tag sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: It only has a couple songs in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does.
[SPEAKER_07]: I admit I haven't been paying attention much I've been too busy with the stuff I have got Well you need to pay more attention to our show young lady No I'm just kidding it's cool
[SPEAKER_07]: it's all good come on you have a shitty attention span I know so any chance of a Misty visit in the future?
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm working on it I wasn't feeling good before that dentist appointment I had the other day so I had to postpone it a pay period so yeah I still want to I just don't know when at least there's always Xbox Live to connect us in the meantime alright Misty any other quick thoughts before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_21]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, have a good one, Missy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoy the new 360.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll do one more call here on Orange Lounge Radio tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Use name on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, this is Bobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm from a far off place called Atlanta.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, Far Off Place I don't know if I've ever heard of Atlanta No, hey Bobby, I'm glad you called in Worst airport ever We're always calling into your show in a way No, no, no Philadelphia is the worst airport Really?
[SPEAKER_22]: Dallas Dallas is cakewalk Y'all have never been to Philly Compared to Atlanta's airport?
[SPEAKER_07]: Philly, Chicago Bobby, you always let us call into your show but you're never on ours What's on your mind, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no, I was just calling in to congratulate you on 300.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of a question for you guys about your show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where do you see yourself at episode 400?
[SPEAKER_07]: Canceled.
[SPEAKER_07]: Somebody had to say it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where do we see ourselves at episode 400?
[SPEAKER_07]: Good question.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll let Loki start.
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: systems.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think honestly in two years it'll be kind of about the next round of systems.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we'll try to do our best to maintain to stay on the cutting edge of interactive tools.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you will see Orange Launch Radio getting into video more in two years.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not necessarily that we're going to be.
[SPEAKER_22]: The hell we will.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not in the way you think.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not necessarily it'll be our mugs reading the news.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be furries!
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe the way folks interact with us I think will be different.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just you know because you know we were one of the first shows to really jump on Skype when that first came out and you know Justin TV we weren't really the first but you know that was a way to kind of expand through that and you know we like to try to stay on the cutting edge of how to stay interactive with the listeners so you know it's it's hard to think of what hasn't been done yet I don't know
[SPEAKER_02]: Does that Sackboy costume have fur on it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Does that count as a furry for you?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like sweatshirt material.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like a giant sweatshirt is what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not furry though.
[SPEAKER_02]: And no Tingle hat on it?
[SPEAKER_07]: No Tingle hat this time.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we figured this is the closest the listeners are ever going to get to seeing Loki in a Tingle outfit.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you got to take what you can.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, because from what I can understand, Loki likes Sackboy, so it's not as fun to see him dressed up as that as it would be to see him dressed up as Tingle.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's still adorable!
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I can't help it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Someone hasn't sold another 800,000 copies of something, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: We're working on it!
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's write friends forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're putting billboards up for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a PlayStation 3 now, so I can add Loki to my friends list, so you don't have to be Loki's only friend anymore, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have more than one friend now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll have you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he dumped me as his only friend.
[SPEAKER_05]: There were some other people that actually had LittleBigPlanet already that were playing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not that I could play at them because the servers aren't up yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Till tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to be up tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, hey, Bobby, now that you're on the R-rated show, is there anything you want to say about Guitar Hero World Tour you didn't get to say on your show?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I see, when you added that I didn't get to say on my show, that kind of cut it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the drums fucking suck, and maybe next time Activision really should kind of look at their own equipment before they badmouth the other ones and say, hey, when theirs breaks, you can come by ours, because it won't break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: It won't break, because it's already broken.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you thought about checking out Rock Revolution's drum set, just to see if it's better?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't think it's out yet, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my gosh, even though the game's out?
[SPEAKER_05]: The game is out, but the drum set's not out until November because apparently they haven't quite figured out the manufacturing of that either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I've played on the drum kit a couple times, but no, the actual drum set's not in stores yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: What I want to know is, the drums weren't, I mean, I don't think I didn't get to play it, but it didn't seem that the drums were broken when they were showing it off.
[SPEAKER_05]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mass production.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember when Rock Band was first shown at the PAX that you guys weren't at the year before, they started out with like three...
[SPEAKER_02]: and they had one by the end of the weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you could actually see the other drum sets all bandaged up in the corner of the booth.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: The sad, depressed, broken machines.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I had Dan Teasdale on... I was doing an interview with him for my show from the booth and I asked him about the durability of the drum sets and while I was asking the question, I looked at the pile of depressed drum sets and he didn't take the bait.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have not seen a single post from anybody that says, my drums work perfectly.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not to say that there's none that aren't effective, but either they're too busy playing the game or they just don't post on forums or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody has some sort of problem with the drums.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I guess it's a good thing I don't buy these games for the drum parts because I'm just not good at drums, so I always buy them for guitars.
[SPEAKER_07]: But still, if I ever was interested in doing it someday, that's kind of depressing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and I mean, I guess now I've got to do the whole RMA process, but I'm kind of worried, you know, have they fixed it yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because some of these threads, you know, I've looked on the official Guitar Hero forums, which I know are mostly negative because the people only post there when they're pissed or can't play.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they've said, you know, one guy said, I've returned it three times.
[SPEAKER_02]: My store has no more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every single drum set that I've gotten from the store has a different pad that's broken.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_02]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: So they kind of insinuate that it's Harmonix's fault that you're trying to play Guitar Hero in a specific way.
[SPEAKER_05]: In a way that works?
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's weird because ordinary drums, they just seem to make noise whenever I hit them.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, Bobby, and it's kind of funny coming from you because I know you're essentially a professional drummer and, you know, it's just kind of funny that, gee, a professional drummer isn't playing the drums right, apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and you have to smack it really hard for it to register.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they say, well, you may need to hit a pad harder or you may need to hit them softer.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm like, not in that sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: You shouldn't have to hit the right pad three times as hard as the middle pad and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I mean, I even plugged in my professional drum kit, which I've been passing around photos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, man, that photo is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to post that photo in chat because it's hilarious seeing all your equipment practically on top of each other.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to ask you though real quick, what about the guitar with the game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because for those of us that aren't so much into drums or guitars, have you played around with that at all?
[SPEAKER_02]: I play around a little bit with the guitar and I am happy to report that my guitar looks like it has absolutely no problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: now that being said I don't really understand the point of that slider thing the tutorial shows you how to use it and it doesn't work all the time but I think it's because I'm doing it wrong not because the hardware sucks but it's kind of like the lower fret notes in Rock Band I'll never use it there's things that you can do with it now one of the things is that is your wah-wah
[SPEAKER_02]: so instead of using the whammy bar for things that maybe you don't have star power you can actually run your hand along that and it does the wah-wah thing which is kind of cool and I did that a couple times just for the novelty factor but the guitar feels fine and they actually did add one of the actual software things for people that didn't buy the guitar that they added to World Tour is that now you can have one note held down and then you can strum down a second note
[SPEAKER_02]: and a third note.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they'll do chords that kind of come on like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not hammer-ons, but you still have to keep one note held down while you bring the second one in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm still using a Guitar Hero 2 Explorer in all my games.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the only controller I have.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's time for me to get a new one.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other than that, people are asking, how's the actual game?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been spending most of the day trying to get the game to work, so I haven't really gotten too far in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I will say that apparently the storyline behind the game, according to the intro screen, is Kenny G comes out and hypnotizes everybody, and it's your job to unhypnotize everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, that's such a Guitar Hero story.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope that's fake.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's the opening cinematic.
[SPEAKER_02]: A guy with a clarinet comes out and hypnotizes the entire crowd, and so the GH symbol flashes on everybody's cell phone and watch and stuff, and they all converge to unhypnotize the crowd.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, aren't they going to feel stupid when they release Clarinet Hero later on?
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, Bobby, we've got to let you go so we can wrap our show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you have any last thoughts?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you people who brag about your hardware that doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take care, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks, guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: We wouldn't have gotten here without you, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_07]: So thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll make you late in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, anything?
[SPEAKER_07]: No?
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki then?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just real quick, there was a little big planet download that was added in for Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know that game Ape Escape?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, now you can download a costume for your Sackboy that's actually the ape in the game, which is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Army of Two is supposed to be getting a movie as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_05]: We hear a lot of these movies that are coming out, but none of them come out except for Max Payne.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess they're all next year?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all talk until it actually happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's it, I guess, for last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, one other quick little dedication here Drew Nami wants to do, and then we're going to go around and get final thoughts tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: A little bit of sad news.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the WoW players that remember the forums, remember Ezra Chatterton.
[SPEAKER_03]: He was contacted by the Make-A-Wish Foundation because he had a brain tumor and talked to Blizzard and had some things customized for him, had a few weapons dedicated to him, had an entire...
[SPEAKER_03]: and the entire few characters and questlines in his honor passed away on Monday, October 20th, from a stroke.
[SPEAKER_03]: And our thoughts are with them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's very unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, I know there was a lot of people that actually went in and did the Will You Find My Dog quest that day, just kind of like to... Because that was his quest, and his voice is still in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's very interesting that, you know, despite what's happened offline, he kind of will continue to live on online, which is really neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is a nice dedication.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something only a video game could do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know that is a very sad note to end Episode 300 with, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: Can somebody make a fart joke or something to bring us back?
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dongle.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm Ross Princess.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, hey, we still have the final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_07]: And here, wait, here.
[SPEAKER_07]: This always makes everything better, guys, if you're feeling a little down here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know how to make everything better.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_07]: This always makes everything better.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, yes, it's good to be back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now that you know where the studio is, feel free to come back sometime.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just make sure there's a show first, because I've had that happen where we cancel the show for a night and someone showed up anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Poor guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Doctor, do you have anything you want to say?
[SPEAKER_07]: Glub, glub, glub, glub.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hiccup Boy, any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a coral reef.
[SPEAKER_07]: Crikey.
[SPEAKER_07]: Drew Nami, anything you want to leave the listeners with tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: You got some red on you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to win my costume contest at work, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_07]: My final thought is, since we're not doing another show before Election Day, please, please, please vote.
[SPEAKER_07]: And please, please, please, if you're in California, vote no on Prop 8.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you do, you'll never have to hear me talk about it again.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I also believe you should vote no on 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hell, I'd give you my entire political opinions.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the one about parental notification.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Vote yes for the monorail.
[SPEAKER_22]: I voted no on damn near everything except the monorail.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, even the presidential election pales in comparison to what rights are in store with Prop 8, but that, obviously, I'm a little biased.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can probably understand why.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_22]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well said.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We won't be here next week, but we'll be back in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wherever you guys are on Wednesday, please send some happy thoughts my way.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to need them.
[SPEAKER_07]: And send a dollar to DarkSakura because she wants them.
[SPEAKER_07]: And send some copies of Eye of Judgment to Loki because maybe you'll get an even better costume for episode 400.
[SPEAKER_07]: You never know unless you try.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll do this all again next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you like what you heard, please tell two friends about our show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Word of mouth is how we spread the word about our program.
[SPEAKER_07]: But for now, that's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Leave us a nice review on iTunes or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're out of here.
[SPEAKER_07]: See you next time on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be back in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_26]: or allgames.com but we're probably right anyway see you next week